♪
The Tribal Arts Exhibit should be right on time.
Even the mayor is here.
Hard to believe all this commotion
over a bunch of beads and blankets.
The heritage of my people is hardly that trivial, Miss Lane.
Professor Blackwing!
I didn't realize you were... I mean, I was just joking.
It's such a wonderful thing, this whole thing.
It's so wonderful, really.
Have you met Clark Kent?
I hear the exhibition is stunning.
I've spent years putting it together.
Many of the artifacts have never left our tribal lands.
They are irreplaceable.
♪
You hear something?
[YELLS]
[GROANS]
[GUNFIRE]
We're under attack.
[OVER WALKIE-TALKIE] Too many. Can't hold them off, I...
[GROANS]
BLACKWING: Hello?
Come in, come in!
Someone's getting an early preview.
I'll get help.
I'll get the story.
♪
Keep looking.
[GLASS BREAKING]
The master said the shaman's staff would be here.
I believe this is your stop.
Get him.
The staff.
I think you're finished here.
[BEEPING]
I've already disabled the brakes,
so you can stop me or stop the train.
The choice is yours.
[GRUNTING]
Till we meet again. Mwah.
[GROANING]
What?
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
Just happened to be in the neighborhood?
Do you have any idea who they are?
The Society of Shadows.
I've been trailing them for weeks,
hoping they'd lead me to Ra's Al Ghul.
Who? A criminal mastermind.
More dangerous than the Joker and Luthor put together.
All I know is they were breaking the law in my town.
Leave it to you to charge in with both arms swinging.
If you were going to operate in Metropolis,
you should've filled me in.
Next time I'll fax my itinerary.
I mean it. I'd like to help.
SUPERMAN: This is where they met?
BATMAN: They're not coming back.
Ra's is too smart to leave a trail.
You said the only thing they took was the shaman's staff?
Yes. It's one of the least valuable items.
According to Professor Blackwing,
it's supposed to have mystic healing powers.
Maybe your mastermind isn't feeling well.
He's usually in pretty good shape for a guy his age.
A bicycle? Or a wheelchair.
Another day, another Pulitzer.
[GASPS]
[COUGHS]
[GROANS]
Pleasant dreams, Miss Lane.
MAN: And this breaking news just in.
Authorities have blocked off Central Avenue
while firefighters try to rescue
an unidentified woman on top of the Luthor Towers.
Lois?
She's too high up, we can't reach her.
♪
[SCREAMS]
Oh, my goodness. Somebody do something.
I've got you, Lois. The name's Tailia.
You.
Sorry for the theatrics,
but I needed to get your attention.
[WIND BLOWING]
You've got it.
What's this all about?
My father would like to meet you.
Privately.
Your father?
Ra's Al Ghul.
And if I refuse?
Then I'll have to insist.
♪
[SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
♪
Wake up, dog.
The master will see you now.
♪
I'm sorry we must meet under such circumstances.
You're not exactly what I pictured.
I'm not the man I was.
[COUGHS]
[GASPING]
Father, you should rest.
Old age, Superman.
It truly is a shipwreck.
One that I have survived more times than I can remember.
For centuries I've kept myself alive
by immersing my body in Lazarus Pits.
Their wondrous powers rejuvenated me.
But each time, the effects were more and more short-lived.
[SIGHS]
Now they can no longer sustain me.
[WHEEZES]
He's dying.
What do you want from me?
Your strength.
[GROANS]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
Easy, Lois. It's me.
Bruce?
It's been a while.
I take it this isn't a social call.
What happened here?
I'm not sure.
Someone attacked me.
A woman dressed in black.
Tailia.
Tailia?
On a first-name basis, are we?
What do you think she was she after?
Your clothes.
Excuse me?
She needed to impersonate you to attract Superman.
Ha! She's going to need more than that.
Maybe my clothes and a nuclear disaster.
And I just had it shampooed.
Do you know how depressing it is
to clean up after your assailant?
I'm sorry.
Forget it, a little detergent and some elbow grease.
I mean, that we're meeting like this.
Hey, I was the one who said goodbye.
Though I can't say I haven't had second thoughts.
Actually, there's been several times
when I almost picked up the phone.
Maybe you felt the same...
way.
I gotta get better locks.
[BATS SCREECHING]
I have the spectroanalysis results
on those samples you've transmitted, sir.
And?
As you suspected, jet fuel.
The kind commonly used for private planes.
Thank you, Alfred.
[ENGINE ROARING]
[METAL CLINKING]
Finish loading those.
The master will be expecting us.
BATMAN: Then he's going to be disappointed.
♪
[GRUNTS]
[SNAPS]
Ah! Ah!
♪
Yah!
I am only going to ask once.
Where's Ra's Al Ghul?
Mesa De Oro.
A lost city defended with honor for centuries.
TAILIA: Father led the conquistadores who finally vanquished it.
The spoils of that victory
formed the foundation of his vast fortune.
Time is short.
[WHEEZING]
Secure him.
[SCREAMS]
No!
Stop him!
[BOTH GRUNT]
[YELLING]
[GASPING]
[GROANING]
Father!
We're too late, mistress. He's dead.
[GASPS, SOBS]
♪
He's gone.
The world has lost its master.
Proceed anyway. But he's...
As long as the body's warm, there's still a chance. Do it.
[GROANING]
[YELLS]
[BOTH GRUNT]
Look.
Master.
[GROANING]
[YELLING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
The power.
I've never felt anything like it.
[GROANING]
More. I must have more!
Father, your body.
Don't stop. I want every ounce
every fiber of his strength.
What?
♪
Beloved.
You're foolish to have come here, detective.
Give me the staff.
I think you've had your workout for today.
Yah!
Father, stop, you'll kill him.
Stay back. I must have it.
Farewell, detective.
SUPERMAN: Ra's.
You're forgetting something.
No!
[GROANS]
[SCREAMS]
The roof won't hold up much longer.
Punish me or save your daughter.
Your choice.
Oh!
[SCREAMS]
♪
I see an underground river, but there's no sign of them.
Alive or dead.
I'm guessing you and that woman Tailia had some history.
Pretty much in line with all my other relationships.
I have to admit, it was clever
using Ra's' devotion to his daughter to stop him.
Well, I thought as long as
I couldn't charge in with both arms swinging,
I better use my head.
You know...
there might be something to this partnership business after all.
Yeah, right.
♪