♪
[IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[MUFFLED EXPLOSION]
[SCREAMING & SHOUTING]
[GROWLS]
You've done well, son.
Thank you, Father.
As you say,
it is our destiny to bring peace and order to the universe.
I chose wisely when I adopted you, Kal-El.
You have honored me where others failed.
As a reward for today's conquest,
I'm giving you your own world to rule.
[LAUGHING]
All hail King Kal!
Way to go, big guy.
This calls for a celebration.
DARKSEID: Go on.
Savor the fruits of your victory, Kal.
You've earned it.
[ALL CHEERING]
Oh, yeah! LASHINA: This is gonna be fun.
By the way, Father,
which planet will be mine?
A wealthy but untamed world.
Bringing it under your heel will be your greatest triumph.
It is called Earth.
♪
BOY: Look!
It's Superman!
There's something you don't see in Kansas.
Earth to Clark.
Hello? Anyone home?
[SNAPS]
Huh? Oh, sorry, Lois...
guess my mind must've been
somewhere else.
Well, snap out of it, Smallville, I'm starving.
Two, please.
[BEEPING]
Superman Central.
How are you holding up, Kara?
I've got my hands full, Ma.
But these robots have convinced everyone
that Superman's still around.
I'm so worried, dear.
Still no word from Clark?
No, and it's been over a month since he disappeared.
I don't know how long I can keep this up.
[MUTTERING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[YELLS] Hey, knock...
it off, you greedy pig.
[GRUNTING]
What?
Oops.
I mean, sorry to be a pig,
but I've gotta eat and run.
Weird.
[SIGHS]
Clark, where are you?
♪
Help us, please.
[ALL MOANING]
[GRUNTS]
MAN: Don't leave us here.
Who are you?
Leave me alone.
[ALL SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
No!
The dream again?
Maybe it's time to see Granny.
[SHRIEKS]
SUPERMAN: The dreams are so vivid.
It's almost like they're symbols of something deep inside me.
Something I've forgotten.
There, there, my precious.
Don't fret.
Granny's going to flush those nasty, old cobwebs
right out of your head.
Just relax.
Let your mind drift back.
[YELLING]
♪
GRANNY: You were born on a dying world
called Krypton.
To save your tender, young life,
your parents launched you into space.
Kind fate brought you here to Apokolips,
where benevolent, wise Darkseid found you.
He adopted you and raised you as his own.
He nurtured your powers
and taught you of his great mission:
to bring order to a lawless universe.
And now, he wants you to have your own world
to tame and rule.
Earth.
It all seems so clear now.
Thank you, Granny.
That's what I'm here for, my angel.
[CHUCKLING]
The witless fool.
DARKSEID: Have a care, Granny.
He must not suspect the truth too soon.
No, great Darkseid.
The reprogramming is a complete success.
He will attack Earth as I planned?
Yes, uniting that planet's military force to destroy him.
The poor lamb.
Earth will be decimated in the battle.
I vowed never to interfere with that world again.
But even Highfather would not object to me restoring order
to the confused and broken survivors.
It's a brilliant scheme, Darkseid.
Earth will be yours.
♪
[BEEPING]
[BEEPING LOUDER]
[SCREAMING] I'm up, I'm up.
Oh, great. The robot's gone haywire.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I saw it at a little gallery in the village,
and I just had to have it.
[SCREAMING & SHOUTING]
I hope you saved the receipt.
[GASPS]
♪
Oh, no.
Clark will have a cow when he hears about this.
SUPER GIRL: Oof!
[GRUNTING]
Whoa!
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
LEX: Super Girl.
I should've suspected you were behind this.
I don't know what you're talking about...
Luthor. Lex Luthor.
I know who you are.
What are you trying to pull here?
I was about to ask you the same thing.
You see, I've known for some time now
that this wasn't the genuine article.
[METAL CLANKING]
Is that right?
I make it my business to know the habits of my enemies.
[BUZZING]
I can spot a fake a mile away.
It was a simple matter to scramble this robot's circuitry
and confirm my suspicions.
Superman is missing.
[METAL CLANKING]
No, he's not.
He's just been kind of busy lately.
It's more than that.
I think he's gone and not coming back.
Admit it, child.
You can keep up this charade only so long.
You'd be surprised at what I can do.
[GRUNTS]
LEX: I've always believed as you do, General Hardcastle,
that Superman poses a threat to national,
even global, security.
That's why I agreed to fund this operation.
Ever since he first appeared in Metropolis,
Project Achilles has secretly monitored
all his activities.
And now, his alien friend Super Girl is using a robot
to cover for him.
What are they up to?
I don't know.
But we should be on our guard.
My troops are ready, Father.
If you're to be a king, my son,
you should fight under your own standard.
♪
I designed it myself.
Does it displease you?
No.
It just seems familiar.
I'll carry it with honor, Father.
Onward!
For the glory of Darkseid and Apokolips.
[BEEPING]
Now what?
Kara, have you heard the news?
It's too horrible.
Is it about Clark?
See for yourself, dear.
The invaders came out of nowhere
and struck without warning.
Our forces were totally unprepared
for the savage onslaught.
Let's go! Move out!
NATO's weapons, communications and defense systems
were all wiped out in a matter of minutes.
But the biggest shock was the revelation
of the invasion leader's identity.
Superman.
Clark.
HARDCASTLE: Luthor, the moment we've dreaded is finally here.
The aliens have turned against us.
I told you they couldn't be trusted, general.
Well, obviously that robot was just a decoy
while he and Super Girl planned the final stages of this attack.
Now, he's trying to knock out
every major military system on the planet.
There's only one thing to do.
I'm on it.
Keep me posted, general.
I never thought it was possible.
Neither did I.
The fury of these attacks.
The cold disdain in his eyes.
It's unlike anything I've seen before.
MERCY: He's a completely different person.
Soon to be a very dead one.
I don't know what twist of fate caused this change,
but Superman's handed us the perfect opportunity
to destroy him.
I intend to exploit it.
♪
Hit him with everything you've got.
I can't believe Superman's really doing this.
Believe it.
[SCREAMING]
Someone's gotta talk to him, reason with him.
Are you crazy?
Dumb question.
Look out!
SUPER GIRL: That's enough, Clark.
What do you think you're doing?
My father's will.
[GRUNTS] Sorry, Clark.
But I can't let you do it.
You wear my shield, but stand against me?
Then die!
What kept ya? We're running out of time.
I wanted to deliver this personally.
Remember, general,
you're only going to get one shot.
Make it count.
Superman, stop! You'll kill her.
You?
Yeah, it's me, Lois.
Lois?
You've always tried to help and protect,
not destroy.
What's happened to you?
I... I don't know.
Fire!
Lois, get down.
Direct hit.
No way he could've survived that.
[COUGHS]
[COUGHING]
Superman?
Oh, my God.
♪