♪
NARRATOR: Previously on Superman:
Great Darkseid.
The reprogramming is a complete success.
He will attack Earth as I planned?
GRANNY: Yes, uniting that planet's military force
to destroy him.
What's happened to you?
I don't know.
HARDCASTLE: Fire!
Nothing could've survived that.
♪
[SIREN WAILING]
[COUGHS]
[COUGHING]
Superman!
Stay back.
Lois?
Where are you taking them?
Lois.
[LAUGHS]
Come to Granny, darling.
She'll make it all better.
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
GRANNY: Bring him here.
Great Darkseid has something special
planned for this one.
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMING]
Welcome, Kal-El, my son.
[GASPS]
[DOOR OPENS]
HARDCASTLE: Gotta thank Luthor
for those red sun lamps.
They sure even things up.
The only reason you're being kept alive
is to tell us what's going on.
I don't know.
Then let me bring you up to date.
You're a military prisoner about to stand trial
for your traitorous attack on Earth.
Sound familiar?
I wasn't responsible.
Of course not.
Where's Super Girl?
Let's go.
MAN [OVER SPEAKER]: The crisis has passed,
and the threat of hostile alien invasion
has been neutralized.
[MURMURING]
Superman's dead?
I repeat, the threat has been neutralized.
That's not true.
He was alive when he was taken away.
Where are you holding him? And where's Super Girl?
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for your time.
You didn't answer me!
Answer me!
First you declare all-out war on Earth,
and now that you've lost,
you'd like us to believe
an alien despot was controlling your mind.
How stupid do you think we are?
Darkseid's attacked Earth before.
He wants this planet any way he can get it.
And how do we know you haven't been in league with him?
I swear to you that I was manipulated.
Just following orders. Hm, is that it?
Believe me,
I'll do anything within my power
to make it right.
To who, Superman?
You betrayed us poor earthlings, attacked us in cold blood.
How would you win back our trust?
Rescue a kitten from a tree?
Take him back to his cell.
[GRUNTING]
I'm here from Washington.
Security clearance alpha.
♪
[BEEPING]
That's one plus of having a father in the Pentagon.
GUARD: See how the mighty have fallen.
Still think you can take us weak,
little earthlings, big man?
[GRUNTS] [GRUNTS]
[ALARM BEEPING]
[COUGHING]
Nice try, traitor.
If he tries that again, alert me, immediately.
I told you.
Superman's too dangerous to keep locked up here.
I agree, Lex.
If he or Super Girl should escape, they'd be unstoppable.
A threat to all mankind.
There's only one permanent solution.
♪
So it ends like this.
Don't think of it as an end, Superman.
My biotech people will spend years studying your carcass.
I'm certain it will be a most profitable endeavor.
Now that I'm as normal as you, Lex,
I wonder if you'd grant me one last request.
And that is?
[GRUNTS]
Thank you.
Filthy alien.
[GRUNTS]
What in blazes...? [GRUNTS]
[YELLING]
Lois!
What are you doing here?
Have you ever tried to get a story out of the military?
I figured it'd be easier to go straight to the source.
Security alert.
Sector three.
[ALARM BLARING]
[BOTH GRUNTING & COUGHING]
We can get out this way.
Not without Super Girl.
Nothing's ever easy with you, is it?
This way.
Kara!
[POUNDING]
I'm not talking to you.
Listen, they wanna kill you.
You have to get out now.
Can't.
Feel so weak.
It's the red lights.
Stand back.
You've got some serious explaining to do.
Later. We've gotta get out of here.
[SCREAMS]
She needs a doctor. Fast.
[ALL YELLING]
Hang on tight.
[EKG BEEPING]
[BUZZING]
♪
[DOOR OPENS]
I'm sorry, Superman. There's nothing I can do.
Emil, she'll die.
But if I help either of you,
it'd be considered an act of treason.
[GASPS]
Hamilton.
[GRUNTING]
Yes, of course. Just don't hurt me.
I'm sorry.
Please, do what you can.
Superman, wait!
Did you see the look on Hamilton's face?
He'll never trust me again.
He doesn't understand.
Frankly, I'm having trouble piecing it together myself.
What happened to you?
It was Darkseid.
He stripped away my memory,
turned me loose to destroy everything I've ever loved.
First the invasion of Earth, then the murder of Dan Turpin.
Now Super Girl's life is hanging by a thread, and I'm an outcast.
Darkseid's responsible for all of it.
What are you gonna do?
Settle it.
Once and for all.
Wait!
Heaven help you.
[ALL GROWLING]
♪
Father, it's Superman.
So the prodigal son returns.
Let him come.
[CRASH] Huh?
[SCREAMS]
You're first on my list.
A joke.
It was only a joke, my little sugar drop.
I'm not laughing.
Now, now. Don't be cross.
Let Granny make everything better.
[SCREAMS] Ungrateful brat!
I gave you a glorious new life.
And now you turn on dear, old Granny?
[LAUGHING]
[GRUNTING]
Well, this time I won't leave you
wits enough to pick your... No!
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
Sweet dreams.
Welcome back, lover.
Give us a kiss?
Get out of my way, Lashina.
[LAUGHING]
Tag, you're it!
Ain't that a kick in the head?
Wanna play footsie?
I'm not finished with you, boy toy.
Yes, you are.
[MUFFLED BANGING]
♪
[THUD]
I can't believe he's blood.
You used me.
I told you once, Superman,
if you would not be my knight,
you would be my pawn.
I see you're a man of your word.
I am many things, Kal-El.
You couldn't begin to imagine half of them.
But for now, I shall take the role of executioner.
[GRUNTING]
A final gift, my wayward son.
A fast death.
Infinitely preferable to the shame
of returning to Earth.
There, your legacy would be one
of fear and distrust.
A pariah desperately chasing the favor of a world
that cursed your name.
You dare strike me?
[ALL SCREAMING]
That's for Dan Turpin.
Who?
The good man you murdered.
Had I known one human's death would pain you so,
I would have killed more.
And kill more I shall.
Carry that agony with you to oblivion, Superman.
[ALL SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
[ALL GASP]
[THUD]
Darkseid is finished.
Do with him as you will.
You're free.
Master.
Let me help you, master.
Gently. Be careful.
I am many things, Kal-El,
but here, I am god.
GIRL: Don't, Clark.
Kara.
You fight by Darkseid's rules, you're gonna kill somebody.
And it won't be him.
Let it go.
Let's go home.
Home.
In the wake of this week's dramatic developments,
we asked the people of Metropolis
how they felt about the Man of Steel.
If you ask me,
the bum oughta go back where he came from.
I used to consider him my friend, but now...
Superman saved the world dozens of times.
We owe him a second chance.
No one man should have that much power.
HARDCASTLE: He's a traitor and a menace.
WOMAN: I'm locking my bedroom door at night.
LOIS: Don't listen to them.
No, they're right.
I did lose control, and it scares me.
If I can't trust myself,
how can I win back the trust of an entire planet?
One person at a time.
♪