You're getting to be a real thorn in my side, Batman.
And you're no rose, Poison Ivy. Unh.
Why fight, Batman, when we can kiss and make up?
Aw.
Who will save you now, jimbo?
Yep, it's official.
I hate vegetables.
Batgirl.
For the last time, Ivy, it's woman. Batwoman.
And Commissioner Gordon won't be staying for dinner.
Devour her.
Oh!
Okay, Batman, awaiting your expert guidance here.
Ahh..
Seriously... help?
Go ahead, Batman, give your little lady friend a hand.
As you command.
Hey!
Guess you were serious about not wanting a sidekick.
Oh..
Hiya. You've probably been wondering what I'm doing here.
Fair enough. Yesterday, I was just your average teen
who was trying to find herself.
Today, I've got some majorly peeved petunias
nipping at my cape.
But enough about my new wardrobe.
Let me take you back to the beginning.
Now, if you think this all started
with a bad girl named Poison Ivy, you'd be wrong.
The situation came down the night before, at a plant.
Um, as in industrial, not vegetable.
And it started with a bad guy.
Target sighted.
'Proceed with your mission, Temblor.'
Hello? Is this thing on?
'Yes, yes, the fine print.'
'Payment in full and in advance.'
Let's rumble.
Freeze!
'Officers need backup. Repeat, backup.'
It's on its way.
Hoo-yah!
Howdy. I'm Temblor.
Let's shake.
'Temblor, I'm waiting.'
'Have you completed your mission?'
Unh... unh.
Set up a perimeter.
If Mr. Quake so much as breathes.
I want someone there to tell me what he had for lunch.
It's okay to show yourself.
You're not on our most-wanted list anymore.
Force of habit.
Third building Temblor's taken out this week
and we still can't nail a pattern.
I'll nail a motive, he's work-for-hire.
I managed to borrow this from Temblor.
Gordon.
Uh, not a good time. What is it, Barbara?
It's your lucky night, pop.
No need to pick me up from gymnastics.
You skipped practice again?
You sound stressed. I should let you go.
'You're letting years of training slip down the drain.'
I just hope you're not out with Pamela Isley again.
I don't give you a hard time about the company you keep.
We'll talk when I get home.
You're with him right now, aren't you?
'No, yes. I..'
We're discussing a case.
Roger that, commish. Over and out.
My daughter. Teenagers, huh?
- Ready, Red? - Let's do it, Red.
This is a stick-up.
Psych.
Quite a mess, huh?
Well, not compared to the amount of pollution
your company, Chlorogene, dumps into our environment.
And don't even get me started on your whole
chloro-mulch-brand mutated super-vegetables.
- Unh. - We'll save you.
Security!
Good job, Red.
Ahh..
Hey!
You're a superstar, Red.
Years of training.
Beats hanging out at the mall, huh?
- Uh-oh. - Busted.
You two need a ride?
Barb, I'm concerned you're on your way to
blowing your shot at the Olympics.
What could've been more important than practice tonight?
Red and I were just out
trying to make the world a better place.
You know, for plants.
I'm all for green, Pamela, really, I am.
But I know from your juvenile-hall record
'that your methods can be a little extreme.'
'Now, sorry to cut the evening short'
but it's past my daughter's curfew.
Thanks for the ride, commish.
Barb, Pam's a bad seed.
You've traced the messages
to their source already, Master Bruce?
Bat-Wave's intercepting a live message, Alfred.
'Temblor.'
'I have a new target for you.'
I want you to destroy the corporate headquarters
of Chlorogene.
It's destruction must be total.
'Pammy, I need you to take out the trash.'
- 'Who was that?' - That was my henchman.
'I said take out the trash!'
In a minute.
'What about my pay?'
In full and in advance, as usual.
Wired straight from my piggy bank.
Yep, this should cover it.
And here I thought earthquakes struck without warning.
Buddy, you just dialed "D" for destruction.
Yah!
Yaah!
'I thought I'd seen it all, Barb.'
'You wouldn't believe the demolition'
'this Temblor character is capable of.'
But the Bat has a lead.
I think he's really gonna come through for us on this one.
So, when are you gonna invite the Dark Knight over
for your killer pork chops so I can meet him?
Beanbags "R" Us. This is Gary.
Hey, Red. I'm not done with Chlorogene
and their mutated super-plants.
What say you and me go down to their research labs
and try some persuasion on their scientists?
No can do. A parental unit is near. Gotta go.
The other Red?
Barb, she's trouble.
Pam's a good friend, and she gets the environment thing.
That's important to me.
Last month, Betsy was a good friend
and beekeeping was important to you.
Look, pop, if you're so concerned Pam is gonna steer me
down some criminal path just remember
I was pretty much set on becoming a detective
'until someone decided to get me'
'a mustachioed Eastern European gym coach'
so I could go for the gold.
Barb, law enforcement is dangerous work.
I don't want that life for you.
Maybe if you'd seen the mess Temblor made
at Neugog Chemicals tonight..
What? Neugog Chemicals?
Gordon. Batman and Temblor are at Chlorogene?
Just now? I'll be right there.
Sorry, hon. Duty calls.
Neugog Chemicals? Chlorogene?
Companies Red and I went to on protests
or scouting missions for Temblor's demolitions.
'Bat-Wave traced the messages to their source.'
Pamela Isley.
I know that name.
I just hope you're not out with Pamela Isley again.
Barbara Gordon's friend.
I do hope the commissioner's daughter
is not somehow involved in this enterprise.
So do I.
Get out before we call the police.
Had your chance.
'Sir, Bat-Wave is intercepting another live message.'
Put it through, Alfred.
'I have a new target, Temblor.'
'Chlorogene research labs. It's located..'
Yeah, yeah, it's just around the corner from me.
But before we discuss that
there seems to be a little problem
with the money transfers.
I'm sorry, but didn't you just blow the last job?
Listen, Temblor, if you're interested in getting
'paid at all, you'd better get over here right now.'
I said here. Stupid.
Temblor?
Is he a friend from homeroom?
Looks like you caught me red-handed, Red.
Did one of your twigs snap, Pam?
You hired a thug.
You'd be surprised what you can find on the internet.
Pam, it's not too late. You have to stop this.
I don't wanna have to watch my dad
read you your rights.
And here I thought we were two peas in a pod.
Should've known I couldn't trust the commish's kid.
I'll miss you, Red. Ahh!
Well, well.
Lemme see how this works.
Testing.
'Testing.'
You are not at all how I pictured you..
Boss.
See, the way it works, boss
is when you don't pay..
You pay.
Hey, we're good for it.
We'll raise the funds with a bake sale.
You like brownies?
Later, Red. You two have fun.
I'm warning you, I'm-I'm an Olympic hopeful.
Rrrr!
Mutant tomatoes. Yum.
You've been terminated.
Huh..
Aah! Unh! Ahh!
Hmm..
Huh?
Ahh..
The Batman.
And he's..
He is awesome.
Red, help. I can't move.
Oh, no. Toxic sludge.
No. Hang on, Red.
That stuff mutates plants.
I don't wanna see what it does to humans.
Here comes the big one.
Yaah!
Aah!
No!
Oh..
Did you, uh, invite him for pork chops?
Will she be okay?
We'll know more after the detox procedure.
Okay, I know.
You still wanna know how we get from here to here.
Well, believe it or not..
Hyah!
This, my friends, is only the beginning.