Hey, me again, Barbara Gordon, sidekick hopeful
and commissioner's kid. Let's get you up to speed.
Proceed with your mission, Temblor.
Third building Temblor's taken out this week
and we still can't nail a pattern.
He's work-for-hire.
I just hope you're not out with Pamela Isley again.
Pam's a bad seed.
And don't even get me started on your whole
chloro-mulch-brand mutated super vegetables.
Barb, I'm concerned you're on your way
to blowing your shot at the Olympics.
I have a new target for you.
I want you to destroy
the corporate headquarters of Chlorogene.
Barb, law enforcement is dangerous work.
I don't want that life for you.
Batwave traced the messages to their source.
Pamela Isley.
Red, you have to stop this.
And here I thought we were two peas in a pod.
Temblor wasn't too happy to find out
his boss was a teenybopper.
The Batman. He is awesome.
Aah!
No!
Catch all that?
We'll pop-quiz you later
'cause right now, things are about to get thorny.
Huh?
Mmm.
We must have hit something.
U-uh, I didn't see a thing.
Hmm.
'Barb, it could've been you'
in the back of that ambulance tonight.
I know you wanted to help your friend
but you need to leave police work to the police.
Is that what you tell the Batman?
T-the Bat's a special case.
- I mean, you can't compare.. - Probably him now.
Hello, commissioner. It's the Batman.
Care to go bowling?
Gordon. What?
You can't find Isley?
'I'm on my way.'
The Dark Knight has a green thumb?
This leave-behind is my only lead, Alfred.
And so far, it's definitely not garden variety.
Ah, aah!
Huh?
What's happening?
Pop's never gonna let me work in law enforcement.
Not after what happened tonight.
Guess it's back to gymnastics.
Unless..
Mild-mannered Olympic hero by day
butt-kicking Batwoman by night.
"Who is that masked woman." The commissioner wonders.
Whoa.
Sit. Uh, uh, stay.
No, wait. You're a plant.
Don't do anything.
Aah!
Prepare to suffer the wrath of mother nature.
Destroy her.
Psych.
- What's up, Red? - Pam?
- What happened to you? - Just a fab makeover.
Green is the new red
and I'm gonna use my powers
to avenge crimes against nature.
We can do it together, Red, the two of us
and I'm betting Chlorogene will listen to me this time.
Hey, sounds great.
Except for the fact that you're a plant.
Ivy, to be exact, poison ivy.
Think about it, Red.
I gotta call dad.
No, wait.
She'll just wind up behind bars.
I have to be the one to help Pam without dad knowing.
But I can't do it alone.
The Batsignal isn't a toy, Miss Gordon.
Didn't have your cell number. But this is urgent.
Pam Isley came to see me
but she's calling herself Poison Ivy now
and, well, how do I put this?
She was part plant.
- It all fits. - It does?
A plant particle I found at the scene of Pamela's disappearance
contained traces of steroids made by Chlorogene.
When Pamela was contaminated, her biochemistry was altered.
Then come on. Let's save Pam.
I'll do everything in my power to help your friend, Barbara.
What? Look, wait a minute.
But you haven't even seen my costume.
Huh?
Aah!
Police.
Tonight marks the end of an era for Chlorogene.
So get ready because it's hostile takeover time.
Consider the fate of Chlorogene a warning, Gotham.
Mother nature just got herself some muscle.
Pamela, you're not well.
- Let me help you. - Batman.
Thanks, but I have all the help I need.
Batman, look out!
Hiya.
A Batgirl. Hmm.
Who knew you had a sidekick?
- I don't. - FYI, it's Batwoman.
Either way, you're bat meat.
Ivy, time to give up.
Tried that. She's not interested.
Maybe she'll be interested in this.
Nice aim.
I'll be practicing that.
Your friend still has lots to learn, Batman.
Teach her how to survive a fall yet?
Whoa!
Whoa.
You're good at this.
No time to babysit.
Gone.
Okay, here goes nothing.
Let me make myself clear.
There's no room for a Batgirl in Gotham.
That's cool because it's Batwoman
as in I'm a grown woman and don't need to listen to you.
Then for your own safety, if you won't listen to me
I'm gonna have to tell your father, Miss Gordon.
Uh, you must have me confused with someone else.
Oh, dude.
You just broke the superhero secret identity code.
Evening, commish.
Pamela?
What do you think you're doing?
'Trying to make the world a better place'
for plants.
Let go of me.
As you command.
Magic spores.
'Mother nature's mind control.'
- A little help here. - Of course.
Up you go.
Freeze, Pamela. It doesn't have to be this way.
Actually, commish, it does.
Because the only law Poison Ivy answers to
is the law of the jungle.
A Batgirl, sir?
Perhaps I should equip the Batcave with a doggy door
should Bathound decide to join the gang.
Barbara doesn't know what she's getting herself into, Alfred.
I'm gonna have to tell her father.
The Batwave reports that James Gordon
'has just been kidnapped by Poison Ivy.'
Isn't nature fascinating, jimbo?
For instance, all that struggling you're doing there
'that lets this carnivorous plant'
'know it's captured food.'
Hmm. Let me show you.
Mmm. Cool, huh?
Some first day as a sidekick.
I failed to stop Ivy.
My aim needs work.
And I blew my secret identity.
As I wondered whether or not I should quit
my crime-fighting career
my world got rocked again.
Breaking news, Police Commissioner Gordon
was abducted a short time ago
by a new supervillain calling herself Poison Ivy.
No word on whether or not..
Dad.
I'll quit tomorrow.
Batman, it's a trap. Mm.
'Well, well, a weed in the garden.'
Whack it, boys.
No, you're not experiencing deja vu.
This is where we began and if you remember.
Ivy used her mind control mojo on Batman.
I made my triumphant return as Batgirl
so I could rescue pop and then the big bat
was asked to eliminate his favorite sidekick.
So now that you know how I got into this mess
the question becomes how do I get out?
Think I need to knock some sense back into him.
Hello. Remember me, plucky sidekick?
- Sidekick, huh? - And he's back.
He's back just in time
to witness the commissioner become plant food.
Dad.
- I'll get the commissioner. - No, wait.
Huh?
Amateur.
Come on. Focus.
Bull's eye.
All in the wrist.
- 'Ivy.' - Huh?
Catch.
Hiya.
Mow 'em down!
Can't ice me if you can't hit me.
Whoa!
Ohh! Aah! Aah!
The thing about plants, love water.
'Missed me.'
No!
I, uh, owe you my thanks, Batgirl.
It's Batwo..
Forget it. Batgirl it is.
Okay then. Gotta go.
Uh, you take care now, citizen.
Another Red? Huh, what're the chances?
So still plan on telling my dad?
Not every child gets the opportunity
to rescue their parent.
I'm sure he'd be grateful if you decided to tell him.
I'll take that as a no.
As you can see, everything ended quite nicely.
Well, maybe ended isn't the right word
because this, my friends, is only the beginning.
Whoo!