'Oh, believe me, Councilman Vargas'
I love Gotham Park as much as you do.
But our citizens need a new hospital.
And the only feasible way to accomplish that
is to pave over the park.
Knock knock Come in.
Come in!
That's my decision, unpopular as it may seem.
Goodnight.
Knock knock.
Flowers?
Well, I guess somebody out there still likes me.
I love this park as much as you do.
So believe me when I tell you
Gotham Park isn't going anywhere ever!
In fact, this will be the first site
to benefit from my new plan to..
' "Green Up Gotham."'
We'll tear up the sidewalks to plant more grass
more trees, and more flowers!
Time for mild-mannered Barbara Gordon
to scope out the commissioner's office for some cases.
Delivery for Commissioner Gordon.
- ' "Baudelaires?" ' - 'You can leave 'em there.'
You got it, commissioner.
Secret admirer, pop?
Hmm.
"From Mayor Grange."
Didn't think you were his type.
Oh, the mayor's really running wild
with this whole "Green up Gotham" thing.
Politicians. How was school, Barb?
Me learned good today. How's work?
Neck-deep in a new case.
Penguin, huh? What crime did he commit this time?
A daughter can't take an interest in her father's work?
We can catch up at dinner, kiddo.
Okay, but don't work too hard.
Remember to stop and smell the... whatever those are.
Gesundheit.
I beg your pardon, Master Bruce.
I seem to be suffering from a touch of..
Oh! Hay fever.
Most unusual this time of year.
That's not all that's unusual, Alfred.
Penguin went to a whole lot of trouble
to steal a truckload of chemicals last night.
Might he be planning to poison the water supply or..
Blow something up?
The chemical Penguin took is nontoxic and noncombustible.
- ' "Ag-I." ' - 'Silver Iodide.'
Used to make photographs or seed clouds for precipitation.
So, Penguin either wants to start a photo album..
Or he wants to make it rain. The question is why.
Clank clank clank.
Ha ha ha!
'Can't say I'm in the mood for rain, Penguin.'
Quack!
I just washed my car.
Too bad, Bat-breath.
Because my forecast calls for a 90 percent chance of showers..
Crash
and 100 percent chance of me kicking your butt!
Thud.
Since when are you so interested in the weather, Penguin?
Don't you read the papers, Bat-wit?
The mayor wants to green up Gotham.
Wa ha ha ha ha!
Clang What?
I bet chopped bat makes good fertilizer.
Whoa. Aah!
Boom
crash.
Penguin?
Plant matter.
Commissioner, moments ago, this mulch was Penguin.
Never mind that.
I thought I could count on you, Batman
but if you won't obey the law
then I will place you under arrest.
On what charge?
Homicide.
You killed this plant.
Click.
Take him downtown.
Since when is it against the law to harm a plant?
Since this afternoon, when the city council
passed the vegetation rights act.
Alright, plant killer, let's go.
Smack
bam bam bam
swoosh boom
whoosh beep Sir?
'Anything strange'
'on the radar, Alfred?'
You mean, anything beside city council
announcing a ban on lawnmowers?
Oh! Forgive me, sir.
'My hay fever has grown even worse'
'since your flowers arrived.'
Flowers?
"From Mayor Grange. Keep Gotham green."
Alfred, destroy them. Now!
The mayor is cultivating rather unusual plants, sir.
He isn't the only one.
The police aren't themselves all the way up to..
Gordon.
- 'Sir?' - Barbara may be in trouble.
- Huh? - Hello, Barbara.
Pop, do we need to put a bell on you?
Dinner will be ready in a few.
I brought you something.
The mayor's secondhand stems.
How sweet.
No, Barbara, these were picked especially for you.
Smell them.
Fishy.
What? Don't you trust me?
I trust my dad.
And you're a little too into flowers to be him.
Daddy's angry.
Daddy's green.
Thud
bam bam bam.
Not even close to human.
- You thinkin' who I'm thinkin'? - Poison Ivy.
And apparently working with a new strain of plant life.
But if she's replacing people with living plant clones
'what's she doing with the originals?'
Maybe we should ask the florist.
' "Baudelaires."'
Let me slip into something more comfortable.
Ting ting ting.
Oh, are you here for some... bam.
You knew she was a plant, right?
I'm betting this doesn't lead to the break room.
Whoa.
'Pop.'
No.
Ivy's replaced the most powerful people in Gotham.
'Well, of course.'
Who better to help me spread the gospel of green?
Release them, Ivy.
Why? They've never been happier.
See, while their plant twins
pave the way for my Gotham takeover
tiny plant toxins are working overtime
helping these human counterparts
'to finally appreciate the wonders of nature.'
Green is good.
Ivy and clovers and dandelions.
It's all so pretty.
They'll love plant life just as much as I do
for the rest of their unwaking days.
There's one slight problem with your plan, Ivy.
Us.
Aww, bummer.
But here, flowers always cheer me up.
I bred these darlings myself.
They possess highly-evolved replication characteristics.
Nature's little mimics, I call them.
What do you say we go turn the rest of Gotham into plant-peeps?
I'm up for it.
Let's party.
It'll be a snap.
These pups are ultra-fast growing with plenty of water.
And with millions of seeds already planted in Gotham Park
I'm gonna just love watching my garden grow.
Oh, and don't worry.
In just a few moments, you'll be feeling right as rain.
Huh? The Batman?
You are going to love it here!
Hey, everybody, look who's checking in!
- I like posies. - Everywhere.
It's so... pretty.
Beep beep beep Brain activity low.
Possible cause, obstruction.
Transmitting electronic pulse.
Crackle crackle crackle
splash.
Five more minutes.
Aww!
Are you alright, commissioner?
Oh.
As long as I never have to pick another daisy.
You're not through picking yet.
They need your help.
'All fixed.'
Gotham's human population is about to be canceled
on account of rain.
Ivy's finished.
Here comes your evil twin.
Mine can't be far behind.
I'm right here, ugly.
Boom bam
swish swish swish swish.
Try again.
Clang clang clang.
Ha!
You must not like broccoli.
Hate it.
Snap
thwack thwack thwack
gulp boom
crash.
Let it pour.
Drink up, my babies.
Too late. Get them!
Swoosh
boom Direct hit.
But it's still pouring.
The projectile was filled with
a highly concentrated herbicide.
It's raining weed-killer.
No!
Attack!
Thud thud.
My babies.
Your babies are mulch, Ivy.
Thanks for doing your part to green up Gotham.