Vroom vroom.
And the Gotham City Speedway
is off to an exciting start.
'The fastest racers in the country'
'have gathered here in Gotham'
'each striving for the charity of their choice.'
'And Gotham's very own Bruce Wayne'
'is the only non-pro racing today'
'for Gotham's Children's Hospital.'
swoosh swoosh swoosh.
'And Bruce Wayne takes the lead.'
Your loss, pop, I could've been driving
for the policemen's charity fund.
He-he, maybe you should finish driving school
before you decide to join the racing circuit, Barbara.
Boosh
thud That vehicle isn't registered.
Screech.
Who's crashing the race?
Stay close, Barbara.
Click click.
I won your race, so I'll collect the prize
for my favorite charity.
Me, Gearhead.
Clang clang clang.
Always wanted to race Gotham's finest.
The prize money should keep this mystery driver's
tank topped off for quite some time.
I don't think Gearhead's in it for the money, Alfred.
He likes the chase.
We're dealing with a thrill-seeker.
It's Gearhead.
Do buckle up, sir.
Could be a bumpy ride.
I think I may have trouble.
Boosh.
Ah!
Screech It's... driving itself?
Batman.
'Time to kick things up a notch.'
It's racing time.
Remember, hands at 10 o'clock
and at 2 o'clock.
I'm learning to drive and tell time.
Whoosh Gearhead!
Whoosh Batman!
Screech
bang bang
whoosh whoosh Ugh.
Oh. Hi.
Vroom
boosh
beep beep beep.
Let's check out your reaction time, Batman.
Screech honk.
Tch-tch. Shouldn't tailgate.
Beep boosh
screech
crash beep beep beep
boom
splash.
Ha ha ha!
Try buffing that out.
No time to be sentimental.
Gearhead will be looking for the next rush
and this is one villain the Batman
needs wheels to take down.
I'm gonna have to retool one of my prototypes.
I'm gonna have to build a better Batmobile.
And I'll start by doing a little shopping
at Wayne Industries.
The Dual EXP Power Core.
Crackle crackle
creak creak.
The power core's unstable at top speeds.
What an odd little giz.. Oh! Uh! My word!
Crackle crackle I assume that is not
an acquisition from Wayne Industries.
Gearhead Industries.
A souvenir from the armored car job.
It injects some kind of nano-virus into machinery
taking it over like a parasite
controlling it.
I aim to make sure this Batmobile
is Gearhead-proof.
'Barbara, the driving school tells me'
'you have quite the lead foot.'
The instructor was making me nervous.
Gordon.
Where? On my way.
Plumbing burst at the courthouse?
Gearhead. Sorry, Barb. Have to go.
Taking the car?
Kidding.
Gearhead is chasing the bullet train?
It was scheduled for a money transfer
from the Treasury Building.
But, sir, the power core has yet to charge.
I'll need an alternate mode of transportation.
Clang crackle crackle.
Ooh, two-wheeler.
Bang bang
boosh
whoosh.
'Autopilot on.'
Hey, no hitchhikers.
I really need my own set of..
Wheels.
'Let's lose the training wheels.'
screech
bang
whoosh.
He he he.
You're in for a surprise.
Hey! What're you doing?
Ha ha ha. Take a bus, Batman!
Ha ha ha!
He doesn't use nanotechnology.
He is nanotechnology.
Screech.
The Batcycle's autopilot isn't responding.
Should've known.
'Alfred. Power core status.'
Charge is complete, sir.
'Lower the chassis.'
'I'm takin' it out for a spin.'
Do come back in one piece, won't you?
Okay, so I stole Batman's ride
and I lost Gearhead.
Not good.
Clang.
Even worse!
Aah!
You look a little young.
'You even have a driver's license?'
No. But here's my permit!
Clang
swoosh.
Whoa.
Clank clank clank.
Don't knock the student driver.
'Pretty cool, huh?'
Here's another trick I learned in machine shop.
Whoa.
You traded up, Batman.
Rematch! Ha ha ha!
Swoosh.
Nice landing.
Ooh! Corinthian leather?
Catch me if you can, Bats.
Crackle
whoosh
thud.
Whoo-hoo!
Screech screech
boosh.
Power core.
Thud
screech crash.
No one beats Gearhead.
- Road rage coming. - You hear me, Batman?
No one!
Thwack.
Gotta admit, Bat, that's one sweet ride you have.
He's jacking you!
Crackle crackle crackle.
What did you.. I'm stuck!
Nanotechnology, Gearhead
yours with some tweaks.
I still have the car. Time to roll.
Wouldn't recommend it.
Crackle crackle crackle
crackle.
So, uh, since Gearhead can't
drive the Batmobile, can I?
Any progress on power core calibration, sir?
Stable.
She's a keeper.
Click I didn't hear the bat-wave.
I just thought I'd take it for a spin.
Boosh screech
whoosh