And now, an update on tonight's election
as Gotham's Mayor Grange defends his post
against billionaire technologies mogul.
Maximillian Zeus
'who earlier in the campaign, appeared poised to win.'
You might say the classics inspire me.
After all, the Greeks and the Romans proved
that great societies rise through strong leadership.
'But despite his popularity'
'Zeus began losing support when his campaign unveiled'
'some unusual ideas.'
I shall remodel our city's
ineffectual police department
after my own private security force
of gladiators.
Glad I didn't vote for him.
You'd be sharp, looking all Spartacus, pop.
With nearly all the votes tallied, Mayor Grange
is guaranteed a resounding victory tonight.
And things are quiet at Zeus' corporate headquarters.
I'm Bruce Wayne, and while Zeus practices his concession speech
I'd like to introduce my friend
and your mayor for another four years.
'Marion Grange.'
Woo-hoo!
Thank you, Bruce.
- Citizens of Gotham... - 'Citizens of Gotham.'
Tonight's results, while disappointing
do not surprise me.
But I cannot allow this beloved metropolis to crumble
like so many great civilizations past.
'Thus I, Maximillian Zeus'
'shall rule over Gotham'
'from New Olympus!'
beep beep
vroom.
So that we may better venture together into the future.
'I shall erase the mistakes of the past.'
Barb, get out of here.
Now watch as your City Hall crumbles
'swift as lightning.'
zap zap
beep beep
boom
vroom.
He destroyed City Hall. What are we supposed to do now?
Time to slip into my jammies.
Citizens, if you wish to avoid
further demonstrations of might
you shall comply with the following decrees.
'First, should any police be sighted'
'I shall incinerate a populated monument.'
'Second, all air traffic is to cease'
'effective immediately.'
'Including bats.'
zap zap zap
swish.
Okay, so where's the Bat?
'I do hope you have a strategy, sir.'
I'm gonna have to meet Zeus..
On his turf.
'There he is.'
'Uh, where is he going?'
I'm out of the loop again.
Lucky for him, I'm in position.
Now boarding, evil fortress of destruction.
Lastly, for now
Gotham shall dedicate the former site of your City Hall
to the new age
by erecting a temple in my honor.
The man wants to be worshipped?
If I had the Bat's cell number
I could let him know I'm up here..
What?
'Gunnery crew, prepare the thunderstorm.'
I don't think Zeus is talking about the weather.
The police can't help us. What are we gonna do, Jim?
Only thing we can. We wait for the Bat.
So he can do what?
Knock down that flying battleship with his boomerang?
Batarang.
With all due respect to the Dark Knight
he's only one man.
Zeus vaporized City Hall.
Batwave link booted.
Dual EXP Power Cores activated.
Thrusters standing by.
The Batwing is ready for takeoff.
Thankfully, Zeus is not the only billionaire in Gotham
to have built a flying machine.
'Gotham is in a state of panic.'
'Citizens are evacuating in droves.'
That must be the power core.
Oh, if I only knew how to shut it down.
Time to steal Maxie's thunder.
Honk honk honk.
'Target locked. Gotham Bay Bridge.'
We must burn a few bridges
if we are to keep our subjects contained.
Ignite thunderstorm.
'Twenty seconds to full charge. Nineteen.'
Well, I hope this one's important.
No.
- 'Sixteen.' - Guess not.
'Fifteen. Fourteen.'
- Lucky number three? - 'Thirteen.'
We've lost power?
Only to the countdown mechanism.
Thunderstorm continues to charge.
It's still powering up?
I'm usually a whole lot better at breaking things.
'Charge nearing completion, sir.'
beep beep beep.
Engine room.
'Provide immediate status.'
Yes, sir.
Master bolt transducer charged and operational.
'Then check all other system functions.'
'It would seem we have gremlins.'
That would be me.
- Airspace violated, sir. - What? By whom?
The Batman.
Missile systems on.
Target locked.
Swish swish Defense systems activated.
Boom boom zap zap zap.
The Bat's got a new set of wings.
Way to keep me in the loop.
Sir, he's neutralized our arms.
Then release the Harpies.
We've locked onto his radio frequency.
Batman. Surely you are familiar with the myth of Icarus?
Of how he flew too close to the sun..
And burned his wings.
Zap.
'I'm hit.'
crackle No.
Come on, the Bat needs you.
'I don't believe it.'
There must be dozens of unpatched cables.
Glad everybody's on break.
'Batman may not know I'm here..'
but he's about to.
Target locked on disabled craft, sir.
Whoever said lightning never strikes twice?
What now?
Uh, gremlins?
Slam crackle.
Heck of a place for an emergency landing.
Screech
zap
zap zap zap.
Bow to your emperor.
Welcome, Batman.
'Your reputation is mythic.'
But alas..
There is only room on New Olympus
for one legend.
Whirr.
'Attention, staff. I need a price check on kumquats.'
She's hacked into our system.
Our gremlin.
'Show yourself, Batgirl'
'and I shall reconsider dispatching your partner.'
Hmph. "Partner?"
That would suggest we actually
speak once in a while.
'You know, keep each other in the loop?'
Enough! He meets his end.
Oh, Maxie, you may wanna hold off on that.
If you ever wanna see your bolt-firing thingy again
over and out.
Search every level.
I want her found.
That ought to give Bats the space he needs to cut loose.
Monogrammed stockings. Janet speaking.
Can't you just once answer like a normal person?
'Well, I gotta be me, pop.'
I just wanted to make sure you made it home safe, Barb.
We've declared a citywide emergency.
'Then maybe we should keep the phone lines clear.'
'Love you, kisses.'
Erin's hair salon.
'Code names will do you no good'
as we have locked on to your frequency
'and triangulated your location.'
Ah!
Beep.
No sign of her.
Keep looking.
We must retrieve the master bolt transducer.
Well, well.
If it isn't the gremlin.
I will take the device.
You wouldn't dare.
Shatter It broke, Maxie.
Then I shall break you.
Zap zap.
And the name is Maximillian.
Zap.
Damage to antigrav unit. We're losing altitude.
'Abandon ship.'
'All hands to the escape pods.'
Cowards. I command you to stop.
Oh, Maxie, if the crew's jumping ship, who's driving?
It is the Fates who steer New Olympus
into the heart of Gotham.
Get to an escape pod.
Sorry, Bat, but I'm needed in the cockpit.
It's over, Zeus.
We need you to land this craft.
If I must fall from the heavens, Batman
then I shall take you with me.
Autopilot, huh? Won't be needing that.
Shatter shatter.
Batgirl.
Gotta steer this boat to a safe..
Harbor!
Whoosh.
Come on.
Nice landing.
The New Olympus?
'It's on its way to becoming'
'the new Atlantis.'
'She'll need work.'
EXP drives need tuning
and the fuel lines are waterlogged.
Thankfully, the Batgirl proved more durable
than the Batwing.
You're right, Alfred.
I think Batgirl's earned some wings of her own.
Where is the Batman?
Out of the loop, again.
What's that?
I'm in the loop.