'New from Krank Co.'
'The Cosmo Flyer!'
Awesome!
'With the Cosmo Flyer'
'the sky's the limit.'
'It's up, up, and away!'
For fim-foobley fun.
I can't think of a toy more fun for a child..
Or one more dangerous.
Just ask Timmy Snyder.
'Or Reese Jones, who went on a wild ride'
over three counties before authorities could save him.
The Cosmo Flyer is yet another in a long line
of unsafe products from Krank Co.
The same people who brought us the Krank Bots..
'And the Zoom Pets..'
- Aah! - Aah!
Flame-retardant they weren't.
Today, I am happy to report that, thanks to the efforts
of Wayne Industries' Project Safety Net
the doors of Gotham-based Krank Co.
Have been permanently shut.
You thought my toys
were dangerous before, Wayne?
Krank?
Well, get a load of the new model.
It's doo-diddly deadly.
Beep
vroom
boom
clang
whoosh whoosh.
Can Bruce come out and play?
No? Oh, he's buried under a building?
Aww.
You like playing with toys, Krank?
Try mine.
Swish.
Broke your toy. Boo-hoo!
Click click click.
Uhh!
Refill sold separately.
Vroom
whoosh.
Whoa! Dipsy doodles!
'Auto pilot on.'
whoosh
clang.
I own your weak bat butt!
'When Krank finds out you survived, Mr. Wayne'
he's sure to try again.
That's why I'm assigning you
around-the-clock police protection.
I really don't think that's necessary, commissioner.
It's not open for debate, Mr. Wayne.
I won't allow Gotham's favorite son
to be harmed on my watch.
Thank you, Commissioner Gordon.
Let me introduce you to your shadow.
Cash Tankenson, the last line of defense you'll ever need.
Hey, Freddy! How about some more of those nachos?
Extra jalapenos this time.
Straight away, detective shades.
Yo, Wayne, you're supposed to be
some kind of billionaire bachelor
so where's the par-tay?
The night is still young, detective.
Call me Cash, 'cause I'm not just your bodyguard, Wayne
I'm your wingman.
Yeah!
Cover for me, Alfred.
Time for the Batman to call a Krank
so we can send our houseguest home.
'Hey, Freddy! ETA on the nachos.'
Do hurry, sir.
Beep beep.
Let me guess. You're not expecting visitors.
Security breach.
Huh?
Special delivery.
No doubt from Cosmo Krank.
Looks like the Cos don't know.
Cash spent a year on bomb squad.
'No sign of a proximity fuse.'
'Amateur hour.'
Someone at the door, Alfred?
Stay back, Wayne. It's Cash Tankenson show now.
"Ding Dong, you're doo-diddle done!"
I don't get it.
Screech
swish swish.
Careful, sir.
Freddy's right. Leave the rough stuff to the professional.
Who ordered the knuckle sandwich?
Extra knuckles!
Huh?
Have another serving! Uhh!
Swish swish swish.
Uhh! Help! Uhh!
'Uhh! Get it off!'
It's payday.
Hyah!
Slam slam.
You got him.
Whew. Thanks, Cash. I owe you one.
Cash is as Cash does, man.
Dark night, isn't it?
I take your meaning, sir.
Uh, Master Bruce has an early meeting tomorrow.
Allow me to show you to the guest room.
That's not gonna work, Freddy.
Cash has to keep Wayne in his sights at all times.
We're roomies, pal.
Awesome.
And we just trashed a robot, compadre.
How can you be tired?
Cash is pumped and ready to party!
'Get down!'
Ah, I'm just doing my job, Mr. President.
Phew!
Sorry I'm late, commissioner.
Krank's made a second attempt
on Bruce Wayne's life tonight.
I have a man guarding him
but I could really use your help.
Let me keep an eye on Wayne instead.
I can catch Krank in the act.
No. Your talents are best used in the field.
We need to stop Krank...
Before he puts Wayne in danger again.
I'm on my way to Krank's factory, Alfred.
I'm hoping to find something the police missed.
Just buy me more time if Cash asks after me.
No worries there, sir.
Your wingman is sleeping like a baby.
Oh. Ahem. Hey, Wayne.
Which way to the john?
Okay, here we go. Let's see.
Ohh. Nah.
Um, occupied?
Oh. Uh, sorry, Freddy.
Phew.
Huh?
Pop.
Surprise, Batman!
Boom boom boom.
Ahh!
Crackle crackle.
You must think Cash is pretty dumb.
Thought you could pull the wool over Cash's eyes, huh?
That's a negative.
I know where you were.
You were out... partying.
You got me, Cash.
I don't know what to say, I...
Without your wingman.
You never, never leave your wingman.
You were sound asleep. I didn't wanna disturb you.
I don't let many people in, Wayne
but Cash has got feelings, too.
- Look, Cash... - It's Detective Tankenson!
Only my friends call me Cash.
From now on, Mr. Wayne, we do this by the book.
Look, detective, I am really sorry I ran out on you
but I'm just not used to...
Not used to having a babysitter?
Well, get used to it now.
I'd rather have a wingman, Detective Tankenson.
My friends call me Cash.
So, Cash, think we could, uh, lose these now?
You know, the commish is kind of jittery about you
being out in the open for this park dedication ceremony.
I refuse to let a madman dictate how I live my life.
And I'm hopin' Krank tries something
so I can see the look on his face
when I take him down hard!
Back seat, Freddy. Cash Tankenson always drives.
Are you certain this is a good idea, sir?
It's the only way, Alfred.
If I don't let Krank get to Bruce
the Batman doesn't get to Krank.
It's Krank! Look out!
Unh! Unh! Unh!
How 'bout we try on a pair of Cash Tankenson's size 13s?
My toy.
Oh. Uh... sorry, kid.
Little help?
Wayne?
Wayne!
Hey, Bruce Wayne, wanna go for a spin?
Come and get me, Krank.
Wayne!
Help!
Help! Help!
Wayne!
Drop Wayne or Cash drops you!
Whee-hee-hee!
Sorry, Cash. Have to rely on another wing man.
Crackle.
Police! I'm commandeering this vehicle!
No one shakes Cash Tankenson.
Welcome to Kranky Town, Wayne.
The play land children will never get to enjoy
all because of you!
Maybe my toys weren't the safest
but they were bim-boobly fun
and now you get to join my collection.
A little dip in my river of molten plastic and voila.
My very own limited-edition Bruce Wayne non-action figure.
What? Where's Wayne?
Safely on his way home.
Ooh!
Time to put your toys away.
Thud.
Freeze, toy geek!
The Batman? Uh, where's Wayne?
Safely on his way home, apparently
but not for long.
Beep rattle rattle rattle.
With both of you out of the way for good
who will protect Wayne, hmm?
Zoom Pets now come with extreme mangling action.
Here, kitty, kitty. Catnip time.
Splash
swish swish swish.
Hyah!
Ahh-nn-nh!
Got ya.
Who's got who?
Oh, no.
Whoa!
New from Krank Co.
Battle-damaged detective.
Oh, Batman, dipsy doodles?
Come on, now, you can't turn Cash into a candle.
I got my whole life ahead of me.
Who's gonna care for my grandma?
Aah! Oof!
Huh?
Ahh.
I'm done playing nice, Batman.
I.. Where, where.. Where's my remote?
Here's why your toys need warning labels.
Some of this? Let's go. What?
No! What-what are you doing?
No! Zoom Pets, you can't do this! I created you!
Uh, about the whole Cash beggin' for his life thing
uh, that never happened, right?
Detective, your assignment was to protect Bruce Wayne.
How do you explain Krank snatching him
from right under your nose? And where is Wayne?
Do you even know?
Well, he's, uh, safely on his way home.
Actually, the detective had my back, commissioner.
Cash is as Cash does, sir.
I want your report on my desk first thing in the morning.
Hey, Wayne's a spoiled rich kid, but you, Bats, you're alright.
You need a wingman?
Hey!
That's cool. Cash prefers workin' alone.