- Commissioner, it's him. - Gordon.
'Maybe I haven't been clear, Gordon'
'so allow me to reiterate one last time.'
No payment by midnight, and I remodel Gotham City.
'I had hoped last night's demonstration'
'would show you I was serious.'
boom.
'But it seems you have chosen not to comply.'
'Fine! Destruction on a much grander scale now lies ahead.'
We need more time.
Time is not something you have anymore.
Goodnight, Gordon, and goodbye.
Crackle Hmm..
Aah!
Huh?
Ugh!
I'm not one of those Arkham loners you're used to, Batman.
'I have a vast organization to deal with you.'
smack smack.
Memo to Black Mask..
You're not the only one with an organization.
Ka-ching
vroom
ka-ching
vroom.
Black Mask's reign of terror is over.
Not with a device still out there
that could destroy half of Gotham.
Black Mask is the only one with the firing codes to activate it.
Without the firing codes, it's useless.
Still, I think we'll all sleep better once we find it.
Let's hope his laptop holds some answers.
I'll try to sweat its location out of him at my end.
And, Batman?
Good work.
You like our work on the others, commish?
Uh, yes. Every little bit helps, son.
Today's lesson, Robin, no props for bagging henchmen.
Since you took point on the Black Mask smackdown
how about Batgirl and I handle finding the doomsday device?
I've got that covered. I want you two on the police escort.
Escort? Does that involve helping Gordon
pin a corsage on Black Mask?
Until I find the device, it's important the police have you
on surveillance should Black Mask's men try something.
If it's so important, you can do escort
and we'll save the city.
Then you know how to deactivate
an electromagnetic shockwave generator?
Vroom How are we supposed to know anything
if we always get the grunt work?
Wonder what Batman will have us on next?
"I have an important mission for you two.
"The Batmobile must be washed.
Two coats of wax this time."
"And don't forget to hang
"one of those tree-shaped air fresheners.
The fate of Gotham depends on it."
East side is all clear.
West side is clear and very, very, very bored.
'Mmm!'
Suggest a 2102, procurement of snacks from police lobby.
'Roger that.'
Weird, sir. We can't ID him.
No fingerprints, no distinguishing marks
and we, um, can't get the mask off.
Yeah, but we have him, and that's what counts.
The shockwave generator is not here anymore, Batman.
But we are.
Hah!
Oh.
Hello, Batman.
I'm Number One, Black Mask's second in command.
Excellent detective work
but we are aware of your abilities.
As soon as the laptop was compromised
we relocated the device.
That just means a little more work for me
and a lot more pain for you.
You can amuse Black Mask with your threats.
He'll be here soon to deal with you personally.
Chomp chomp Eaten by a crow.
I think he fell on a spoon.
Nah. I bet he's not even missing an eye.
He just thinks eye patches are cool.
Backup has arrived, which means we can punch out.
If you don't tell us the location
of the shockwave generator
it's gonna be 30 to 40 years
'before you walk out of this building.'
But, Gordon, I plan to walk out of this building
in 30 to 40 seconds.
And how exactly are you going to..
Fizz.
Excuse me, commissioner, I have a city to destroy.
We wait for the gas to clear, then go get him?
No need. Black Mask will walk out all by himself.
Not that I'm impressed or anything
but how'd you know where to find the vent controls?
Commish's daughter. I practically grew up here.
So, think this has something to do with Black Mask?
Magic pool ball says..
"It is certain."
We can make this hard or easy
but I am walkin' out that door.
Hard!
Aah! Uh!
- Aah! - Ha ha!
Aah!
Ohh!
Something is wrong.
Too bad your plan didn't count on us.
Or the army of cops that just arrived.
Screech.
Huh?
Looks like more grunt work.
Thoughts?
What would Batman do?
'He'd use his superior crime fighting skills'
to deduce two against a whole bunch equals, uh-oh!
Wait. This building has emergency security gates.
They're meant to keep the bad guys in during a jailbreak
but I bet they'd keep the bad guys out too.
What are we waiting for?
The gates are downstairs.
'Okay, let's get ready.'
You hold them off. I'll find the gate switch.
Hey, what part of that plan is fair?
Huh!
Oh!
Where is it?
Beep beep beep.
Okay, not it.
Less deejaying and more gate closing!
Aha!
Robin!
- Aah! - Ohh!
Boom boom
swoosh
Robin! No!
Miss me?
Batgirl and Robin are causing delays.
Children. I was beginning to think we had a real problem.
Still, we should have been out of here by now.
Find a way in and find it fast.
He'll be fine. They all will, but it's going to be a long nap.
Well, I'd be snoozing too
if you didn't save me with my own re-breather.
Rookie mistake. I made my share.
I'll check for all possible entry points. You call Batman.
Don't waste your time.
By now, my men have ensured the Batman can't help anyone..
Anymore.
No answer. You think...
No. Batman's finding the shockwave generator
and we're keeping happy face away from it until he does.
The Batman was the only roadblock to my freedom.
- Yeah? What are we then? - Speed bumps.
Ask Joker and Penguin if we're just speed bumps.
Take credit for Batman's work
but that doesn't change the fact that without him
all you two are are scared, little children.
So, Robin, what do you think? The unibrow and bad perm?
Hmm... I'll go with delicate cheekbones
and a 13-year-old's moustache.
What are you talking about?
Robin, how about an all-precinct distress call
to even things up?
Click Or not.
They found a way in.
These guys are good.
Swish
swish swish.
Ooh!
Swish swish swish They just keep coming.
Not if we can plug the hole. Keep 'em busy.
Hey! Who made me the keep-'em-busy guy?
Aah!
Hah!
Rizz
zap zap zap.
Ohh!
Snap
swoosh.
- Aah! - Aah!
Crash.
Phew!
We still own this place.
Thud But how much longer?
We're almost through, Number One.
Almost isn't fast enough for Black Mask.
Thud.
A barricade? Are we making our last stand?
I don't know what else to do.
Batman would.
Screech
crash.
When my men arrive, I'm considering
having them peel you like a grape.
Says the man locked in a cage.
You still don't get it, do you?
This time Batman doesn't save the day..
Or you.
Tried to pick his nose and missed. Huh? Huh?
Do you ever get... scared?
What? You're scared?
A, no, and B, let's not redirect the question.
Do I get scared?
Yeah, sometimes, I guess.
Showtime.
Something keep you?
The device is ready, sir.
All you need to do is enter the firing code
and half of Gotham will be destroyed.
Bet you wish you had this right now, huh?
Utility belt, charge to stun.
Who's he talkin' to?
Activate.
Rizz clang.
Our chance to step up as crime fighters, and we choke.
What would Batman say if he saw us like this?
The word stop whining come to mind.
These boots aren't just made for walking.
Now, wanna save the city?
No sign of them, but their ride's still here.
Then they must have another way out.
Rooftop!
You will be able to enter the firing code
on a computer waiting in the copter.
Very good, Number One.
You're to be congratulated for getting me out.
And fired for letting children slow you down.
You, you're my new Number One.
Finish them.
Hah!
Almost missed my flight.
Ahh!
Unh!
Aah!
Let's see if this robin can fly.
Unh!
Huh!
Aah! Whoa!
Swoosh
clank.
'Enter code.'
'Firing sequence activated.'
Huh?
You're going back to Gotham PD.
Highly doubtful, since there won't be a Gotham PD
to go back to.
- Dad! - We're too late!
Huh?
Rizz rizz.
Batman. Figures.
No wonder you always take point.
You're good.
And you guys are pretty good at grunt work.
Now who wants to wash the Batmobile?
Huh?