'I think it's time for practice.'
That must mean you've finished everything on your plate, Dick.
Chomp chomp.
Okay. Okay. Let's go.
Whoo-hoo!
I'm telling you, Mary, a leash is the only answer for that boy.
Wait for us, son.
Dick, your father said to wait.
Looks like the circus is in town.
Tony Zucco. Welcome to Gotham City.
John Grayson, the circus manager.
Can I help you?
I'd like to think I'm here to help you, John.
For a small fee my brothers and I
'we'll provide your circus with protection.'
Protection?
I'm not sure I understand why
we would need your protection.
Hmm.
I come from circus folk myself
so let me put this in terms you can understand.
You don't pay us, and you'll have to
deal with the strongman..
'...a lion tamer..'
thud '...and a juggler.'
bam bam
thud.
Stop!
Dick!
You've got quite a family here, John.
My pop's always said
family is the most important thing.
'I know my brothers mean the world to me.'
I'm not sure what I'd do if something happened to them.
Beep
boom
whoosh.
- Unh! - Let me be blunt, John.
I don't think this circus
or your family can afford
not having our protection.
Funny, because I think we can.
And what makes you so sure about that, sonny?
I called the police five minutes ago.
And guess who intercepted that call.
Aah! Ooh! Uhh!
Huh?
Come on! We got to go.
Swish.
Our family has been divided.
I think we should return the favor.
Chomp chomp Okay, Dick, come on out now.
'No. I look like a loser.'
Your mother put a lot of work into the new costumes.
'Well, are you gonna just stand there?'
Ah! Uh! Aah!
Is there a reason why this costume has to be so colorful?
Because when I see you up there, Richard
'you make me think of a little robin.'
Uh! A robin, like the bird.
You know, kids my age get beat up for nicknames like that.
How about if we call you our flying squirrel? Better?
You know, dad, I'm not the only one who looks like a loser.
Loser? I'll teach you!
- Oh, John. - Ha-ha.
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls
'children of all ages'
I present to you
the fearless Flying Graysons..
'...as always, performing their daring feats'
'without the safety of a net.'
Aren't they fantastic?
Clang.
'And now the youngest member'
'of this amazing family.'
ting ting Huh?
Dick!
No!
I think the Flying Graysons
might have to change their name.
Hello, Dick. I'm Bruce Wayne.
I'm sorry about your loss.
Thanks, Mr. Wayne, for everything.
I heard you paid for all this.
So how are you holding up?
I'll be okay
at least that's what everyone's been telling me.
I miss them.
It's just not fair.
'Anyway, thanks again.'
His parents were all the family that boy had.
That's why I've decided to take him in
as a foster son, if he'll have me.
I was lucky enough to have you
to guide me through those dark days, Alfred.
'Dick deserves the same.'
Welcome home, Dick.
Dinner is served.
I think this table might be bigger
than my family's entire trailer.
Indeed. It can seat 22 and sleep half that number.
Now, be sure you finish everything on your plate.
So where's Bruce?
He's never around, is he?
Unfortunately, his work demands much of his time.
Master Dick has been asking for you.
I can't sit back and wait for the police
to link the Zuccos to the crime.
Now that the boy is part of this family
I suspect he may need a father figure
more than he needs a crime fighter.
The criminal responsible for my parents death
was never brought to justice, Alfred.
That's a burden I won't let Dick carry.
Boss Zucco and his brothers have been harassing
Gotham business owners for years.
'So far, my only lead is a toothpick I found at the circus'
'carrying traces of Zucco's DNA.'
'That would seem to confirm what you already know'
'his involvement.'
This specific brand of toothpick is carried
in only two places in Gotham, Alfred.
Garrett's Family Restaurant
and the Ice Pick Club.
Password.
Tony Zucco..
Where is he?
You got a lot of guts coming onto our turf like this.
Ugh!
'Come on! Let's get out of here. Uh!'
- Where is Zucco? - I don't know.
He's laying low, but his brothers
they're still shaking down parts of Old Gotham.
You'll find him there.
Tell Zucco I'm coming.
Tell him I'm coming for all of them.
Master Dick, could I see you? Chop, chop.
Huh?
'I thought you might want to see this.'
One day, Alfred, Zucco's gonna have to pay for what he did.
I'm gonna make sure of that.
We should prepare for dinner.
Perhaps Master Bruce will even join us this evening.
And perhaps monkeys will fly out of my butt.
Chomp chomp.
And, uh, give me one of those.
Hmm? Huh!
Crash
swish
pow
splat - Huh? - I want answers.
Where is Zucco?
No way I rat out family.
You already have.
Pow
clack
click clack.
Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow!
Batman.
Uh-oh.
You're..
'Under the circumstances'
it was only a matter of time
before you learned my secret.
Okay, let's talk about what you saw.
You're the Batman, the Dark Knight
the world's greatest detective!
That's you!
And it's in large part
why you haven't seen a lot of me lately.
I don't want your childhood to be consumed by revenge..
Like mine was.
You're going after Zucco, aren't you?
No. That's for me.
I wanna make sure he gets what's coming to him.
Maybe we should finish this in the morning.
It's late.
Late for Bruce Wayne
'early for the Batman.'
Zucco..
I know you're here.
Boom.
If I find Batman, I find Zucco.
The circus.
But I can't go dressed like this.
Mornin', sunshine.
You know, being here has really brought back memories.
Believe it or not
once upon a time my pops and I were in the circus.
We were knife throwers.
'Well, I threw the knives'
and dad hoped I wouldn't hit him.
It was quite an act, really.
Zing.
We put him on a board just like the one you're on
and I'd say, "Ladies and gentlemen
"please don't try this at home.
I'm a trained professional."
'Then my dad would say'
'"I knew we should have given you'
piano lessons instead."
Ha-ha.
Always good for a laugh.
Zing ching ching ching.
Why'd you give up such a promising career?
Well, one day, I missed.
Swish clang.
Huh?
'So Batman's got family, too.'
Cute.
Didn't you parents ever teach you any manners?
Creak.
I watched you take down my brother, Batman.
Now it's your turn to watch.
Huh?
Huh? No.
A-a-aah!
Zucco!
Huh?
Ohh!
Nice save.
But I thought you wanted Zucco to get what was coming to him.
Well, he did, didn't he?
Justice.
I've been thinking, Dick.
I'm not sure Bruce Wayne has what it takes
to raise you properly.
Yeah, I kind of noticed he's never around.
But if not Bruce Wayne, what about the Batman?
We'd have to give you a name.
How about Robin?
Like the bird?
It's a family name.