Combat log, final entry.
Should I fail, let this be a record
for those who come after me.
Two nights ago, a madman unleashed a plague on Gotham
turning the infected into what I can only describe
as zombies.
Mindless drones at his command.
I'd say it's a nightmare..
But it can't be
because I haven't slept in days.
The pieces are now in place.
I have one chance to save this city.
'No!'
Hard to believe this all started 48 hours ago.
'"I am proud to accept this award on behalf of all'
"who work to ensure that Gotham will once again stand proud
as a shining beacon to a brighter future."
- What do you think, Dick? - Sure.
You could give that speech..
Or to save time
I could fly over in the Batwing
and drop knock-out gas on the crowd.
I for one, hung on every word.
Still, I'll see to it that pillows and blankets
are available for those who may require them.
Don't worry, sir, we still have two more days
to work on the speech before Gotham honors
the good works of Bruce Wayne.
And speaking of good works
it seems the city requires some from the Batman.
'Dr. Hugo Strange is requesting to see you. He won't say why.'
'I doubt it's to thank me for the new accommodations.'
Be careful what you say in front of him, Robin.
Strange may be a madman
but he's also a brilliant psychiatrist.
If he finds an opening, he'll mess with your head.
I don't usually make house calls, doctor.
- What do you want? - Thank you for coming, Batman.
And what I want is your help
with an experiment I'm conducting.
You see, I'm going to release
a toxic agent into Gotham's air.
It's odorless, invisible, and extremely fast-acting.
It will twist the body and weaken the mind
turning those infected into monstrous living drones.
Zombies, answerable only to me.
Each victim, in turn
will become a carrier, infecting others.
Sadly, if the antidote isn't administered
within 48 hours of infection
the condition becomes irreversible.
If the toxin is being released everywhere
why won't you be affected, Strange?
I've already taken the antidote
which I'm sure could be very useful to you.
Oops.
Oh, that would mean the toxin is being dispersed
throughout Gotham as we speak.
Robin, filter on.
And now that you're safe from the toxin
perhaps we'll watch Gotham go down together.
Let the games begin.
Get them!
This isn't over, Strange.
You're right, Batman. It's just beginning.
'Collecting air sample.'
How did Strange pull it off?
With clinical precision.
- I wanna know why. - 'Sir?'
Hugo Strange has released a toxic agent
into the city's air. Stay in the cave.
The filter system should keep you safe.
And notify Barbara. We'll need back-up.
'Straight away, sir.'
'Analysis complete.'
The chemical analysis shows nothing weird.
The air is safe to breathe.
The toxin must have dispersed quickly
after doing its damage. But the drones are carriers.
Commissioner?
No!
Orders.
Arkham.
Batman.
Batgirl, I'll totally deny I said this
'but having you here doesn't completely..'
stink?
Aah!
Aa-aa-aa!
I know. We'll get them back, Dick. I promise.
'Hair?'
Whatever toxin Strange used
if it's in the victims tissues
'we can identify it from this.'
You help Alfred research.
'Alfred?'
Sick.
Rest easy, old friend.
How'd he get infected down here?
I don't know. But I intend to find out.
Combat log.
I've checked against every known
infectious agent and toxic compound.
No match. There has to be a variable we're not seeing.
No!
You, help... Stop it! Stop it!
Dick, I need you to focus.
It's not fair. We're all alone.
Alfred, Batgirl, the whole city's infected
and we don't even know why.
But there's one man who does.
Tell me, Batman, what do you see?
That you're still crazy about me, Strange.
Now, how do I save everyone?
And rob myself of the chance to peer behind the mask
at the moment of the Batman's greatest defeat?
You wanna see behind the mask?
Give me the antidote, and I'll remove it.
Of course. You first.
The truth is, you saw me spill my last sample.
Sample? Then there's more antidote.
Where is it, Strange?
It's true, I wanted a small quantity of it
stashed away for my experiments.
Sadly, last week an orderly found it.
I believe it is in police custody now.
Feel free to borrow it.
Of course, with all those zombies running round
I don't think I'd feel comfortable
going into that neighborhood alone.
- Robin. - We are finished here, Batman.
Guards, there is a bat in my belfry.
Combat log. Second night.
Robin's gone. I'm alone.
'And I have less than a day to distribute'
'Strange's antidote to the entire city.'
I'm being tracked by the Batwave transponder.
Not for long.
Priority one, Batwave override.
Power down.
Batman.
Stop you.
Poison you.
'Destroy.'
Priority one, Batwave override.
Autopilot, engage.
Argh!
Batgirl, Robin not sure you can understand me
but this will help you.
Alfred's cure will have to wait.
With Batgirl and Robin infected
returning to the mansion and the cave is too risky.
Fortunately, I have other resources.
A home away from home.
Built in case Bruce Wayne and the Batman
ever needed to go off the grid.
Only 17 hours left.
Strange's antidote is concentrated.
To get it to work over a large area
the antidote must be vaporized.
Thermo charges.
A lot of 'em, wired to pick up the Batwave signal.
Everything is ready.
"Bruce Wayne, Gotham's White Knight."
We'll see.
All that's left is to transmit the signal.
For that, I'll need to get to higher ground.
I have one chance to save this city.
No!
Clank.
Grab. Hold.
- Hurt you. - Mess ahead.
Mess ahead!
Whoosh.
Mess ahead.
Strange may be a madman
but he's also a brilliant psychiatrist.
He'll mess with your head.
Robin and I were hit with Strange's antidote.
Moments later we were attacked.
The air was safe to breathe.
The chemical analysis shows nothing weird.
There was no trace of toxin in Gordon's hair.
Strange virtually sent me to the police station
as if he wanted me to get the antidote.
But why?
What if..
What if this isn't the antidote?
What if this is the toxin?
Boom Arkham. Batman.
If this is a mistake, it's my last.
No more. Mess ahead.
- You okay? - That depends.
Were you a zombie ten seconds ago?
You were under Strange's influence
the moment he spilled that vial and infected us.
'That's why he was moved upstairs to maximum security.'
Then there were no traces of the toxin
in anything we tested.
'Because there was no toxin there.'
And when I captured Robin
doctors were able to take a sample
of the real toxin from his tissues
and quickly synthesize an antidote.
Two more seconds, and you would've delivered.
Strange's real toxin to the crowd.
For future reference, there are easier ways
to duck out of giving a speech.
I was this close to hurting all the people
I try to protect, Alfred.
What if I'm not as lucky next time?
If you'll forgive my saying so
luck had nothing to do with it.
Even under a madman's influence
and believing himself to be alone
the Batman fought his way to the truth.
That's who he is. It's who you are.
'And now Gotham's very own white knight, Mr. Bruce Wayne.