Ah, there it is.
Oh, stupid, stupid, stupid!
Hey! Stop right there!
Oh. Oh!
Ha-ha. Smooth move, Colonel Klutz.
Alarm on the cabinet, go right in the hall
door is locked. Watch the bucket.
What're you talking about?
Whoops.
Hold on a minute, cowboy.
Hey, stop right there!
Smooth move, Colonel Klutz.
Last level, come on, almost there!
I don't believe Master Dick has moved
in the five days since you gave him his Christmas gift.
I would've given him a book
but then he might've learned something.
I am learning something. How to beat this game, Babs.
Call me Babs again, and that controller's...
Does anyone have any New Year's resolutions? Master Dick?
I resolve to kick more butt.
I resolve to leave more butts unkicked.
- Gotta leave some for Robin. - Har har.
How about you, Master Bruce? Any resolutions?
Same as every year, do my part to help Gotham City.
Blast! And I resolve to finally have this old clock repaired.
I got him down to half strength!
I own you, Draketh!
- Batwave. Let's move. - Now? Hrmm.
Another robbery at the chemical lab
this time at Gotham University.
Third one this week.
- Same perp? - Mm-hmm.
And I doubt he's done. Let's split up.
We can cover more ground if we each stake out a different lab.
Report in.
Nothing. Nada. Zip.
How about you, Robin?
All clear. Ahh!
I said I wanted to kick butt, not freeze mine off.
I've spotted our man.
Bingo.
Ah, the Batman.
I knew it was a matter of time before you showed up.
Then you know what's gonna happen next.
You try to stop me, and fail.
Okay, okay, let's try this again.
I knew it was a matter of time before you showed up.
You try to stop me, and fail.
Oh, yeah, that hurts.
Whoops! Missed me.
Ugh. You're quicker than you look.
Aha.
Lights out.
Huh?
Ah, typical.
Let's try this one.
It's been a barrel of laughs, Batman.
Oh, that's terrible.
Better luck next time, Batman.
'Let's look for a match.'
I know this doesn't make sense
but the whole thing seemed... staged.
Like he knew exactly what was going to happen.
Whatever helps you sleep at night.
It's almost done, Beth.
They stole you and Matt away from me
but soon they'll pay.
It's okay, Matt. It's okay. Daddy's here.
Shh. Shhshhshh.
How are we gonna pay all these bills?
Don't worry, honey. We'll get through this.
For once, I'm gonna make things right.
Yeah, I'll take a dog with the works.
- 'Night. - Goodnight.
For once, I'm gonna make things right.
Idiot!
Ahh!
Huh? Gas leak!
Run!
Ah, I can't do anything right!
Francis Grey was paroled last month
after spending 17 years in prison.
That's a long time to be away from your family.
Apparently, they thought so, too.
His wife left him while he was in prison.
He didn't see her or Matthew again.
Trying to set the time on your VCR?
The atomic clocks in the cave and my suit
should keep perfect synchronized time
yet there's a discrepancy of several seconds between the two.
- Strange. - Uh.
I hate being late, too
but shouldn't we be more concerned
with what Francis has planned with the chemicals?
Grey has most of the base components
to make radium tricholoromethate.
I'm guessing that's not the secret ingredient
in Alfred's eggnog.
It's a deadly poison gas.
He needs one more component
and there's only one place in Gotham he can get it.
You okay, Bats?
It's nothing, it's..
Just a sudden sense of deja vu.
Deja what?
It's a French term, describing when you feel
like you've experienced a situation before.
"Robin," by the way, is French for "Duh."
Why is it deadly chemicals are always green?
Why can't they ever be pink?
You're going back to the big house.
- This time for good, Francis. - You know who I am.
Then you know that my prison sentence was totally unfair!
- You committed a crime. - I took a watch!
Everything else was an accident.
For that, they put me away for 17 years?
You make one little mistake..
And you spend the rest of your life paying for it.
- How'd you do that? - I don't know.
We've had this conversation before.
But that's impossible, isn't it?
- Unless.. - Time.
You can manipulate time.
And in such a way, you're the only one aware
you've experienced the previous moment.
It explains the atomic clock discrepancy, the deja vu.
Very good, Batman.
It's easy to become obsessed with time
when that's all you have.
It was all I could think of when I was in prison
all the time that was stolen from me.
And when it became my job to fix all the guard's clocks
I was suddenly surrounded by it.
Seconds, minutes, hours, days, weeks, months, years.
I was so obsessed with the time I was losing
I began to actually see it unravel before me.
Cuckoo, cuckoo!
I thought I was going mad.
Stop!
Huh?
I could turn back time.
I spent every day of the next 15 years working on it.
One second became five seconds. Then 10, then 20.
Whoa! Oh!
I wanted to go back 20 years
before any of this happened.
But all I got was 20 seconds.
I can't get my time back
but I can punish the city for taking it.
You know what time it is now?
Time to kick my sorry butt?
To you, this is all happening for the first time
but we've already had this fight eight..
No, nine. Nine times.
Left hook, right jab, spin kick
flying kick from Batgirl.
Left, right, right, right, left.
Right, right, left, right, left, left, right, kick!
That was fun. Thanks for playing.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I need to make sure
that Gotham rings in the new year with a bang!
I don't care if he's Father Time himself
he is not outrunning us in that.
It's his power, that's how he's outrunning us.
It's like a video game.
He can play the same level over and over again
memorizing every move until he wins.
So everything is a do-over, including our memory.
Then this could be the 10th time we've had this conversation.
Whoa. Brain hurt.
Whoo-hoo!
I'm circling back to 8th street to try and cut him off.
This'll be fun.
I got him.
Here we go.
Not good.
So, how do we stop someone who..
Knows what we're gonna do before we do.
Deja vu again?
It seems to grow stronger
each time I face off against Grey.
Get any sense of what he's gonna do next?
He said he wanted Gotham to ring in the New Year with a bang.
Tonight's New Year's Eve celebration
in Gotham Times Square.
And thousands of people to hit with his poison gas.
Gotham Square's already filled with revellers.
An evacuation would only cause panic.
We have to find the device before it goes off.
Wait. I have a special mission for you.
Gotham will only understand how precious their time is
after it's taken away.
Hello, Batman.
I suppose we've been through all this before.
If it matters, you did catch me off guard.
But that only works the first time.
The New Year's ball.
That's where you've hidden the device.
And when it reaches zero
this city pays for what they took from me.
Only one minute to midnight, Batman.
Ice try, Batman.
Oh, I did not just say that.
Wait, wait, wait. Okay, I got it.
Ice pellet? That's cold, Batman.
Okay, so I'm not so good with quips.
Your deja vu telling you how this fight ends?
Yeah. Not well.
Then let's hope batgirl gets here soon with plan B.
Time's up.
Please..
You can't stop me. It's fate.
I don't believe in fate. I believe in choice.
You and your little toys.
It's adorable, really.
He can mess with time
but he can't be in two places at once.
Hmm.
I totally saw that coming.
Don't make all these innocent people suffer.
But I was innocent, too, Batman.
Where was my justice?
You made a choice 18 years ago
and you have to live with the consequences.
Don't make another mistake.
I don't make mistakes, Batman.
Not anymore.
Let's try that again.
Left jab. Ooh! Oh!
How are you doing that?
Call it deja vu.
Batman! Had a bit of trouble tracking him down.
But..
It's not too late to make the right choice, Francis.
Dad?
What're you doing?
Matt?
- Get out of here! - Four, three, two, one..
Dad..
My son! No!
Oh..
Nooo!
It's not too late to make the right choice, Francis.
How about you, Master Bruce? Any resolutions?
Same as every year, do my part to help Gotham City.
All set, Mr. Pennyworth.
You're a miracle worker, Mr. Grey.
Sure you won't join us for some eggnog?
No, thanks, Mr. Wayne.
I have my own family to get home to.
All done here, son. Let's get going.
Aw, dad!