We're through. We found it.
We found a cave, Moira, not necessarily the cave.
This is it. You know it is.
Beep.
We found the Batcave.
Archeological log, Gray reporting.
We seem to have found definitive proof
that ancient Gotham's legendary Batman
long thought to be a myth, actually existed.
The time is exactly 1900 hours.
The date is August 8th, 3027.
Vroom
ka-ching
vroom.
Remember, don't disturb any artifacts
until your recorder's taken a complete 3-D scan.
'Gray, over here!'
We think this was some kind of primitive computer, but...
This was just the user interface, Moira.
The memory anagrams may still be preserved.
Rizz rizz.
If the data we need is lost
all of New Gotham will be destroyed.
You need to get this machine on line.
Do you know how old this tech is?
What you're asking is impossible!
Find a way.
And remember, time is not a luxury we have.
Whoosh
I still can't believe we found the place.
You know, when I was a kid
my father read "Tales Of The Bat" to me
every night before bed.
He always said the stories were true.
Smart man, your father.
Beep.
Full scan complete?
It's the Batmobile, isn't it?
Let's find out.
It's exactly how I imagined it.
'Batman, confirm sighting.'
'He's at Gotham Airport.'
'Batman?'
'Batman, do you read?'
'What do you read, anyway?'
'After all these years, I never thought to ask.'
'Mystery stories, romance novels?'
' "The Sunday Comics?"'
I read, Oracle, loud and clear.
I'm heading to the airport.
It's the headaches again, isn't it?
Ever think that's Mother Nature's way of telling you
that you should be playing Bingo right now?
I'm fine. Today it ends.
This dance can't go on forever.
Swoosh.
'Are you sure this homemade anti-Freeze is gonna work?'
I've spent years studying Freeze's cryogenic biology
and how to neutralize it. It'll work.
'It better, because you know I am not a fan of plan B.'
bang.
Try again, Batman.
We didn't pierce the exosuit.
Guess it's time for plan B.
Great.
Swoosh
clang.
The Dark Knight returns.
'Batman, I've tapped into Air Traffic Control.'
'Gotham Tower has rerouted all flights.'
Good. Hm..
You'd think so
but a cargo plane from Africa
was already on final approach.
'It's out of fuel and its wings are icing over.'
'The pilot's issued a Mayday. He has to land now.'
Oracle, the Batmobile.
Swish swish swish.
When did this get so hard?
Thump crash.
Time, Batman, has made you weak
slow, irrelevant.
Facts you refuse to accept.
'Pathetic.'
Freeze, a man's life is at stake.
'That plane needs to land.'
And land it will crash-land.
Do it.
Beep.
That's more like it.
No wonder this place is still standing.
It's been secured with titanium reinforcements.
This much titanium in the 21st century?
It must have cost a fortune!
Who was this Batman?
We'll probably never know.
The details have been lost to time.
'Maybe not.'
According to records we found
the estate that was once above this cave
was owned by a Dr. Thomas Wayne.
We can't be certain
but I bet he was The Batman
which means his wife, Martha, may have been the Batwoman
and their young son, Bruce, the Red Robin.
- The Red what? - I'll show you.
The Batsuit.
Vacuum sealed.
Perfectly preserved.
'Look how small the Red Robin's uniform is.'
'I never realized Batman's partner was so young.'
The upgraded Freeze 2.0
comes complete with flame-proof cybernetics
and a shatter-proof, internal liquid nitrogen supply.
It's why your cold medicine didn't work.
'Oracle, the plane!'
Chill, Batman. I sent up a flare.
'Robin's on his way.'
Maybe you didn't get the memo, Oracle
but I've been going by Nightwing
for, oh, about a decade or so.
Oh, yeah! I don't know why I can't remember that.
'Maybe I should try saying it ten times in a row.'
'Nightwing, Nightwing, Nightwing.'
'Wing de-icers are at maximum capacity'
and still losing ground. Oracle, take control.
'Why? You got something better to do?'
Kinda. Yeah.
Mayday! Mayday!
Please stow all tray tables and unfasten your seat belt.
What are you doing? Whoa!
Boom.
Whoa!
Get out of here!
Whoa.
- Oracle. - 'Way ahead of you, wing gnat.'
'I've alerted Commissioner Yin and Chief Bennett'
'that the pilot's headed their way.'
'They've evacuated the airport'
'and their men have the place surrounded.'
Which means they're still waiting for us
to do the heavy lifting, right, Batman? Batman?
Sit this one out. I can handle Freeze.
Maybe it's time to pass the torch.
I'll pass the torch when the mission's over.
We both know the mission will never be over.
Where is it? Ugh!
Ah, the African Star.
A diamond, Freeze?
You brought that plane down for a diamond?
Diamonds are the hardest substance in the world, Batman.
I knew it was the only thing
that could survive the crash.
After all these years you're still nothing but a cheap crook.
As I've been trying to tell Batman
things change.
You see, Batman
the African Star is no ordinary diamond.
Its uniquely perfect structure
will allow it to act as an energy amplifier
for my cryo-cabin a machine with the power
to alter this city's weather forever!
Beep.
You think you got one more in you, old man?
I'm just hoping you can keep up, Robin.
It's almost poetic, don't you think
that that which is most precious to me, diamonds
'will allow me to achieve my ultimate dream'
turning Gotham into a frozen kingdom
over which I will rule.
'It's over, Batman.'
You've given this city all you have to give.
Now, it's time to sleep.
So what was it that finally defeated The Bat?
That's something probably lost to history.
I'd like to think, old age.
- 'Gray, progress report.' - Uh, yes, commissioner.
We've made a number of important historical discoveries.
Forget history. Have you found what we need today?
No, sir, nothing yet
nothing that will solve our problem.
'Gray, it's not a problem, it's a crisis.'
Find something and find it fast
before New Gotham enters another ice age.
- Somehow, this Dr. Frost... - Mr. Frost...
- Freeze. - Whatever!
Somehow, this 1000-year-old monster is destroying our city
and we can't seem to stop him!
Everyone is depending on you and your team, Gray!
What's the status of that computer?
We found data storage.
Huh.
If the code's recoverable
we'll have it online in a matter of minutes.
An antique wheelchair.
The Waynes employed an Alfred Pennyworth
for decades who would've been quite old near the end.
This must have belonged to him.
Batman, come in. Come in, Nightwing.
There's still no answer, Alfred. Radio must be down.
He's always seemed to think he wasn't doing his job
unless he worried me half to death.
I'm certain he's fine, Oracle.
Lopez Hair Removal, this is Jose.
It's dad, Barbara, just wanted to check in on you
you know, with everything that's going on.
'There's nothing for you to worry about.'
'And I am kind of busy right now.'
Well, if you weren't so mysterious
about that job of yours maybe I wouldn't
have to worry about you so much.
You never stood a chance against me, Batman.
Sorry, dad. I gotta go. Love you. See you tomorrow.
'Okay. Goodnight, Barbara. Love you, too.'
Batman's remotely ordered the Batwing
to fire on his position.
I can't override it.
Fire on himself? Oh, dear.
Senility has finally set in.
Huh?
Boom boom boom.
- Huh? - Ah..
Thanks for the ice pack, Freeze.
All you did was numb the pain.
Diamonds cut even the hardest glass.
How's that for poetic justice?
No.
Oh, no!
Not bad, old man. No sign of Freeze.
Which means the mission isn't over.
The cryo-chamber.
Cold enough to put me on ice..
Until someone wakes me up
and puts me back together in a future
without The Batman.
Still can't believe some fool woke Frost up
and put him back together.
It's not all bad.
Freeze's revival forced us to look for Batman
and we found him.
We didn't find Batman
we found artifacts, lots of pretty things
but unless we recover that data
nothing of substance.
It's no use.
This machine just wasn't built
to hold code for a 1000 years!
The memory anagrams are hopelessly degraded.
Unacceptable! Get us access.
It can't be done, I'm sorry!
Gray, your hand.
It's nothing. It's just a scratch.
A scratch with a pattern.
The titanium!
- Gray, what are you... - Binary code.
The titanium's covered with binary code.
'Batman knew they couldn't survive'
'on his primitive computer'
'so he found another way!'
Have we scanned it all?
Can you translate it?
Yes. Yes!
Here we go.
Welcome. If you're viewing this message
I can only assume one thing
the mission isn't over.
'State the nature of the emergency.'
Dr. Frost.
- Mr. Freeze. - Mr. Freeze.
Beautiful.
I love the future
especially since it's 100% Bat-free.
'If you believe that, Freeze'
'the cold must be numbing your brain.'
What?
No, it's not possible.
There's nowhere you can run!
But I waited a 1000 years.
You can't still be here!
And yet I am here
and always will be here to stop you, Freeze
always.
No!
It can't be!
'Freeze.'
No-o-o!
Mission accomplished. We did it, Gray.
But not without The Batman.
Even a 1000 years
into the future, he refused
to leave Gotham unprotected.
Time changes nearly everything
but the mission and the legend
of The Batman lives on.