Hello?
Stop. Don't move.
They can see us.
What is this?
I don't know.
- Where are we? - Where do you think?
Hello?
Oh, my God!
It's all right, okay? It's all right.
-You're okay. -Help! Help!
- Just calm down. - John.
-You're fine. -Where are you?
Oh, shit.
Is she dead?
I think so.
Jesus Christ. What was that?
I don't know.
What was that?
Shit.
What the fuck?
- Everyone freeze! - Oh, my God.
They can see if we move.
Stand still and we'll be fine.
Don't lift your feet off the ground.
Don't touch anyone.
-What's that noise? -Shh.
Oh, my God.
-Where's that coming from? -Quiet!
Okay, now...
- Calm down. Calm down. - It's no use.
-Susan. -Bruce?
Everybody calm down.
You need to calm down, guys.
Everybody calm the fuck down!
Just... just think, breathe.
What the hell is going on?
No. No.
Here we go.
Everybody shut up for one second!
Does anybody know what the hell's going on?
- They're killing us. - No, it's not them.
Are you guys seeing this?
The lights on the floor. You see it move?
-I don't see anything. -Over there.
- What are you talking about? - Look at your hands.
When you move 'em, it changes the floor.
Oh, shit, yeah.
I only see one.
Yeah, I only see mine.
I think you can only see your own.
What did they do to us?
- I think they messed with our hands. - -What does that mean?
- It's us. - Us?
- What do you mean? - We're choosing who dies.
- Fuck! - What happened?
- Somebody did it. - -Nobody fucking do anything.
Well, it's not working, you see?
- We have to try something. - Nobody do it!
Okay.
- Goddamn it. - What the hell?
What is wrong with you people?
All of us, we're gonna die. All of us, we're gonna die.
We're all fucked.
Oh, my God.
This is unbelievable.
- It's a vote. - What?
We're voting. Look, they're killing whoever gets the most votes.
How do you know that?
Because... Because the chimes go off when you close your hands,
and that's when you choose.
- We should try not doing it again. - -Forget it.
- Someone's gonna screw it up. - Wait.
What if we... What if we vote for her again?
- Yeah, let's try that, okay? - Guys, that's not...
- No, it's not gonna work. - -We have to try something.
Yeah, everybody, let's vote for the dead woman again.
-Really? -Are you serious?
Come on. Come on.
-You guys picked the wrong person. -No, we didn't.
- Guys, it just doesn't work. - -But why him?
Maybe he got the second most votes.
Or the most so far?
-We have to try something. -No, it's not gonna work, guys, okay?
There's nothing we can do. We're all screwed.
-Let's try not voting again. -Please.
- It's not gonna work. - We need to try.
Okay, nobody vote. Let's wait it out.
How do we know that won't kill us all?
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four, three...
Is it over?
-Oh, my God! -Okay, nobody move.
Just, everybody, let's ride this out.
If we don't choose, it chooses on its own.
Somebody needs to do something. This is not working, obviously.
-What you said, that didn't make sense. -Everybody quiet!
Now, there's no reason
for us all to just keep killing each other off like this.
Well, what the hell else are we gonna do, my man?
We don't have a choice.
What I mean is we can choose to go about this in a certain way.
Look, so there's about a minute or two between each round.
-That's not a lot of time. -Yeah, no shit.
Maybe if we spend less time worrying about who's gonna die next
and more time trying to figure this thing out,
we'll get somewhere and be able to stop this.
What do you suggest?
Okay, I've been looking round the circle
and I see... five or six people in their 70s and 80s.
If this a vote, I say they go first. That'll buy us some time.
- Wait a second. - No, no. Hell, no, man.
Are you serious?
Look, the way I see it, they'd be the next people to die in real life, right?
-What's the difference? -He's right. Old people first.
That's... That's fair.
-How is that fair? -They'd be the next to die anyway.
Yeah, of natural causes, not of us killing them.
-What's the difference? -This is crazy.
-We have no choice. -That's fucked up, kid.
It's a fucked-up situation, but we have to do something.
Which one first?
We'll start with him, go clockwise after that.
One, two, three...
No, wait a minute.
...four, five, six.
That should buy us ten minutes.
No. No, no. There has to be another way.
You have a better idea?
Anyone?
I'm sorry. It's the only way.
But I have just as much of a right to live as any of you.
You've lived your life, old man.
Please.
Please!
Okay. I know that was hard.
But you all did the right thing.
We're gonna have to make some difficult decisions.
Just shut up, all right? We get it.
You wanted to buy some time and we did that. Let's not waste it.
Let's figure out what the hell this is. Any ideas?
Come on. Somebody?
-What about him? -Who, me?
Yeah. I mean, you ought to know something about this.
-I don't know anything. -Bullshit.
-Yeah, yeah, you guys had to know. -Know about what?
What about a fucking alien invasion? I don't know.
-What? -Look, I know just as much as you do.
- Bullshit, man. - I swear, I don't know anything.
Does anybody remember anything else?
I was in Glendale.
Yeah, I do.
We were stuck in traffic on the freeway.
- Me too. - So was I.
Right.
We were trying to get out of the city, but it was a total log jam,
so we got out of the car and started running.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Everybody was running.
Yeah, and then... and then everything went dark.
That's what I remember.
- So what happened? - I was pulled up.
- Into the ship? - I... I don't know.
-Tractor beam. -Fuck.
So are we in the ship now?
Do you think there are other people doing this?
Other circles?
They wouldn't go through all this for 50 of us.
Why would they do this?
I don't know. But the next time that I could see, I was in a small room
and everything was red, like... like a dark room,
and there were a ton of bodies piled up on one another.
I... I assumed that they were dead,
but, I don't know, they might have just been unconscious.
Everybody but me and one other guy.
- An alien? - No. No, no, no. He was a human.
-Who? One of us? -I don't know. I don't see him in here.
Everything else is kind of a blur.
I just remember waking up right here and there was some kind of gas.
I... I think that we were all drugged.
Does anybody else remember anything?
Come on, anybody.
Yeah, yeah, I do.
-You? -Yeah.
I remember the red room.
And I saw him.
And I saw them.
Well, what did they look like?
Well, they were, er, big and black.
Dark green, maybe.
And... and... and wet.
And they spoke too. It sounded almost like Chinese.
- Chinese? - Yeah, Chinese.
Or Japanese maybe.
- Chinese aliens? - Bullshit.
He's lying.
Yeah, he's next in line. He's just trying to buy some time.
No, I swear. Tell them. Tell them you saw me.
-You see? He's full of shit. -I swear, I'm telling the truth.
Just give me some time to think.
It's a trick. Don't believe him.
It's coming back to me. It's coming back.
Numbers. I remember numbers.
And there was something else that they...
-Now, where were we? -Wait. Who's next in line?
Her. With the hat.
-Who, me? -Yeah.
-How old are you? -52.
-That's not old. -Old enough.
Hey, we said 70 or 80, not 50.
What's the difference?
-That's a big difference. -Come on, lady, you're not 52.
-How old are you? -Don't lie.
-I'm 52. -Bullshit.
Yeah. Why is your hair so white?
Chemotherapy. I had cancer.
Aren't you supposed to be bald, then?
-What kind of cancer? -Breast cancer.
-So you're dying, then? -No. It's in remission.
I'm better now.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I beat it.
-It could come back, though. -What the fuck is wrong with you?
I'm just saying, she's more likely to die than the rest of us.
-That's not true. -What are you, a doctor, lady?
Actually, yes, I am, asshole.
Look, cancer or not, she's over 50. She's gonna have to go eventually.
What?
-We never agreed to that. -Yeah, no way, man.
Are we gonna start killing off people over 40 next?
I'm 43. You wanna kill me next, asshole?
-Hey, you got a problem? -Yeah, I got a problem.
I think maybe anyone over the age
of maybe, I don't know, 35 might have a problem.
What do you guys think?
Look, hey, now, just hold on a second.
Let's...
I'm just trying to help.
Fuck you.
Listen, we can't be afraid to talk to each other in here.
It's the only way we're gonna figure out how to stop this.
Oh, man, we're not gonna stop this. We're just fucked.
- We don't know that. - Exactly. We don't know anything yet.
If they wanted to kill us, they would have done that already, but they didn't.
So let's use this time and try and figure out why.
Okay. What do we do?
Maybe we should figure out why they chose us.
- Chose us? - Yeah.
Why they picked us to be in here.
It was a giant space vacuum. I don't think we were hand-picked.
No, he's right. This is... This is just random.
We don't know that. Maybe it wasn't random.
Maybe they chose us for a reason.
There's probably a zillion people doing the same thing we're doing right now.
Okay, but it's just us in here, right?
I think we need to know more about each other.
Maybe if we do...
this will all make sense.
It's worth a shot. Anybody wanna start?
Yeah. I'll go first. Hi. I'm Beth.
Erm... I live in Woodland Hills, California,
but originally I'm from Richmond, Virginia, born and raised.
I've worked in human resources for the past 11 years.
I just kind of fell into it.
I actually went to college to be an English major.
University of Virginia. Go, Wahoos.
I'm 36, single, no kids,
but I do have two nephews from my sister Noreen.
She's actually my twin sister. What else?
Oh, I have a dog. Her name is Clootie and she's a terrier mix.
And I have two cats, JJ and Ricky.
Oh, my God.
I think that's about it. Is there anything else I should say?
No, that's great. Great job. Who wants to go next?
Fuck!
-At least she didn't have kids. -Yeah, yeah.
-That's what I was thinking. -Me too.
So what? That doesn't matter.
She was still a human being just like any of you.
- What was her name? - Beth.
Maybe we shouldn't say our names.
Why not?
How does it help?
What's the point in talking at all, then?
No, no names, he's right.
We don't need to make this harder than it already is.
Yeah, yeah. I mean, if it's anonymous, it's...
What? Easier to kill everyone?
That's not what I was gonna say.
-I'll say it, then. -It doesn't matter.
Names aren't necessary.
Someone else should speak. How about you?
-Me? -Yeah, you're next in line.
Well, fuck that, man. I ain't saying shit.
You seen what happened to her and she didn't say nothing wrong.
Well, someone should speak.
Okay, I will. I'll try to keep this short.
- My name's Craig... - Hey, no names.
Right. I'm sorry.
Anyway, the reason I'm saying anything
is because my wife is standing next to me.
I thought that would be important. That can't just be a coincidence, right?
Is anyone else related? Anybody?
- Know each other? - Yes.
I know her. Susan.
How?
-We're, er... co-workers. -Neighbors.
Never mind. It's not important.
Affair. Got it.
Anyway, I just wanted to ask everyone respectfully,
please don't vote for my wife.
You can vote for me, but please just spare my wife.
No.
No, everyone will take that into consideration.
Okay, thanks.
Er... Okay. You go next.
Come on, go. Hey, you speak English?
Oh, well, he's gone.
It's okay. I speak Spanish.
We don't need a fucking translator.
Yeah, I'm sorry, but he's right, it's a waste of time.
No, it's not.
- What's he saying? -See? It's already wasting time.
No, it's not. We're all human beings.
Yeah, we all count the same in here.
We shouldn't kill someone else
over someone who can't even contribute to the conversation.
He's right. That's not fair.
I mean, I'll bet he's not even here legally.
Oh, my God.
What, now you need a green card to be fucking abducted?
You know what I'm saying. I mean, he shouldn't even be here.
What does that matter?
Ask him if he was in the country legally.
Ask him.
Ah, see?
- Come on. It doesn't matter. -Sure it does.
This guy was probably hanging out in front of The Home Depot
with 20 other illegal aliens.
Whatever.
While we were running away from the ships,
he was running towards 'em going, "Trabajo! Trabajo!"
Asshole, these guys work their asses off for barely minimum wage.
Taking American people's jobs.
Here we go, huh?
What, you don't think I work hard?
Yeah, I'm sure your corner office is a real drag.
Hey. Hey.
- Who, me? - Yeah, don't I know you?
- Huh! I wonder why. - No, seriously.
He asked if we knew anyone in here. I know him.
I don't know you, man.
You're a mechanic in North Hollywood.
Raul. Raul Jimenez. I remember you.
-What'd he do? -I didn't do shit. He's lying, man.
He beat the shit out of his girlfriend.
Really bad. At least I think it was his girlfriend.
-Hopefully not any more. -Come on, man. Serious?
Are you sure it was him?
Yeah. I remember him 'cause of that tattoo under his right eye.
That teardrop. See it?
- Fuck you, man. - What's it for?
It's for my cousin. He got shot. By a pig like you.
Yeah, and it's my fault you guys are criminals.
- He was 16. - One less criminal on the street.
Fuck you, man.
-Is it true or not? -About his cousin? I don't know.
- No, about him. - Yeah, it's true. Tell them.
Tell them how you beat the shit out of her.
And it wasn't the first time and it won't be the last time, either.
Tell 'em!
Okay, maybe we shouldn't stereotype in here.
Bitch got what she deserved, man.
There he is, see? These assholes. Man, these assholes never learn.
She shouldn't have fucked around on me, man.
Like that makes it okay to beat the shit out of her.
Oh, yeah? What are you gonna do, man?
You gonna shoot me, huh, pig?
I don't think I need to.
Recognize anyone else?
- No, I don't think so. - -Yeah, anybody else?
Unpaid parking tickets?
-What if that's important? -Huh?
Like... maybe we're supposed to figure out who's good and who's bad.
World doesn't work that way, sweetheart.
That's right. Too much gray area.
But maybe that's what they want us to do.
Kill off certain people.
And like, oh, my God, who's gonna decide? You?
No, not me. All of us, as a group.
Kind of what we're doing already.
Kind of not stopping this whole thing at all.
We don't know that. It might.
There has to be a reason behind all of this, right?
Oh, my God, sweetheart.
Not every shitty thing that happens in this world
has to have a reason behind it.
Maybe they just wanna fucking watch us kill each other.
Well, we should at least consider it.
Consider what?
What she means is... who deserves to live?
Okay. Based on what?
Based on everything.
Morals, values, what you have or haven't done in life.
I think we need to put it all out there.
We got plenty of time standing around debating everybody's character.
Well, we're here to do something.
It's to die.
Hey, hey, I got an idea.
How about we... How about we kill all the black people next, yeah?
What are you talking about?
Don't play the race card, man. This is all just fucking chance.
Yeah? Right. That's why most of us are dead, right?
It's every man for himself in here.
Yeah, you need to shut up with this racism stuff, okay?
-Nobody gives a shit around here. -I give a shit around here.
Look, I'm just saying, I'm not fucking next, all right?
Y'all done reached your minority quota.
That's fair.
This guy. Man, you see anything fair going on in here?
This is the exact fucking opposite of fair!
Okay. We'll see.
Don't look at me, man. You started this shit.
Come on, man. You know I'm right, bro.
Think about it.
They'll kill each and every one of us off until there's none of us left.
Come on, man. Plenty of white people are dead too.
Come on, man. There's plenty more still alive too.
What exactly are you trying to do with this? Make yourself a target?
Because that's exactly what you're doing.
Yeah, real smart.
You don't see me counting Asians.
-Well, maybe you should try. -Don't fall for this racism bullshit.
He's just trying to save his own ass.
You damn right, you uptight asshole. So what?
So, what, you feel like you deserve a free pass because you're fucking black?
Nobody cares.
Exactly. Nobody gives a shit.
-I ain't talking to your stupid ass. -I'm trying to help you, bro!
You shut the fuck up talking to me, man.
It's not gonna fucking help you in here.
Right, 'cause it usually helps me out there, right?
Here we go. Let's all feel bad for the black guy.
'Cause he had to struggle so much more than we did.
All right, just drop it.
Like you people don't get enough help.
- What the fuck you just say? - -You guys are all the same.
You run around, you just want people to hand you things
like you fucking earned it.
That's what's wrong with this country now.
Socialist bullshit.
What? You want some reparations too?
I mean, Jesus Christ, give me a fucking break around here!
I think we need to keep our personal prejudices out of this.
- It's not helping the situation. - -They don't matter any more.
No, no, hell, no, they absolutely matter, to me.
I'm not gonna die so some racist can live.
Everything, every single thing needs to be out there on the table.
Yeah, so if we could have all the racists step forward, that'd be great.
Look, whatever your race, ethnicity, nationality, it's not important.
What's important is that collectively we figure out how to stop this.
-We're on the same team here. -Are we, though?
- We all wanna live, don't we? - Yeah.
So let's work together. We can't keep turning against each other.
- Yeah, that's what they want us to do. - -I think she's right.
That's what this about. They want us to play their little game.
- Maybe they're watching us right now. - -Studying us.
- Let's not give them what they want. - -Exactly.
Any ideas?
What happens if we force a tie?
- We tried that. - -We tried not voting at all.
There'd be more time between rounds.
Okay, everybody vote for yourself.
How do we do that?
Well, you can't vote for yourself. It doesn't let us.
All right, then everybody vote for the person to your right, then.
- The living person. - -Don't vote for empty spaces.
If we do it right, we should all get exactly one vote.
Okay.
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four,
three, two, one...
-No! -Oh, fuck!
-Damn it! -It didn't work.
-What happened? -We screwed up.
Let's try it again.
It won't work. They thought of everything!
Did you vote for the person to your right or your left?
I did right, this way.
Well, somebody messed it up.
Somebody just made a mistake.
Okay, look, we have to try this again.
All right. Very carefully this time.
Everybody vote for the arrow that points to the person on your right.
Got it?
Sweetie, you see that arrow?
This arrow. You're gonna... You're gonna pick that arrow, okay?
You're okay. No, we're all gonna be okay, I promise. Okay?
Come on!
It's a tie. Everyone vote again!
What the fuck just happened?
- They tied. - How?
We all got the same number of votes, right?
No, we didn't.
How do you know?
'Cause I voted for him.
-What are you... -Why would you do that?
Because he voted for the pregnant girl. I saw him.
If I didn't vote for him, she'd be dead.
- You sure? - Yes.
Why would he do that?
Look, we all know that we can't vote for ourselves, right?
Well, what do you think happens
when we get down to the last person left?
One of us gets to live.
It's a game. It's process of elimination.
The last man standing gets to walk out of here alive.
Or woman.
Why would they do that?
I don't know.
But between the kid and the pregnant girl, I'm sure that guy figured
it's most likely gonna come down to one of them in the end.
If we get rid of them, we'll all have a better chance.
You know what? If he's right. If one of us do get to walk out of here,
it should be one of them.
-Why's that? -'Cause it's common sense.
People, come on. Things are different in here.
Women and children first? I'm sorry, but that shit doesn't matter any more.
Look at the pregnant woman. She counts as two people.
One of them's gonna die eventually, so...
Which one?
It's okay. It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
No! No!
-No! -Come on, come on, come on.
-Don't do anything. -They'll both die.
We have to know what happens.
What is wrong with you people?
She's just a kid. Why would you go after her?
Well, one of 'em has to die. We need to decide.
No, we don't.
We should just leave 'em out of this for as long as possible.
-Let's just forget about it. -No, we can't do that, not any more.
- Why not? - It's too dangerous for them.
-They've been exposed. -Come on.
No one is going to vote for them again, right?
She's never heard of birth control, so she gets to live?
We need to come to a majority decision before each elimination
otherwise they are constantly gonna be in jeopardy.
He's right. We need to protect them now.
We don't even know what kind of a kid she is.
I mean, what if she's a miserable brat?
-She's like ten. -Hey, kid. You get good grades?
-Uh-huh. -Yeah. Straight As?
Oh, my God, she got a B. Let's kill her.
Look, at least one of them is gonna have to die.
So we should decide now.
Just kill 'em both. Just fucking kill 'em...
What about volunteers?
- What? - Volunteers?
Are you nuts?
I don't know. Maybe someone wants to step forward.
I'll do it.
- Why? - Now, wait a minute.
He doesn't have to tell you or anybody else why.
He's volunteered. That's enough.
I wanna know why.
Lady, it's none of your business.
Hey, let him answer.
Why?
I guess I just don't wanna kill anyone.
-How old are you? -16.
-No. Someone else. -What do you mean, someone else?
-He's a fucking kid, man. -He's 16. That's old enough.
-Old enough to what, to die? -To make your own decisions.
He's a stupid kid. He doesn't know any better.
I don't care. If you volunteer, you volunteer.
-It's his choice if he wants to die. -Yeah, yeah, that's right.
If someone wants to volunteer, we should respect that, no matter who it is.
Son, what's your name?
-I'm Shaun. -Shaun.
Are you sure that you wanna volunteer?
No.
I'll do it.
It's fine.
Well, this is gonna be a whole lot easier if we can get a few volunteers.
Easier for who? You?
Look, we gotta take control of the... the situation, and this is the best way.
I mean, hey, if we're all gonna die, it might as well be on our own terms.
Yeah, yeah, that'll teach those fucking aliens.
Hey, we're doing what we can, man.
Yeah, it's the best idea we got.
-Then you volunteer. -I don't see you stepping forward.
We should all step forward. I mean, everybody but her.
So mass suicide, then? That's great. Let's do that.
Hey, kid, you still wanna volunteer?
No.
Yes.
You're a fucking hero, kid, you know that?
- Yeah, right. - No, I'm serious.
Look, if I make it out of here, I'm naming my next kid after you.
-Thanks, Scott. -Thank you, Scott.
Fucking assholes. You knew his name was Shaun.
- Whatever. The kid's a hero. - He bought us two minutes.
-Somebody toss him a Purple Heart. -All right, enough.
What? What are you looking at me for?
You think it should be me?
I was in Afghanistan for the past two years
risking my life to keep the rest of you safe.
I just got back two days ago.
I was on my way to see my family.
I got a seven-month-old...
who doesn't even know who I am.
My wife...
I haven't seen my wife in...
I'm not fucking dying in here. I'm not.
I'm going home to them.
Don't worry. I'm not voting for you.
Me neither.
Yeah, we're gonna get out of here, man.
- Yeah, sure we are. - Come on, man.
No, you come on, man. He knows the truth.
-We all do. Let's just accept it. -Just stop.
You're gonna die, dude. We all are.
- Time is running out. -Yeah. We still need a volunteer.
Anybody.
I volunteer.
My son, Oscar,
he passed away last year.
He was riding his motorcycle.
It's okay.
I forgive her.
-You'll see him again. -You think?
Absolutely.
Okay.
I go in peace.
Bye, everybody.
-Goodbye. -Goodbye.
Goodbye.
"You'll seem him again. Absolutely."
- Bullshit. - Yeah, seriously.
He was just trying to give her some peace in her last moments of life.
There's nothing wrong with that.
She sacrificed herself so that others could live. That doesn't go unnoticed.
-Says who? -Says God.
-How do you know? -I'm a minister.
God is watching over all of us.
He has a plan. We just have to have faith.
- Amen. - Enough, man.
I'm sorry?
With all due respect... that's just bullshit.
Standing around there talking about faith
when people are being blasted to shit left and right.
- That's fucking ridiculous. - Hey, man...
If there is a God, he doesn't give a shit about any of us!
-That's not true. -Oh, my God, we're all dying in here.
This shit's not gonna end until this motherfucker gets all of us, okay?
So you wanna have faith in something? Have faith in this!
Okay? Because that's God in here now, right?
That's God, right now, in here.
So pray to him or ask him, even better.
I mean, what does thou sayeth, God?
Who among us will get to go to your divine kingdom?
- Hey, take it easy. - Or what?
You gonna fucking kill me 'cause I have an opinion?
Just as valid as yours, man.
Looking around this room, actually, I think I might have some friends.
I think people agree with me.
95 percent of people believe in God. You're in the minority.
Yeah, well, 95 percent of people are idiots.
Are you calling us idiots?
I'm not calling anybody idiots, all right? All I'm saying is this.
If there is a God, is this something... Does this seem like he would allow this?
Is this something he would do?
You fuckers are gonna kill me because you're afraid I'm right?
What are you doing? You're fucking cowards, huh?
Wait, please. I didn't even say anything wrong.
-He did. -Who the fuck is this?
Looks like God just cut you a break.
Yeah, for another two fucking minutes.
Guys, I know this girl. Don't I know you?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I know you from somewhere.
-Me? -Yeah. Are you an actress?
You're so familiar.
No, I'm not an actress.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Stacy something.
-No, Christina. -Christina...
-Christina? -Yeah.
Wait a minute. Is Stacy your stage name, then?
No, I told you, I'm not an actress.
That's what it is, right.
Guys, actress, porn star. I get it now.
It's a huge difference.
What? I'm not a porn star.
Hey, I don't think anybody cares around... around here, you know?
I mean, I just couldn't figure it out before. Now I know.
- What? - I'm a huge fan.
What the fuck are you doing? I don't do porn.
I don't think it's a problem. Everybody's gotta make a living.
-I don't have a problem with it. -I don't do porn.
All right, whatever. I'm just trying to pay her a compliment.
He's lying.
I gotta be honest with you, you know, I mean,
I did like you better, though, before your enhancements,
because now it's just like, "Wha-bam! Look at these bad boys."
- He's lying. - Are they real?
-That is none of your fucking business. -Are you saying they're real?
So what? Half the girls in LA have big boobs.
Yeah, and I'm sure it's great for business.
-I don't do porn! -Who paid for them?
Tell them, go ahead.
It's okay, sweetheart. Who paid for them? Was it your employer?
-No. -No?
-I mean, he did. -He did?
But it's not like that.
Now it's getting really difficult to decide.
No, David is my boss, but we're also...
-I am not... -Uh-huh.
You see, Stacy over here thought if she gets those double Ds,
David's gonna love her.
I mean, he's gonna love her way more than his own wife and kids.
I mean, who cares if they're already a family?
It's never stopped you before, has it?
What, are you gonna run off with him?
Gonna have a bunch of kids on your own?
Settle down by the beach?
Is that what you're gonna do, Stacy?
I think we should take into account if people have families.
Children.
Why? How many kids do you have?
I have seven.
-Of course you do. -Yeah, I got 12.
-Yeah, I got 27. -Now, now, come on, seriously.
Shouldn't that be taken into consideration?
-Yeah. Yeah, we have a daughter. -Yeah. Emily.
-She's three. -We all got families.
Your kids ain't gonna save you in here.
Hey, and I'm not asking to be saved. I... I'm just saying...
if you don't have children,
maybe you should volunteer. I think that's reasonable.
Yeah, well, maybe some of us wanna have kids someday.
Yeah, well, I still am a kid.
Yeah, me too.
And I think that if you don't have children,
you should do the right thing and step forward.
How old are you?
What, me? 35. But I have a kid.
-Just one child? -Yeah, a daughter.
-You married? -Yes.
-What does your husband do? -I don't...
You don't what?
Why the sudden interest in me?
We're all just being honest. I just thought I'd ask you a question.
Well, I'm not on trial, so how about you tell us about your life?
Easy. 41.
I've got two boys, an 18-month-old baby daughter.
Been married to the same amazing woman for 12 years. Erm...
That's it. Your turn.
Shit.
Still waiting.
I raised my four younger siblings
during my father's heroin addiction and mother's clinical depression,
then attended Vassar under a work/study scholarship
before serving in the Peace Corps for three years in Nepal
and then returned to the US where I've worked for a non-profit ever since.
Okay, but you still haven't answered my question.
-What does your husband do? -I have a wife.
Oh! So you're a lesbian.
Yeah. So what? Doesn't make any difference.
That's not necessarily true.
So she's gay. Big deal. What's the matter?
You think it's okay for a child to be raised with two gay moms?
It's not fucking 1950, dude.
Yeah, seriously, mind your own business.
What, you think it's okay to raise a baby girl in that environment?
Two gay moms having sex all over the place?
It's not as bad as two men, but it's still wrong.
Maybe it's a good thing that you're here.
You're gonna give that little girl a chance to have a normal life.
Whoa, come on, man. Where are you going with this?
- I'm not homophobic or anything... - -Yeah, right.
Do you think that this is someone worth dying for?
I know a lot of you are religious.
This country was based on family values.
This is a woman who has sinned.
Doesn't that mean something?
-We've all sinned. -Yes, but some more than others.
I mean, maybe that's the whole point of this thing.
Maybe if we figure out who the sinner is amongst us
that maybe this whole thing will end.
I mean, we have no idea what these aliens want.
I mean, maybe that's the answer.
So aliens want me to die because I'm gay?
Look, nothing personal. I'm just trying to get this to stop.
You think I'm the only one?
Cowards.
My son's gay.
And there's not a damn thing wrong with him.
- What if he had a point? - Just drop it already.
No, no, not about the gay stuff.
I mean, what if one of us dies, the one they want, and this all ends?
Jesus. We just keep going in circles.
Why would they single one of us out?
We have a problem.
What?
Well, this guy said that one of us might make it out of here alive, right?
-Yeah. -Because we can't vote for ourselves.
Right.
Well, I'd like to know what's gonna happen
when there's only two people left.
What do you mean?
If there's only two people left, you can only vote for the other person.
-Shit, they would tie. -And they would both die.
No. No, no, no. Not necessarily. One person doesn't have to vote.
-What? -A sacrifice.
-Yes. -What does that mean?
It means that if it comes down to one of us and one of them, we don't vote.
Somebody would have to sacrifice themself to save the other.
Yeah, right. And who would do that?
I would.
- Sure you would. - I would. Wouldn't you?
I really don't know what I would do.
Let's hope it doesn't come down to you, then.
At least he's being honest.
In here the truth gets you killed.
In here everything gets you killed.
We should pick someone we can trust.
We can't trust anyone in here. I think we know that by now.
Well, somebody's gonna have to do it. We should decide.
We don't have to decide anything.
Whoever's left in the end will make that decision.
What if it comes down to the two of them?
Well, then, they'll have to decide.
Or we can decide for them.
You should have never married that asshole.
I know.
Together?
What happened?
- They tied. - How romantic.
I thought if no one voted, it chose randomly.
Not in a tie, I guess.
See? They both can't live. That means one of them has to go.
- They're not going anywhere. - One of them has to die.
You guys want them to decide?
A little kid? That's too much responsibility for a child.
Yeah, he's right. We need to be the ones to do it.
-Do what? -He wants us to kill one of them.
I'm just saying we do what needs to be done.
Bullshit! You're just trying to save your own fucking ass.
It doesn't save me any more than it saves you,
but it guarantees that one of us will make it out of here alive,
otherwise we will all die.
Listen, this is a trick, all right?
Once he gets one of them out of the way, he'll just go after the other.
Don't fall for his bullshit.
If we had to choose one of 'em... who would it be?
What do you do?
- What? - Come on, man.
Hey, it's a fair question.
-What do you mean, like for work? -Yeah.
Of course it'd be the guy in the sweater vest to start this class bullshit.
Hey, hey, hey, we're trying to decide who deserves to live, right?
And career choice is the way to do that.
I'm just saying that some people contribute more to society than others.
Who cares what she does? She's pregnant, that's what matters.
There are plenty of babies. I mean, people have lots of babies.
The world has enough single moms on welfare.
-She might be unemployed. -So what?
That doesn't matter.
What does your husband do?
-What? -The daddy. The baby daddy.
What does he do?
Do you even know who the father is?
-Yes, I know who the father is. -Yeah, but you aren't married, huh?
Look, he's... We're waiting.
Waiting for what? For him to get out of prison?
-Oh, come on. -He's not in jail.
Okay, so what does he do for a living, then?
Enough with the inquisition.
What do you do?
- I work for a bank. - -Of course you do.
We lend people money to start their own businesses.
Does anybody here have their own business?
-How much did you make last year? -I'm not talking about salaries.
You were the one that started talking about the jobs.
No, I'm talking about being a contributing member of society.
Now, I work my ass off every single day
and I never, never take handouts from anyone.
I lend people money to live their dreams.
And outside of work I contribute a significant amount of money to charity.
Well, that's easy when you're pulling down six figures.
Oh, uh-huh, and what do you do?
-I'm a graduate student. -Uh-huh. In?
Psychology.
Well, that's useful. How about you? What do you do?
-Fuck off, dickhead. -What do you do?
You collect your disability checks?
Listen, guy, if you're trying to get us to not vote for you,
you're going about it the wrong way.
- Seriously. - Look, look, look.
We need to come up with some sort of metric here.
Some way to decide who lives.
All I know is if one of us gets to live, it's gonna be one of those two,
at least if I have anything to say about it.
Well, I think we all know what that means.
Yeah, yeah, he's right. She's gone. He should be next.
How nice. Two for one.
-Seriously. -I mean, somebody has to go, right?
Don't you see what they're doing here?
They just killed her to get the majority back in their favor.
-They knew that she was on our side. -What side?
-Yeah, there aren't any sides here. -Really?
So you've never voted for the two of them?
-No, of course not. -Bullshit.
You don't know who's voting for who in here. None of us do.
I think we have a pretty good idea.
People, please, if they get the majority back on their side,
they will kill both of them.
That's what they want, to get them out of the way.
Only the rest of us can stop that from happening.
You're paranoid, man.
Okay, who's with me? The two girls plus me, that's... that's three.
There's 16 of us left in here. We just need six more to get to nine.
-That's enough. -Nine what?
-Nine votes for a majority. -Exactly.
I'm in.
Good, good. Five more.
-Everybody understand? -This is crazy. It's not gonna work.
All right, I'm in.
-So am I. -Okay, that's six. We need three more.
What about you guys?
What exactly are you asking us to do?
-We're asking you to help us. -Yeah, but how?
Look, they are gonna vote for one of those two girls each and every time.
Eventually they're gonna get what they want.
- Unless we stop them. - Stop them how?
-By block voting. -Yeah, man, it's just playing defense.
-He's right, there's no other way. -It's just a numbers game now.
This is ridiculous!
Are you with me?
What do we do?
No one's voting for them this round, okay?
Yeah, we said the guy who doesn't speak any English.
He can't help us now, so once he's gone, we can all discuss what to do next.
You all know what needs to be done!
Vote for the kid. It's the only chance that we have!
Goddamn it!
You're fucking pathetic, man. You'd kill a kid to save your own life.
That's right, I wanna live, just like you.
No, not just like me. I wouldn't do that.
Oh, yeah, well, we'll see what you do when it's your ass on the line.
No, I don't think you will.
What's that supposed to mean, huh? What, you're gonna kill me now?
Why? Because I wanna live, huh?
I'm a fucking bad person because I don't wanna fucking die in here?
Well, you know what? Fine.
You wanna play games? I'll play your game.
I say we get rid of both of them right now, starting with the kid.
That gives us all a chance to walk out of here alive.
Now, I know I'm not the only one in here that wants to do that.
He's right. There's 15 of us left.
All we need is six to even the playing field.
-This isn't a game. -No, it's not.
But you decided to make it a game when you chose sides.
Well, we chose. We just chose the side that said everyone in here is equal.
No one's special. You of all people should understand that.
-Hey, you. Don't you love your wife? -Of course I do.
Well, don't you want to give her a chance to get out of here?
How's that gonna happen if you're on their side?
Listen to him.
If you choose their side, you're just sentencing your wife to death.
Our way will give her a chance to live.
-Right. -I...
-Yeah, yeah, but... -But nothing!
Do you wanna save her or not?
Okay, okay, fine! We're in!
-Me too. -What?
We're all equal. He's right.
-What? -Okay. That's... That's five.
We just need three more.
- Everybody vote for the kid. - We're voting for you.
Come on, people. Don't you wanna live?
All right, make them tie again. They'll both die. That's fair.
-What? -He's right. We'll take that trade.
- What are you doing? -Don't do it. She's a kid!
Fuck. What just happened?
You lost, assholes.
Fuck you. Why didn't they tie?
Why did they tie the first time and not the second?
Somebody changed their vote.
Who?
Why don't you ask your wife?
-It was you? -No.
I mean, yes, but...
Why'd you switch?
I didn't. I just didn't vote the second time.
I couldn't. I'm sorry.
Right, because you're a good person.
Hey, stay out of this, okay?
Look, listen, lady, nobody said this was going to be easy,
but it needs to be done.
Yeah, listen, they both can't live anyway.
He's right. One of them is going to have to die eventually.
We need to band together, otherwise they're gonna win.
There's no winning here, man. We all lose, okay? And that's fine.
We've had plenty of time to accept that.
There's only one thing left that we can do,
and that's go out of here with some dignity.
And maybe we can save two people instead of one.
He's not talking about her.
He's talking about getting R-I-D of the K-I-D sooner rather than later.
- Think she can spell. - We just need to get this over with.
Rip the Band-Aid off. Why drag it out?
-You're outnumbered, man. -That's right. It's over.
Okay.
You wanna live, right?
Yeah.
-But I don't... -Wanna kill a little kid. It's okay.
Fine, everybody vote for the guy with one arm.
-Oh, please, man. -No, no, no, listen, listen.
If we get rid of him, it'll even things out
and we'll actually have more time to talk about this.
There's nothing left to talk about.
Listen, you're just trying to buy yourself more time.
I'm trying to buy everybody some time.
All right, what the hell just happened?
What does that mean?
It means the tables have turned, bitch.
People are starting to see things clearly.
Who did that?
GI Joe next. He's the leader of the pack.
Kill him first, the rest'll cave.
Great idea. There's only 13 of us left. We only need seven.
What do we do?
There's nothing you can do. We've got the majority now.
Let's vote for her.
-What? -He wants to protect her?
-Let's put him to the test. -Hey, hey, hey. Wait a minute, okay?
-Everybody do it. He'll switch. -No, wait. Give me a second.
-Be reasonable, man. -I am being reasonable.
-You wanna give your wife a chance? -Yeah.
Then do the right thing.
-Otherwise she's got 30 seconds to live. -No!
There's no right thing in here.
Yes, there is. We all know it.
Listen, you kill me, you'll die and she'll die next.
We all know that.
-Come on. -Do you love your wife or not?
Come on, please!
Fuck, okay, yes, I'll switch! Fucking pick somebody else!
-Wait, wait, wait. -Everybody vote for the black guy.
Wait, what? Fuck y'all, man!
Of course. True love conquers all.
You're out of options, my friend.
Yeah? Well, you all just killed yourselves. Congratulations.
You, you, you. You all did this.
And you... You just killed your wife.
-I hope you're happy. -I did what I had to do.
Yeah, well, now she's gonna die because of you.
At least my way gave her a chance.
- Just shut the fuck up, man. - -Yeah, man, just drop it.
-They're probably not even married. -What?
I mean, think about it.
What are the odds of them being the only married couple in here?
Those other two knew each other.
-So they said. -That's not gonna work, dude.
So you're saying that they're married
and they just happen to be placed right next to each other?
Uh-uh. Think about it, people.
Isn't it possible that they just made this whole thing up?
- No. - Why would they lie?
To survive. Nobody wants to kill someone's wife or husband.
Especially right in front of each other.
They just made this whole thing up to get our sympathy.
-You're crazy. -Am I?
How long have you been married?
-Five years. -What's his parents' names?
-Erm... Mark and Lisa. -Where'd she go to college?
UCLA.
When's his birthday?
- Er... April. - April...
9th. April 9th.
What's his name?
What?
What is your husband's name?
- He already said his name. - -That's right, he did.
-When? -The first time he spoke.
He said his name.
Just drop it, man, okay?
What's his name?
- She doesn't know. - Of course she doesn't.
Yes, of course she does.
She's just not gonna play your fucking games!
Let's put 'em in a tie and see what happens.
What?
If they're married, there's no way they will vote for each other.
Okay. We made it up.
-But it was her fucking idea. -What?
Yeah, yeah. I just went along with it.
No, he said it first. I had nothing to do with it.
-Come on! She's a liar. Look at her. -Please don't kill me.
No, kill this bitch!
-Why are you crying? -Just shut the fuck up, all right?
You shouldn't have lied to us.
I didn't lie.
Yes, you did. You said you were married.
I am married, just not to him. And I do have a daughter, Emily.
I didn't lie about that.
How many people do you think were married, had husbands, wives kids?
You had no problem with killing any of them.
- I didn't kill them. - Yes, you did.
We all did.
But, listen, you still have a chance to make it out of here.
There's 11 of us left. We just need six votes.
If you join our side, I promise I will keep you alive.
Don't listen to him. He's just trying to use you.
Hey, you wanna get out of here?
You wanna go back home and see your real husband, see Emily?
Yeah.
Good.
How about you? Whose side are you on?
What, you don't speak?
Okay, he doesn't wanna tell us who he's voting for,
and that's fine, I understand that.
Nobody wants to make enemies in here.
I'm gonna go ahead and say that he's on our side.
You have a daughter, don't you? What's her name?
Chloe.
That's a beautiful name, Chloe.
-You wanna see her again? -Obviously.
-And your partner? -Wife.
-Amelia. -Chloe and Amelia.
Do you wanna see both of them again?
- I'm sorry. -Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Hey, that's five. We just need one more.
-Come on, people. One more. -Who are we voting for?
-The army guy. -No! Pick somebody else.
-Cancer lady. -What?
No, no, no. All right, you all know who to vote for.
Shit!
Fuck. All right.
Fuck.
Holy shit.
What do we do?
Listen, it's okay. It's okay.
Okay, there's seven of us left. All we need is four.
One, two, three...
Is it a boy or a girl?
I don't know.
Don't you wanna find out?
Yes, of course I do.
All it takes is one vote.
It's really that simple. Just once.
No.
No, don't, please.
Please.
-Please. -No, no, I won't do it.
I will not do it.
Well, then, you're killing your own child.
How about you, man? You wanna live?
You know where I stand.
-What about you? -Jesus Christ.
What do you think?
Forgive me.
No! Don't!
Yes! Jesus Christ. Thank you, Jesus.
That... Okay, so it's... There's three to three.
There's no way you can protect them now.
Yeah? Okay, well, we'll see about that.
You realize that it's you or them, right?
-So be it. -You're volunteering?
If I go, you go.
Okay. How about this? I'll make you a deal.
You give me one of them and I'll give you her.
- What? - We'll trade.
Which one do you want?
Either one. Doesn't matter to me.
What? What are you doing?
Okay, deal. Deal.
You get the little girl, I get the phony wife.
The three of us will vote for her, the three of you will vote for her.
-How do I know I can trust you? -No.
We'll... We'll vote in order.
One, two, three.
-Okay, deal. -Wait a second.
It's okay. Listen, trust me, just...
Okay, I'll go first.
-There must be trust. -I don't know about this.
It's okay. It's okay. I got you this far.
-Okay. -Let's do it.
Okay.
-What are you doing? -Just do it.
No, no.
Okay, now her.
Okay, it's your turn. Go.
Hey, go. It's your turn.
-What are you doing? It's your turn. -What are you doing?
- Come on, man, vote. - Hurry!
-What are you doing? Vote for the kid. -Vote!
- Are you nuts? Vote! -Vote, please! Please vote!
-What's he doing? Vote. -What are you doing? Come on, vote.
Please vote! Vote!
Jesus Christ. Why didn't you vote?
Because he doesn't vote.
- Never has, not once. - What?
He's never even said a word, never voted, and he's made it all this way.
Dumb fucking luck.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
What?
-Maybe it was no accident. -What are you talking about?
I think that there's a reason why he's still alive.
Yeah, because he's been hiding, hoping we wouldn't notice him.
Well, guess what, buddy? Your time's up.
There's nowhere left for you to hide.
No. No, I don't think that's it.
Then what?
Think about it. He's the only person in here who has never voted.
So he's survived this long just because he hasn't participated?
I don't know. Could be.
That's the answer to all this?
So... what does... what does that mean, that he... he gets to live?
Maybe.
Does that make him untouchable?
There's one way to know for sure.
Yeah. Let's see what happens.
If we vote for him, maybe all this will stop.
Come on.
Wait...
So you made all that up?
No, no. He's never voted. I don't think so.
At least, that and he's never said a word.
I mean, not that I can remember.
I don't think he wants to give them anything.
We've already given them enough.
Do you want us to vote for you?
He knows we don't have a choice.
Why are they doing this to us?
It's some kind of experiment, I guess.
And that's it?
Yeah, maybe. I mean, maybe they just wanted to learn about us.
Learn what?
I don't know.
Maybe just to see what we would do
and who we would choose and why.
For what?
To understand us, what we value, what we don't, what matters to us.
By making us kill each other.
When we kill someone, we're judging them
and we're saying that there's something wrong with them.
I think that's what they've been looking for.
So what do we do now?
That's up to the two of you.
-But how do we choose? -I don't know.
But once I'm gone, one of you is gonna have to step forward,
otherwise you'll both die.
But you're gonna have to decide for yourselves. I can't do it for you.
You don't have much time.
I'll go.
-For the baby, right? -Uh-huh.
It's very brave of you.
What's your name?
-Katie. -Okay, Katie, we'll go together, okay?
Okay. Okay.
It has to end this way.
There's no more time. Do it!
Fuck. Come on.
Of course.
Of course. All that...
All that for nothing.
All that. What's the matter, huh?
What, I'm not good enough for you?
What? I'm not the one that you wanted?
I'm exactly the same as everybody else in here.
They all got to make their own choices.
They chose to kill each other.
That's what you wanted to see, right? Huh?
Well, there you go, congratulations. We're assholes.
Fuck you.
We all know that we can't vote for ourselves, right?
Well, what do you think happens
when we get down to the last person left?
It's a game. It's process of elimination.
The last man standing gets to walk out of here alive.
Between the kid and the pregnant girl,
I'm sure it's most likely gonna come down to one of them in the end.
You're gonna have to decide for yourselves. I can't do it for you.
It has to end this way.
You don't have much time.