什么情况
What the fuck?
我接住你了
I got you!
我去
Fuck...
Harper
Harper.
有个警官要见你
There's a police officer here to see you.
只是想问你一些问题
Just wants to ask you some questions.
我一个小时后回来给你换绷带
I'll be back in an hour to change your bandages
到时候你就该走了
and it'll be time for you to go.
Harper Sykes 我叫Slayton 我
Harper Sykes. My name is Slayton. I'm a state detective.
I gotta be honest. My boss doesn't believe your story.
Thinks your little trip through the Wachitumi Valley
is a hillbilly fairy tale.
Sent me down here to find out if you're just another
mountain tweaker who burned herself up in a meth lab.
And once you're discharged she's gonna
lock you up for stabbing the state trooper who found you.
But I read his report.
And that's the reason I'm here.
See I've been hearing about Wachitumi Valley
since I was a boy.
Those myths are legendary where I come from.
I used to love to hear about
cop-killing Catholics who didn't bury their dead,
runaway slaves still practicing voodoo,
leftover Chinamen from the railroad who ate their own.
But they were just stories Harper.
That's all they were, no proof.
Never any answers. No evidence.
So I came here
to get some answers from your story
and you're going to have to convince me that you got them.
Or we're going to lock you up.
Report says you were covered in a slimy gauze.
Totally whacked out, you stabbed a trooper in the arm with a knife.
You were about to stab him again...
He was one of them one of them.
One of who?
He said plenty more where they came from.
Who said that, Harper?
Who said that?
Ravener.
Who is he?
He killed Billy.
Billy.
Billy, right, Billy Harrison, your missing boyfriend.
They've been ringing the phone number you gave
for Billy and no answer.
Harper!
-No Billy.
No Billy. No boyfriend.
Billy's not missing.
Ravener killed him.
Where's his body?
I got guys out there looking for bodies.
They haven't found a body. Are you...
Are you batshit crazy, Harper?
Is that what you are? You're just fucking out of your mind nuts?
Fuck you.
So you're a photographer, huh?
Take pictures of animals in the wild.
I read your bio.
Pretty impressive.
Credited with photographing two species
thought to be extinct that...
I guess that means you're pretty good at your job.
What were you doing in the Wachitumi Valley, Harper?
Looking for a red snake.
What's so special amount of red snake?
We're not supposed to be there.
Hello.
Hey, can I help you?
- ...with something? - Hey, uh...
Yeah, I need to make a report.
Okay.
I saw something.
All right.
And?
You okay?
I took pictures on my camera.
All right.
Tell you what,
I'll make us some coffee.
And don't you go get what it is that you want to show me
and then we can sort it out, is that a deal?
Deal, yeah.
Oh, don't mind him.
I just hire him every once in a while to keep him out of his mama's hair.
All right. Have a seat.
Hey, Harper, it's Billy, just calling to give you an update.
I just left the city, I got about five hours until I am in the Wachitumi Valley.
And, um, don't call me back, I'm sure you're out there in the woods
taking photos, being super cute, um...
I'm going to head right to the bed and breakfast, I've got extra clothes for you.
Hey, hey!
What the fuck!
Hey, stop!
No!
Somebody help!
You know, I was on my way to Horsefeathers.
I was just gonna TGIF it.
You know? But I got a call from the town retard
who said the sheriff had had a little shutterbug visit.
You're a little snoop, huh?
He said you've been putting your camera
where you aren't supposed to.
I'm a nature photographer
What?
- You can have my camera. - I can't hear you.
You can have the camera.
I don't want the camera.
You can have the pictures.
I don't want the pictures.
I want you.
Okay?
Here's how it's going to go.
It's going to be super simple.
You and I we're just going to duke it out right here. Pow.
These boys?
They're just here to make sure I do my job. Okay?
So...
Come on out when you're ready, sweetheart.
No rush.
Come on, it's showtime, lady.
Fuck.
Yeah!
You are on the scoreboard.
These boys ain't got shit.
Look at you, huh?
I said I'd give you a fair fight, getting a jump on me.
Where'd you learn to shoot like that.
Oh, yeah! Ooh, I'm falling for you.
- You're a psycho. - Oh, I'm a psycho?
Girl, you just killed yourself somebody.
Come here, you are exactly the type of girl I have been looking for.
You really are. You got spirit!
I swear to God, I mean, I...
I'm falling for you.
I saw you.
At the tree tearing that man apart.
That man...
That man was going to tear my valley part.
That man was a timber and mineral scout.
We caught him with samples.
You know what that little fucker was gonna do?
He goes to a big oil company,
he gets a big fat check,
then they go and they lobby
and you know what happens when the feds get to it?
They sell off the timber and mineral rights to the highest bidder.
You ever been to West Virginia?
You see what they've done to their fucking mountains?
What I did was preserve a way of life.
That fucker would have changed everything. Everything!
I saw what you did. Oh, fuck!
You don't understand, you stupid bitch. I'm doing what I believe in. Hmm?
Just cause you believe in it doesn't make it right.
Yes, it does!
You're not listening!
This place is mine!
And I really thought that you could appreciate this.
We've got the last old-growth forest on the Atlantic seaboard.
It's just like when the settlers got here.
Nature girl like you should be able to appreciate all that.
Hello?
Fuck!
Don't know why some photo bitch is up here...
Probably sending her pictures to some fucking prospector.
Man.
Ha ha ha.
You gonna come here...
Force me out of the valley. I ain't gonna have that, yeah, I'm gonna find it.
I'm gonna catch her...
I'm gonna break her. I'm gonna break that bitch!
Little cunt.
Dumb fucking bitch.
Come on, bitch!
Where you at?
Little Red Riding Hood, come back out of the forest, huh?
Where's that devil?
Fucking...
Woo-wee!
Yeah. Yeah.
You hear me?
What do you think...?
Help.
How do we get out of here?
You ain't ever gonna get out of here.
I took you on that. Just so you know.
I had...
I had you good.
You ain't nothing.
Jesse, you there?
Jesse?
Harper Sykes.
Guess you'd be off squawking away. Had to be you.
You left your wallet in the truck, so I looked you up a bit.
Googled ya.
A month in Arkansas looking for the ivory-billed woodpecker,
then hunting tigers in Asia.
You're G.I. Jane with a camera.
You're the real deal.
Now, you're wondering if I'm going to hear you coming
and try to ride that rig out of there.
You're wondering whether it's worth the risk.
Well, here's the thing. There's only one way out of the valley.
Burning Falls to the north is impassable.
The gas station is a 16-day hike to the west.
And it's going to take you nearly a month
if you try to go through the national forest east.
The only way out of there
is coming down the river
and you know that's gonna happen sooner or later...
Hello?
Good to see you.
Mallinckrodt.
Harper Sykes.
Sykes.
Very good. Wonderful name.
Want a bourbon? Yes, yes, you do.
Could I use your phone?
I don't have a phone, ma'am.
I haven't had a phone for 15 years.
I just really need to make a phone call.
Um, let's go in there by the fire and get you sorted.
Every time I spill just a little bit.
You know what I mean?
Daytime drinking.
You're wondering.
This is for my heart, all of this stuff.
One, two, three, this, four.
This, uh, comes with my supplies once a week.
- Your supplies. - Mm-hm.
Everything here is delivered to me once a week.
And allows me to stay here.
Those books there.
They're a document of how we tamed this valley.
Felled trees from all around here
Went down to the river
and got big stones and brought them up here.
And that's when there were mosquitoes bigger than hummingbirds.
And there were bears running around killing people.
It was grim, but we did it.
We built this place.
We tamed this whole valley.
- It's a lot of death. - That there?
That's the progress of civilization.
Progress?
Of course.
What do you mean progress?
Societies have long distinguished themselves
in how they killed their own.
Seems like torture.
No, no, torture's a whole different matter.
Execution is the measurement
of a country's civility.
Torture is the barometer
of a nation's creativity.
How do you kill people? How do you keep a man alive
enough to get him to say what you need him to say?
And everybody had different ways of doing it.
Proudly named their methods.
The Spanish Donkey the Iron Maiden.
And there was a cruel, cruel competition
between the Kings of Pain.
But what do you think scares man more than anything else?
What do you think scares him the most?
Mother Nature.
Because Mother Nature is the true Lord of Pain.
- Want another drink? - No, thanks.
I'm going to have one, if you don't mind.
I know you didn't ask for it. There you go.
You murder it.
Wow.
Thatta girl.
While I do this can you come over here and turn this thing off?
Oh, my God.
You motherfucking bitch.
Sykes.
Sykes!
Goddamnit!
I know what you saw down at the river.
Where you were taking your pictures.
What you saw was a hollow cross.
I, uh, came up with that myself.
You run on along.
They're waiting for you.
...continue to indicate a severe thunderstorm
capable of producing large damaging hail up to golf-ball size...
The severe storm...
...capable of producing large, damaging hail up to golf-ball size.
The severe storm is located near Presbiet...
or about over Presbiet and moving southeast at 30 miles per hour.
Further locations in the warning include
East Mandura Western Pierce...
This is a dangerous situation.
If you are in the path of this storm, prepare immediately for destructive hail
which can significantly damage roofs, windows, siding and vehicles.
Seek shelter now inside a sturdy structure and stay away from windows.
Report any damage to the nearest law enforcement agency
for relay to the National Weather Service.
Hello?
Hey? Hello?
Darlene, damn pump's out again. Darlene?
I'm going to take my revolver out and put it down on the ground.
Billy and I have been looking for you since yesterday.
Where you been?
That boyfriend of yours has covered nearly every inch
of this valley looking for you.
It's okay.
Okay.
Where'd you run off to? Huh?
I found your truck. I got all your stuff in my cruiser.
Alright?
It'll be okay.
Let's go.
Can you tell me what happened?
I'm running from them.
Who?
I'll show you.
No! No! No!
In ancient times the Slavs used to get answers from people
by using their cows for more than just milk.
You see, digesting all the food
that one of these guys eats in a day,
that requires a very special system.
So these big beautiful beasts they have four stomachs.
They're basically just a big old vat
of the world's most toxic acid.
A long time ago there were these
-two dairy farmers.
And they had overthrown this horrid king
who was famous for his most wicked ways.
He just loved torture.
He loved impalements.
He loved Judas cradles.
He loved coffin tortures. All the good stuff.
Now, these brothers, they'd sacked the castle, right?
And the king, who obviously has no idea about his predicament,
he just offers up his kingdom.
Throws the queen and his children and the village
if they'll just let his cowardly ass go.
These revolutionaries...
-they're just simple
little dairy farmers.
And to them, you know, this doesn't sound right.
So... they throw a huge banquet in the king's court.
Everybody's there, the whole royal family.
The brothers are sitting there and they're all just having a grand time.
Then somebody leads a cow in.
One of the brothers, he gets up.
He goes to the banquet table
and he takes out a huge carving knife.
Then the dairy farmer takes a knife.
He creates a small cavity just below the anus.
Then the other brother, he binds the king's feet.
And his hands.
And then to everyone's shock,
they slide the king inside the cow.
They start stitching up around the king's neck.
These Slavs had seen it all.
Their king...
with a head sticking out of a calf.
This was new this was groundbreaking.
They said it took about three days for the king's body to decompose.
What are you laughing at?
I saw the picture of all of you at the old man's house.
That's what you're laughing at?
I killed all of them.
Yeah. I blew that Kinsey guy's face off.
And the tweaker...
He got shot to pieces.
And then that creepy guy with the smile.
Lost his head.
And that old sick demented fuck.
He had himself a meth-induced heart attack.
He was in a lot of pain.
So I shot him.
Yeah, I got your whole fucked-up clan.
Well, there's a lot more where that came from.
You're the coward who couldn't find me.
You get some tired cop to come pick me up?
Untie me.
So I can claw your fucking face off.
Yeah.
I'm going to torture you.
- You are? - Yeah.
And then I'm gonna kill you.
Yeah.
Then...
I'm going to drag you across...
the floor over to that door.
I'm going to watch the pigs
-tear you apart.
- Come on. - You motherfucker!
I got you, you motherfucker!
I got you, you motherfucker.
No?
Harper!
The doctor is waiting for you with the lab results.
And it's time for you to go.
Wait.
I'm almost done.
After he beat me...
And no one cares...
After he stabbed me.
After he fed my boyfriend to his pig.
No!
After he hung me upside down
and left me for dead.
After he terrorized me.
After he butchered a cow.
And gutted it.
After stitching...
Where are you going, Ginger?
You're gonna miss the best part.
I think you're ill.
I think you are the victim of a dangerous opioid epidemic and...
you're troubled, and you and whoever you're hanging out with...
pose a great danger to yourselves.
Detective Slayton, shut the door, please.
In your officer's report it says my patient was covered
in a Vaseline-like substance and that her burns
- are the likely result of an explosion. - I know all that.
She wasn't covered in Vaseline.
And it wasn't heat which created her third degree burns.
What kind of burns are they?
The lab report states that she was embalmed
in the digestive enzymes of ox bile.
She was being digested.