Green Lantern: Previously on Justice League...
I don't believe it. Rex Mason? - Hey, John.
Meet my fiancée sapphire Stagg.
You're dating the boss' daughter?
I've accepted a job offer in Chicago.
And I'm going with him.
But you can't!
Daddy, I'm not your little girl anymore.
I made you,
And I can just as easily unmake you.
[screaming]
No. No!
Please, you're his friend. You have to help us.
I'll find him, I promise.
Thank you, John.
It was no accident, Simon,
And I want to know who's responsible!
Aah!
I want them to see what my creation can really do.
I knew you were jealous,
But I never thought you'd go this far.
Mase, stop. I never--
I don't want to hear it!
Aah!
[grunting]
Relax, I've got him.
Come along quietly, or I'll--
Aah!
Mase, don't! You're killing him!
What's happening to me?
Hawkgirl: Let him go!
Haa!
Uhh!
He's more powerful than I ever imagined.
Huh?
Stay back, all of you!
[moaning]
Uhh!
Aaah!
[growling]
Enough!
Aah!
That's not going to hold him for long.
[sobbing]
[rattling]
Aah!
How could you?
Rex?
You heard me.
How could you dump me like that?
What are you talking about?
My so-called buddy Green Lantern.
But who wouldn't rather be with a superhero
Instead of a freak like me?
How could you even think that?
Don't bother denying it. I know what happened.
Shut up and get this through that thick head of yours!
I love you, you big dope,
And I always will, no matter what.
But the pictures-- I saw you and John together and--
Whatever you saw was a lie.
Who showed them to you?
It was...
Good lord.
How could I have been so blind?!
Rex, wait. Come back!
Haa!
Uhh!
Simon: Well, is Metamorpho everything I promised?
Everything and more, Simon. We want him.
I thought you would.
Let's set up a meeting for next week,
And bring your checkbook.
A toast, Java,
To unbridled capitalism.
I don't get it, boss.
How are you going to get Mason to work for him?
Mason? He was just a prototype.
Now that I've perfected the process,
I don't need him anymore.
So, I'm just a guinea pig, huh?
[growling]
Keep away from-- uhh!
Why me, Simon?
Was it because I asked too many questions about your pet project
Or because I took your daughter?
You leave her out of this.
I'll never let you touch her-- never!
Aah! Uhh!
Fun science fact:
All chemical reactions stop at sub-zero temperatures,
Even yours.
Good work, Java.
What do you want me to do with him?
Dump him.
And then he just turned into smoke and disappeared.
Can you think where he might have gone?
No. He wasn't rational.
There's no telling what he might do.
Don't worry. We'll find him.
I see why he always looked up to you.
To me? He was the one who had it made.
No. I've seen him watching you on the news.
The way you're always helping people--
I think he'd trade places with you in a second.
Hmm. Guess the grass always looks greener.
I'll bring him back safe, I promise.
So I told my broker,
"industrial waste management--
That's a growth business."
Am I wrong here?
Like they say, garbage in, garbage out.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
[banging]
What was that? Aah!
Mind if I take the wheel?
What is that thing?!
It's toast!
Think we got him?
Hey, is that the stuff?
Luckily, I was able
To get another shipment of the mutagen...
No thanks to you.
Now we can shift into full-scale production.
[crash]
Not if I can help it.
Stop him!
Not this time, Flintstone.
Haa! Huh?
You did this to me, Simon,
But you won't do it to anyone else.
Ever!
Mason, don't!
[screaming]
Ohh.
Simon? Simon, can you hear me?
Looks like we're too late.
Maybe not.
[moans]
John,
Thank heavens you're here.
Let me go.
Haven't you done enough damage?
It wasn't me.
Stagg made some kind of synthetic monster.
You've got to believe me.
After you tried to deep-fry me? I don't think so.
Look, I'm sorry I went off like that.
I was wrong,
But we can hash that out later.
Right now, there's another monster loose out there.
Did you feel that?
What was it? Felt like an Earthquake.
[screaming]
[roaring]
Open fire!
Pull back!
[screaming]
Ohh!
Uhh!
It's like punching dough.
Hawkgirl confirms finding another monster.
See? I'm telling the truth.
Let me help.
So, what do you know about this monster?
Stagg was working with a mutagen
When I smashed the controls.
The chemicals came to life.
I think it's the same compound he used on me.
Ok, we'll take it from here.
Wait.
You can't beat it by yourself.
Let me go with you.
I don't know.
Batman: He's right.
We're gonna need all the help we can get.
You two go.
I'll stay here and test this residue.
Maybe I can find a weakness.
All right, but I'm keeping my eye on you.
That didn't work.
Aah!
[coughing]
Are you hurt?
Only my pride.
Uh-oh, more trouble.
No, he's here to help.
I see you've met Stagg’s synthoid.
Learn anything?
Yeah-- don't hit it with an energy mace.
Maybe we can talk to it-- reason with it.
Not a chance. It's totally mindless.
J'onn: No, I sensed a mind within the creature--
Incomplete, irrational,
And driven only by base desire.
Maybe the feedback from the accident
Transferred part of Stagg’s mind into it.
So, what's it after?
Oh, no.
Newscaster: A gigantic creature
Has defeated the Justice League.
Now it's continuing its rampage
And heading relentlessly uptown.
Residents are advised to evacuate.
Oh, Rex, what's happened to you?
[growling]
Sapphire.
Rexie?
Aah!
Look out!
He's got sapphire!
I'm coming for you, honey!
Let's see how it likes an acid bath.
Green Lantern: No good. He's neutralized it.
Hawkgirl: Look out!
Uhh!
Haa!
I'm ok. Keep going.
[coughing]
Aah!
Thanks, but this is getting us nowhere.
Batman: Lantern, I've got something.
The creature's composed of artificial protein.
We can destroy it with a complex polypeptide.
Green Lantern: Like a designer amino acid?
How soon can you whip up a batch?
That's the problem.
It'll take days to synthesize.
We don't have that long.
Wait.
Tell me what's in the stuff. I'll do the rest.
Change into the polypeptide?
Not a chance.
If you come into contact with that thing,
The chemical reaction will destroy you both.
Yeah, you're probably right.
But I don't have time to argue.
Sorry, pal,
But sapphire needs me.
Batman: Lantern, are you still there?!
He's resting. What's the formula?
Rex, please, you don't know what you're doing!
What I wouldn't give for a couple of biplanes right about now.
Stagg!
Rex?
Mason!
Daddy?
It's over, old man. Let her go!
Never!
Ohh!
Daddy, don't!
I love you, Saph.
Rex!
Mase!
[screaming]
The crazy fool!
Aah!
[crying]
I'm so sorry.
He was a good man and a real hero.
It would have meant a lot to him to hear you say that.
Sapphire.
[gasps]
Here we go.
Heads up, people!
I wouldn't want to do that again.
Rex?!
You're alive!
You can't get rid of me that easily.
Come here, you big ape.
Still dreaming about the road not taken?
What do you think?