Previously on Justice League...
You hijacked a truck and drove it off a bridge.
Any of this ringing a bell?
What?
It's possible they simply snapped under the strain.
My name is Solovar.
I'm chief of security for Gorilla City.
Safely hidden from humanity,
We apes have lived in peace for thousands of years
Until the black day
When a power-mad genius named Grodd
Tried to conquer our city with advanced mind-control technology.
Grodd has sworn terrible revenge on all who reside in Gorilla City.
Where's Grodd, your little monkey pen pal?
Aah! Uhh!
Don't move, Grodd.
You can't control us while we're wearing these.
Actually, I wasn't thinking of controlling you.
I hate to do this.
Uhh!
My apologies for the hasty exit,
But I have a city to destroy.
Aah!
J'onn: Diana! Hawkgirl!
What is it, J’onn?
Central City-- it's gone.
That's impossible.
See for yourself.
Sensors indicate that the city has vanished without a trace.
Weren't G.L. and Flash down there?
Flash, Green Lantern, this is the Watchtower calling.
Please come in.
[static]
Repeat, come in.
[groaning]
We're still here.
So it would seem.
The mind control. Is he still--
No.
This should protect him.
Who, what, where?!
Aw, man, not again.
What did I miss?
That dumb ol' gorilla got away.
Go ahead, rub it in.
This time, we're getting some backup.
Green Lantern to Watchtower.
Watchtower, come in.
My comm link's off-line.
Mine too.
Solovar: And for good reason.
Man, what is that?
It's just like the shield that protects my city.
Nothing can get in.
Or out, unless I can shut down the generator.
Whoa, not even a scratch.
Gorilla technology is highly advanced.
Come. We must find Grodd.
Approaching Central City.
Or at least where it used to be.
See anything yet?
Negative.
It's as if it never existed.
Proximity alert, 12 o'clock.
I see nothing.
Batman designed this ship.
If its sensors say something is there--
[crash]
Great Hera!
Hang on!
Your trust in Batman's engineering skills was well placed.
So what did we hit?
Some sort of energy field.
Can you phase through it?
It seems to be an asynchronous dimensional interface.
Let me take a whack at it.
No, don't! Haa!
Aah!
Perhaps we should try a different approach.
Weird. Am I the only one creeped out here?
Where is everyone?
Perhaps the shield frightened them.
Could be, but usually when a city looks this empty,
Flesh-eating zombies are involved.
You watch too many movies.
Shh! Listen.
[crowd shouting indistinctly]
Maybe you don't watch enough.
[crowd chanting "Grodd!"]
We're too late.
They're already under his control.
Uh, how many of these headbands you got left?
Two.
That's not gonna be enough.
Diana, I've analyzed the data you sent.
Can you tell us how to penetrate the force field?
Not yet, but I've discovered something else--
A second energy signature
Similar to the one you've encountered,
Except it's in Africa.
Africa?
Could the city have been transported there?
Unlikely, but it's worth investigating.
I'm sending coordinates to your onboard G.P.S.
I'll rendezvous with you there.
[crowd chanting "Grodd!"]
Grodd: People of Central City,
The age of hairless, simple-minded humanity is over.
Today a new age dawns.
Today Grodd rules.
Humans are slow, ugly, immoral,
And have an unpleasant body odor.
Hey, who you calling slow?
Flash, don't heckle the supervillain.
We don't have to listen to this.
Humans are inferior creatures,
Fit only to serve at my whim.
But after Gorilla City falls,
You will be the paving stones
On which I will build my new empire.
Hey, monkey boy, why don't you go climb a skyscraper?
Intruders! Destroy them!
[crowd chanting "destroy them!"]
Couldn't keep your big mouth shut, could you?
We need some breathing room.
Make yourselves scarce. I'm going after Grodd.
Stop the intruder. Fire!
Both: Destroy! Destroy!
Stay back!
Hey, girls, it's me, remember?
I saved your lives this morning.
Destroy! Destroy!
Ow! That's gratitude for you.
Ohh!
Would you excuse me?
[electronic whine]
I'd bail if I were you.
Where's Grodd?
There's no question.
This energy field is identical to the one in Central City.
Great. We couldn't get through that one, either.
Wonder Woman: And there's still no sign of the city or its inhabitants.
Hawkgirl: Perhaps if we--
Aah!
They are awake, sir.
Where are we? Who's in charge?
You misunderstand the situation, intruder.
You will answer my questions.
Sure. Just get us out of these things.
It is not my policy
To allow spies to roam free.
J'onn: We are not spies,
Nor will you hold us against our will.
We-- aarr!
J'onn!
You will find Gorilla City much more difficult to leave
Than it was to enter.
Gorilla City?
Now, let us begin again.
Who sent you?
Halt! Who goes there?
Your lord and master.
Would you be so kind as to direct me to the missile control room?
As you wish, lord Grodd.
Launch codes accepted.
The nuclear missiles are at your command.
Excellent. Enter these targeting coordinates.
Targets locked.
Confirming Gorilla City.
All systems are go.
Commence firing sequence.
Flash, I can't hold them off much longer.
How much do you weigh?
About 400 of your pounds.
Why do you-- aah!
Ahh! Oh! 400 pounds, huh?
You sure you did the math right?
Green Lantern: Grodd got away again,
But if he used his rocket bike,
My ring can follow his trail.
I've gotta get me one of those.
Green Lantern: He must be inside.
Halt, in the name of Grodd!
Hurry, before Grodd finds out we're here.
[alarm sounding]
Something tells me he already knows.
No, that's a launch alert!
I'll go after the missiles.
You stop Grodd!
Right.
Stop Grodd? How?
Unh!
Quit stalling, spy. Tell me who sent you!
No one sent us.
Lies!
I want the truth,
Or you'll all pay most dearly!
I'll give you one last chance,
Starting with you.
Take your best shot.
Grrr! No!
Get him!
Oof!
Let's go.
Haaa!
Security, stop them!
What madness is this?
Let's not wait around to find out.
Aah! Aah!
Try to escape like that again,
And I promise you will regret it.
What?
The shield wall-- it's shutting down!
Get it back up immediately!
It's not responding.
Someone's overridden the system.
Grodd.
Sir, defense scans have detected
Armed missiles heading this way.
What are your orders?
Evacuate the city immediately!
But what about the humans?
I've got bigger problems now.
Wonder Woman: Maybe we can help.
You?
What could you possibly do to save us?
Just watch.
That's one down.
Missile number 1 deactivated.
What happened?
Flash: Best guess?
It was my buddy with the power ring.
You again!
Grodd, you're under arrest for crimes against Gorilla City.
In 5 more minutes, there won't be a Gorilla City.
Come on, come on.
Uhh!
Missile number 2 deactivated.
It's over, Grodd.
No!
I won't lose to the likes of you!
Guess who?
What?
Where are you, human?
You want a piece of me, chuckles? Come on.
Raah!
Uhh... Whoa!
No. I'm too late!
Haaa!
[gorillas screaming]
It's coming this way!
There's nowhere to hide!
[grunting]
Hera, give me strength!
Diana!
Wonder Woman: The fates were kind today.
Your city is safe.
Missile number 4 deactivated.
I'll rend you limb from limb!
Unh! Oof!
Gotta catch me first.
Stand still and fight me, you simpleton!
We could do that.
Tell you what.
You ditch the mind control helmet,
And I'll ditch the headband.
Flash, don't!
Come on, gorilla my dreams.
Take off the helmet!
Heh! You're a bigger fool than I thought.
Oh, yeah? Well, you're... naked.
The world will miss your sparkling intellect.
Good-bye, Flash.
Aargh!
What have you done to him?
Simple. When I pushed the helmet down over his eyes,
I also crossed some wires.
How could you?
You've destroyed the greatest mind on Earth.
You'll be ok,
Now that you're free from his mind control.
What are you talking about?
He never used that on me.
I loved him.
Internet romances, huh?
Go figure.
I'm sorry we misjudged you.
We can never repay you for all you've done.
No biggie.
What's gonna happen to Grodd?
I'll show you.
The feedback from his helmet completely wiped out his mind.
I almost feel sorry for him.
You have my solemn word that he will receive the best of care.
Not bad, huh?
I outsmarted a supergenius.
Guess you're not as dumb as you look.
Yeah, and I--
Hey, I resent that.
No one makes a monkey out of me.