[grunting]
[sighs]
What's the saying?
Mad dogs and Englishmen?
All for a good cause, my dear.
What's this?
Let me see.
It appears to be older than the Proconsul africanus.
This could be the greatest discovery
In the history of mankind.
Aah!
Humans!
What was that?
Flash: So there I was, cornered.
Solomon Grundy thought he had the drop on me,
But he didn't, and you know why?
[slurp]
Because I'm the Flash...
All: The fastest man alive.
You told us.
Did I?
Anyway, so when Grundy tries to grab me, I--
[tires screeching]
Aah!
[both scream]
Would you excuse me?
Are you ok, man?
He's a madman!
Ran me right off the road!
Someone's got to stop him.
Right.
Later, ladies.
And you didn't want to give him our phone number.
Oops.
Sorry.
Whoa!
[grunts]
[whimpering]
[knock knock]
Ok, pull over.
Hey!
Uh-oh.
Lose something?
I was handling it.
So I see.
What are you doing here?
Responding to a police call.
Someone hijacked a load of radioactive isotopes.
No wonder these guys were in such a hurry.
Ohh.
Where am I?
You hijacked a truck and drove it off a bridge.
Any of this ringing a bell? What?
Let's see some I.D.
Professor Arthur Chin and Dr. Mark Stevens.
Both work at the River Bluffs research center
Where the isotopes were stolen.
And I feel guilty when I take paper clips from the Watchtower.
Let's see if we can get to the bottom of this.
Woman: I'm sorry. I can't explain their behavior.
They're both highly respected experts in their fields.
They certainly don't fit the profile of armed robbers.
To be fair, they've been under enormous pressure
To finish their current project.
It's possible they simply snapped under the strain.
I wish I could help you,
But frankly, the whole thing just seems so...
Preposterous.
What are they working on?
That's classified information.
Want one?
Hey!
If you'll excuse me, I have work to do.
Would you hurry up?
We're supposed to be conducting an investigation.
Can I help it if I have
A hyperaccelerated metabolism?
Besides, it's just a little snack.
[Siren]
Now what?
Man: Get out of my way!
There's a gorilla on the loose.
Aah!
Whoa! Move!
I'm on it.
Wait! I'll go-- with you.
Not without paying for that.
[sighs]
There he goes!
Cool.
Whoa!
All right, watch him. Watch him now.
Fire!
Hey!
Stop him.
My insurance doesn't cover a second driver.
Now there's something you don't see every day.
Huh?
Having fun, mojo?
[people shouting]
[groans]
Flash: Easy, boy.
We'll have you back behind monkey bars
Before you know it.
Get your stinking paws off me, you filthy human.
Say what?
Aah!
[screaming]
[panting]
Huh?
[gasps]
Ahh.
Ha ha ha ha!
Aah!
[grunts]
[panting]
[screaming]
Aah!
[groaning]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[roaring]
Hey, wake up.
Huh?
Come on. You're in my spot.
[groans]
Where am I?
You Justice League hotshots
Think you can do whatever you want.
Not in my city.
But--
Let's go, red.
You've got a lot of explaining to do.
Sit.
Hey, easy.
What did I do?
This is a surveillance tape
From the police impound.
See that stuff?
The isotopes from the robbery
You and Green Lantern broke up?
Watch.
I don't understand.
Too quick for you?
Let's try the freeze frame.
Recognize anybody?
Detective: Let's go over it again.
There's nothing to go over. I'm innocent.
So that's not you on the tape?
No.
I mean, yes.
I mean, I don't remember.
Where did you stash the isotopes?
Just tell us your side.
I'm sure the D.A. Will understand.
After all, you're a hero.
Was a hero.
Forget his statement,
We've got the tape.
He's right.
If you want to help yourself out,
You got to do it now.
I can't think.
I'm tired and hungry.
Maybe some coffee will help you.
How do you take it?
Cream and 37 sugars.
Really.
Green Lantern: Put it in a paper cup. He'll be taking it to go.
You actually posted bail for this lowlife?
If he were really guilty,
Do you think you could have held him here
with a pair of handcuffs?
Thanks for sticking up for me in there.
Ow!
What were you thinking?
I wasn't thinking anything.
Obviously.
Look, if I wanted the third degree,
I could have stayed in there.
Like I told 'em, I don't remember.
All right.
Then let's start with the last thing you do remember.
Let's see. After I caught the gorilla,
It told me that--
The gorilla talked to you?
Yeah. Right after I stopped his car.
I'm supposed to believe this?
Hey, we've both got a Martian’s phone number on our speed dial.
I think I deserve the benefit of the doubt, here.
Let's check it out.
Together this time.
Looks like he's still at large.
Wait. I've got something.
[roars]
Was that really necessary?
Ok, so he can talk.
Who are you?
My name is Solovar.
I'm chief of security for Gorilla City.
Gorilla City?
You've gotta be kidding.
I assure you this is no laughing matter.
Go on.
Safely hidden from humanity,
We apes have lived in peace for thousands of years...
Until the black day when a power-mad genius named Grodd
Tried to conquer our city
With advanced mind control technology.
We were able to thwart his evil plot...
But we couldn't prevent his escape.
It wasn't until later that we discovered
He had also stolen our city's security plans.
Grodd has sworn terrible revenge
On all who reside in Gorilla City.
So that's why you're here?
Yes.
To stop him from carrying out his threats.
If it's true he has a mind control device,
That could explain the isotope thefts
And your memory loss.
He needs those isotopes to power his devices.
So where is he?
My investigation showed
That Grodd had been carrying on
An e-mail correspondence with a local scientist,
Dr. Sarah Corwin.
I knew there was something weird about that lady.
We better call the others.
Why?
You think we can't handle one dumb old gorilla?
No offense. It'll be a piece of cake.
Wait. First you must--
He's very fast.
Yeah. What were you gonna say?
These headbands will protect us
From Grodd's ray.
We'd better catch the kid
Before he gets into anymore trouble.
[monkeys shrieking and chittering]
Don't move.
Ahem.
How--
You blinked. Where's Grodd?
I don't know what you mean.
Don't play cute with me, doc.
Grodd, your little monkey pen pal.
Aah! Uhh!
That's for the banana.
I hate bananas.
Foolish humans.
They're so easily deceived.
Aren't they, Doctor?
[explosion]
Don't move, Grodd.
Solovar, you're a fool to come here.
You can't control us while we're wearing these.
Actually, I wasn't thinking of controlling you.
Destroy them.
Aah!
Should have seen that coming.
[grunts]
Flash, snap out of it.
Come, my dear.
Hold still.
[groans]
Uhh!
[Solovar groans]
Are you all right?
Yes, I--
Look out!
I hate to do this.
Unh!
Sorry, kid.
Had no choice.
[groans]
The system is operational.
Then we'll take our leave.
Not this time.
[gasps]
My apologies for the hasty exit,
But I have a city to destroy.
No!
[grunts]
[grunting]
Aah!