Captioning made possible by Warner bros.
Would you look at that?
A little slice of heaven.
If your idea of heaven
Is a barren, lifeless rock.
You have the soul of a poet.
Carter, we didn't come for the view.
Our mission here is purely scientific.
Are you getting any readings?
[beeping]
No detectable levels of H2O.
Hold on.
What?
Could be an ice crystal.
Unh!
No. It almost looks organic.
[rumbling]
Carter! Look out!
Aah!
Carter!
[grunting]
Carter, do you read me? Are you all right?
Repeat-- Carter, do you read me?
Unh! I'm ok, ed.
Ed? Come in, ed.
[feedback]
Dead.
[gasps]
[grunting]
Unh!
Aah!
Man: Remember, barbecue at my place Saturday night.
You're all invited.
Venus is rising early,
And you know what that means.
I'm there. Sounds great.
See you then.
Ha ha! You guys are animals.
[clicks tongue]
Good night.
[speaking alien language]
[speaks alien language]
Batman: I doubt that modification is legal.
Should have stuck to your desk jobs.
[grunting]
Superman: Need a hand?
Thanks, but I can handle this.
They don't look so tough.
[shouts in alien language]
Aah! Oh!
Unh!
[beeping]
[grunting]
[crack]
[clicks tongue]
Unh...
What happened?
You tell me.
I don't know. I-- I saw images,
Just so intense,
And then-- well, that's all I remember.
Obviously, they didn't want to leave evidence behind.
What's this all about?
Over the past few months,
I've detected several security breaches
In our global deep-space monitoring network.
And no one's claimed responsibility?
No. There's more to this than meets the eye.
I'd like to stay and look into it,
But I'm expected back in metropolis.
Another key to the city?
Here. It's a signal watch.
Call if you need any more help.
Right.
They've stockpiled enough nuclear missiles
To destroy our entire planet,
And yet they continue to build more.
We demand they stop this madness!
All, chanting: Stop the madness! Stop the madness!
Man: Weapons of mass destruction.
My people believe a lasting peace can only be achieved
By eliminating them.
Different man: Nonsense!
Those weapons are our only defense against aggression.
Is this your official position?
No. General wells does not speak for our government.
But, senator Carter, only a fool would--
General, when I was an astronaut on Mars,
I survived an experience
Which profoundly changed my life.
Looking at Earth from that distance,
I saw, for the first time,
How small and fragile our planet is.
Its fate is in our hands.
Ladies and gentlemen, that is a responsibility
We must not take lightly.
Therefore, today I propose
A bold new solution for peace,
One that would use a force more powerful
Than any before,
A force dedicated to the good of all mankind,
A force known to all as Superman!
[indistinct chatter]
With all due respect, senator,
We can't entrust the security
Of the entire world to one man.
I understand your feelings, general,
And when senator Carter first approached me,
I was reluctant to get involved.
But after meeting with him and his advisors,
I became convinced that I could make a difference.
I have fought hard over the years
To earn your trust,
And I solemnly swear to all of you
That I will continue to uphold the ideals
Of truth and justice,
Not just for America, but for all the world.
[applause]
[excited chatter]
Thank you, Superman.
Good evening. This is Snapper Carr reporting.
It's been 6 months
Since senator J. Allen Carter's
Dramatic disarmament plan was ratified.
While Superman has been working around the clock
To disarm hundreds of deadly warheads,
Public support for the plan has swelled.
Superman rocks!
Carr: Yet some remain skeptical.
Hey, the big guy's heart's
In the right place, but give me a break.
I'm the fastest man alive...
And even I can't be in 5 places at once.
Carr: Still, with more missiles being dismantled every day,
Most of us will sleep better
Knowing that Superman is watching over us.
Aah! Aah!
[panting]
[door opens]
[speaks alien language]
Ohh...
[dog growling]
[barks]
Unh!
[grunting]
[beeping]
No!
Batman!
[screaming]
[tires screeching]
[groans]
[siren]
Let's go!
Medic! He needs help!
What happened?
I'm not sure.
[gasps]
Don't even think about it.
Man: Look at the size of that thing!
Stay back. It's still hot.
[all gasp]
What was that?
Aah! Aah! Look out!
Incredible! Is it some kind of machine?
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Unh!
Man: Is he ok?
Woman: Oh! Is he alive?
Aah! Aah! Look out!
Come on, guys. Are you getting this?
We better get out of here before...
[grunting]
Aah!
[rumbling]
Whatever that thing is,
I've got to stop it.
Look!
It's not safe here. Get out.
Aah!
Are you ok?
Freaky.
Superman?
Where's he going?
Confirmed. We have visual contact.
On my mark, fire!
Man: Tactical 7.
Full frontal assault!
After hours of intense battle,
The heart of the city lies in ruins.
As the devastation continues,
The question on everyone's lips is: Where is Superman?
Meanwhile, we're getting reports
That similar objects have landed all around the world--
In Paris...
Cairo...
Malaysia.
And more are arriving by the hour.
[neighs]
Easy, girl. Easy.
These omens don't bode well, mother.
Mankind may be facing its darkest hour.
Then mankind will have to face it alone.
How can you say that?
Whatever happens beyond these shores
Is not our concern.
Here the gods will protect us.
I hope you're right.
[gasps]
[banging]
[grunting]
Batman: Hold it, Superman!
Destroying government property isn't your style.
What's going on?
See for yourself.
[grunting]
What is it?
Mankind's only hope.
He's been trying to reach out to me telepathically,
But that stasis field interfered.
When his message finally broke through, I came to rescue him.
What's he doing here?
[deep voice] the invasion.
I came to warn you,
But I was captured and imprisoned here.
They wouldn't listen.
Big surprise.
I sense you do not trust me.
Perhaps this will help.
I am J'onn J'onzz.
Don't take it personally, J’onn.
He doesn't trust anyone.
A wise policy.
We'll need to contact the joint chiefs right away.
Man: Stop right there, Superman.
You're trespassing in a restricted area.
Our orders are to keep that freak here.
Wait. I'll vouch for him. You must let us go.
I don't think so.
But the world's security may be at stake.
That's why he'll never leave here alive.