Previously on Justice League...
Superman, get away from there before it--
Green Lantern: How could this happen?
You were supposed to be monitoring the situation.
Do you want to stand here pointing fingers,
Or do you want to do something about it?
I heard something about a kryptonian.
He was being taken to War World.
War World?
Nasty place. Heavy into carnage for the masses.
Take us to this War World.
[crowd chanting "Draaga!"]
Save your cheers.
Draaga fights for honor
And for our leader the great Mongul.
Still weak.
Something in the atmosphere is sapping my strength.
Uhh!
I won't leave without you.
You've got a better chance of helping me out there. Now go!
The kryptonian-- he tried to escape.
Give him to Draaga.
Urgh!
Uhh!
Aah!
Give me an honorable death...
Here on the battlefield.
I order you to finish him.
No.
Then destroy him!
No!
[groaning, then screaming]
No, the kryptonian won.
Don't you want to see him fight again?
I gotta admit, he's a real champ.
He's more than that. He's a Superman!
Aah!
What? Still alive?
You're tougher than I thought, kryptonian,
But I doubt you'll survive another blast.
Take your best shot.
Guards!
Superman! Superman!
[crowd chanting "Superman!"]
Are they mad?
If you execute him now, it might not go over too well.
Fine.
The people have spoken.
[groaning]
What's this?
You defied Mongul.
It was great.
Hasn't anyone ever stood up to him before?
Draaga tried once, but then he decided he liked living.
After what you did, you deserve to live, too,
So we've arranged an escape.
There's this garbage scow, see?
It'll take you off planet and then--
Wait. I can't go.
[all murmuring]
I won't leave without my friend J’onn.
If you stay, Mongul will kill you.
I've dealt with others like him.
I'll take my chances.
I don't know if he's brave or just plain crazy.
Come on.
Where are you taking him?
Where the weak and defeated always go--
The pit. Don't.
But if you spare him,
He'll never rest till he's evened the score.
Do you think he'll fit on that garbage scow?
Definitely crazy.
Hawkgirl: Ow! Get off my wing!
Sorry.
Why do we have to ride in this rust bucket?
What's wrong with your ring?
Lady, the galaxy's a big place.
I need my navicomputer to find War World.
He's got a point.
Great, take his side.
I'm not taking his side. I'm just saying--
I'm wrong again.
Uh, do you two want a little privacy?
What exactly is your problem, anyway?
Your attitude, girl.
Is everyone on Thanagar as thickheaded as you?
Thickheaded?!
Why, you self-righteous, green-eyed...
Ohh!
My attitude is just fine,
Except when you're involved.
And another thing-- just 'cause you've got that fancy ring
Doesn't make you a real--
[both coughing]
Urr!
Heh heh!
What? No!
Aah!
Dump me like so much garbage, will you?
But I won't forget you, Superman,
Or the shame of my defeat.
[screaming]
You there-- stop that!
[crowd chanting "Superman!"]
Listen to them.
Why do they flock to him? Why?
Because the kryptonian is so powerful,
He doesn't fear anyone--
Not even you.
Then we must teach him fear.
Ohh.
Lantern?
Over here.
Looks like we got taken for a ride.
I knew we shouldn't trust that freak.
Any idea where we are?
Not a clue.
Great.
So we don't know where we are,
We don't know where War World is,
And we don't even know how to get back to Earth.
How much worse can it get?
My ring could get us off this planet,
But without knowing exactly where we are,
We take the risk it'll run out of power
Before we find another habitable world.
So we're stuck here. Is that what you're saying?
Maybe forever.
Just the two of us?
Oh.
Look, maybe I shouldn't have been so hard on you.
I--
Lights!
What a dump.
I've seen worse.
I'll bet.
[sniffs] ugh.
One man's trash is another man's treasure.
No stealing!
Arr!
That's mine!
Aah!
We don't want trouble.
Liar!
Aah! Uhh!
No one touches our stuff.
Hiya!
Green Lantern: No!
I'm asking nicely.
How do we find War World?
Draaga: You want to find War World?
Talk to me.
We're almost there.
Draaga, that scar on your chest...
What about it?
I was just wondering.
Our friend wears something just like it.
There it is!
It's a big place.
How will we ever find them?
Draaga: That's your problem.
Hey! Are you nuts?
Draaga!
Forget him.
J'onn and Superman are more important.
The people want fights. That's what I give them.
You're just giving them a cheap substitute for what they really need,
Like food, housing, and medicine.
No one talks to me that way.
No? That wasn't your name they were chanting out there.
It was mine.
Someone else once said that to me.
It was Draaga.
The mob loved him,
And he wanted to change things, too,
But I convinced him the old ways were best.
How? Show him.
Its power can decimate a planet.
And that's exactly what I would have done to Draaga's
If he hadn't cooperated.
I can do the same to your world.
You're too late. Krypton's already gone.
No matter. Any planet will do...
Even Draaga’s.
You can't. Oh, really?
Now listen, and listen carefully.
If you want that planet spared,
You're going to have one last fight--
Against me...
And you're going to lose badly.
Understand?
I thought so.
Announcer: Today, the fight of the millennium;
History in the making;
Superman versus the great Mongul himself.
Remember, a planet's life depends on you.
I remember.
What are you doing?
Making it convincing.
All of you hurry. We must be ready to fire.
Didn't you hear me?
His royal pain could send the order at any minute.
My lord! B-b-but I thought you were...
My plans changed.
Decommission this weapon immediately.
Decommission it? But--
Or do you think I'm being a royal pain?
No, sire. Of course not.
Good. Then do it before I--
Uhh...
Are you all right?
What?! Get him!
[crowd gasping]
Uhh! [crash]
Time to settle our score.
Wait! Uhh!
If I let Mongul finish you,
How will I ever regain my honor?
Listen to me.
You have to stay out of this.
I can't do that.
You have to,
Or he'll destroy your planet.
What?
Don't you see?
I promised to lose.
You'd sacrifice your own life for my planet?
It doesn't make sense.
Aah!
Mongul: Now, kryptonian, it's just you and me.
Haaa!
You ok?
The cannon!
Haaa!
[alarm sounding]
Green Lantern: Let's move!
[crowd murmuring]
Hear what they think of their new hero now?
Game over.
Green Lantern: Not yet.
We're going into overtime.
We destroyed his death ray.
Draaga's world is safe.
Then all bets are off.
You're mine.
Draaga: No, he's mine!
You'll regret that, Draaga.
Uhh!
Keep your guard up on the left.
[crowd chanting "Draaga!"]
This is for my people!
And this is for my humiliation!
And this is for justice!
Ohh...
Go, Draaga!
[crowd chanting "finish him!"]
No. He doesn't deserve the honor.
Then it's over.
Not yet.
Here. You should wear Mongul's crown.
Keep it. You've earned a chance for a whole new life.
What's life without honor?
I'm not worthy.
Draaga, the real test of honor
Isn't how you die. It's how you live.