Flash: Do you think we'll make it?
Green Lantern: I should have enough juice to get us home,
But my ring's going to need some serious recharging
After towing you clowns halfway across the galaxy.
Hey, at least we won the battle.
Javelin 7 to Watchtower, come in.
Batman: Watchtower here.
Prepare the landing bay. We're coming in.
Just when I was starting to enjoy the peace and quiet.
Same old bats.
Great Hera!
[groans]
[all shouting]
Ungh! Ungh!
Ungh!
[straining]
[disturbance fades, stops]
[all groaning]
What was that?
I don't know. But look!
Hey, where did the Watchtower go?
Batman, come in. Do you read me?
Batman!
J'onn J’onzz: He's gone.
And so is the Watchtower.
I don't get it.
There was no wreckage, no debris, Zippo.
How could the entire Watchtower disappear without a trace?
Perhaps we'll find an answer
When we locate the source of that mysterious pulse.
Where the heck are we?
Looks like we're home.
Wonder Woman: Metropolis.
But how?
Flash: Either the city fathers
Did some high-speed urban renewal while we were away, or--
Or what?
I don't know.
Wait.
This dude's picture is everywhere. Who is he?
Man: You, there!
Show me your papers.
What?
You heard me. Let's see your identity papers. Now!
Sorry, but my identity's a secret.
Chicks dig that whole "man of mystery" thing.
You think this is a joke?
You're under arrest.
On what charge?
Out of the way.
Argh!
Ungh! Unh! Ooh!
Unit 295, we need backup.
Ungh!
[bullets ricocheting off force field]
[aircraft approaching]
Green Lantern: Scatter!
Ungh!
[men grunt]
Ungh! Uh!
Uh-oh!
Man: Over here.
Bats?
Hurry!
Ugh!
Nice wheels.
[bullets ricocheting]
Hang on!
Whose hand is that?
Sorry.
This is too weird. Even for him.
Hey, wait up. I've got some questions.
[guns clocking]
No. I'll ask the questions.
Who are you?
Bats, you're starting to scare me.
I scare a lot of people.
The resistance might be able to use you,
But you're going to have to prove we can trust you.
Are you kidding?
You've known us for years.
You must have me confused with someone else.
I don't think he's kidding.
Listen, if we wanted to hurt you,
We would have.
Let's talk.
The storm troopers came to our house.
I was 8 years old.
And they murdered your parents. Why?
For speaking out against the regime.
Incredible.
Not really. It happens every day.
That's why I started the resistance.
[crowd cheering, laughing]
We're all orphans and outsiders,
Fighting the good fight.
How long has this regime been in power?
Since World War II.
But we won that war, didn't we?
No.
They did.
You're telling us we lost World War II?
That's insane!
The Allies invaded Europe on D-day, and--
It was a disaster.
D-day was the beginning of the end for the Allies.
I can't believe I'm hearing this.
Something's obviously happened to the time/space continuum.
Probably caused by the disturbance we saw.
But why weren't we affected?
Perhaps the aura from Green Lantern's ring protected us.
Want to share?
Have you detected any large electrical
Or magnetic disturbances recently?
We experienced some interference on our com links.
Why?
Batman: According to my sources,
The pulse emanated from here--
Vandal savage's research center.
Who's vandal savage?
You're joking.
He's everything I've been fighting against--
The undisputed dictator of this repressive regime.
Let's see what's inside.
[low, beating pulse]
Woman: It's still unstable and rapidly deteriorating.
How soon before it flatlines?
48 hours, give or take.
Just as savage predicted.
If only we could have controlled the wave fluctuations,
Practical time travel would be a reality.
[banging]
Ungh!
Ungh! Ungh!
Ungh! Ooh! Ooh!
Ungh!
[coughing]
J'onn J’onzz: Over here.
What is that?
Heavy matter, like a black hole.
They used it as a tunnel into the past.
And altered history to change the outcome of the war.
Can we change it back?
It would be risky.
We only have 48 hours before it collapses.
[beating pulse]
[loud boom]
We've got to try.
Batman: Wait.
Are you saying that my world,
My whole life, is like this because
Someone went back in time and changed the past?
That appears to be the case.
Then doing this could save my parents.
I can't promise that.
Will you come with us?
No. If this doesn't work,
Someone's got to stay here and fight.
You understand that if we do change the past,
You-- this version of you--
Will never have existed?
Nothing would make me happier.
Now go.
[muffled, echoing screaming]
[all groaning]
Where are we?
[rapid gunfire]
Great jumping Hera!
It's just like those old documentaries.
Not quite.
[rumbling]
[men yelling]
Hey, colonel Klink!
Argh!
Ungh!
[rapid gunfire]
[grunting]
[struggling]
[straining]
Unh... Ungh!
Ungh!
[all straining]
[cheering]
I feel like road kill.
[wolf whistle]
Thanks, doll!
Ungh!
I pulled this from the control panel.
Transistors?
They weren't invented until after the war.
The scientists at the laboratory
Said the hole was unstable.
Whoever left from our time
Could have gotten here months ago,
Perhaps years.
So where do we start?
[large explosion]
Those troops are getting decimated.
You help them.
I'll fly to Berlin.
I suspect the answer to this mystery lies there.
Wait.
I can't let you go into enemy territory alone.
Go, then. We'll handle things here.
Man: Mein Führer!
Mein Führer.
This just came in from the front.
Another report about costumed fighters with magical powers.
Ally propaganda.
[men murmuring]
Man: What if it's not propaganda?
What if these super men are real?
Are we prepared to deal with them?
You have a short memory, Hoffman.
You've obviously forgotten about the weapons
I've already created,
Weapons the Allies have never even dreamed of.
And more are coming...
Like this.
Argh!
[groaning]
Ungh!
Any other questions?
[loud crashes]
What now?
[sirens blaring, men yelling]
Halt!
Mind if I borrow this?
Ungh!
[groaning]
Stop him!
So long, fritz.
Ungh!
[coughing]
[gasps]
Oh...
An angel.
I must be in heaven.
You're not dead.
Are you a deserter or a spy?
I'm not sure I should tell you.
Well, I did just save your life.
Why were they trying to shoot you down?
Just between you and me:
I've got something they want.
Go on.
Word is, they're planning an invasion of England,
And I have a way of finding out when and where.
But it's not going to mean a thing unless I can get to France,
So if you'll excuse me...
And if you're ever stateside after this is over,
Look me up. The name's Trevor.
Steve Trevor.
Whoa!
Wonder Woman: It's all right.
He's with me.
You're sure?
These new weapons the Axis has-- where did they come from?
Some genius named vandal savage.
The high command was so impressed,
They made him their new Führer.
Vandal savage made these weapons?
Yeah. He's still got a lab over on Grundstrasse,
But you'll never get in. I've tried.
I have a feeling it'll be easier for me.
You're sure I'm not dead?
J'onn J’onzz: A laptop?
Man: This way. I thought I heard something.
Fascinating.
Argh!
[groaning]
Oh... Ungh.
Ungh!
Get those soldiers out of here. I'll cover you.
Can't hold them much longer.
Hurry!
[straining]
Green Lantern: Argh! Ungh!
Uh!
[rapid gunfire]
Lantern!
I'll be ok! Take off!
Go!
Ungh!
Dead.