J'onn J’onzz: Previously on Justice League...
Where the heck are we?
J'onn: Something's obviously happened
To the time-space continuum.
You're telling us we lost World War II?
J'onn: They used it as a tunnel into the past--
And altered history to change the outcome of the war.
Uh! Oof! Oh!
Agh!
Wonder Woman: Why were they trying to shoot you down?
Word is,
They're planning an invasion of England.
And I have a way of finding out
When and where.
The name's Trevor--
Steve Trevor.
Yow!
J'onn: These new weapons the Axis has--
Where did they come from?
Trevor: Some genius named vandal savage.
The high command was so impressed,
They made him their new Führer.
Lantern!
I'll be ok!
Take off!
Go!
Dead.
[gunfire]
[screaming]
Unh!
Soldiers: Unh!
Where's G.L.?
His ring went out.
He's stranded back there.
And you just left him?
I had no choice.
These men needed medical attention.
Don't you even care what happens to him?
Of course I do, but--
I'm going back.
Flash!
Man: Heads up, we've got company!
Great.
Unh!
Oof!
Ugh!
Aargh!
Radio: Allied forces counterattacking in sector 5.
Faubius-- redeploy.
G.L.!
Where are you, buddy?
Come on, this isn't funny!
G.L.!
[coughs]
[spitting]
Come on, let's go!
Ok. This time, all bets are off.
Aargh!
Ugh!
Uh! Oof!
Friends of yours?
They are now.
Raaahh!
Oof!
Ugh!
[cheering]
Thanks for the lift, angel.
I can take it from here.
If your mission's as important as you say,
I should stay and protect you.
What about your green friend?
J'onn has a way of blending in.
Yeah. Real inconspicuous.
Just like you.
Come on. Let's get inside.
Why are we here?
I'm supposed to rendezvous with a man named Ernst.
He's a code breaker. See this?
It's some kind of new communicator.
If we can break the code, we can listen in on the Axis high command
And find out when the invasion is.
So where is this code breaker?
He'll be here. In the meantime,
Let's make ourselves at home.
[gunfire]
I couldn't find G.L. Anywhere.
I still can't believe
You left him behind.
Come with me.
Do you see that?
Yeah, so?
Look again.
The casualties would have been much worse
If we'd stopped to help J’onn.
We had to make a choice.
Some choice.
Thanks for helping us out up there.
Don't thank us.
We would have shot those planes down anyway.
I've never seen an insignia like that.
What country are you from?
We're not from any one country.
Andre's from France.
Hendricks is from Holland,
Olaf comes from Norway.
And I'm Blackhawk, from Poland.
All countries occupied by the Axis authorities.
We Blackhawks bow to no authority
Until our homelands are free again.
Vive la liberté!
Are these guys for real?
We would gladly lay down our lives for our cause.
But we can't win this war alone.
How can we help?
Oof!
Man: What have we here?
Whatever he is, he doesn't look German.
Don't let that fool you.
What if he's a spy?
Man: Back off, bulldozer.
He's no spy.
I saw him in action while I was out on recon.
You a partisan?
I guess you could call me that.
The name's John Stewart.
What's that fancy ring?
Some kind of secret weapon?
Not any more-- it's out of juice.
Too bad. Seeing as how we're stuck behind enemy lines,
We could have used some help.
I'll do whatever I can.
Forget it, Sarge.
He may be a hotshot flyboy,
But he ain't a real soldier.
Uh.
Ugh! Oh!
Ow! Ugh!
Uh! Oof...
Where'd you learn that move?
U.S. Marine corps.
Why, you lousy-- oof!
Sarge: Knock it off, bulldozer.
We've got a war to fight.
There's an enemy airfield
Around here somewhere,
And our job is to turn it
Into Swiss cheese.
Welcome to easy company, soldier.
Uh...
Who would have thought
The ubermensch would be green.
Ubermensch?
The superior man.
Those destined to lead the world.
I thought that was your goal.
My only desire is peace--
Progress, unity.
With you in charge, of course.
Why not?
Under my enlightened leadership,
I can build a new world order.
All this from one laptop computer?
I am from the future, the same as you.
I am not from the future.
But this is.
60 years from now, it will be a child's toy.
But today, it's the most powerful weapon on Earth.
Where did you get it?
A gift to myself.
Greetings from the future.
You age gracefully.
You have no idea.
I have finally found a way
To open a door into the past.
And through that door, I have sent you this.
Over the last few years I've come to realize
That World War II was the last, best opportunity
For me to assume full and permanent power.
The technology inside this device
Will give you a huge advantage in the war.
And I will also give you a second advantage--
Knowledge of the future.
First, the war cannot be won
If that raging lunatic continues to run things.
He must be pushed aside.
Second, the Allies will invade Normandy on June 6, 1944.
Be ready.
Third...
Well, you get the idea.
Knowing the future,
How can I not succeed?
I've seen your future. It doesn't work.
Indeed?
How many friends did you bring with you?
What are their powers?
I'll never betray them.
We'll see.
He's yours, Josef.
Perhaps your powers of persuasion
Will loosen his tongue.
Has anyone ever held anything back from me, mein Führer?
[electrical crackling]
[J’onn screaming]
Amazing what the nobility keeps in their cupboards.
Caviar?
How can you think of food at a time like this?
I hate to see expensive stuff go to waste.
You're a strange one, Steve Trevor.
You have no special powers,
Yet you're willing to risk your life here.
Aren't you afraid of dying?
Some things are worth dying for, angel.
Besides, if I hadn't taken this risk,
I wouldn't have met you.
But the war--
The war can wait.
Right now let's just enjoy the moment.
How can we?
I found this while I was making dinner--
A good year.
Unh!
It goes all the way back to the last war.
Huh. Ha ha.
Maybe you could, uh...
[gunshot] ugh! Get down!
You are completely surrounded.
There is no escape!
How did they find us?
They must have caught Ernst.
And he betrayed you?
Don't blame him, angel.
He's just a civilian.
This is what they want.
Make sure it doesn't fall into their hands.
What about you?
I'll create a distraction.
But--
Mmh.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
There he is! Get him!
Aagh!
Oof!
Shoot her, shoot her!
[fighting and groaning]
Ahh! Oof!
Unh!
Ahh!
[motorcycle engine revving]
Unh!
Ahh! Oof!
Holy Toledo.
Uh!
Where is Ernst?
[whimpering]
This one's tougher than he looks.
I'll need my special tools.
Make sure no one goes in until I return.
Jawohl.
Man: Help me.
Corporal Florstein.
[gasp]
Man: Colonel.
Ugh.
But I ask you-- how can you run an army this way?
The old Führer was a little crazy,
But at least he had more respect for his generals.
Welcome to Blackhawk island.
We were doing routine reconnaissance yesterday when we saw this.
Some kind of factory complex.
What are they building in there?
We don't know, but whatever it is,
They're determined to protect it at all costs.
It's defended by antiaircraft batteries--
Here, here, and here.
If you can take those out,
We can cripple the factory.
Consider it done.
Take those brainbuckets down!
Wild man-- you think you could put a grenade
Into that rat hole?
Used to pitch in the bush leagues.
Got a nasty spitball.
We'll cover you.
'dozer and ice cream, hit 'em from the side.
I'll stay in the middle.
Wild man, come in from the other side.
Stewart, watch our backs.
[gunfire]
Aah!
Wild man!
Ahh!
Uh.
[screaming]
Got me in the leg, Sarge.
You'll live.
I thought you were watching our backs.
Guess you ain't such hot stuff without that ring.
Savage: Ruined!
How can this have happened?
Apparently, the prisoner overpowered
The guard and escaped.
He knows too much.
We'll have to move up the invasion.
Send out the signal immediately.
Begin operation end game.
We can't.
Why not?
We just learned that
One of our coded communicators is missing.
We think the spy took it.
Imbecile!
Get it back, or destroy it.
Uh, yes, sir, we are already working on that.
Wonder Woman: According to our friend,
Ernst is being held here.
Up in the south tower.
Do you think he was telling the truth?
I can be very persuasive.
A souvenir.
Uh!
There he is.
Unh!
Ernst.
[mumbling]
Hang on. I'll cut you loose.
You shouldn't have come here.
You can thank me later.
No, you don't understand.
Look.
It's a trap.