Announcer: Previously on Justice League...
Vandal savage is the undisputed dictator
Of this unholy regime
Since World War II.
But we won that war, didn't we?
Batman: No. They did.
J'onn: We only have 48 hours before it collapses.
Superman: Those troops are getting decimated.
You help them. I'll fly to Berlin.
Flash: Where's G.L.?
Hawkgirl: His ring went out.
He's stranded back there.
You're a strange one, Steve Trevor.
You have no special powers, yet you're willing to risk your life here.
Some things are worth dying for, angel.
There's an enemy airfield
Around here somewhere,
And our job is to turn it into Swiss cheese.
Welcome to E.Z. Company, soldier.
Hawkgirl: Some kind of factory complex.
It's defended by antiaircraft batteries.
If you can take those out, we can cripple the factory.
We just learned that one of our coded communicators is missing.
Imbecile!
Get it back or destroy it!
If we can break the code,
We can listen in on the Axis high command
And find out when the invasion is.
Steve: It's a trap!
I tried to warn you.
They know you've got the communicator,
And they want it back.
Give it to me.
What are you doing?
Trust me.
Brace yourselves!
Unh.
Keep looking. Leave no stone unturned.
Lieutenant, look!
Mein fuehrer!
News from the field.
You were lucky, Hoffman.
The stolen communicator has been destroyed.
Send out the order.
Begin operation endgame.
It's safe now.
Angel, I'm sure glad you're on our side.
Ja. Danke schön, fraulein.
You're German?
Please, believe me, we're not all like them.
I understand.
Ok. Now that they think this thing is kaput,
Let's see if you can figure out how it works.
We should be nearing the target.
There it is.
Aah! Aah!
[machine gun fire]
[men shouting]
All right, everyone! Quitting time!
[muttering in German]
You heard me! Get out!
'raus, schnell! Chop, chop!
[alarm]
[shouting]
[machine gun fire]
Arrgh!
That's the last cannon. We're clear to make our run.
Let's make it count.
Good work, Flash.
You saved all those workers.
But what were they building here?
I saw them working on that.
[straining]
Superman: A jet engine.
But this technology's way too advanced.
J'onn: It's from the future.
And I know how savage is planning to use it.
We've cased the whole area.
Maybe G.H.Q. Got some bad info.
Yeah. Wouldn't be the first time.
Or maybe the map's no good.
You're right. This hill isn't even on it.
I wonder.
You're so smart, why don't you go find the runway
With your magic ring?
Enough of that, dozer.
Sarge, he almost got us killed.
What do we need you for anyway?
You're a big man when your ring's working,
But without it, you're just-- ah!
What in blazes...
I thought so. The hill's a phony.
That's why it wasn't on the map.
[groaning]
There's your runway.
Any luck?
The code is complicated, but...
Yes. I've got it.
What are they saying?
Oh, no.
What is it?
The invasion. It's starting.
Does it say where they're going to land?
Dover, Brighton?
Britain is not their target.
They're invading America.
I'm not sure the signal is strong enough.
We've got to alert the Allies. Keep trying.
It's not too late. I can still stop the invasion.
Wait.
What if I never see you again?
Wish me luck.
Good luck, angel.
[men shouting in German]
Man: Very good, lieutenant.
No time to call for backup.
Maybe we could string some mines across the tarmac.
Too late for that. Look.
Is everything prepared?
Just as you ordered, mein fuehrer.
Excellent. I will personally lead the invasion force.
It's the big man himself.
Let's hit 'em and hit 'em hard.
[screaming]
Commandos!
Ignore them. We're not stopping for anything.
I've got a plane to catch.
You can't stop 'em single-handed.
Watch me!
He's crazy, Sarge.
Shut up and cover him.
Over here, you bums! Over here!
Did the hero make it?
Yeah. The man's got guts, I'll give him that.
Now let's show him what we're made of.
We just intercepted a message
From the resistance.
Savage has mounted an airborne invasion.
He's headed for America!
That's why he needed the jet engines.
Got to warn the good guys. Which way is west?
That way, but--
[rumbling]
What's the matter?
We're losing altitude.
Radio the others. Tell them to go on without us.
[feedback]
The radio's not working.
Find out what the problem is.
Jawohl!
Why are they slowing?
I don't know. They're maintaining radio silence.
If the fuehrer's slowing down,
He must have a good reason.
We'll follow his lead.
Man: You there!
Man: We found the problem, mein Führer--
A saboteur.
Unh!
Striker is repairing the damage.
Good.
[groaning]
Any more of you aboard?
Very well. I'm in no hurry.
It's a long way to America,
Even with these new jets.
[screaming]
Now, talk.
Talk is cheap.
[screaming]
[loud banging]
What now?
What are you waiting for? Shoot them out of the sky!
Unh!
Behind you!
This isn't going to be easy.
Wonder Woman: When is it ever?
Hunh!
Let's go get 'em.
[beeping]
The wiring is repaired, mein fuehrer.
All systems operational.
Then signal the others. Fire the afterburners.
Unh!
Aah!
They're getting away!
Maybe not.
What?
What did I tell you? Right on schedule.
Take evasive action!
You're not going anywhere.
You think you can kill me?
You're welcome to try.
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Lantern.
J'onn!
Green Lantern.
I'm sorry. We didn't have time to tell you. We lost--
No. He's here, onboard that plane.
What?
Say your prayers, savage.
Unh!
A god doesn't grovel.
Hah!
Hawkgirl?
Come on! Let's go!
[gasps]
Aah!
What took you?
I had to fix my hair.
They're turning back! We did it!
[cheering]
Shouldn't we go after them?
I don't think we'll need to.
Hawkers!
Hoffman: Savage's plan has failed.
His ridiculous air force has been utterly destroyed.
But despite these setbacks, we must fight on.
But who will lead us, Herr general?
Who, indeed?
Home sweet home...
I hope.
Batman: I should have known you'd be here.
The instruments in the Watchtower
Picked up this anomaly a few hours ago.
Batman! It's really you!
Am I missing something?
Ahem.
Uh, sorry. It's just that...
Well, it's a long story.
Hawkgirl: You're not going to believe what we've been through.
Try me.
Please keep your visit short.
He tires easily.
Thank you.
Wonder Woman: Steve?
Angel.