Previously on Justice League...
This is U.S.S. Defiant.
We are under attack and have sustained heavy damage.
We are going down.
Let it sink.
All this could have been avoided.
Come and air your grievances at the world assembly.
Negotiate for peace.
Mera, what kind of future am I making for our son?
Man: First you sink a nuclear submarine,
And then you threaten us to make peace.
Who gave you the right?
I knew we couldn't trust that fishman.
The sub's been stripped, and the plutonium is gone.
You tried to kill Aquaman. Why?
Spanish doubloons.
Where would they get coins like this?
Atlantis.
Now is the time for mighty Atlantis
To rise up and strike terror
Into the hearts of its enemies.
Orm! What treason is this?
I'm only doing
What you never had the courage to do.
I'm in charge now.
For years, I've stood in your shadow
And watched while you led Atlantis to the brink of ruin.
I'll stand no more,
And neither will your generals.
This is a battle we should have fought years ago,
But you betrayed us by siding with our enemies.
[grunting]
Unh! Ohh.
Take him away.
General Brak, ready your troops at once.
Yes, my lord.
Orm, they said my husband has returned.
Is it true?
I wish it were,
But it's only an unfounded rumor.
I've tried to be strong,
But without him...
Don't worry, Mera.
I'll take care of you
And your son.
My son?
I've already taken the precaution
Of placing him under my protection.
[gasps]
These are dangerous times, Mera.
We can't be too careful.
Where is he?
The prince will come to no harm
As long as you cooperate.
How can you do this?
I assure you I am only doing
What is best for Atlantis.
Wonder Woman: We're almost there.
Atlantis is just beyond that reef.
Don't expect them to welcome us with open arms.
Set the ship down here.
Maybe we can slip under their defenses.
Too late. They've already seen us.
If it's a fight they want, they've got it.
Wait!
Remember why we're here.
Superman: Hold your fire.
We come with an urgent message for your king.
How should we respond, general?
Destroy them.
[booming]
Green Lantern: There's your answer.
Oh! Unh!
Unh!
What? [gasps]
Behind you!
Thanks.
Aah! Aah!
[grunting]
Aah!
This way.
There it is.
Not even close.
Aah!
Oh!
Depth charges.
Unh!
[electronic beeping]
Worthless surface scum.
[grunts]
Where's Aquaman?
I thought your kind already took care of him.
No. He came back here.
Superman: We came to warn him about a plot against his life--
An Atlantian plot.
Lies and deceptions!
Aah!
I consider this latest incursion
Nothing less than an act of war.
You will be executed as enemies of the crown.
Then I will wipe out the surface world forever.
[grunting]
Oh.
J'onn, can you phase free?
No. Can't focus.
Me neither. Some kind of synaptic discharge.
Then we'll drown.
[grunting]
Your troops are almost ready to depart, my lord.
Proceed, general.
I will join you after I attend to
Some unfinished business.
[grunting]
[both grunting]
Which one will go first?
My money's on the girl.
You think?
Aah!
Aah! Oof!
[grunts]
[all gasping and coughing]
[all coughing]
[coughing]
Thank you. But why...
You believe someone in Atlantis has betrayed my husband.
I also fear for his life,
But I need your help.
Green Lantern: You've got it.
[grunting]
Orm: Enjoying the view?
Getting rid of me
Won't make the people of Atlantis serve you.
I know. That whole lineage thing
Could get messy.
Fortunately, I have a solution.
What do you mean?
[baby crying]
No!
Your kingdom is truly magnificent.
I see why Aquaman protects it so passionately.
Unfortunately, there are those
Whose ambitions would destroy it.
Get down!
[grunting]
Aah!
Stand back!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Thank you.
This fight is far from over.
[crying]
A pity.
The young prince will be yet another innocent victim
Of the surface dwellers' aggression.
[grunting]
Sadly, that will also make me
The rightful heir to the throne.
[crying]
Well, I'm off to avenge your deaths.
Orm!
[grunting]
Aah!
We've searched the entire palace.
But there's still no sign of him.
[sobbing]
[gasps]
My love, you're safe.
And so is our son.
[gasps]
Your hand...
Where is Orm?
[grunting]
His own hand.
I can't believe it.
I told you he was a madman.
Is it madness to sacrifice all
For someone you love?
Can't you work any faster?
This is a delicate operation, my lord.
It can't be rushed.
[grunting]
[beeping]
Batman: Superman, a situation has developed up at the north pole.
Thermal readings show temperatures increasing rapidly.
If that continues,
The ecological effects could be catastrophic.
Then let's check it out.
But what about the crisis here?
There may be a connection.
What do you mean?
It's the doomsday thermal reactor.
We designed it to create a polar meltdown.
What?
I had it built as a weapon of last resort--
To protect Atlantis should the surface world ever attack.
But I never armed it.
Then Orm must have,
Using the plutonium from the submarine.
If the polar cap melts,
The world will sink beneath the waves.
Everything will be destroyed.
Orm must be stopped.
Aquaman: And he will be.
I'll see to it personally.
[barking]
Superman: Aquaman! Wait!
Why do you follow?
We want to help.
This is my battle.
No one asked you to fight it.
Like it or not, we have a stake in the outcome.
We're not leaving.
Just stay out of my way.
Soldiers of Atlantis, attack!
Here we go again.
Superman, the glaciers are already starting to melt.
I know, but we've got our hands full here.
Aah!
Unh!
Huh?
Aah!
Unh!
For Atlantis!
I saw it,
But I still don't believe it.
Stay with him. We'll handle things here.
[exhales]
[ice cracking]
Aah!
Ohh.
Apparently, I underestimated you, brother--
A mistake I won't make again.
Raah!
There's not much time.
If we can't shut that down,
The entire world is doomed.
Green Lantern: I suppose this is a bad time to say I told you so.
[both grunting]
It's over.
You're right, and you've lost.
Unh!
The tide is against you.
The reactor can't be shut down.
We're too late.
Not yet.
[both grunting]
Unh!
No good.
I'll have to go inside and manually shut it down.
Inside?
Your ring-- can it protect me?
We'll find out.
No! Get away from that.
Orm! Stop!
Still you defend them.
[both grunting]
Unh!
You're not fit to wear the crown,
You weak and gutless--
Whoa!
Please, brother!
Help me!
I believe this is mine.
Aah!
Hurry, Batman.
It's shutting down. You did it.
No...
We did.
Then the threat is over.
Brak: And surely you must know, my lord,
Our loyalty belongs to you and you alone.
We never believed in Orm's plan, but your brother forced us.
The truth is we were only following orders.
Get them out of my sight.
[sighs]
I can only blame myself.
My fear of the surface dwellers blinded me
To those I should have feared most,
And it cost me dearly.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
Maybe we've all misjudged.
Perhaps.
All I want... All I've ever wanted...
Is peace and security for Atlantis.
After what's happened, it won't be easy.
I know, but some sacrifices are worth it.