[crowd shouting]
Order! Order!
We will have order!
Man: Silence!
This high tribunal is now convened.
Never before have so many put aside their differences
And come together in pursuit of a single goal.
Woman: But never before has there been
A crime so heinous, so vast,
That it had power to unite us
In grief and revulsion.
Second man: We are gathered here today to seek justice.
Where is the accused?
Unfortunately, he's still at large.
Manhunters, step forward.
This is no ordinary criminal.
Finding him and bringing him back
Will almost certainly involve great peril.
Are you prepared for that?
No man escapes the Manhunters.
All: No man escapes the Manhunters.
Show us an image of the accused.
He's a native of the planet Earth.
The Green Lantern,
Known as John Stewart.
Man on TV: Johnson kicks out to Berry
At the top of the key. He shoots!
And the marauders score again!
[all cheering]
Come on, come on!
Unh!
[tires squeal]
Man.
[groaning]
Aah!
Yo, a little help?
Over here!
Man: Time was, you could have made that shot
With your eyes closed.
Mr. McGee?
You're not in my history class anymore, John.
Call me Al.
Guess my game's a little rusty.
Well, Chris can give you some pointers.
He's my grandson.
Grandson?
You've been away a long time, John.
Maybe too long.
Back on Thanagar, you were a cop, huh?
Detective.
What's it like there?
The same as anywhere, I suppose.
There are criminals, and we catch them.
And what about when you're not catching criminals,
When you're not at work?
What about it?
Well, is there a... Hawkboy?
I'll be doing maintenance.
What? Don't you ever get lonely?
More than you could imagine.
Sorry, I didn't mean to--
[alarm sounding]
It's an incursion.
More like an invasion.
I'll notify the others.
Wonder Woman is on another case.
Superman's dealing with an Earthquake,
And Batman would only say that he's busy.
Typical. What about G.L.?
I couldn't reach him.
And real short,
Practically shaved here, but more on top, like his.
The usual.
Aw.
Looks like you got your hands full.
He's smart, impatient, headstrong.
Sort of reminds me of you.
I hope not.
John, you still got friends here, man,
Real friends.
What's bothering you?
Huh?
What in the world?
What's going on?
Get out of the way!
J'onn J’onzz: Stop!
What do you want here?
John Stewart, the Green Lantern.
What for?
That's not your concern.
Want to bet?
Hah!
Aah!
Aren't you gonna thank me?
Down, boy.
Aah!
Grrr.
[whirring]
Aah!
Hiya!
Hah!
[grunting]
[groaning]
Grrr.
Unh! Unh!
Ohh...
Why do I feel like a hockey puck?
Hawkgirl: Hah!
Aah!
Superman: Back off!
[grunting]
We thought you were busy with an earthquake.
It was just a 4.0. You mind telling me what's going on here?
I wish I--
Aah! Aah!
Flash: J'onn!
Whoa!
What's with that?
Stay here.
Whoa! Whoa!
Awesome!
Could he do that in high school?
Green Lantern: Stop!
Better late than never.
You are the Green Lantern known as John Stewart?
I am.
Your ring.
John. What are you doing?
Stay out of this.
You will come with us.
[crowd shouting]
Welcome to Ajuris 5, John Stewart.
Don't expect your stay to be a pleasant one.
What now?
With any luck, this matter
Won't require our attention.
And if it does?
I don't need to tell you how much
We've gained because of the Corps' diversity,
But sometimes, it forces us
To make sacrifices.
He was the best of us.
That's for sure, but now...
Galius.
Arkkis, Kilowog,
Good to see you.
I wish I could say the same, Stewart.
You're a disgrace to the Corps.
Get me out of here.
Hey!
Stupid robot.
No. Not yet.
What's next?
Your trial begins soon.
If I'd been programmed with emotions,
I'd almost feel sorry for you.
I sense turmoil,
A heavy heart.
I could have told you that.
He's looking at stars.
But which stars?
There.
That's where he is.
Why would he give them his ring?
It still doesn't make any sense.
John's a strange one. That's for sure.
I'm beginning to think all you humans are.
Sorry.
It's all right.
I take it as a compliment.
Initiate landing procedure.
Oh!
They're not responding to our signal.
It's clear what they want.
I say we give it to them.
No. We're not here to start a war.
Flash, take the controls.
Huh?
Hah!
Superman: Hawkgirl!
What?
Oh, that.
[all grunt]
[screaming]
"Flash, take the controls."
Does anyone ask if I know how?
[beeping]
[gasps]
Well, they say any landing you walk away from is a--
Come on! Starter! Starter!
Which one's the starter?
Yah!
Unh!
Hah! Hah!
Ugh!
Unh!
Aah!
Ohh.
I had everything under control, honest.
Uhh...
Green Lantern is close by.
That way.
There is no excuse for this horror,
And there can be no escape from punishment.
An example must be made.
[crowd exclaiming]
Oh, no.
Man: Order!
We will have order!
What is this, some kind of trial?
Apparently.
Judge: Remove the intruders immediately.
Aah! Aah!
Ugh! Oh!
Wait!
We apologize for disrupting these proceedings,
But John Stewart is our friend.
This is a public trial.
Very well.
You may take seats in the gallery.
But this tribunal will not tolerate
Any further outbursts.
Thank you, your honor.
Judge: Are you ready to call your first witness?
I am, my lord.
I call Kanjar-Ro.
[crowd murmuring]
Kanjar-Ro,
Do you agree to let us probe and display
Any and all memories you have?
I got nothing to hide.
State your name and profession.
Kanjar-Ro. I'm... A pirate.
A criminal?
Yet you come here to bear witness to another crime.
Why?
I may steal things,
But it's nothing compared to what he did.
[crowd murmuring]
Tell us about your encounter with John Stewart.
It all started with these blasters I...
Found.
I was on my way to sell them
To some rebels on Ajuris 4.
That's when he showed up.
I figured he was gonna try to stop me,
So... I shot first.
His ring tore out my engine.
Ha! But he still wasn't done with me.
He wanted to know if I was working with anyone.
I told him to turn around, see for himself.
He tried to shoot my friends,
But his beam bounced off their deflector shield
And shot toward Ajuris 4.
There, it hit a volcanic fault line,
Starting a devastating chain reaction.
3 billion--
That's how many were on that planet.
I have no more questions.
This account is most disturbing.
We will recess 20 petacycles.
Now I get it.
You wanted to clear your name.
That's why you didn't put up a fight back on Earth.
I told you to stay out of this.
That scum's an obvious liar.
Give me 5 minutes alone with him.
I'll get the truth.
Green Lantern: Hawkgirl, Flash, all of you--
Listen to me.
Nobody's lying.
Do you see that?
I did it.
I'm guilty.