Previously on Justice League...
What are you doing here?
I'm investigating a crime.
We suspect one of your amazons may be involved.
Hippolyta: I feared as much.
You see, Aresia was not born an Amazon.
She comes from man's world.
Her homeland became the battlefield
For a bloody and senseless war.
Aresia survived,
Clinging to a piece of floating wreckage.
Miraculously, she washed ashore here on Themyscira.
Then we amazons adopted her
And magically endowed her with Amazon strength.
Aresia? Diana.
I'd love to stay and chat,
But you might want to look after your friend.
Superman.
Uhh.
What is all this?
I think we have a right to know.
[coughing]
Ohh.
Hawkgirl: It's like some kind of plague,
And half the city's got it.
Batman: Yes... The male half.
[Sirens]
Emergency response units,
We need backup at 5th and Horton.
Oh...
Woman: Got another one.
Eyes glassy and nonresponsive.
So the poison only affects men?
Exactly. That's why it didn't hurt you two.
But why?
What do you have to gain from all of this?
What do I have to gain?
Look around you.
Man's world is filled with greed, deception, and cruelty.
But I'm going to change all that.
Today, we women take control.
You can't be serious.
Can't I?
Lucky I found this one,
But he's not doing well.
I'll get him to a hospital.
Wonder Woman: Batman!
You were right. It was a renegade Amazon.
I know.
I just couldn't believe
That one of my sisters could actually--
Uhh!
Woman: Look out!
[groaning]
Batman!
Wonder Woman: How is he, J’onn?
Just like the others.
Whatever they have,
It appears to be an allergen,
Not a virus.
But I can't seem to isolate it.
Still, every puzzle must have a solution.
So where do we start?
That's easy. We find Aresia.
Even when she was a child,
I sensed a bitterness within her.
She was never really one of us.
I think she fits in pretty well.
How can you say that?
Aresia's just taking
Your precious Amazon code
To its logical extension.
We don't teach hatred.
Except when it comes to men.
Aargh!
Woman: You there! Halt!
Well done.
It's perfect-- absolutely perfect.
For what?
More betrayal, more destruction?
Your highness.
You of all people should understand why I'm doing this.
No. You have violated sacred Amazonian law.
I'm sorry you see it that way.
Hippolyta: Oh!
But I've come too far to turn back now.
[Sirens]
Do you need help here?
Thanks, but we finally got this one contained.
Any remaining victims?
Just sent the last one to Gotham general.
Good work, ladies. Let's wrap this up.
They seem to be on top of things.
Impressive.
Almost reminds me of home.
Yes, but who wants to live in a world without men?
They can't possibly be that essential to your life.
Don't knock it till you've tried it, princess.
Let's find Aresia.
This is Medivac 9 requesting clearance, over.
Look out!
Aah! Aah!
I've got you, sisters.
Aah!
Great. Hurry!
Star Sapphire: Need a hand?
Relax. I'm not here to fight.
In fact, I came to warn you.
About Aresia?
She's crazy.
She wants to wipe out all the men in the world.
We noticed. Where is she?
She and Tsukuri are at the air base,
But it may already be too late.
That's the last one. All the chemicals are on board.
Good. Then there's just one unfinished matter to attend to.
Woman: And it will remain unfinished.
Oh! Uhh!
Haaa!
Uhh!
[groaning]
What took you?
Forgive our little deception.
Diana, I had Star Sapphire bring you here
So I could offer you one last chance
To join our noble cause.
Man's world may not be perfect,
But destroying it isn't the answer.
You would stand against us, your sisters?
Yes. A pity.
Aah!
Uhh!
A valiant effort, Diana, but you won't stop us.
I guarantee it.
Let her go!
You're in no position to give orders here.
Don't move! I'm warning you.
I don't want to hurt her, but I will.
Aah!
Well done, Sapphire.
Tsukuri, get us out of here.
Mother!
Diana, I found this inside.
The allergen? Has to be.
It might be the key to an antidote.
You take it to J’onn. I'll stop Aresia.
Think you can catch that thing?
It's fast, but so am I.
Almost done.
Good. We'll be at the launch site in less than an hour.
And then?
I shoot these cruise missiles
Into the upper atmosphere.
After they explode,
The winds will scatter my poison all over the world.
And I can say good-bye to some very unpleasant men
I've known over the years.
You can say good-bye to all of them.
[grunting]
J'onn, I've got a sample of-- oh, no.
The allergen-- it must have been on Superman's costume,
And when I touched it...
J'onn!
What happened?
I've lost the hydraulics.
[grunting]
How long can you keep us in the air?
I don't know. We're still losing altitude.
Then we'll have to launch from here.
I'll recompute the coordinates.
[crash]
Go see what that was!
Uh-oh. Better hurry with those launch codes.
What?!
We've got company!
You know what to do.
Aah!
You fools, don't you see?
We're not your enemy. It's the men.
They must be destroyed.
Hippolyta: You're wrong, Aresia.
Without men,
You wouldn't still be here.
After your ship sank,
You must have lost consciousness
As you drifted on your makeshift raft.
You would surely have drowned
Had the ship's captain not found you and pulled you to safety.
Valiantly he struggled to keep you alive...
Until he brought you to the shores of Themyscira.
[neighs]
But the effort was too much for his heart.
His final resting place is a simple unmarked grave.
He's the only man ever buried on Themyscira.
So, you see,
For all your hatred of men,
It turns out you owe your life to one.
Why didn't you ever tell me about this?
I didn't think it was important.
I didn't think he was important.
Maybe it's time to reconsider that.
So everything you ever preached was a lie.
Not everything.
Still, the acts of one man
Cannot redeem the sins of his kind.
They all must pay.
No! Aah!
Haaa!
Bay 2 won't open!
Try number 3!
Uhh! Ugh!
Ugh! Humpf!
Haaa!
Shut the missile off!
It's too late!
Wait! You can't leave!
I like you, but not that much.
Poor Aresia.
May the gods grant her peace at last.
How are you feeling?
Better. It's a good thing you were able to recover
Aresia's notes from her hideout.
Yes. Without them, we might never have found the antidote.
Hawkgirl: Superman and Green Lantern
Have almost finished distributing it.
If only Aresia could have learned to see
The noble qualities in you men.
Flash: I definitely could have taught that bad babe
A thing or two about guys.
Too bad we never met.
[burps]
Maybe it's just as well.