Ugh. Uhh.
Ohh!
He's down.
Well done, Copperhead.
Sss.
Grundy, be a dear and get the door.
Ok.
Hey!
[beeping]
Grr!
Man: You there!
Don't move!
Tsukuri.
Ah! Oh!
Ugh!
[men moaning]
We're behind schedule.
Shade, cover us.
We've got 3 minutes before the police respond
To the silent alarms.
Plenty of time.
At last, here it is.
Uh, what are we stealing?
Who cares?
As long as we get paid.
Let's go.
Ugh!
Ugh! Ugh!
What?
I'll take care of this.
Aah!
Oh!
Grr!
Aah!
Oh!
Tsukuri: Hyah!
Ugh!
[grunting]
[karate yells]
Ugh!
Uhh!
Not so fast.
Who are you?
I answer to no man.
Ugh!
Not even you.
[gasps]
Woman: Cranberry or cinnamon frost?
I'm leaning towards the cranberry.
That is so definitely your color.
Don't you agree, miss?
Why would anyone want to cover up her natural beauty?
Easy for you to say, Ms. Cheekbones.
What about the autumn sunset?
Impertinence?
[coughing]
Aah! It's the latest scent!
You wear this,
And you'll have to beat the men off with a stick.
Believe me, I don't need a stick.
[car honking]
Come on, I'm late for a doctor's appointment.
Keep your shirt on, lady. I'm on a break.
Men.
Hey! Aah!
Thanks.
Next time, mind your manners.
Batman: Wonder Woman...
We need to talk.
Wonder Woman: An Amazon? That's ridiculous.
I don't think so.
I managed to take this off her.
It's an Amazon design, isn't it?
Yes, but it could be a forgery.
Besides, amazons don't steal.
It's against our code.
And we never leave the island.
Never?
I know it seems complex,
But if everyone does their job,
We'll crack this place wide open.
You still haven't said what we're stealing.
More chemicals?
No. Our target's the gem depository.
It holds almost $25 million in precious stones.
Gems? Count me in.
I like her style.
A definite improvement over Luthor.
So, we're all on board?
Grundy don't know.
We need everybody, big man.
Would a little advance persuade you?
What about the Justice League?
Grundy not want to fight them again.
Don't worry your pretty little head, Solomon.
I'll take care of them.
Mmm.
Batman, I've reached Themyscira.
Now what?
See what you can turn up, and be careful.
Roger that.
Hawkgirl out.
This is a waste of time.
Whoever did this wouldn't dare remain on the island.
You may be right, but we have our orders.
A stranger.
Get her!
Wait! I'm a friend of--
Unh! Whoa!
No one escapes from Amazonian justice.
Unh!
All right, if they won't listen to reason...
Haaa! Unh!
She's getting away!
No, she's not.
Aah!
[grunting]
Now, intruder,
You'll pay dearly for what you've done.
Unh!
Are you all in position?
Copperhead ready.
Star Sapphire ready.
Shade and Grundy ready.
[groaning]
Tsukuri ready.
You all know your jobs.
I'll take out the security cameras
And meet you at the vault.
Unh!
This message is for the Justice League.
As I speak,
My friends are robbing the gem depository.
We dare you and the police
To try and stop us.
That should get their attention.
[groaning]
Mmm, sweet.
I do love sapphires.
They're so radiant.
That's enough. Take what you have
And head back to the hideout.
What about you?
I still have one last thing to do.
I'll stay with you.
No. Go with the others.
But-- do as I say.
[Sirens]
Sergeant, get your men in position.
I want this whole block sealed off before they--
[boom]
Superman: You might want to put that back.
You want this?
You'll have to take it.
Have it your way.
Ugh!
I intend to.
Aah!
You're stronger than you look, but you can't win.
Oh, really?
[coughing]
Still think so, big man?
Uhh... Ugh.
Here comes another one.
[gunfire]
Stop!
That's far enough.
Diana. Aresia?
Unh!
I'd love to stay and chat,
But you might want to look after your friend.
Ohh!
Superman.
Superman!
[groaning]
Hey, what's wrong with the big guy?
I'm not sure.
I found him like this after meeting Aresia.
Who? One of my Amazon sisters.
I thought they never let them off the island?
Where is this Aresia?
She got away.
You track her down
While I take Superman back to the Watchtower.
An Amazon, huh?
So, what now? We look for clues.
What? Like fingerprints, matchbooks,
Self-addressed stamped envelopes?
No. Like this.
We've captured the thief, my queen.
I'm not a thief.
Then you deny that you took the gold?
I'm a friend of your daughter Diana.
What are you doing here?
I'm investigating a crime.
We suspect one of your Amazons may be involved.
This is a serious accusation.
What proof have you?
Recognize this?
Have my horse made ready immediately.
That necklace belongs to Aresia.
She's supposed to be here
In solitary meditation.
Looks like she got tired
Of contemplating her navel.
Nobody's been here in weeks.
I've feared as much.
So, why was she in here?
Did she do something wrong?
No. It was the final step of her rebirth.
You see, Aresia was not born an Amazon.
She comes from man's world.
When she was but a child,
Her homeland became the battlefield
For a bloody and senseless war.
The victors were cruel
And denied even the basic humanity
Of their defeated foes.
Soon, neighbors, friends, and schoolmates were all gone.
[jet approaches]
Her family had no choice but to flee.
They eventually made their way to a refugee ship...
But even here, fate was not kind.
[cannon shots]
Pirates raided the ship
And stole their few meager possessions.
[screaming]
Aresia survived...
Clinging to a piece of floating wreckage.
Miraculously, she washed ashore here,
On Themyscira.
I found her and nursed her back to health.
Then we amazons adopted her,
Trained her...
And magically endowed her with Amazon strength.
I've often wondered if we did the right thing.
Still, how could we refuse?
You couldn't.
And now she's deserted us.
Maybe we'll find some answers in here.
[grunting]
Ah!
What is it?
Books, maps, city guides.
These things are forbidden here. Why?
We believe contact with the outside world
Could corrupt us.
It's sure starting to look that way.
J'onn: His condition continues to deteriorate.
Wonder Woman: He's practically invulnerable.
What could do this to him?
Unfortunately, there isn't much data
In kryptonian physiology,
But I'll do my best to help him.
I know you will, J’onn.
[beeping]
It's Green Lantern.
Maybe he and Flash have found something.
Diana, I need a hand.
What happened?
I don't know.
Flash collapsed, so, I brought him here to--
Actually, I'm not feeling all that good myself.
Ugh!
Lantern!
Not bad.
Be a dear and hand me those, would you?
Hey!
Why'd you do that?
Grundy not understand.
Solomon, for once,
You and I are in perfect agreement.
I want some answers.
We all do.
What is all this?
I think we have a right to know.
You're right.
It's time I showed you exactly what my plan is.
[gasping]
[coughing]
Batman: So, this Aresia is not really an Amazon.
She's an orphan.
It's hard to imagine
What that kind of trauma could do to a child.
Woman on radio: Emergency situation.
Repeat. This is air-traffic control.
All runways are full, and we've got 30 planes stacked up in the air.
Second woman: What's the nearest secondary airstrip?
I'm low on fuel.
Third woman: I've got sick people on board.
Please clear this channel unless absolutely necessary.
Woman: Unit 32 requesting backup.
Pulse is erratic. He's going into shock.
Knock down those flames
Before they hit the main line!
Aah!
It's like some kind of plague,
And half the city's got it.
Yes...
The male half.