Previously on Justice League...
When I was an astronaut on Mars,
I survived an experience
Which profoundly changed my life.
I propose a bold new solution for peace.
Carr: With more missiles being dismantled every day,
Most of us will sleep better
Knowing that Superman is watching over us.
Batman: Over the past few months,
I've detected several security breaches
In our global deep-space monitoring network.
There's more to this than meets the eye.
[growling]
Unh!
Unh! Aah!
Carr: We're getting reports that similar objects
Have landed all around the world.
I am J’onn J’onzz.
Our orders are to keep that freak here.
But the world's security may be at stake.
That's why he'll never leave here alive.
Mother, forgive me.
It's them.
Unh!
Unh...
Stay down.
Behind you!
Unh!
J'onn, are you--
[groans]
Hang on!
Get him to safety. I'll cover you.
[groaning]
Unh!
That was close.
We're not safe yet. Look.
Aah!
[straining]
What happened?
Help has arrived.
Unh! Unh!
Hawkgirl? What's she doing here?
Sorry I'm late. There was an uprising near Rigel IX.
[straining]
Hah! Hah!
Aah!
Unh!
Allow me.
Who's the rookie in the tiara?
I'm not sure.
Unh!
Thanks.
Flash: Hey, bats!
I think you dropped this.
Whoa. Where have you been all my life?
Themyscira.
Huh?
Hawkgirl: The home of the amazons.
I always thought it was merely a legend.
I assure you, it's as real as the ground on which we stand.
I am Diana, princess of the amazons.
Pinch me. I must be dreaming.
Ow!
Themyscira is protected by the gods,
But I could not idly stand by while the rest of the world was in danger.
It was lucky you showed up when you did.
No, not luck. I telepathically summoned them.
Look, I'm usually pretty quick on the uptake,
But would someone please tell me what the heck is going on here?
Diana: So, J’onn J’onzz, you came from Mars to warn us?
This is just too weird.
I've seen stranger things.
We first encountered them
A thousand of your Earth years ago.
It was a golden age.
Our Martian civilization was at the height
Of its peace and prosperity.
And then...
They arrived.
Where they came from, no one knew,
But they were determined to make our planet their own.
We Martians were peaceful people,
And the taking of any life was abhorrent to us.
But we quickly learned the ways of war.
For centuries, the battles raged on.
Every trace of our once-great civilization
Was obliterated.
We fought valiantly,
But the invaders were parasites who fed on our psychic energy.
As we grew weaker, they grew stronger.
They even absorbed our shape-changing abilities.
Finally, a small group of Martian survivors
Planned one final desperate attack.
Unh! Unh!
Aah!
[beeping]
Inside their underground stronghold,
We unleashed a powerful nerve gas which paralyzed them.
[shrieking]
The attack was successful,
But the cost was dear.
I was the only survivor,
The last of my kind.
I sealed up their citadel
To keep them in a constant state of suspended animation.
For over 500 years,
I stood guard over them,
But then, while I was in a hibernation cycle,
Astronauts from Earth unsealed the stronghold
And accidentally revived the invaders.
Flash: Wait. Those astronauts
Never said anything about finding life on Mars.
Hmm. Some pencil pusher in Washington
Probably decided it should be
Classified information.
With all the Martians gone,
The invaders had nothing left to feed upon,
So they turned their sights to Earth.
I narrowly escaped and came here to warn of the coming danger.
While I was being held against my will,
The invaders sent advance agents to disable Earth's defenses.
That's why they sabotaged the deep-space monitoring network--
So we couldn't detect their activities.
We've got to stop them before it's too late.
It may already be too late.
Carr: This is Snapper Carr reporting live
From ground zero in metropolis,
Where the alien walkers continue to clear the area around the impact site.
General wells,
Our military seems unable to stop them. Why?
All our big missiles have been disarmed,
And our self-proclaimed protector Superman has abandoned us.
Earlier,
Senator J. Allen Carter had this to say.
When I first proposed my peace initiative,
No one ever imagined we would face
An invasion like this.
Now we must stand together and resist this aggression.
Uh, wait. We have a breaking development.
Something's moving inside the crater.
Oh, my lord.
[thunder]
What was that?
It's begun.
[thunder]
What are they doing?
The invaders are nocturnal.
They want to blot out the sun so they can live in perpetual darkness.
Friends of yours?
It's no joke.
What's the big problem?
Can't you just whip up another batch of that nerve gas?
Unfortunately, no.
The gas can only be made from a rare Martian plant.
I brought a sample with me, but it was destroyed when I was captured.
Uh, what's plan "b"?
We'll have to take out those factories.
Lady, this is no job for amateurs.
We amazons are warriors born.
Want to test me?
Let's not fight among ourselves.
J'onn, we're going to need all the help we can get.
Fine. Sorry... Your highness.
Tactically, we'll have multiple objectives,
So we'll need to split into teams.
Dibs on the Amazon.
You are no fun.
This isn't supposed to be fun.
We've got a job to do,
And we will do it better without distractions. Understood?
Yeah, yeah. I hear you.
That's our target. Now, listen up. Here's the plan.
What plan? We kick their butts, right?
Let's get this over with.
[sigh]
[whistles]
Hey! Over here!
Hah! Missed me!
Aah!
Oh!
[grunting]
Fool.
Green Lantern: Hang tight, hotshot.
Huh. I'm sort of stuck here.
I hope the others are having better luck than we are.
Hiding like cowards is not the Amazon way.
They must have a weakness.
When we find it, we'll strike.
I have scouted the outer walls. There are no openings.
Then we'll make our own.
Wait. Let's see what she can do.
Hera, give me strength.
Unh!
There's your opening.
Not bad.
They run like cowards. What are you waiting for?
Hah!
Unh!
[grunting]
Hawkgirl, follow me!
Keep a sharp eye out.
I always do.
Stay back! I'll--
Hah!
Unh! Unh!
Whoa.
What? There's a time for words and a time for action.
J'onn: Of all the idiotic, boneheaded,
Glory-grabbing moves!
Haven't you ever heard of teamwork?
Uh, maybe we'd better save the motivational speeches till later.
Unh!
[coughing]
G.L.!
Uh-oh. Got to run.
They're close by. I can almost smell them.
Are you always so eager to fight?
My home Thanagar is a warlike world.
There, one must strike first or die.
[coughing]
Hang on, Hawkgirl! I'll--
Aah!
Unh!
They've blocked us off again.
It's almost as if they know what we're thinking.
Any ideas, J’onn?
J'onn!
Superman and Hawkgirl are down.
They have failed.
What? Are you sure?
I can sense it. This way. Hurry.
We lost them.
For the moment.
J'onn: Look.
It's the central core.
How can we shut it down?
The ion matrix crystal.
If we can remove that, we'll shut down the whole plant.
I'll need a diversion.
You've got it.
Unh!
Aah!
J'onn!
Batman: Get him out, now!
Unh!
Unh! Unh!
Batman!
[gunfire]
No!
Wait. There's nothing more we can do for him.
You don't mean he's--
Gone.
Hera, help us.