[thunder]
Uhh... Aah!
Aah!
As feared, tropical storm Gardner
Has been upgraded to hurricane Gardner.
Metropolis residents are warned to take immediate shelter.
Roads are open to emergency vehicles only.
Dispatcher: Ladder unit 79,
Respond to overturned vehicle at Fifth and Bryant.
It never rains, but it pours.
Out the back! Hurry!
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Woman: Hang on!
Man, that was close.
Are you guys ok?
A little worse for wear, but ok.
Girl: Mommy!
Mommy! Help!
[screams]
I've got you, little sister.
You're not my sister!
Woman: Cassie!
Mommy!
How could you run off like that?
You almost scared me to death.
Cassie: I'm sorry.
I don't know what I'd do
If anything ever happened to you.
You're my whole world.
Unh!
You're usually more careful than that.
I'm sorry. I was just... I don't know.
What's wrong?
My mother used to say the planets revolved around me.
She called me her little sun and stars.
You know, I left Themyscira against her wishes.
Maybe you should go back and set things right.
But what would I say to her?
Try the truth.
If only it were that easy.
But you're right-- I can't put it off any longer.
When will you be back?
I don't know.
[thunder]
You look more radiant than ever.
No.
Gone, mother? I didn't go anywhere.
I was in my room.
Alone. For 8 months.
Definitely not.
The world was in peril.
Would you have me stand by and do nothing?
Hera, give me strength.
Home at last.
What?
Sisters!
Philepas! Antiapi!
[gasps]
By the goddess...
Mother.
Mother!
No!
Forgive me.
I should have been here to protect you.
I should have...
Unh!
Who are you?
Niminus stektor.
[grunts]
Unh!
How dare you defile this sacred ground!
Wait!
Harm me, and the others will remain as they are--
Cold, hard stone.
Who are you? Talk!
My name is Faust-- Felix Faust.
I am a humble student of the mystic arts.
Why did you attack my sisters?
They left me no choice. I had to defend myself.
By turning them to stone?
I came here in pursuit of ultimate knowledge.
To gain this,
I must find the fragments of an ancient sacred relic.
The first piece was here on this island.
Go on.
I'll make you a deal. I'll restore your sisters
If you help me get the other fragments.
Why should I believe you?
A small demonstration.
Gravis vitae.
Uhh...
Mother!
Diana? Athena heard my prayers and sent you.
I'm so sorry, mother.
Faust: Oh, what a touching reunion.
The intruder. We must stop him.
We must!
Patropa kistes.
[screaming]
Monster! Give me that!
I need your answer.
Will you help me?
What kind of man are you?
A practical one.
You have 24 hours to bring me the rest of the fragments.
Otherwise...
Your unfortunate mother will remain like this forever.
And where will I find these relics?
These gems are attuned to the mystic vibrations of each fragment.
They will lead the way.
Heed my words, Faust.
If you break your vow,
No magic in the universe will save you from me.
I'd hurry if I were you. The meter's running.
Deep voice: Faust, why do you linger there?
A change in plans, my lord.
What?
The relics are protected by powerful forces.
Why should I risk my neck when someone else can get them for me?
If you fail me, it's not your neck
You'll need to worry about.
The prize will soon be ours
With the help of the Amazon queen's own daughter.
Batman, it's Diana.
I need some background information on a man named Faust--
Felix Faust.
He's some kind of sorcerer.
Care to tell me what's going on?
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Computer, track coordinates on javelin 7.
Menolipi. Good for you.
I always said your work was museum-quality.
[alarm]
First things first.
Why would Faust want this?
[gasps]
Great Gaia!
Unh!
[grunting]
No! Give that back!
I must have it!
I am Diana, princess of the amazons.
I won't be denied!
[grunts]
Diana, what's going on?
This is not your concern.
When my friends start tearing up museums,
It becomes my concern.
I've already alerted the others.
When they get here,
They'll want an explanation.
Of course I don't trust this Faust,
But what else can I do?
I say we go back and kick
That would-be sorcerer's butt.
No. Men are forbidden from ever setting foot on Themyscira.
Somebody should have told him that.
Besides, I gave my word
That I would find the other relics.
I'm afraid that leaves us but one course of action.
We'll have to help you.
Picture it: The sun, the sea,
Hundreds of women just like her running around,
And me-- the first man they've seen in...
Oh, maybe forever.
Oh, and look what I brought--
Iced mochas for everyone.
Sweet.
I fail to see the attraction.
Man, you really are from mars.
Perhaps we should concentrate on finding the relic.
No problem.
See? That was easy.
Or not.
There must be some mistake.
No. According to the gem, it's in there.
It's like some kind of temple.
Yes, for those who worship their credit cards.
How could any female wear such ridiculous garments?
You got me.
Superman: There it is.
Why would it be buried here?
I don't know. I'd say it's been here a very long time.
Someone went to a lot of trouble
To make sure these pieces were never disturbed.
Aah! Aah!
Superman?
[snarling]
Diana... What?
What have you done with Superman?
Answer me!
[roars]
[screeching]
Ohh! J'onn!
You're toast!
You ok?
You get the relic. I'll take care of the rest.
Remind me to never get on your bad side.
Unh!
Man: Professor Erlich?
No conferences without an appointment.
See my secretary if-- aah!
Ohh...
Tell me about Faust.
Foul demon!
Unh!
Raah!
[screaming]
Diana?
Diana, it's me!
Unh!
Diana, stop. It's an illusion!
[roaring]
[grunting]
I won't ask again!
[groaning]
Where's Superman?
[gasps]
I tried to tell you.
[groaning]
Superman, I'm so sorry.
What kind of horror have we unleashed?
Deep voice: Where is she, Faust?
Where is the Amazon princess?
Try to have patience, my lord.
Patience?!
I have been patient for over 3,000 years!
Forgive me.
I simply meant that the relics will soon be here.
I feel it in my bones.
And then, lord Hades, the world will be ours.
Indeed it will be.
Indeed it will.