Announcer: Previously on Justice League...
Something's not right here.
Green Lantern: The Streak, Tom Turbine, Green Guardsman--
They were the stars of my favorite comic book
The Justice Guild of America.
Ray, the decoder rings.
Consider yourselves honorary members of the Justice Guild.
Tom Turbine: I have long hypothesized
That there are an infinite number
Of parallel dimensions,
Each containing its own planet Earth.
Don't worry, friends.
I will toil night and day
Until I discover a way to get you home.
Aaaaah!
A sudden dizziness-- so strange.
I propose a contest.
Each of us will see who can pull off
The most spectacular crime.
The winner will earn the honor
Of devising a plan to destroy the Justice Guild.
Hawkgirl: "here lies Scott mason,
The Green Guardsman"?
No.
It's true. I saw the grave.
But it doesn't make any sense.
Hawkgirl: Look, I don't know who that is,
But the real Green Guardsman is gone,
And so are the rest of them.
No. I don't believe it!
He seemed to take this quite personally.
I'll bring him back. Wait here for Flash.
Gentlemen, that's why I lead the league in steals.
Don't be so fast to toot your own horn, sportsman.
Then it appears we have a hat trick.
That leaves Dr. Blizzard out in the cold.
Man: Not quite.
I'd say this entitles me
To victory in our nefarious contest,
Don't you agree?
Bravo.
To the victor goes the spoils.
It was nothing, my friends.
[grunts]
What are you going to do now, doc,
Turn us into snow cones?
Oh, no.
I have bigger plans than that--
Much bigger plans.
Still no word?
I'm afraid not.
[telephone rings]
Maybe this is it. Hello?
The Injustice Guild has just robbed
The Seaboard City mint.
Now they're escaping by blimp.
Only they would commit such a heinous act, and on a Sunday!
Thanks for the tip, sergeant.
We're on the case.
The inJustice Guild's on the move.
Then we should be, too.
Together: Let justice prevail!
John, I'm sorry.
You were right. They're gone.
All of them.
Then who are those people
Back at the mansion?
Robots? Clones?
I don't know,
But I intend to get some answers.
[whistling pop goes the weasel]
Stop!
[tires screech]
What can I do you for, folks?
What can you tell us about those graves on the hill?
Sorry, I've got to finish my route.
Can't keep my customers waiting.
What customers?
I noticed you before.
You never stopped.
Business has been kind of dead.
When's the last time you actually sold any ice cream?
Please, no more questions.
He might hear you.
Who?
I can't say any more.
[truck playing pop goes the weasel]
Have a nice day!
[tires screech]
Curiouser and curiouser.
[tires squeal]
Up there.
I'll let the air out of their balloon.
Not so fast, Guardsman. Look.
[both grunting]
Holy hostages!
Cue the orchestra.
[plays two notes]
Aaaaah!
[gasps]
Fore!
[coughing]
Guardsman: I've got you, old chum.
Presto change-o.
Aaaah!
Ooohph!
It's true what they say:
Television is bad for you.
[grunting]
Looks like it's up to me.
[tires screech]
[tires screeching]
All: Aaah!
Oooogh! What was that?
Oooogh!
Don't bother welcoming me aboard.
Get him!
Oooh! Uuugh!
The library?
I want to bone up on my history.
Hello?
Blank.
What?
They're all useless.
Aaaargh!
Let's check the newspaper archives in the basement.
Right.
[flips switch]
Why am I not surprised?
I've had enough.
Haaaah!
Ladies first.
Hawkgirl: A subway station?
Must have been an Earthquake or something.
No.
These are battle scars.
You're right, and look at the date.
40 years ago.
The same day as the last Justice Guild comic.
Prepare to be foiled, cat man.
Yeaaaah!
Aaaah!
Oh!
En garde.
I'll have you free in a jiffy.
[grunting]
It's no use. We'll never get free.
Want to bet?
Decorative and functional.
Uhhn!
Aaaah!
All: Whoa!
Oooh!
Whoa!
Aaaaah!
Flash!
Gotcha!
[gasps]
You two need a lift?
Ooh! Oh! Oh!
We've sprung a leak.
I can't control it!
Cat man: Then it's time to bail.
Wait! What are you doing?
Stop! Stop!
Uuuugh.
Whoo-hoo!
That was amazing--
When Black Siren fell and Flash caught her,
And then Cat Man knocked Sir Swami off the blimp.
Gosh, that was the best battle yet.
Indeed.
The city's in your debt, Justice Guild.
Just doing our job, sergeant.
Take them away.
[engine purrs]
[tires screech]
Is it just me, or are those two
The only cops in this town?
Then, at the last second,
Green Guardsman flies in and...
[imitates explosion]
Some friends.
It's a good thing the Justice Guild
Was around to save me.
They're not the Justice Guild.
Say what?
You heard me.
They are not the Justice Guild.
How can you say that?
This is a serious accusation, young man.
Explain yourself.
No. You explain this.
"Justice Guild killed in battle"?
It's a hoax.
Some kind of sick joke.
It's no joke.
The real Streak, Green Guardsman,
Tom Turbine--
They're all dead.
I've seen their graves.
He can't be serious...
Can he?
I don't know. It sounds fantastic, but--
[telephone rings]
Hello?
Justice Guild, we need your help.
A monster's tearing up main street.
You must hurry.
We're on our way, sergeant.
We're needed downtown.
We're not done here.
But Seaboard City needs us.
Haven't you noticed that nothing here makes sense?
Library books with blank pages,
Ice-cream trucks that never stop.
Dangers that spring up whenever someone gets too close to the truth.
What truth?
That your world is an illusion,
A living memory of a civilization
Destroyed 40 years ago
When the Justice Guild gave their lives for this Earth.
That's why they stopped publishing
The comic book in our world.
No more Justice Guild.
And any time someone starts to figure things out...
Nuns and dynamite.
If what you say is true,
Who or what is creating this illusion?
I suggest you ask Ray.
Ray?
Why would I know anything?
Because you are the source.
No!
[all gasp]
You ruined it.
You ruined everything.
Aaaaah!
That's it.
I officially want to go home.
Justice Guild, attack!
No!
Don't! It's an illusion.
He's the real menace.
Take that, monster.
Green Lantern: It's over, Ray.
It's been over before. I changed that.
Aaaah! Aah!
Haaaah!
Aaah!
This is my world.
I decide who wins and who loses.
Uuaaah!
Aaaaah!
Aaaaaah! Aaah!
Ha uh!
Uh!
Aaaah! Ugh.
[snarling]
[Green Lantern groaning]
Green Lantern: Aaargh.
The Justice League needs our help.
Wait. If what they said is true,
Defeating Ray could destroy this reality and everything in it.
Including us.
[Green Lantern groaning]
[Ray giggles devilishly]
[groaning louder]
We died once to save this Earth,
And we can do it again.
[groaning]
You'll be sorry you messed things up.
Aaah! Oooh. Ugh.
What is this?
In Seaboard City, crime doesn't pay.
Aaaah! Oooaaah!
You can't. I made you.
All: Let justice prevail!
[grunts]
Yaaah!
Aaaaah!
Stop!
Eeyaah!
Black Siren: Aaah!
Yaaaah!
Uuuugh!
Ooomph!
Uh!
[snarls]
[grunts]
Oooorgh!
[groaning]
Huh?
Whoa.
Aaah! Uugh. Aah!
Aaah! Aaah!
[Ray grunting and groaning]
Yaaaaaah!
No.
Uh. What happened?
He couldn't maintain the illusion.
The strain was too great.
But how did he get like that?
Martian Manhunter: The radioactive fallout
From the nuclear war mutated his DNA,
Giving him the psychic ability
To mold this world to his choosing.
So he chose to recreate it
With the heroes he worshipped as a child.
Who could blame him?
Listen.
[car engine]
[truck playing pop goes the weasel]
You're all real?
It's like waking up from a dream.
Green Lantern: I'm sorry. We destroyed your world.
No. We did that.
But now, all that's left is this nightmare.
Being stuck in an ice-cream truck for 40 years--
That's a nightmare.
Compared to that, rebuilding our world
Will be a piece of cake.
Thank you for giving us back our future.
[all murmuring]
Can't believe that's over.
So what now?
How are we supposed to get home?
I have an idea. Come on.
Remember when Tom Turbine said
He had been working on a transdimensional gateway?
It's possible that--
Yes! There it is.
What good's that going to do?
He was never able to find a way to power it.
True, but maybe I can.
[explosion]
I don't know how long I can hold it.
Go!
Flash: You should have been there.
It was so freaky--
Those cornball villains with their bad puns,
And the heroes with the decoder rings.
What's up with that?
Still, Black Siren was a hottie.
Where's G.L.?
Are you ok?
It's stupid, really.
Why should I feel like this?
I mean, they weren't even real.
They gave their lives for us.
That's real enough for me.