Announcer: Previously on Justice League...
This is the end of an era.
The end of your era, maybe.
Ack! Uhhh! Ohhh!
My tests indicate you have a rare form of blood poisoning.
It's terminal.
Lex: Cheetah, Sapphire, Grundy,
Glad you could make it.
And of course, you all know the Ultra-Humanite.
You will all be paid most handsomely
If you can do one simple job--
Destroy Superman and the Justice League.
Hyah! Aah!
[groans]
That venom almost killed you. So?
So, you're staying here.
You're the only one of us without special powers,
But you don't need to prove yourself.
Aah! Ugh!
Ohh...
Joker: Wakey, wakey, Batman.
Batman: Joker.
I should have known you'd be in on this.
Really? Ha! I must be falling into a rut.
You're not going to leave him like this, are you?
Why?
Hello?!
He's still alive.
And he's going to stay that way
Until I say we don't need him anymore.
Lex, Lex, listen to someone who knows.
[whispering] Don't wait. Do it now.
You don't like my decisions? Leave! Oof!
And they say I'm crazy.
What?! Those restraints are pure titanium.
He'll never get loose.
And that stasis field
Will prevent the Martian from locating him.
Now, Batman, you must have some kind of pass key
Or access code I can use against your friends.
Where is it?
Guess.
Grundy?
Ugh!
Oof.
I told you.
Shut up!
Bring that upstairs. I'll get it open.
Ohhh.
Humanite, Grundy, watch him.
Grundy,
What's Luthor paying you for this?
Money-- lots of it.
As much as he's getting?
I don't know.
Look at all you've had to put up with.
You should be getting more.
More than me? Preposterous.
Is it?
[growls]
[engine whirring]
Fascinating.
Careful.
Just because you won't live to see old age
Doesn't mean the rest of us don't want to.
[booming]
What was that?
[grunting]
[booming]
I should have known.
[grunting]
Humanite: Unhand me, you worthless zombie!
[groaning]
Grundy: Take that back!
Lex: Stop it right now!
You imbeciles are killing me faster than the kryptonite.
Both: Sorry.
You did this, didn't you?
Well, it won't happen again.
Cheetah!
Take over here.
If our friend causes any more trouble,
Gag him!
[hisses]
[groaning]
What's wrong?
You don't look so good.
Maybe we should get paid now.
I'm fine.
Now get out!
I've got work to do.
Humanite: They're right.
You don't look good.
Can't give up now.
I just need to buy more time.
Can't you help?
Perhaps, but...
But what?
It will cost extra.
[groans]
I keep telling you, I don't know anything.
I'm just an innocent--
Flash and Copperhead: Victim of circumstances.
Yeah, yeah, we know.
Copperhead, when are you gonna get some sense
And tell us where Luthor is?
Ooh, this must be the part
Where I get so scared I spill my guts.
I'm warning you!
What are you gonna do, boy scout,
Short my sheets?
Give me a wedgie?
Guards!
Take him back to the holding cell.
Hasta la vista. [hisses]
That went well.
How does Batman do it?
And then what happened?
My research opened whole new worlds.
There was so much to do.
But so little funding.
You know about that.
You didn't have enough for research subjects,
So you used yourself.
And now I'm a freak.
That's not what I see.
I see someone who was willing
To give up everything
For a cause she believed in.
How do you know so much about me?
Let's just say cats aren't the only ones who are curious.
Too much curiosity can be dangerous.
Maybe... I like danger.
Do you?
Try me.
Mmm.
She's been down there too long.
Forget it. There's no way
I'm going to leave you alone with him.
But, Lexy, where's your sense of fun?
Besides, it won't cost you a cent.
Humanite, go relieve cheetah.
Can't you send Grundy?
Just do what I say.
It's your funeral.
[engine powering on]
Finally!
Hey, what are you looking for--
Batcar keys, batbreath mints?
[electric sizzling]
Ooh!
[giggling]
Careful, you idiot!
Wait. This is it.
What?
The key to our victory.
Grundy: Whoa!
Grundy not like heights!
Hang on. We're almost there.
[alarm beeping]
What?
Intruders.
[alert sounding]
[grunting]
Oof!
Well done, Grundy. Shall we get to work?
[grunts]
Still no word from J’onn?
Not since he sounded the alarm.
Something's wrong up there.
I can feel it.
Then let's go!
Joker: Show time, everybody!
Live and in color,
The end of the Justice League.
Don't make me laugh.
Ha ha ha! It's no joke!
There's a surprise hidden in your little clubhouse.
And once your chums get there... Kablooey!
Popcorn?
Oh, well, more for me.
Joker, you nauseate me.
Ohhh!
He's going to miss the show
And the sequel.
What sequel?
After the bomb gets your friends,
I get you!
[cackling]
[groaning]
Flash: J'onn!
He's out cold.
What could have happened?
I'll take him to the medical bay.
You find Batman.
[device beeping]
Any minute now.
Any minute.
And then we get paid, right?
Please, can't you let me savor this one moment?
Sorry.
Hawkgirl: We've looked everywhere.
Batman's gone.
And so is the shuttle.
[telephone rings]
That must be him. Hello?
I beg your pardon? Where?
Hello? Hello?!
What did he say?
It wasn't Batman.
It was someone saying there's a bomb up here.
Must be some kind of joke.
No, this is serious. That's a secure line.
Then what are we waiting for? Spread out and find it.
Nope.
Zilch!
Nada.
Unh!
Not here.
Upper levels are clear.
Nothing on this deck.
Keep looking.
Wait. I've got a thermal pattern.
It's faint, but...
Flash!
I'm on it!
Unh!
Yes!
No!
It's not fair. They should be cosmic dust!
Unh!
Luthor, calm down. Your condition--
What do you care?
You're just a bunch of incompetent,
Money-grubbing crooks!
That's it.
I don't know about the rest of you,
But I'm out of here. Me, too.
Wait! I'll double your pay.
What's the point? It's over!
No. We can still win if we lure them here.
I have a plan, but we've got to stick together.
Grundy not that dumb.
All right then, triple!
Batman's still not answering.
J'onn: It was Star Sapphire,
Grundy, and the Shade.
I saw them coming, and then everything went black.
How could they have gotten in?
Only one way--
With Batman's transmitter.
Oh, they ruined the punch line.
But I can still have my fun.
Oh!
Ugh!
Not funny, bats!
Ooh!
Luthor not want you alone with him.
Oh, come on, Grundy, old pal.
What's a couple of nicks between friends?
Go away.
Party pooper.
Batman: Thanks.
If you hadn't come along when you did...
Could I have some water?
Ok.
Grundy: Hey!
Thanks.
Uh-oh.
Batman, thinking: J'onn, can you hear me?
I know where he is.
[engine powering on]
[beeping]
[screaming]
Ohh!
Will he be all right?
This containment unit should stabilize his condition.
The next few minutes will tell.
Mr. Luthor?
Batman broke that... Static thingy!
He's probably already contacted the Martian.
They'll be here soon.
What are we gonna do?
Lex: Don't panic.
We'll be ready for them
Once we get rid of the traitor.
Traitor?
Lex: Think about it.
The only way they could have found the bomb is if someone told them--
One of us!
Fortunately, this old place still has
Functioning surveillance cameras.
No, I didn't! I wouldn't!
You can't think--
Get her!
Ugh! Oof!
Unh!
Hello, kitty.
Aaahhh! Unh!
And they say I'm not a team player.
Lex: Grundy,
The pretty kitty's all yours.
Unh... [gasps]
No, it wasn't me.
You've got the wrong one!
Wait! [grunting]
Now, let them come!
There!
Batman's definitely inside.
And so are the rest of them.
Green Lantern: Then it's a hostage situation.
They may try to use him as a shield.
Not if I can help it. Wait!
[whispering] Batman?
J'onn, don't!
Aaahh!
Ohh!
Lex: And so, it begins.
Time's up.
Now we do it my way.
[Hawkgirl yelling]
Unh!
Oof!
Ahh!
Ugh!
Oof!
One down.
Ugh!
Oof!
Ugh! Oof!
[grunting]
Catch!
Mama!
Ugh!
Ahh!
Oof!
Ugh! Oof! Unh! Ugh!
Duck!
Unh!
I tried to warn her.
Lights out, Shade.
Unh! Oof!
Oh! Ahh! Oof!
[grunting]
Whoa!
Oof! Oh!
Enough!
Where's Luthor?
Right here!
Unh!
And I'm going to enjoy every moment of this.
[groaning]
Why so surprised, Superman?
It's a basic rule of business--
Turn every weakness into a strength.
[Superman screaming]
Of course, that's a lesson
You may not live to appreciate.
Neither will you, Lex.
[screaming]
Ooh...
Et tu, Humanite? Oof.
Green Lantern: Don't move!
I surrender.
Whoopsie. Time to run!
But there's still one unfinished piece of business.
What?!
Unh!
Oof! Oh!
No fair!
How'd you get free?
I could have escaped anytime,
But I thought I'd stick around
To keep an eye on you clowns.
Oof! Oh...
You're despicable.
[sighs]
Wait!
You'll keep our bargain?
Yes. Double what Luthor was paying.
Flash: What was that all about?
[opera playing]
[groaning]
Humanite!
You'll pay for this, you turncoat!
Do you hear? You'll pay!
TV announcer: This program was made possible
By a grant from the Ultra-Humanite
And viewers like you.