(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
SINESTRO: Prudence, intellect, strategy.
They've never been your strong suits, Jordan.
Don't count me out yet, Sinestro.
(GROANS)
WONDER WOMAN: Lantern, this is Justice One.
We're entering your quadrant. How's it going?
GREEN LANTERN: Oh, you know. Could be better.
I don't know how he's doing it.
Sinestro's ring should be drained dry by now.
Sort of like mine is.
WONDER WOMAN: Hold on. We won't be long.
(RUMBLING)
SINESTRO: You think you can hide from me?
- (GRUNTS) - No power. No protection.
What do you have left, Hal?
A charming personality, a great haircut,
and abs so good, you can wash your clothes on them.
What's the plan?
Superman and I distract him
while you get the battery to Green Lantern.
(BEEPS)
(GRUNTS)
(BEEPING)
Good-bye, Jordan.
You were an adequate foe.
(GRUNTS)
Ah, Superman.
It will be an honor to destroy you.
(LASERS FIRING)
(GROANS)
G.L., you okay?
Yeah. Right.
Here, your lantern battery.
In brightest day, in blackest night,
no evil shall escape my sight.
To all who worship evil's might,
beware my power. Green Lantern's light!
(EXCLAIMING)
This is the best the mighty Justice League can do.
I thought you'd at least offer me a challenge.
(SUPERMAN YELLS)
Ah. Fully loaded.
So how come you need to recharge and he doesn't?
It seems like his ring is more powerful than it's ever been.
We need to find out how he's doing it.
Hey, get me close enough and I'll get inside and check it out.
(GRUNTS)
(WHOOPING)
Uh-oh.
Time to shrink.
Ah. My safe place.
I know many of you had to take time
out of your busy schedules to be with us today.
But after Atom destroyed Sinestro's power and saved the universe,
we just couldn't let that go unnoticed.
Without further ado, let me introduce the Atom.
- (CROWD CHEERING) - Wait. What?
Thanks. I'm not sure I remember exactly how...
I mean, just a moment ago, wasn't I...
-(LAUGHTER) -(STAMMERING) And you were... I mean, I...
(GASPS)
(CROWD LAUGHING)
What's happening to me?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RUMBLING)
Old Man Miller's dog!
Puddles!
(GRUNTING)
GREEN LANTERN: Atom, can you hear me? It's Hal.
How's it going, old buddy? Better?
(ATOM YELLING)
What? That good, huh?
G.L., what's going on?
I thought we were fighting Sinestro.
GREEN LANTERN: We are. The ring's yellow energy is playing on your fears.
You can't let it. Don't give in.
Yeah, dude. Everything is so real.
(GROWLING)
(GROANING)
(ATOM GRUNTS)
Ow.
(BARKING)
I forgot how mean that sucker was.
(PANTING)
(GROWLING)
- (EXCLAIMS) - (BARKING)
GREEN LANTERN: Atom, whatever it is, it's not real. You know that.
Yeah? Tell him.
(YELLS)
WONDER WOMAN: Implosion torpedo initiated.
(GRUNTS)
Okay, this guy is really ticking me off.
(YELLING)
GREEN LANTERN: What's going on in there?
I don't know what's happening.
I'm shrinking to a sub-atomic level.
I've never gone this small. I can't control this.
GREEN LANTERN: Atom. Atom. Listen.
The Yellow Ring's power is fueled by your inner fears and nightmares.
What you're seeing isn't real. You have to calm down and relax. Trust me.
Right, right. Okay. Focus.
Just calm down.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
(POWER PULSATING)
- Looks like you were right, G.L. - What do you mean?
Well, this doesn't look like any fear or nightmare I've ever had.
There's energy emanating from...
A giant yellow lantern battery.
GREEN LANTERN: Oh, that's why Sinestro has unlimited power.
The lantern battery is charging him from inside the ring.
MALE VOICE: Sinestro.
What the?
MALE VOICE: We have an intruder.
It's the Atom.
SINESTRO: Go after him.
GREEN LANTERN: What's going on?
I don't know if the Yellow Ring
is messing with me again, but, uh...
There's a giant spider mushroom thing
with what appears to be a yellow ring inside of it
and it's coming right towards me.
GREEN LANTERN: Spider mushroom? Yellow ring?
(GASPS) Atom, that's Despotellis.
He's one of the deadliest soldiers from the Sinestro Corps.
Run!
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLING)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(STRAINS) Oh, no, you don't.
(GRUNTS) What's this?
Oh, no. G.L., he's squishing me.
G.L., help! Please help!
(YELLING)
Atom, you still there?
Atom?
Can you hear me?
Sinestro, the intruder is dust.
The little pest is gone, Jordan.
But don't worry. You'll all be joining him shortly.
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
ATOM: I didn't think spider mushrooms gave up so easily.
Intruder, you are alive. Show yourself.
ATOM: Oh, I can't.
I'm actually too busy changing your chemical make-up from a sub-atomic level.
No!
ATOM: (LAUGHS) Oh, yep! That's gonna hurt.
(GROANING)
ATOM: You know, I really gotta thank you.
I actually didn't think I could shrink this small.
Stop! (GROANING)
ATOM: Do you need to lay down for a little bit?
(STRAINING)
What is this?
(GROANING)
ATOM: Whoa! What was that?
I feel like I got hit by a train.
Atom, you're alive?
Yes, I am, Mr. Jordan. You mind shooting me some oxygen?
(CHUCKLES) Sure thing, buddy.
What's up, guys?
I got our culprit right here.
Little spider mushroom fella.
Spider mushroom? I'd say he looks more like a crab fungus.
Oh, I don't know. Might be more of a squid pickle.
Really? Hmm. I'm thinking more
of a moldy, pineapple cockroach.
The name's Despo... Oh, never mind.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)