(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROWLING)
(GROANS)
Thanks for the assist, partner.
I didn't see Parademons in today's weather forecast.
I traced the battalion's energy signature when they deployed.
That's 12 for me.
On Apokolips we vie to see who can down the most enemies.
Do you not do the same?
No.
(GROWLING)
(GROANING)
58, but who's counting?
(GROWLING)
- 59. - Show-off.
Be warned, these Parademons were followed by a singular entity.
- Darkseid? - Possible.
But one squadron doesn't sound like Darkseid.
Darkseid's inner circle is legion and mighty.
It could be anyone...
Steppenwolf!
(GRUNTING)
Excellent, Superman.
As powerful as ever.
That's good.
What's this about, Steppenwolf?
It's about you, Kryptonian.
And your utter defeat at my hand!
(CHARGING)
Behind you!
BIG BARDA: He took Superman!
BATMAN: But where?
You can waste all day shooting at me, Steppenwolf.
Not this day, Kryptonian.
We'll see about that.
That's it, Superman,
burn through your body's precious energy.
Hardly the ferocious heat vision I expected.
What... What have you done to me?
Your body is a solar battery for the yellow Sun of Earth, Kryptonian.
But we are no longer on Earth.
Behold!
You are betrayed by your own biology.
And by my own genius.
Yes! Thrash and flail!
The more energy you expend...
(GROANS)
The faster you descend into powerlessness.
Once I beat you,
I will forever be the warrior that bested Superman!
Even Lord Darkseid will be impressed.
Don't count on it!
(GRUNTS)
Argh!
If you were any kind of "super man,"
you would face me!
How's this for "super?"
(ROCK CREAKING)
Argh!
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(FLUTTERING)
Fetch me my Astro-Harness!
I will hunt him, I will find him,
and I will break Superman,
before this red sun sets.
Welcome to Apokolips.
Steppenwolf's starscape maps are compiled in his war room.
There, in Darkseid's citadel.
(THUNDERING)
Just like home.
(GROWLING)
Demon dog! Get behind me!
(WHIRRING)
(STRAINED GROWLING)
Boo.
- (WHIMPERING) - That's one for me.
BIG BARDA: You said you didn't keep count!
Pa was right, "Once a scout, always a scout."
(GROWLING)
Sensors indicate the canyon dead-ends to a lake.
He won't be far.
I thought this was between you and me, Wolfie.
I didn't think legends needed help.
Spread out! Find the Kryptonian!
(BLASTER FIRING)
(CRASHES)
Two down.
(GROANING)
A tactical blunder, Superman.
You've squandered your head start.
I've had my fill of your feeble traps.
(ROCKS FALLING)
Now I'll bring this entire mountain down upon you.
Up, up and away.
There. Steppenwolf's war room.
Give me five minutes.
Wait.
(GROWLING)
If they spot us, they'll alert the entire citadel.
I'll count to three.
One. Two.
(GRUNTS)
That's one. To my two.
Hundreds of planets earmarked.
- All under a red sun. - That's bad.
MAN: Well hello, intruders.
You mistakenly thought you could hack
- the impenetrable system of... - Batman, no! He's...
Virman Vunderbar!
Short.
It seems that while my partner crushes Superman,
I have to deal with my own infestation of heroes.
Where is Steppenwolf?
(GRUNTS)
- (BIG BARDA SCREAMING) - (VIRMAN VUNDERBAR LAUGHING)
My newest invention, the kinetic force shield.
Your back will break before my device does, my dear.
- Argh! - Barda, the field is kinetic. It matches oncoming force.
You push, it redirects your own energy to push back.
But what about...
Erm, what are you saying? Whispering? That is so rude!
(SCREAMING)
Hey, what is this?
Just testing how long your shield can last, Vunderbar.
Fools! My device can last forever!
(CACKLING)
Maybe under kinetic impact, like punches. But I'm guessing
it won't work as well against steady pressure.
- Like say, solid rock. - (GRUNTING)
I'll repeat the question. Where did Steppenwolf take Superman?
(EXCLAIMS) All right, all right,
you're correct! I'll tell you everything! Don't let me squish!
No way! I get this one. I did the heavy lifting.
You cannot hide from me.
(GRUNTING)
(LASER SCANNING)
(BEEPING)
You will not deny me my immortality, Superman.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
Are you mad? We'll both crash!
(STRUGGLING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTING)
Ahh!
(GRUNTS)
(BONE CRACKS)
(GRUNTING)
I win, Kryptonian.
The entire universe will know the name of the man who destroyed Superman.
(SCREAMING)
(MOANING)
Pretty. But I still prefer yellow.
(WHIRRING)
Ah, good. I was wondering how I was gonna get home.
Wait, you defeated Steppenwolf, without powers?
And I... (GRUNTS) Broke my leg.
Hurts, doesn't it?
It really does.
- What was the final tally? - We tied.
Two to two.
I got three.
Half a day under a red sun and he still beat us both.
That's why they call me Superman.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)