(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Okay, we're here, Professor.
Just in time for the important thingamajig-y.
The new Metropolis University Science Building dedication ceremony.
(SIGHING)
PROFESSOR STEIN: I'm curious to see who the guest of honor is.
It is my pleasure to bring out our guest
and newest faculty member, Dr. Michael Holt.
No!
Also known as Mr. Terrific.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
So cool. He's the only Justice Leaguer we never worked with.
Consider yourself lucky.
I don't know why he didn't just call himself "Captain Ego."
- (SIGHS) - (GRUNTS)
This is so great, and I'm so humbled to be here today,
dedicating the new Mr. Terrific Research Center.
(CHEERING)
Oh, he's humbled. Someone take a picture.
Not only will this be a new home
for my ingenious T-Spheres,
but a place where young minds can totally revolutionize science.
Just like I did a few short years ago.
(CHEERING)
Blah-blah-blah, me, blah-blah-blah, spheres.
Blah-blah, not listening. Let's go.
Mr. Terrific is an Olympic-level athlete,
a master martial artist,
and has doctorates in engineering, physics, law, psychology,
chemistry and mathematics. He's terrific!
Ha! What an appropriate name!
I'm gonna be sick.
What is up with you?
(SIGHS) We were roommates in college.
I was a grad student and he was a 14-year-old prodigy.
A 14-year-old scheming, conniving prodigy.
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
(CROWD CHEERING)
I'm sorry, what was that?
It will mean a whole new world for everyone.
But mostly for me.
MAN: Huh? What?
Oh, I recognize you. Calculator.
I've been sitting on the sidelines
crunching numbers for too long.
Now, it's time to play ball.
(BEEPING)
No.
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
Ah!
(GASPING)
FIRESTORM: Uh, everybody, heads up.
Lot of high fructose corn syrup in those but, uh...
The heat of battle! Whoo-hoo!
(CALCULATOR LAUGHING)
(LAUGHS FALTERINGLY)
You think you're just gonna take his T-Spheres and run?
I don't think so!
(CALCULATOR LAUGHING)
(FIRESTORM GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(CALCULATOR LAUGHS) Oh!
Nice hustle, kid. You're Firestorm, right?
Yeah. Terrific to meet you, Mr. Great.
Wait, stop, I'm sorry. (IMITATES REWINDING) Reverse that. (CHUCKLING)
Martin Stein's in there with you, too, huh? How's my old roomie?
I still have hives from those cats you weren't supposed to have in the dorm!
Oh, he's great. "Lovely seeing you," he says.
I did not.
(CHUCKLING) He's ecstatic.
MR. TERRIFIC: Gotta hand it to Calculator, he's clever.
I can't locate my T-Spheres by any conventional means.
It would have been impossible to cloak my "S-Cubes."
I'm sorry, your what cubes?
Cubes? You gotta be kidding.
He's not bringing that up. Please don't bring that up.
Come on with the cubes, man.
She was mine, mine, mine, and he took it!
Not so loud. Ugh! How did I become the adult in this?
Now, what's this all about? Really?
Stein is crazy.
He thinks I stole the idea for my T-Spheres from his science project.
I just think it's quite a coincidence
that he happens to invent his ridiculous globes
while I was developing my magnificent S-Cubes in the very next room!
Okay, yes, I got it. It's very clear. But...
- (SIGHS) - What exactly are S-Cubes?
My cubes. So beautiful.
They were a perfect blancmange of form and function.
Like stepping stones to the sky.
MR. TERRIFIC: Those things were as elegant as a brick.
(YELLING)
- You take that back! - Terrific?
You know he could hear you.
He can hear, but he doesn't listen.
My designs were totally different.
He can't accept that we were working on similar concepts, independently.
FIRESTORM: Um, did someone forgetsy to pay the billsy?
MR. TERRIFIC: It's happening over the whole city.
PROFESSOR STEIN: Isn't he observant?
You can just tell he was a prodigy.
They've connected themselves to the power grid.
- They're shutting everything down. - Why?
Don't encourage him to talk, Ronald.
No power, no security.
The Calculator can send the T-Spheres into any bank
and government installation and take what he wants.
CALCULATOR: Correctamundo, Mr. Wonderful.
How great minds think alike.
CALCULATOR: Ha! I'm not there. I'm over there.
Ah, where'd I go?
Well, it looks like you're losing all your marbles.
(YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
Wait, what? Dr. Stein?
Ronald.
That, uh, wasn't part of my calculations.
(YELLING)
Let me go!
RONALD: Hey, come on. Hey, guys. Guys, you're stretching my shirt.
You're stretching my shirt.
Ronald!
Wow, you've gotten old, man.
Look at all that gray.
Never mind that. How did he split us up?
The T-Spheres can hack into any system.
They saw Firestorm as just another system to deprogram.
Huh? They can do that?
That's... Phew. That's pretty impressive.
Thanks. Yeah, they're pretty great.
I ought to get that in writing.
But it still won't help us find your friend.
I think I know what will.
RONALD: Look, you got the wrong guy, man.
I'm just a typical, but great-looking, teenager...
Obviously, look at me, let's take a pause. All right, back.
Who was just walking by, and these things just grab me up like an appetizer.
You don't fool me.
You're one half of the hero Firestorm.
Wait, what? That's ridiculous. You believe these things?
I would never burn my hair.
Glad that's sorted out.
So, I'm just gonna pop back home,
where, you know, I'll grab you a latte, of course, and I'll fetch...
Intruders?
Intruders? No, no, no. He said your sprinklers are broken, so...
I'm just gonna watch some things here, and, uh, you go check that out. Coolsie?
Coolsie.
- Maybe in Gotham you don't signal but in Metropolis... - Yeah, yeah!
I programmed my cubes to follow your spheres' tachyon emissions.
(LAUGHS) That's pretty slick for an old guy.
Respect, man.
- They seem to lead to that building up ahead. -(BEEPING)
(BEEPING)
- What are you doing? - Just adding a couple upgrades.
The "Terrific" touch.
You always had such an ego. Does it ever stop?
I had to talk big because I had to room
with the smartest student on campus,
and he was always putting me down.
What choice did I have?
(EXPLOSION)
(EXCLAIMS)
Keep going. I'll get their attention.
Sorry about this, guys.
(GROANING)
(EXCLAIMS)
Gotta pick up some ice packs.
RONALD: Professor?
Ronald? Are you okay?
Yeah. You know, just hangin'.
I guess my S-Cubes were no match for your T-Spheres, after all.
The game's not over yet, Martin.
CALCULATOR: Au contraire, T-Man.
One click of my... Ow! (EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTING)
As I was saying,
one click of my controls and that sphere will blast you to oblivion.
And I estimate your chance for escape will be zero!
(DIALLING TONE AND LONG BEEPS)
Zero!
Oh, this sphere, right?
I think I know what's wrong.
Hey, Prof, what are you doing?
It's a long drop.
Professor, that sounds like a first-team, starting line-up bad idea.
It's the only way, Ronald.
Here I come!
Not in the face!
Reunited, whoo!
And it feels so good!
(CALCULATOR GRUNTS)
Wanna hear my calculations for you?
(CALCULATOR GROANS)
Fifteen to 20 at Stryker's prison.
I've severed Calculator's control over the T-Spheres.
Gotta change their programming so they can't be hacked again.
Wouldn't mind your help, Martin.
Ronald. Please tell him that now I realize
the schematic of his spheres are completely original.
Uh... The Prof says he's sorry about being such a bonehead.
I didn't say that exactly.
I feel for you, kid. Martin may be brilliant,
but he's a terrible roommate.
PROFESSOR STEIN: I'm a terrible roommate?
Ask him about the dirty dishes,
the cat hair, the burping and the firecrackers!
I haven't forgotten about the firecrackers!
And don't get me started about the bathroom etiquette!
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)