(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROUND RUMBLING)
(GRUNTING)
This is crazy.
(GRUNTS)
No kidding.
When we heard there was a breaking at the Watchtower,
who expected the invaders to be toys?
(GRUNTING)
(RAPID FIRING)
(EXPLOSION)
Their weapons are real enough.
(RAPID FIRING CONTINUES)
Who's supposed to be on watch? (GRUNTS)
(ALARM BLARING)
Mmm-mmm. Mmm-mmm. Mmm-mmm. Mmm-mmm.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(EXPLOSION)
(SUPERMAN GRUNTS)
- (THUDDING) - (GRUNTING)
(CRASHING)
Ha! Got you, Beetle.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
Huh?
Aren't you supposed to be guarding the tower?
I am.
- (EXPLOSION) - (CRASHING)
Uh-oh.
- (GRUNTING) - (EXPLOSION)
(WONDER WOMAN GRUNTING)
BATMAN: You play rough.
WONDER WOMAN: We didn't have toys when I was a child,
but there was a Cyclops.
(BEEPS)
Better late than never.
BATMAN: Where have you been?
He was gaming, again.
Blue Beetle challenged me online.
I've only been playing...
Whoo! That long?
So, who do we have to thank for all this fun?
It's a little too playful for the Joker.
I bet if I interface with it, I could tell you.
(SQUEAKING)
SUPERMAN: I think I know.
It's my old maturity-challenged enemy,
Toyman.
TOYMAN: Superman, you do remember me?
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
That's my special Star Sparkle Super Puddy.
FDA approved, for humans.
Kryptonite.
- (AIR HISSING) - (GRUNTS)
Huh?
What?
(GRUNTS) Hey! I can't move.
We've been given accessories.
And Toyman is redecorating the training room.
FLASH: No way.
It's Boulevard Brawler 2.
Which is?
A popular fighting game,
where contestant battle for street dominance.
Robin plays it all the time on the Bat-computer.
That's what I was playing upstairs!
(CHUCKLES) It is addictive.
TOYMAN: Addictively awesome.
I should know, I'm the Boulevard Brawler master.
(RHYTHMIC BEEPING)
(BEEPS)
(RHYTHMIC BEEPING CONTINUES)
(DISCO MUSIC PLAYING)
(LAUGHING)
- (MUSIC PLAYING STOPS) - I don't like this.
(BEEPING)
(CRACKLING)
(WIND BLOWING)
CYBORG: See why it's popular?
The fighting is so realistic.
And the moves are so responsive.
- Best combo system ever! - Best combo system ever!
Sorry.
Whatever you're doing, Toyman, you need to stop now.
Please! You will fight till the finish for my enjoyment.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) Now who'll be first?
Yo, this game has two players.
How about a little friendly competition?
Oh, sure, I'll let you play
and you take advantage of the situation
to free your friends.
How stupid do you think I am?
I thought you were the guy in control here.
Maybe all that trash-talk about being the master
was just you flapping your gums.
You disappoint me, man.
That's it! It's on, tin man.
(VINTAGE VIDEOGAME MUSIC PLAYING)
Shall we play?
Okay, first we have to...
Dibs on Superman.
GAME VOICE: Superman.
Hey, not fair.
Fine, I'll go with...
GAME VOICE: Batman.
Oh, come on!
Batman doesn't have any powers!
Not that he needs any.
TOYMAN: Okay, Brawler brats, it's game time.
Truth, justice and the American way.
- (CHEERING AND APPLAUDING) - What did I say?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
I am Batman!
- (CHEERING AND APPLAUDING) - I am Batman!
- (MONITOR BEEPS) - I am Batman.
Just getting used to the buttons.
I don't think I can hold back.
I know.
We have to put our faith in Cyborg's skills.
(KNUCKLES CRACKING)
GAME VOICE: Round one. Ready?
Fight!
- Super-punch! - Bat-swing!
(SCOFFS) Bat-kick!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Fist of justice.
(GRUNTS)
Super charge.
- Watch out. - (BEEPS)
Smoke bomb! Use my Super-move.
Can't, you got to charge up your Super-meter first.
Rules are rules.
Deal with this, dork Knight.
- (BEEPING RAPIDLY) - And spread.
Hey, Superman can't do that!
Justice charge!
(GRUNTS)
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Batman, move!
Now!
Kryptonite...
Ring punch!
(GRUNTS)
You just carry that with you?
(JEERING)
(JEERING STOPS)
GAME VOICE: K-O. You win.
- I win! I won! - (CROWD CHEERING)
(CLEARS THROAT) I mean, we win.
(LAUGHS) We, we win.
No, you don't, metal-head!
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
GAME VOICE: Here comes a new Challenger.
(RAPID BEEPING)
Ha!
(GRUNTING)
In a world of ordinary men,
I am Wonder Woman.
I kind of like that.
GAME VOICE: Ready? Fight!
Wonder-punch.
Wonder-kick.
Batarang!
BATMAN: Smoke bomb! WONDER WOMAN: Lasso of Truth!
WONDER WOMAN: Wonder-punch! BATMAN: Batarang!
- Batarang! - Wonder-punch!
- Lasso of Truth! - BATMAN: Bat-swing!
- Kick! - Wonder-kick. Wonder-kick.
- Wonder-kick. - Batarang!
(WHIRRING)
- Bat-swing, Batarang! - Wonder-punch, Wonder-punch.
Bat-kick!
- Wonder-kick! - (GRUNTS)
Ah, shoot!
(SNIGGERS) Now I've got you.
(GRUNTING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
- (BATMAN SCREAMS) - (GRUNTS)
Bat-kick! Bat-swing!
WONDER WOMAN: Lasso of Truth.
- Wonder-kick. Wonder-kick. - Batarang!
Wonder-kick. Wonder-kick.
- Wonder-punch. - (RAPID BEEPING)
Bat-swing!
Wonder-kick. Wonder-kick.
- Wonder-punch. - Smoke bomb.
- Batarang! - Wonder-punch!
Batarang! Batarang!
Wonder-punch.
- (BEEPS RAPIDLY) - Why did you pause it?
I just want to say,
this is the most epic match
of Boulevard Brawler 2 I've ever played!
- I know, right? - Huh?
They say you're only as good as your opponent,
and I have to admit you're a magnificent challenger.
You're not bad yourself.
BATMAN: We can hear you.
Maybe it's time we raise the age for new members.
It's unfortunate your friends will be the real losers.
Un-pause.
- Super time! - (BEEPS)
Oh, no.
- Amazon rolling thunder! - (BATMAN SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
GAME VOICE: K-O. You win.
Robin's better.
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
See what happens when you mess with the master?
Wait, don't I get another player?
- You did! - Sorry, spoilsport.
Game's over.
'Cause you can change the rules.
I was right about you from the start.
You're just a big baby.
(BABY CRYING)
As a matter of fact,
there is one hidden player available.
GAME VOICE: New character unlocked.
You know what the problem is with sore losers?
They can get a lot more sore.
(BEEPS)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
What is going on?
I've actually been playing two games at once.
One with you,
and the other with him.
(WHIRRING)
He's overridden my controls!
How?
CYBORG: I interfaced with him,
it just took a while to get him here.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(EXPLOSION)
(GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMING)
Good game, Toyman.
Boo-yah!
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)