(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
- (ALARM BLARING) - COMPUTER: Warning.
Plant security breached.
Nuclear core compromised. Evacuate, all personnel.
Evacuate, all personnel.
- (RUMBLING) - (ALARM CONTINUES BLARING)
(GROANS)
BATMAN: There's an incident at the Hudson Nuclear Power Plant.
A group of unknown origin has infiltrated the central core.
It's 10 minutes from total meltdown.
Are any of you close by?
I'm in the middle of something halfway across the world.
I'll never make it in time.
Me neither. I'm a couple of galaxies away.
It'll take several hours for me to get there.
Hold on a second.
There has to be someone close enough
to get there in time.
Flash, no one can get a hold of.
Green Lantern is in another galaxy, same as you.
Martian Manhunter... Well, he's on Mars.
Wait, it looks like somebody might be on their way.
Who is it?
According to the database, he has the power
to control matter at the atomic level.
He sounds perfect.
Just one thing, he's a teenager.
He talks to himself a lot.
The kid calls himself Firestorm.
Fasten your seatbelt, Professor Stein.
(CAMERA FLASHING)
'Cause the heat is on!
The heat is what?
The heat is on! Whoo!
Yeah, that's our new superhero catchphrase. Pretty cool, huh?
What's not cool is this power plant.
By my calculations, it's in the final phases of meltdown.
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
Yeah, the Firestorm is up to bat and saves the day.
The heat is on! Whoo!
I'm sorry, I'm just... I love saying it.
It's crudely put, but, yes.
Oh.
(ALARM BEEPING)
It really takes us back, huh, prof?
That's right, Ronald.
Back to when I built this plant,
I just brought it online when thieves invaded looking to steal plutonium.
FIRESTORM: Grabbing a kid on a fieldtrip for a hostage,
mainly me. You know, even though I was just a high school junior,
I was no slouch in a fight.
Till I stopped fighting fair.
Then there was the big boom.
You and I wind up fused together,
the world's first nuclear-powered superhero!
The heat... I'm just kidding. I'm not gonna do it.
But I like saying it. I mean, that would be appropriate
for the timing, to do it.
(GROANS)
Careful! That's radioactive steam.
It was radioactive steam.
Now it's pine-scented air freshener. (SNIFFS)
Hmm. Let's see. A hint of cinnamon. Interesting.
They're in the nuclear core! Said they'd blow everything sky-high!
And they are...
Freaks! Monsters! Get out! Get out!
Let's meet these freaks face to face.
(JOYFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
How do you do, little youngster?
Oh, welcome to our happy home.
And who are you guys, exactly?
You can call me Dad.
And this gorgeous gal right here is Mom.
Quite the looker, huh?
Oh! Oh, you. He's terrible.
These are the twins, Biff and Sis.
Hey.
Do you know who that is? Firestorm, the nuclear man.
I've seen him on TV. He's dreamy.
- Gotcha! - MOM: And that's Brat and Dog.
DAD: Together, we're the Nuclear family.
Okay, this is cute, really, but you can't be here.
We are talking maximum wipeout.
Oh, not for us, silly.
She's telling the truth, Ronald.
They're androids, and dangerous ones.
What? You mean robots?
(GASPS)
He said the "R" word. Naughty.
We prefer automated Americans.
Sensitivity, dude.
Sis, our friend here needs a lesson in manners.
Yes, Dad.
Careful, Ronald, don't underestimate her.
What? She thinks I'm dreamy.
Sweet dreams.
(GRUNTS)
Ronald, listen to me.
Way ahead of you, Prof. I'm gonna take on those rust buckets in full power!
No, I'm trying to tell you...
That this is the toxic waste vault?
Yes.
And I just ignited those chemicals. Awesome.
Ronald, rise and shine.
(GRUNTS) I'm always shining, I can't help it.
Wait, where are we?
We're in my memory.
In addition to sharing a body,
we also share combined mental images...
Uh, real quick. Am I dressed appropriately for this?
No one can see you or hear you.
We're at a test I witnessed several years ago
conducted by Dr. Eric Shanner.
Shanner opposed nuclear warfare
and built the Nuclear family
to show the terrible effect of that power on ordinary people.
Only he built the androids too well.
They absorbed the blast power and escaped.
They've been at large ever since.
Okay, right, right. So you're saying it's up to us to stop them. Got it.
- Let's do this. - Yes, I would be saying that,
except that our combined physical form
has been unconscious for hours
and by now, we must certainly be
their prisoner.
Can you, Prof, be wrong for just once?
- Not a chance. - Ow.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, there, Sparky.
Nothing like a good old-fashioned pool party. Am I right?
Why are you doing this? I mean, there's better ways to barbecue
than by causing a nuclear meltdown.
(LAUGHS)
Good one, Sparky. Uh, can I call you Sparky?
Uh, no.
It's like this, Sparky.
For as long as we've been a family,
Mom, the kiddos and I...
Well, we've been wanting a little place we could call home.
Oh, it was so hard living on the run.
Squatting in fallout shelters and hazardous waste dumps.
Certainly no way to raise a growing family.
Then, Dad brought us here.
Isn't it awesome?
And now, we're gonna blow it up.
Ka-bluey!
Wait, but that's gonna wipe out half the state!
Sure, it'll be a little toasty for the folks outside,
but here's the good news.
We can finally live in peace in a radioactive wasteland.
Our radioactive wasteland.
(GRUNTS) Nothing's gonna go ka-bluey if I can help it.
(GROANING) What happened?
Interesting. The androids have connected us to the main reactor.
The more you struggle, the more power the reactor absorbs.
Okay, so how do I break free?
A super charge to the fuel rod pool might do it.
Say, from one of the androids?
Uh, I don't see any of them jumping in the pool to play Marco Polo.
(GASPS) Well, maybe...
Squirrel in the pool!
Dog! No!
Good boy!
(ALL SHOUT)
Don't freak, don't freak, the pup's okay.
- (GROWLS) - Ow! You're welcome.
What do we do, Dad?
I didn't want it to come to this.
Seeing as how our powers make us keen to Sparky and all,
but, uh, spank him.
Honey, we can still blow the reactor
if you give the core one of your famous blasts.
(KISSES NOISILY)
Just watch me cook.
My power is thermal pulse.
It can raise the temperature higher than a nuclear reactor.
In other words, the heat is on!
Ah, it sounds so lame when he says that, am I right, Prof?
(BOTH GRUNT)
What's going on?
Ah, no reason to fight fire when I can absorb it!
Leave my brother alone!
You're next, small fry.
Not fair! Mom!
In a minute, sweetie.
(BEEPING)
Huh?
- Good heavens. (GRUNTS) - (THUDS)
(GRUNTS)
You're no match with the old masters, Sparky.
(SHOUTS)
(WHIRRING)
(ALARM BLARING)
Ahhh!
(GRUNTING)
Dad? If our powers really do make us related,
well, let's be like other families and hug it out!
(ALL GASP)
What happened to the androids? Did you destroy them?
No, I didn't have the heart.
I mean, at the end of the day, all they really wanted
was a little place to call home.
So I gave it to 'em.
WONDER WOMAN: Powerful and compassionate.
That goes a long way in my book.
Just so he's not too soft on criminals.
Superman? Wonder Woman? Batman?
Am I in trouble?
I can fix that. Yeah, I'm gonna need some duct tape.
All right, I need, like, a lot of duct tape.
We saw the end of your fight. You did very well, Firestorm.
Even Batman was impressed.
We feel you could be a candidate for the Justice League,
if you're willing to work with us first.
Whoa! The Justice League? (STAMMERS) That'd be awesome.
What do you say, Prof?
Well, Ronald, what can I say, but...
The heat is on.
Yeah, that's the spirit, Prof! High... (STAMMERS)
Uh, headbutt, let's headbutt.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)