(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(RAPID GUNFIRE)
Oh, please.
It would take a millennia for your petty weapons to hurt me.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
And I do not have that kind of time to waste on you.
(BEEPING)
Make time.
Batman.
I thought they'd send someone more challenging.
Surrender, Luthor. (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
Give it your best shot.
Gladly.
(RUMBLING)
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
(GRUNTING) Quickly, go, go!
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
I think you're through, Luthor.
You would, you dunder-headed troglodyte.
(BEEPS)
Nice try, Luthor.
But I've played this game.
(INHALING)
(COUGHING)
Power down, before we rip off the suit for you.
Oh, uh, you and what army, Batman?
SUPERMAN: This one.
Back so soon? (CHUCKLES)
I am baffled you made it back at all.
Ugh.
(GROANS)
Superman.
What's the matter, Superman?
Did my gas leave a bad taste in your mouth?
(LAUGHS) It's so vile and fun. Still fun.
It's not good.
He remains unconscious and his vitals are dipping.
Something is taking down Superman from the inside.
It's actually quite fascinating, if you think about it.
What is it?
It's a nanobot swarm. Really nasty bugs, too.
They're constructing a colony in his heart.
Gross, right? Luthor's no slouch.
These guys are harvesting the solar energy stored in Superman's cells.
Ready for more bad news?
Here's their queen.
She's single-handedly birthing an army.
WONDER WOMAN: I saw this in a movie once.
And she wasn't a good mother either.
We stop these bots and take out their queen.
To do that, we're gonna have to go inside as a surgical team.
LEX: Now this is my kind of medical show.
Live streaming from the bloodstream. (CHUCKLES)
Look at those vitals plummet.
According to my calculations, Superman will be finished within the hour.
Teatime.
We'll need these to travel through the bloodstream.
(STEAM HISSES)
These devices will allow me to extend my shrinking power to you.
I wish I could bring you along, Red Tornado,
but this tech doesn't work well on robots.
Story of my life.
Also, fun fact.
This device can't keep you microscopic for any longer than 30 minutes.
And if we're not out by then?
Then it's gonna get awfully cramped inside the Man of Steel.
Okay, if everyone's ready, we'll have to get small.
(BEEPS)
Laser sword with just a pinch of kryptonite energy.
Great for hacking through super nose hairs.
- WONDER WOMAN: Is that... - Yep. Super booger.
Big one, too.
- (BEEPS) - Get down.
Ugh. I am sending Luthor my dry cleaning bill.
Ugh. This is awkward.
Ha. At least you're not dating him.
What did you say?
Uh, we should get going.
BATMAN: We'll take the sinuses into the lungs and get into the bloodstream from there.
Going down.
(MACHINE TRILLING)
(PULSATING)
That's the machine sucking up Superman's solar energy.
Then it's time to operate.
(GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
(GRUNTS)
Say goodbye to your little friends.
(GRUNTING)
(CRACKLING)
It's working.
His vitals are ticking upwards.
LEX: Impossible.
How is he convalescing?
(MACHINE BEEPING)
Of course.
He must have some tiny assistance.
Well, I'll have to do something about that, won't I?
ATOM: Toss those parts into the bloodstream
so his immune system can dissolve it.
Their queen is close.
You think she'll mind if I don't curtsy?
There she is.
Mother of the year.
(CHITTERING)
(GROWLING)
She's leaving. Was it something I said?
Bet she's looking for a safer nesting ground.
BATMAN: We can't lose her.
We only have five minutes left.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Bad guy here. (LAUGHS)
Anybody home?
(RED TORNADO GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(SHUDDERING)
I thought that would knock the wind out of you.
-(DEVICE BEEPING) - The Watchtower's been breached.
LEX: Unconscious.
Unprotected.
How unfortunate for you.
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GROANING)
What was that? A seizure?
It's Luthor.
He's in the Watchtower.
I'll go. We need all your power to catch that queen.
You'll only have three minutes.
Let's move.
- Big mamma up ahead. - (SCREECHING)
(GRUNTS)
(MOANING)
(BOTH GRUNT)
Holy Aeolus. Who turned on the fans?
BATMAN: We're in his lungs.
We've got less than two minutes to get out of here.
(GRUNTS)
Back off, bug.
(SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING)
I should've known Superman's breath was super fresh!
LEX: You won't take this from me, you little nut.
(INHALES)
His immune system is attacking us.
(GRUNTS)
It thinks we're a disease.
(BEEPS)
(SCREECHING)
(WONDER WOMAN GROANING)
(STRAINING)
Now, to disinfect this place.
(GRUNTING)
(CRACKLING)
That's one disease that won't be coming back.
We've got less than 15 seconds.
It's too far. We'll never make it.
Maybe this'll help.
(GRUNTS)
How can one infinitesimal imp cause such big problems?
(SUPERMAN GROANS)
(SNEEZING)
(ALL GRUNT)
You've just been quarantined, Luthor.
(GROANS)
(SNIFFLING)
Uh, what's going on here?
Isn't anyone gonna say anything?
Yeah.
Gesundheit.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)