(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(BEEPING)
BRAINIAC: Triangulation complete.
Target sighted.
Observation. That could only be Superman's secret hideaway.
It has all the charm of a Kryptonian condominium.
Oh!
And here comes the doorman now.
(BEEPING)
(GRUNTS)
(WHIRRING)
(POWERING UP)
A Superman robot.
Inferior.
But not even the real Man of Steel
will stand between me and what I am here to retrieve.
You're telling me there's an entire city, with real people in there,
- breathing, eating, shopping? - Mostly shopping.
Actually, the city of Kandor was famous for its massive shopping center,
the Mall of Krypton.
It's the capital of my home planet,
before Brainiac miniaturized it.
Hopefully, we'll change all that.
The Kryptonite's set,
there's just enough to weaken you
so that my white-dwarf tech can take effect.
At least, in theory.
Then let's do it.
You sound in a hurry.
I'm going home, Cyborg.
(BEEPING)
ATOM: System's up. Kryptonite assimilated.
Initiating white-dwarf transfer.
(WHIRRING)
Cellular absorption at 60%, 90%...
And the big, blue boy scout is going Smallville.
How do you feel?
Excited.
Be sure you bring back
all the tissue samples I requested.
If we're gonna return Kandor back to normal,
we have to test its molecular stability.
Remember, Kandor's artificial red sun
means you'll be entirely without superpowers once you enter.
There is no threat to me there.
The only kind of hunters down there are bargain hunters.
(WHOOSHING)
(CHIMES)
BRAINIAC: Hello, there.
I'm, ahem, just returning for
a little overdue maintenance.
(BEEPING)
(RUMBLING)
- Easy. - (CLANGING)
(BEEPS)
- Chancellor Al-On. - At last, we finally meet.
My fellow Kandorians, a son of Krypton returns.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Intruder, identify yourself.
(SCOFFS) More fodder. You know what to do.
(CLANGING)
(GRUNTING)
I suppose it's all going well,
or we would have heard something.
-(GRUNTS) - You know the saying, Atom. Don't sweat the small stuff.
(RUMBLING)
I thought this place was supposed to be a fortress!
(GRUNTING)
Life-forms recognized, Atom and Cyborg.
The two of you will surrender the Bottle City of Kandor.
You got faulty data, Brainiac. This is the Bottle City of...
Cleveland.
Beep, beep, error. You are lying.
You will now pay.
Atom, the bottle!
(GRUNTING)
Atom!
Deploying concussive explosive.
(GRUNTING)
(CLINKING)
Oh!
Falling is arrested. Kandor is preserved.
At last.
My collection is complete.
No, not again.
Not if I can help it.
Observation. Superman absent.
Reaction. My visit is well timed.
(STRAINING) Must move.
Can't move.
Very embarrassing.
Atom, you're okay!
Oh, yeah. When someone points a disintegrator at me,
I make it a policy to duck.
Now, let's go get Kandor back.
I got news for you Tiny,
Brainiac's blast was some sort of advanced EMP.
Even if you could get me on my feet, I'd just fall on my face.
I need time to reboot.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Until then, I'll have to improvise.
When I get back to my laboratory,
I will add you to my collection.
Permanently.
(GLASS SQUEAKING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(BEEPING)
Superman?
(CLANKING)
ATOM: Kandor, now!
Negative.
(GRUNTING)
(METAL CLANKING)
Uh-oh!
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(RUMBLING)
Give me Kandor.
(CRACKING)
(GRUNTS)
Mmm-mmm, negative.
(STRAINING)
- (GRUNTING) - (THUDDING)
Where is Cyborg?
(DIAL-UP MODEM TONE)
(YELLS)
(BEEPING)
(LAUGHING)
Huh?
- (RUMBLING) - Whoa!
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(SHIVERS) Great Ra.
What is this chill?
Gratitude noted, B3.
Let's get it home before...
(BRAINIAC GROANS)
Give me the bottle now!
Terminate the pest.
(GRUNTS)
Observation. The bottle has lost an accessory.
(BEEPS)
No!
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(CLANKING)
Hee-yah!
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(EXCLAIMS)
(GROANING)
Boo-yah! Back in...
Action?
(GROANS)
Groan.
CYBORG: Aw!
Looks like I missed a party.
And your bottle looks more like a snow globe.
(CHIMES)
(CHUCKLES) You know what they say about the weather in Kandor...
"If you don't like it, wait five minutes."
- (APPLAUSE) - (CROWD CHEERING)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)