(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(WEAPONS FIRING)
(CRASHING)
(GRUNTS)
What is Hive planning?
BEE: I'm not gonna tell you.
The Hive master is gonna detonate a cobalt fusion bomb.
- Where is it? - It's in the Metropolis...
(GRUNTS)
(THUDS)
Greetings, Wonder Woman.
Hive Master.
Your lasso of truth won't help you.
By the time he wakes up
from my sleeping gas, Metropolis will be destroyed.
We've gotta find the bomb.
Destroy Metropolis?
What's going on down there?
We've got this, Superman.
Keep your focus on New Genesis.
A bomb that size would have a large radioactive signature.
You think we can trace it?
GREEN ARROW: Guys?
I think we've got trouble.
(CRACKLING)
(CRASHES)
Athena.
Who else?
- Who is... - Athena.
Goddess of wisdom, strategy, victory,
and half a dozen other things.
Forgive me, Athena, but what wisdom
have you come to impart?
You know, you could do your hair a little differently,
maybe parted on the other side.
We could throw some highlights in there, maybe shush it up.
She means why are you here?
Rejoice mortals,
for the Goddess Athena has come with glad tidings.
Diana of Themyscira, the eyes of Olympus
have been upon you and beheld your great deeds.
Self-sacrifice, triumphs over evil, etcetera, etcetera...
So, I pulled some strings
and you are about to become the brand new.
Goddess of Truth!
In other words, sweetie, I got you a job.
Ta-da!
But I... I have a job.
Oh, I know, honey. Punching people in bee outfits...
But this is a real job.
I accept your gracious offer.
But Hive has to be stopped.
Oh, fine. One last mission.
It'll be fun to stretch my legs.
We know the mercenary group Hive
has a cobalt fusion bomb somewhere
- in Metropolis. - (OWL HOOTS)
What we need now is... Could you not do that?
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
Booboo just thought you might wanna know
where the bomb is hidden.
Let's go.
Pretty smart bird you got there.
Are there other job openings?
I could be a bow and arrow guy. Hmm.
Sorry, kid. Artemis has that job.
So, I'll just be here, helping out New Genesis, then?
(AIRCRAFT SWOOSHING)
You sure you know how to fly one of these things?
It's kind of cramped in here.
Why don't you fly alongside us?
Not all of us gods can fly,
like not every superhero can fly.
Right, Batman?
I swear I can almost hear his blood pressure rising.
The gods test us in many ways.
Diana, if you don't wanna leave...
It doesn't matter what I want, Oliver.
An Amazon doesn't defy the gods.
Period.
I'll do my duty.
I just wanna do one last good thing for the world.
Before I leave it.
BATMAN: We've reached the docks.
The base must be hidden nearby.
Correct, Batman.
But you'll never see it.
(BEEPING)
(MISSILE FIRING)
(WEAPONS FIRING)
(BLASTING)
(ENGINE DECELERATING)
(AIRCRAFT CRASHING)
(GRUNTS)
(CRASHING)
(WEAPONS FIRING)
(EXPLODING)
(SNAPS) Ah!
(GRUNTS)
That wasn't a very dignified landing.
Next time, I'll let you swim.
WOMAN: Oh, no! WORKERS: (EXCLAIMING IN ALARM)
(SHOUTING)
(CRASHING)
Everyone, I need your help.
There's a cobalt fusion bomb in the area.
(ALL GASP)
Don't panic. I need each of you to round up
as many people as you can and evacuate the area.
Are you with me?
ALL: Yeah!
MAN: We're with you. We're with you, Wonder Woman.
Well done.
What did I miss?
I'm still picking up trace amounts of cobalt.
If the shipment left the warehouse,
we should've seen it.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(CLEARS THROAT LOUDLY)
It's underground.
Thank you.
There's got to be a switch to open it.
(OWL HOOTING)
(ELECTRONIC WHIRRING)
We could be walking into a trap.
- Athena, stay here. - Stay here?
(LIGHTNING CRACKLES)
They don't call me the Goddess of War for nothing.
Lead the way.
(ALARM BUZZING)
(THUDDING)
(WEAPONS FIRING)
(GRUNTING)
Ah!
Let's see Artemis do that.
Eh!
Really? Come on, look at me.
(WEAPONS FIRING)
(LAUGHS)
How adorable are you?
(GUNS FIRING)
You okay, soldier?
Yeah. (STAMMERS) I mean, freeze!
(CRASHING)
BATMAN: That's the last of them.
But where's the Hive master?
Looking for me?
(WEAPONS FIRING)
Please tell me this is just honey.
(GRUNTS)
(WEAPONS FIRING)
(LASER WHOOSHING)
(GRUNTS)
Get off me!
It's over, Hive Master.
Oh, it is. But it is you who have lost. (BEEPS)
COMPUTER: Detonation sequence activated.
Stop the countdown!
Ha-ha! Never!
Fine! Have it your way.
Here! Stick around!
We need to load these people onto the escape vehicle.
(ELECTRONIC COUNTDOWN CONTINUES)
COMPUTER: Detonation in 10...
Where are you going?
Nine, eight, seven,
- six, five... - (WHIMPERS)
four, three...
All right. Computer, cancel autodestruct sequence.
Hive master, one bee, two bee, three.
COMPUTER: Code recognized. Deactivating bomb.
(SIGHS)
Brava, Diana.
But weren't you worried the bomb would go off?
He was always willing to sacrifice others,
but not himself.
(GASPS)
You would've made a good Goddess of Truth.
Thank you... Wait! What?
It doesn't take a lasso of truth to know you belong here.
Athena, I...
Diana of Themyscira,
I have witnessed your strength,
your resourcefulness and your ability to inspire.
Heroing is a bit more important than I thought.
I am nothing but proud.
Anyway, I better get going. Traffic and all.
See you later, grumpy.
Hey, what about the God of Love?
That's an archery job, right?
I'm a natural.
Yes, that could work.
Although you'd have to wear a diaper.
A diaper?
Well, never mind.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYS)