(male narrator) Previously on "Justice League Unlimited."
You invent a time machine
and can't think of anything useful to do with it?
I can use it to get away from you.
David Clinton, inventor of the chrono suit
at your disposal.
You tried to steal Batman's utility belt.
Don't hurt anyone. We could accidentally change history.
We've been expecting you.
zap
Static? What's going on?
Dad?
[theme music]
[music continues]
[instrumental music]
We need to get out of here.
Leaving so soon?
You didn't even take any party favors.
swoosh
Incoming!
zap
bam bam bam
That's not gonna hold.
Where do you think you're going, sugar?
rizz
[whirring]
[grunts]
screech
Look, Dee Dee, another Green Lantern.
He's much cuter than the last one we Killed.
Don't you think, Dee Dee?
tish
swish
[grunts]
How'd you..
swish
[grunts]
[laughing]
swoosh
thud
swish swish
Hold still so I can pound you.
Yeah, that's what I'll do.
[grunting]
bwok bwok bwok
thud
rizz rizz rizz
zap
clang
crackle crackle
zap
[pulsating]
crackle crackle
zap
Hey, what's the big idea?
(Dee Dee) You shouldn't oughta have done that.
whoosh
We're getting out of here now.
Not a chance. Hold the line.
He's right. We're the Justice League.
We don't run from a fight.
[grunts]
thud
I don't remember putting this up for a vote.
boosh
screech
swoosh
crackle crackle
(Green Lantern) 'Keep your head in the game, kid.'
There's always another way.
Virgil, I need some cover.
crackle crackle
swoosh
They're gone, Dee Dee.
Bet I know which way they went, Dee Dee.
After 'em!
I think we've lost them.
Where are we headed? The Watchtower?
Not exactly.
slam
crackle crackle
This is Justice League headquarters?
For now.
We're all that's left of the league.
You've traveled about 50 years into your future.
Last time I saw you, you were too young to drive.
You look good for a man your age.
The miracles of modern medicine.
Sixty five is the new thirty.
- And the Watchtower? - It's gone.
We lost a lot of good people that day.
You mean, Superman, J'onn, all the others?
Yeah. You too.
And the bat-cave?
(Bruce) 'This is all we have left now.'
Deal with it.
- Surprised to see me? - A little.
I'm more surprised that I lived so long.
Batman, Bruce Wayne. Bruce Wayne, Batman.
Or have you met?
- Not now. - Not now.
Great. What did they used to call it?
Stereo?
This is a little weird for everybody.
I'm Warhawk, Rex Stewart.
Your mother. Who is she?
Kind of obvious, don't you think?
Even if it isn't, leave it be.
You don't wanna know too much about your future.
Trust me, you really don't.
Shayera was one cranky pregnant lady.
Although, to be fair, if I'd laid an egg that size.
He's kidding, dad.
Not that I understand why you think
'this is anything to joke about.'
Because we already won. Think about it.
If old Bruce is here
that means he already lived through this as Batman.
Flawless logic.
Except that I have no memory of ever going to the future
and meeting my older self
or of anything else that's happening today.
Those historical buildings we saw on the street.
The timeline's been polluted.
So polluted that history itself is becoming fluid.
We'd better compare notes.
Enid, I have to say that I'm vexed.
Yes, vexed is precisely the word for it.
You shouldn't let yourself get upset, David.
You're right, dear.
But here we are.
Now, look at it from my point of view.
I go to the trouble of taking over the whole city
so I have a nice place to keep my collection.
And it's a beautiful collection, David.
I was gonna say the same thing, boss.
For instance, this is a really nice boat. Big!
Don't patronize me, Chucko
and especially, don't interrupt me.
I'm sorry.
Sorry what?
Everybody?
(in unison) Sorry, Lord Chronos!
It doesn't seem right. I go to the future.
I get the technology that gives you all your new super powers.
I let you run amuck in my town
in return for the occasional security job
and what do you do in return?
(both) 'Um..'
Rhetorical.
My point is, I give you an easy job.
Take care of Batman, Wonder Woman and Green Lantern.
It should have been ten minutes work.
But the JLU showed up.
They got in our way.
Yes, they did.
And the question arises
who told them where
and when our targets would arrive?
I mean, I told you
and I only know because I'm the undisputed master
of space and time.
I'll look into it, boss.
I'll find out where the leak was.
No, don't trouble yourself, Chucko.
No, don't bother.
[whispers] I already know.
beep
Somebody's getting a payoff.
Yes, he is.
Chucko, Chucko, Chucko.
You've been a very bad clown.
Enjoy your stay.
[roaring]
You think I'm scared?
I'll be runnin' this dump in a few years..
varoom
Oh, phooey.
ka-boom
Do you know what killed the dinosaurs?
Uh, no, sir.
Well, Chucko does.
And unless you want to find out firsthand
you'll go finish off the Justice League.
Skedaddle!
Time is money.
Actually, time is the non-spatial continuum
in which events occur linearly
usually in the direction of increased entropy.
But the clowns seem to relate better to the money thing.
[gasps]
Oh, Enid, look at what I've done.
And you always said I wouldn't amount to anything.
I guess I showed you.
[both laughing]
Now, I've taken over Gotham
which gives me plenty of space to store my antiques.
Did you notice I took that stuff out of the garage?
You can park there now if you want to.
Thank you, David.
David, didn't you tell me it was dangerous
to take important things from the past?
That it could damage time somehow?
Don't you think I can handle it?
O-of course I do.
- Dear? - Hmm?
Do you know what would make me happy?
If you let my mother out of the thing like you promised.
We'll see. Rub my neck.
It's just that it seems cruel to keep her there so long.
Your mother was the one who always said
I'd never amount to anything.
And you agreed with her.
Whatever I do, whatever I accomplish
it'll never be enough for you, will it?
I just wanted you to love me.
I'm sick of this! I'm sick of you!
Wait, baby, please.
Isn't there anything I can do to make things right?
I sincerely doubt it.
We still don't know much about him.
Obviously, he's a time traveling warlord.
He's littered the streets with buildings.
He's stolen from other time periods.
He's not a warlord.
At least, he wasn't at first.
When we chased him to the old west
all he was stealing was historical trinkets.
beep beep beep
He's causing severe damage to the space-time continuum.
The degradation is increasing exponentially.
(Batman) 'I've got something.'
When we were in the old west
I got a good look at his time belt.
beep
I've written a program that should disable it.
If we can get close enough to upload it.
(Wonder Woman) 'If we can get our hands on the belt'
maybe we can stop any of this from ever happening
in the first place.
We could even undo the death of your friends.
Diana!
She never left the island.
Or she was never born.
Time is running out.
Literally.
We need to find Chronos.
How? He could be anywhere.
Sometimes the old ways are best.
It's not gonna work.
You don't know your way around here.
'A lot of things have changed.'
Are criminals still superstitious and cowardly?
Yup.
Good enough for me.
You're supposed to be the real Batman, right?
I mean, the first one.
I've seen history cubes about you.
Hard to believe somebody stupid as you ever beat the joker.
Maybe I'm smarter than I look.
rizz
zap
crackle crackle
[grunts]
Oh, terrific.
You've got some information we need, Ghoul.
You won't find me the talkative sort.
Hey!
[grunting]
[screams]
Where's Chronos?
My arm's getting tired.
I can't believe I was ever that green.
[grunting]
This is how you interrogate someone.
And we've got 9,453 active jokers
organized into about 200 smaller groups.
I don't know where Chronos is.
He contacts us.
He spends every night in a different
one of those old buildings.
There's no way of knowing ahead of time where he's gonna be.
And that's everything I know.
Everything?
I wet my bed until I was 14.
Losing my patience.
I can't control my friend here much longer.
You better give us something we can use.
His wife. I know where his wife is.
Wow! Batman playing good cop.
Everything's relative.
[instrumental music]
swoosh
Get me another box of bonbons.
thud
bwok bwok
Will you hold it down out there?
You guys are always fighting!
crash
crackle crackle
Enid Clinton.
We've got business with your husband.
What?
John?
Hal Jordan. Another time shift.
I'm up to speed. Carry on.
Okay, I'm starting to get a migraine.
We'd better get used to it.
This is going to get worse before it gets better.
Any one of us could change or even cease to exist.
That's why you have to tell us where to find David.
We just wanna undo the harm he's caused. You have my word.
We'll do everything in our power to keep from hurting him.
Between you and me
I wouldn't mind one bit
if he got roughed up along the way.
(Warhawk) 'Then where is he tonight?'
The Parthenon? The Great Sphinx?
He just wants people to think he moves around.
He always sleeps in the same place.
[intense music]
zap
No booby traps.
At least none that my ring can detect.
Make up your mind, would you?
Anyway, it's safe to go in.
If we don't beat this guy
it's the end of everything.
- We've been there before. - Not like this.
What are you supposed to do when you have the weight
of the world on your shoulders?
Plant your feet.
[intense music]
(Green Lantern) I don't understand, with all of the places
'he could be why sleep here?
Because a loser with a kingdom is still just a loser.
(Enid) 'See for yourself.'
Huh...Enid?
Nice on the stealth thing, lady.
boosh
Get the belt. Nothing else matters.
clink
bash
crackle crackle
[rumbling]
crackle
[Batman grunts]
A real gentleman, isn't he, Dee Dee?
They're practically extinct, Dee Dee.
swish
zap
boom
zap zap
zap zap zap
[screams]
It happened again.
Look out! Monsters!
Fire at will!
bam bam bam
[grunts]
swish
Batman's not paying us any attention, Dee Dee.
He should be punished, Dee Dee.
[screaming]
Terry!
Terry.
clang clang clang
rizz
thud
bam bam bam
How could you betray me, Enid?
Everything I've done, I've done for you.
Don't blame this on me.
I just wanted you to assert yourself
not destroy the universe.
thud
bwok
[grunting]
boosh
[trumpeting]
[Warhawk grunting]
zap
Get away from my kid!
[grunts]
Chronos!
You are good. Isn't he good?
Look at what's happening around you.
Look at the sky!
Pretty.
Stay with us, man, we've got a problem here.
Right. You're right.
This calls for another approach.
You'll love me next time!
zap
Where's he going? There's nothing left.
Yes, there is.
The beginning of time.
He can reset everything. Make himself into a God.
Only if he gets there first.
[dramatic music]
The Green Lanterns have a legend.
No one can see the beginning of time.
It's a universal law.
Write him a ticket.
[dramatic music]
No!
Uploading the program.
Make it fast.
Having a little trouble with the brakes.
[Green Lantern grunting]
[indistinct chattering]
That all really happened?
Think so.
Then, we won.
Everything's back to normal?
That's a nasty cut, John.
You don't remember going on a mission with us today, do you?
I just got here.
The timeline's restored to equilibrium.
We're the only two people who remember what happened.
That complicates things.
What happened to Chronos?
I reprogrammed the belt to make sure
that Chronos would never come to exist.
(Enid) 'You worthless, good for nothing'
wretched waste of space.
You invent a time machine and can't think of anything
useful to do with it?
I can think of one thing.
Worthless, good for nothing, wretched waste of space!
You invent a time machine and can't think of anything
useful to do with it?
I can think of one thing.
(Enid) 'Worthless, good for nothing'
'wretched waste of space.'
[theme music]