[eerie music]
hiss
- Whoa! - Whoa!
hiss hiss
[screaming]
roar
hiss
boom
[screaming]
[dramatic music]
The new Bermuda Platform's under attack.
If it collapses, we're gonna have the worst
oil spill in history on our hands.
'I've told those idiots to stay out of my ocean.'
ETA is three minutes, Aquaman.
Right behind you, Superman.
(Batman) 'See you there, Diana.'
[music continues]
roar
[grunting]
swish swish
crackle
whoosh
[grunting]
swish
splash
These geniuses, dug right into the Earth's magma.
Never occurred to them that there'd be anything
living down there.
whoosh
whoosh whoosh
Not to worry, fellow heroes.
The Ultimen are here.
[instrumental music]
Not them again.
[theme music]
[music continues]
bash
whoosh
roar
[groaning]
Now, was that nice?
crackle crackle
[roaring]
You know, Juice, Superman was my hero when I was a lad.
It's not his fault he's getting old.
Old?
[grunting]
Old, but spry, sir.
Old, but spry.
[intense music]
swish swish
[grunting]
It's, uh, really an honor
to be working with you, Wonder Woman.
Thank you, Long Shadow.
- Lend them a hand, brother? - Absolutely, sister.
splatt
- Flood! - Sea serpent!
roar
splatt
[growling]
[music continues]
[roaring]
splatt
whoosh
[roaring]
Don't be afraid, Wonder Woman.
It's only me, Shifter.
Any chance you could warn me before you try to drown me?
We were only trying to help.
bash bash
Can you make telepathic contact?
Do they look like fish to you?
Don't despair, old chum.
[instrumental music]
whoosh
I didn't know you could do that.
Neither did I.
(Wind Dragon) 'Finding new sources of fuel'
'for an energy-starved world'
'is truly a worthy endeavor.'
But in man's quest to better himself
he must respect all of the world's creatures.
Including those poor beasts whose homes you've disturbed.
'It's imperative that we learn to share our planet'
'if Earth is to survive.'
He's certainly...earnest.
I think the word is corny.
Our paths keep crossing.
And our goals are very much the same.
Isn't it time you accepted our offer?
Alright!
We're truly flattered, Wonder Woman.
But we're simply not ready yet.
All of you in the Justice League
stand as shining examples of what true heroism is.
I only hope that one day..
...the Ultimen can live up to your legend.
Oh, for cryin' out loud.
Wonder Woman?
-1 think it'd be terrific
if one day we could join the league, but..
[dramatic music]
Maybe you could come with me on patrol sometime.
Oh! Oh, that would be..
Let's go, Romeo.
crackle crackle
Mr. Lord, your Ultimen have taken the country by storm
these past six months.
- Why do you think that is? - Simple, Mike.
They're heroes people can trust, relate to, depend on.
They're not aloof.
They don't put themselves above us mere mortals
the way that some heroes do.
Are you referring to the Justice League?
Who?
But what about those who criticize you
for the millions you've made in licensing
and endorsement deals?
All the money generated by the Ultimen
is funneled back into the group
to cover overhead and such.
Fighting crime isn't cheap, Mike.
And even superheroes have to eat.
I can't listen to any more of this.
This guy's dripping more oil than that platform ever did.
And he has the gall to take cheap shots at us.
I know Maxwell Lord.
All he cares about is money.
Well, it takes money to do what we do.
And not everyone's independently wealthy.
Lord's a walking ego
who'd do anything for a buck and some free publicity.
If he's involved in this
it isn't about helping people.
I don't know about Lord, but I think these Ultimen
have potential that should be encouraged.
Especially Long Shadow.
I admit, they're a little overeager.
But they're really a nice bunch of kids.
So last night, "Inside Celebrity"
did a whole segment on Wind Dragon
'and Mr. Swelled-head here didn't even mention'
'the rest of us.'
When do I get to be team leader?
When your teeth sparkle like mine.
Kids, kids, you know you two play best at the 'tweens.
Your faces are on the walls of every 12-year-old in America.
I don't know about Shifter but I'm sick of being a teen idol.
There's more to me than just a pretty face.
[chuckles]
(Maxwell) Did I forget to give you the royalty check
for the new water-spouting downpour action figure?
And that's just domestic.
What-what I want to know is..
(in unison) Why can't we join the Justice League?
Hey, it's alright. I used to think like that.
Used to? What happened?
I don't know. I guess I just started wanting stuff.
[cellphone ringing]
Yes, ma'am, but just because Wind Dragon has a new power--
Yes, I know, but-but-but..
I'll check it out, ma'am. I'll check them all out.
[grunting]
Come on, Giganta, how long are you going to be
Grodd's errand girl?
As long as he needs me.
I took you apart before. Why go through it again?
Because this time, I've got help.
♪♪ Bizarro's here to save the day ♪♪
[grunting]
[dramatic music]
thud thud
[gunfire]
[grunting]
creak
crash
[music continues]
thud thud
Out of the way, tiny.
whoosh
- You were saying? - Oh, poop.
bash
Can't you see Giganta's just using you?
[grunting]
Me do anything for woman I love.
Even break her boyfriend out of jail.
And what's gonna happen then?
Uh..
[grunting]
bash
crash
whoosh
Good job.
[instrumental music]
Believe it or not, when I was born
I was small, sickly.
But lucky for me, my folks were scientists
experimenting with growth hormones.
Guess the experiments were a success.
- Where are your parents now? - Well, mom passed away.
Dad's retired.
Do you really think I could make it in the League?
Yes. Yes, I do.
But I guess...I guess I owe it to the Ultimen to..
[cellphone ringing]
Yeah?
Okay. Right away.
I've got to go.
beep beep
How long are they gonna keep us here like this?
What's the hurry, sis?
Gotta get home and wax your mustache?
Ha ha ha.
Well, I, for one, have a date.
And I have to get her home by 10:00.
It's worse than we thought.
[dramatic music]
The Ultimen's cellular matrix isn't holding.
Wind Dragon, in particular
is showing massive cellular atrophy.
But they're all in the early stages of failure.
- How long? - A few months, a few days.
The progression will be painful.
We should do everything we can to help them.
(Amanda) 'That's not our priority.'
[dramatic music]
But, Mrs. Waller, I really think that we--
Since when did your opinion count, Lord?
How fast can you get the second team up and running?
I swear, he still wets the bed.
(male #1) 'If we push ourselves, five days.'
Can I help it if I keep turning into a puddle all night?
- Quiet! - Do it in three.
'I saw her turning into Britney Spears..'
(Maxwell) 'But what about the Ultimen?'
Quiet!
(Amanda) 'They're expendable.'
[instrumental music]
whoosh
Great news, troops.
Dragon's new power is nothing to be concerned about.
But, uh, just to be safe, Professor Hamilton
wants to keep you overnight for observation.
- Overnight? - No problem, Max.
We'll be happy to stay.
[siren blaring on TV]
[woman screaming on TV]
crackle crackle
boom
[dramatic music]
whoosh
[screaming]
[groaning]
What exactly are we looking for?
We'll know when we find it.
bang
[dramatic music]
[gasps]
What is that?
Over there.
[music continues]
[crying]
The clones are unharmed.
Security can't find a trace of our Ultimen.
But I want you to find them, Mr. Lord.
And bring them back.
They're not gonna trust me or anyone now that they know that--
Bring them back or I'm calling in the squad to put them down.
I want this laboratory dismantled and relocated.
No loose ends.
whoosh
[screaming]
[dramatic music]
[groaning]
You lied to us, Max.
I was only trying to protect you
from people who don't have your best interests at heart.
I've always been on your side
and I promise, I won't stop until--
Spare us the performance.
- Water. - Lion.
[music continues]
whoosh
What'll it be, Max? Drowning on a rooftop?
Or eaten by a lion?
[mumbling]
pop
[gasps]
[coughing] You are..
You're artificial life forms..
...grown in a test tube..
'...designed to be the ultimate superheroes.'
That's a lie! I remember my parents! How much they loved me.
I was with my mother when she died. I--
'Implanted memories.'
But I spent Thanksgiving with my father.
Actors.
How long have we?
You're...just a little over a year old.
The purpose of the Cadmus project
was to create a popular group of superheroes
who were completely loyal to the government.
Unlike those loose cannons in the Justice League.
And the clones?
Replacements for when...you wear out.
'Once they're complete..'
'...the clones will think they're you.'
They'll be you, and no one will be the wiser.
How could you do this to us?
Huh! Me? This is so big, even my superiors are small fish.
[music continues]
- But .. I-l was just-- - Following orders?
crackle crackle
No. He's nothing.
We want the big fish.
[groaning]
whoosh
[music continues]
bang bang
[dramatic music]
- They're gone! - And we're dead.
They're here somewhere. They've got to be.
Rhino!
roar
crash
Tidal wave!
splash
whoosh
Take this place apart.
No, wait! There are other offices in this building.
Innocent people who..
burble burble
rumble rumble
[indistinct chattering]
whoosh
crash
- I'm here to help. - We're out of here!
[screaming]
boom
[dramatic music]
splash
boom boom
[screaming]
(Wonder Woman) 'Need a hand?'
swish
whoosh
whirr whirr
splash
roar
crackle crackle
What's the point of this?
We'll never find Cadmus or a cure. It's hopeless.
Then what? We just die and let them replace us?
No one ever knows we were here? That we mattered?
I say we just bring the whole building down
right on top of us.
Don't give up hope yet, Downpour. We've got friends..
...in high places.
You idiot, do you really think that they can help us?
Whatever's going on, we'll do everything in our power to--
Yes, power.
That's what it always comes down to, doesn't it?
And that's the only way we'll ever be remembered.
whoosh
If we're the ones who take down the Justice League
'the world will never forget us!'
whoosh
Listen to yourself. You're not making any sense.
You're getting sicker.
Translation, they're afraid to face us.
No!
As a man said, you're either with us or against us.
whoosh
zap
[screaming]
[grunting]
burble burble
clang
chomp
[dramatic music]
zap
sizzle
Where'd he go?
swish
sizzle
bash
sizzle sizzle
thud
hiss
Light's out, old chum.
[dramatic music]
crash
burble burble
roar
crash
[grunting]
[groaning]
roar
burble burble
Nobody does that to my sister!
Do you hear me? Nobody!
whoosh
crash
[dramatic music]
King of the seas, remember?
[screams]
[grunting]
bash
thud
You don't have to do this!
It's all I know!
It's what I was created to do!
You're confused, Dragon.
- The cellular degeneration-- - No more words!
I'll suck the wind right out of you.
whoosh
[gasps]
Look what you're doing. Look!
whoosh
(Long Shadow) 'Is this what you want to be remembered for?'
- 'He was your hero.' - No!
whoosh
He was my hero.
And a hero is all I ever wanted to be.
[dramatic music]
click click
Project Cadmus? That's all you know?
Everything else is an implanted memory.
How much time..
...do you have left?
Who knows?
[dramatic music]
We'll take it from here. The Ultimen belong to us.
- Belong? - A poor choice of words.
We'll see to it that their last days are comfortable.
We will take care of you.
You have my word, for whatever it's worth.
[instrumental music]
Alright, Max.
- No. - You need to step back.
Not gonna happen. Long shadow's with us.
Safeties.
[dramatic music]
Mine are bigger than yours.
Stand down.
He's free to go with you.
'For however long he's got.'
Who are you people?
That's a national security matter.
And if I were you, I wouldn't probe
the situation too closely...
...rich boy.
vroom
[instrumental music]
whoosh
Welcome to the Justice League.
[theme music]