What's with the running, doc?
We both know how this is gonna turn out.
I didn't tell anyone.
I swear!
Good, then you're the only loose end.
You can scream now, if you want.
I've never fully understood
the mechanics of dreams.
I don't have them myself.
Well, this one's doing
a number on my ceiling
and pa Kent's getting tired of patching it.
I will say this.
What I saw was far more linear
than ordinary dream logic.
But it didn't seem like a memory either.
It was inconclusive.
You mean, I might actually
have done these things?
I'm sorry.
I just don't know.
J'onn, President Chojeb on one.
I'm going to put you on the inactive roster
for a few days.
Let me know what you find.
What's the big deal?
You had some nightmares.
These weren't just dreams.
They felt like they really happened.
I don't know. I've had some dreams that felt mighty real.
There was this one the other night...
The point is I couldn't live with myself
if I really did what I saw.
Now, are you gonna help me or not?
Of course, kid.
But vague memories of a probe
like one of those alien abduction things.
Maybe you've just been hanging out in Kansas too long.
Wouldn't be so sure.
Especially when she's the alien.
Got all the signs of repressed memory.
People dream what their minds don't want to remember.
Easier to convince themselves it's all bunk.
Repressed memories of what?
When?
You've been to S.T.A.R Labs
treated for injuries there.
Yeah, a few years ago.
When Superman was brainwashed and attacked the earth.
I got hurt, and he took me to S.T.A.R for help.
I was in a coma for part of it.
Meaning there's a gap in time
you can't account for.
That's when.
Okay, enough. Don't listen to this guy.
Everything's conspiracies with him.
Not conspiracies.
Conspiracy.
Singular.
Reaching back to ancient Egypt
there's been a single cabal of powerful individuals
directing the course of human history.
But the common man prefers to believe
they don't exist.
Which aids their success.
Global warming
military upheavals in the third world
actors elected to public office?
The spread of coffee bars
germs outpacing antibiotics
and boy bands?
Come on.
Who would gain from all this?
Who indeed?
What does any of this have to do with my dreams?
If I'm right, you're part of it.
You're going to need my help.
I'm going with you.
Hold your horses.
No one asked for more help.
This whole trip might just prove
the kid shouldn't eat nachos before bed.
Peanut butter sandwiches.
How did you...
What? Do you go through my trash?
Please.
I go through everyone's trash.
This is where we treated you
when you were in your coma.
You were on life support the whole time.
I promise, you weren't running around
on violent missions.
Well, then, Professor Hamilton, maybe you can
explain why her memories led her here?
I think I can explain it.
You mentioned some sort of torture device.
- Yes. - With robotic arms.
And a long probe in the center.
Cut to the chase.
You say you've seen something like it?
In fact, I have.
That's it.
It's not a torture device.
It's a surgical robot.
That's a kryptonite-tipped lance.
It was the only way to operate on you, Supergirl.
That robot saved your life.
As for the rest of your dream
we humans are used to being vulnerable.
But to you, surgery must have seemed
terribly invasive.
And powerless to defend yourself
it's possible your mind constructed
a scenario of fighting back.
So, I think that answered everything.
Little too well.
Does everything have a sinister motive in your world?
Yours, too. You just don't know it.
Uh, guys.
Huh. Ooh.
What was that about?
What do you think?
We're asking questions
someone doesn't want answered.
Oh, learn a new tune already.
I'm starting to think he's right.
That robot came after me.
The rest of this was just
a distraction.
Standard Z8 combat trainer.
Like the ones we use.
The League buys 'em in bulk.
So?
So, who do we buy them from?
The army, I think.
Oh, wait a minute.
Another fun fact.
The man who commissioned the Z8 project.
The same man who put you in the hospital.
General Hardcastle?
He's retired now, isn't he?
Gone.
And hoping to be forgotten.
Figured someone would come
for me some day.
Only, I thought they'd be
from the other side.
This weapon fires a projectile
of kryptonite pellets suspended in
a liquid silicon core.
Causes maximum scatter on impact.
Only gets one shot
but trust me, alien
it'll do the job.
We're not here to hurt you.
We just have some questions.
Sorry if I don't take your word for it.
As I recall, your kind can be fickle.
Okay, now what, smart guy?
Use up your magic bullet on me and you're left with one
very ticked off Supergirl.
Now, be a good host
and tell us a story.
The army shut me out
after Superman invaded.
The feeling upstairs was I failed
when it counted most
so how could I lead again?
I got the message
and took early retirement.
Problem is I know too much.
One of these days
they'll decide to shut me up.
Who will? What do you know?
The military and big business
have been in cahoots for decades.
Top secret stuff
experiments on metahumans
mutants, aliens.
Searching for new technologies
both for national security
and profit.
That volcano woman... she was one of ours.
Same with those freaks
The Joker made up like playing cards.
Any of it have to do with Supergirl?
It has to do with all of them.
Your little club up in that spaceship?
There's a file on every one of you.
But I don't know anything
about these dreams of yours.
If it is connected to these people
I've been out of the loop
too long to know.
And how do we find "these people?"
You don't. They find you.
Sorry, kid.
Dead end, I guess.
Not necessarily.
Need some time to process this.
Martian, pick us up.
What? I told you everything I...
Supergirl?
Yes.
And no.
Friends call me Tea.
Are you a friend, general?
Guess that's a no.
It's okay.
You fell asleep.
Excuse me if I bore you.
Hey, lay off.
Hardcastle's gone.
I just know.
- 'Question.' - Go ahead.
Look at your monitor.
I'm patching through a live feed.
A scientist named Gilbert Halstrom
has been reported missing.
He's from a biotech company called Nuvo-Gen.
It's the man from Kara's dream.
He really exists.
Or did anyway.
And only one network had the story.
Now, that's the first lead in this whole business
I can wrap my head around.
We go to Nuvo-Gen.
We find out who this guy is.
No. First we find the source of the report.
What for?
Don't you know who owns the eagle network?
The real owners.
Look, why don't we split up?
Kara and I will go to Nuvo-Gen.
You go wherever you want.
Hey, Lasser.
Saw that piece on eagle today.
Now, that's reporting.
Thanks. You get home safe.
The thing is that Nuvo-Gen's
a real hush-hush joint
and, uh, Halstrom didn't have no family
to file a missing persons.
So, between you and me
how'd you hear about that story?
Good old-fashioned legwork, Jerry.
You should try it sometime.
Commodore Hotel.
- Something wrong? - Gotta write up my fare report.
So, what do you think of that
corporate prepackaged pop
kids like these days?
Hate it.
♪ Fell in love again ♪
Hey, I just said...
♪ Tell all my friends ♪
How you doing? Ollie, filling in.
What happened to Frank?
I heard some contest guy showed up at his door.
Free trip to Aruba.
Why him and not me?
Tell me about it.
You have a good one.
Good cold one's more like it.
Free trip to Aruba?
Had to send Frank somewhere.
Shame how he dropped his keycard though.
I never heard of Nuvo-Gen or-or Halstrom
until last night.
This girl I've been seeing
she-she slipped it to me.
Said I-I could run with it.
The girl.
Tell me more.
She's just a girl.
Blond hair, blue eyes.
Real farmer's daughter type.
And a handshake like a vice?
Yeah, really strong. How'd you...
- How long you been seeing her? - About a week.
She have bad dreams?
More like tossing and turning.
Can't sleep at night.
Halstrom was getting drowned in e-mails
from their legal department.
Sounds like they were scared he was gonna
blow the whistle on something.
Doesn't say what.
I don't believe it.
That crazy old Hardcastle was right.
These guys claim they're splicing heartier tomatoes
but really they've been experimenting
with metahuman DNA.
Not just any DNA
My DNA.
Look.
This folder was marked "Metropolis Training Exercises."
It's me.
Um, a little more
mature than you.
But I see your point.
They cloned me.
We must have some sort of psychic link.
That's why I'm seeing things I didn't do.
What is this place?
It's a hologram chamber.
Hard light constructs.
Must be a training program.
My training program.
And so.
What do you think?
It's important that you like yourself
and I'm you...
just accelerated a few extra years
plus better trained.
And I have to say
a heck of a lot smarter.
You lured us here.
After your lackeys couldn't get rid of me at S.T.A.R
you decided to deal with me yourself
on your home turf.
It's like you're reading my mind.
Which is actually the problem
and why you have to die.
Arrow!
♪ Fell in love again ♪
♪ What am I gonna tell my friends ♪
♪ It just happened ♪
♪ You walked in my door ♪
♪ And now I don't wanna ♪
♪ Be alone no more ♪
♪ Oops I've done it ♪
♪ Told you how I feel ♪
♪ Just hope this time ♪
♪ That our love is real ♪
Anything break?
Just my stride.
Nap's over.
Come on.
Next time, get your own dreams.
- Who do you work for? - Really?
At the top, even I don't know that.
But I do know I can't work in secret
if you keep seeing what I do.
So, sayonara, sister.
That's not the only reason, is it?
You were setting up this bait
even before Supergirl started asking questions.
It's because the link works both ways, doesn't it?
While she was seeing what you were doing
you were feeling her conscience.
That's why you couldn't sleep at night.
And I bet it got in the way of your work.
It bites having someone in your head
doesn't it?
You don't know what you're talking about.
No?
Prove it.
Kill me.
Understood.
No! I can do this.
It's too late!
We searched what was left of the place
but we never found the clone.
Maybe there was nothing to find.
Or that's what they want us to think.
I'm just glad you're okay, Supergirl.
Professor, to make this clone of me
they would have needed a DNA sample.
Is there any chance it came from your lab?
No, we always destroy
genetic material after surgery.
It's standard procedure.
Okay, thanks, professor.
Give my best to Superman.
Will do. Bye.
I still don't get why someone
cloned you in the first place.
This all started because Superman went renegade.
They want a Superhuman alien on their side
if it ever happens again.
Whoever they are.
You rest.
We'll have you fixed up in no time.
Galatea.