Patience, princess.
Intergang moves in mysterious ways.
Tell me about it.
What use could they possibly have
for the Rosetta stone?
We'll find out soon enough
and in the meantime...
I know... patience.
Don't you ever wish you were down there?
I'm down there all I need to be.
Yes, but it's just a job to you.
I'm talking about going down there and having some fun.
Maybe... maybe with someone special.
No. No dating for the Batman.
It might cut into your brooding time.
One, dating within the team always leads to disaster.
Two, you're a princess from a society of immortal warriors.
I'm a rich kid with issues... lots of issues.
And three, if my enemies knew I had someone special
they wouldn't rest until they'd gotten to me through her.
Next.
There.
Saved by the bell.
Just a common thief.
What happened to Intergang?
J'onn must have gotten a bad tip.
It happens. I'll take the crowbar.
Whatever you say.
That trick always went over big in Egypt.
Circe. Be careful. She's...
Yeah. I've read "The Odyssey."
That it for you?
What are you doing here, witch?
You were banished.
They needed more space down below
so they paroled me.
Of course, I had to promise to leave your mommy dearest alone
before they'd let me out.
Mother sent her to the pits of Tartarus.
Circe had a nasty habit of turning innocent people
into animals.
I'm real good at it, too.
So I've read.
Let's not give her another chance.
I promised to leave your mother alone, little princess
but nobody said anything about you.
Rest assured, after I get done with you
Hippolyta won't want you for a daughter
and your pointy-eared boyfriend here won't want you
for anything.
My poor assistant. He's fallen all to pieces.
Let's see if I can help him pull himself together.
Oops.
Thank you. You've been a wonderful audience.
And for my final illusion
I'd like to pull a rabbit out of my hat.
Trust me, it isn't as easy as everybody thinks.
Come on, bugs. Where are you?
Well, you're not as furry, but you're just as cute.
Kcab ot lamron!
Hmm. A little slow on the switch.
Gotta watch that.
What was it? Some kind of hologram?
Or was it the real thing?
It's called sorcery, Bruce.
Usually, I play it straight, but for the big closer
I throw in a little dazzle.
But enough about my secrets.
What have you been up to?
I haven't seen you in so long.
Can we discuss that later? Someone's in trouble.
Who? What kind of trouble?
Well...
Ew. Circe, huh?
It was all over the mystic Ethernet that she made parole.
I'll see what I can do.
Lleps eb nekorb!
Anaid, emoceb namuh!
Well, I've given it my best shots.
I guess my powers run a distant second to those of a goddess.
We could call in one of the other lead magicians.
- Dr. Fate, maybe. - No.
I mean, let's keep this between us.
But why? If there's a chance to help Diana
shouldn't we tell everyone and then...
Oh, wait, wait. You and her.
- Are you two... - Just good friends.
No. You and I are just good friends.
There's something more between you and Diana.
Well, maybe there was.
Don't worry, Bruce.
I'll find a way out of this for her...
and you.
But I'm beginning to think that only Circe
can turn our chubby friend here back into Wonder Woman.
And Lord only knows where she is right now.
♪ Gotta get your own tuxedo pressed ♪
♪ Gotta sew a button on your vest ♪
♪ 'Cause tonight you've got to look your best ♪
♪ Lulu's back in town ♪
♪ Gotta get a half a buck somewhere ♪
♪ Gotta shine your shoes and slick your hair ♪
♪ Gotta get this guy a boutonniere ♪
♪ Lulu's back in town ♪
♪ You can tell the mailman not to call ♪
♪ You ain't coming home until the fall ♪
♪ And you may not get back home at all ♪
♪ Lulu's back in town ♪
Come on, Sid, are you gonna sell me the chimera scale or not?
You know the rules.
The elements of magic always come at a price
and I don't take cash or plastic.
So what do you want?
Hey, is that thing housebroken?
I'll take care of her.
Now, about that final ingredient I need for my locator spell...
It's all yours for one silver good luck fin.
Mid-Ching dynasty, if you please.
What? That is robbery!
What robbery? I'm giving it to you at cost.
It's a total rip.
I could conjure it up for nothing.
Try it.
Chimera scale is all but
impossible to get
by magic or not.
I'm this dimension's only supplier.
Okay. You win.
Esrup raeppa!
Thank you.
We'll be done here soon.
I call upon the spirits of Earth and air
to reveal our enemy and make her whereabouts known.
This invocation works better frontwards than backwards.
Whatever.
Circe, show yourself.
Well, that was a lot of nothing.
Circe's pretty powerful.
If she doesn't want to be found
there's not much anyone can do.
Then, what was the point of all this?
Give me my coin back.
Sorry, kid. No refunds.
You slimy little...
Zatanna, she's gone.
Dnufer.
Hey!
Uh! Whoa!
Well, that's it.
From mud hole to sty, we've looked everywhere.
Obviously we haven't, because we haven't found her yet.
Don't get snippy with me.
How many other girls would go
this far out of their way
for a cold, insensitive...
- Yo, Bats. - Aah!
Relax. He's one of us.
B'wana Beast. How ya doin'?
My legs are fine as is the rest of me.
- Up here. - Whoa.
She's got the fire of the cheetah in her.
Why are you doing this to me?
Apart from being an expert tracker
he can communicate with animals.
I called him in to help search.
We're looking for a lost pig, pink, about 60 pounds
wearing two silver bracelets.
It used to be Wonder Woman.
Right on. I'll yank in some of the other guys.
Let's keep the circle small... very small.
Soo-eee!
Ding-dong
Excuse me, sir. I'm looking for a pig.
Gladys, it's for you.
Yo, Wonder Pig!
Bats, Beast.
Got a fix on your girl.
Good work.
I'll have her ready for pickup in...
Yeah, look, Bats
I think I might have jumped the gun
when I said I found the pig.
Keep looking.
Zatanna and I are are going after Circe.
How? The locator spell didn't work.
It's time for one of my tricks.
We need a snitch.
Thank you for setting this up.
Please. Your league has done much good in my name.
When you summoned me, how could I refuse?
Here comes our stoolie.
Don't look at her directly.
Medusa, you have a chance to earn leniency...
if you help our visitors.
You were Circe's cellmate, weren't you?
Sea girl and me did some time together
back in the pit of eternal torment.
That's where they hang you by your ankles
and weasels come each night to eat your fingers.
They grow back the next day, but trust me
it gets old real quick.
Did she ever mention Hippolyta?
Are you kidding?
"Hippolyta! Hippolyta!"
All the time Hippolyta.
"When I get my hands on her..." Yada yada yada.
That much we know. We're wasting our time.
Wait. Wait. Uh, there was one other thing.
Circe was always saying she wanted to headline
at the amphitheater.
The amphitheater...
on Mykonos, duh!
It seems Circe was wicked jealous
of her cousins the Sirens and swore she'd some day
get her turn on the bandstand.
Sophocles got his start there. Aristophanes. All the big names.
You know those statues at the entrance?
Mine.
Thank you, Medusa.
And know that you've earned 300 years off your sentence.
Freedom in 4010.
Ring-a-ding-ding.
Uh... there's a small service charge.
When you see Circe
tell her I want my curling iron back.
Come on, guys. Help me out, here.
Newcomer, silver bracelets, kind of stuck up.
Hey! Get back here!
Gotcha! Oh!
That's it.
Soo-eee.
Here, piggie, piggie, piggie.
Have to admit, Medusa does good work.
Too good.
Thank you, thank you.
You've all been so kind to me tonight.
You know, my cousins the Sirens never thought I could sing.
Really? They thought they were all that
with their charm the sailors routine.
But I'm showing them, aren't I?
Oh, thank you.
I love you all!
Are there any requests?
Stcejbo kcatta ecric.
I'm not sure I know that one.
Insolent trickster!
You dare to strike...
You dare to strike... Ouch!
Quit it!
Oh, no!
Well? Defend your mistress.
Here, piggie, piggie.
Sooie!
Say goodnight, pork chop.
Wow. Loose meat.
Hooh!
That'll do, pig.
Good job, boys.
Side of bacon, coming up.
Elbat mrof egac.
You're both beginning to remind me
of Sisyphus after a hard day pushing his boulder
up the mountain, but me?
I could keep this up all night.
Wait. It seems that magic always has a price.
And your point is?
What would I have to give to make you lift your spell
on Diana?
Well, now you're getting interesting.
I want something from you that's very precious.
Something you've worked very hard to conceal.
Something when gone you can never regain.
Something... so shattering...
♪ Am I blue ♪
♪ Ain't these tears in my eyes ♪
♪ Tellin' you ♪
♪ Am I blue ♪
♪ You'd be too ♪
♪ If each plan that you had ♪
♪ Done fell through ♪
♪ There was a time ♪
♪ I was your only one ♪
♪ But now I'm the sad and lonely one... ♪
Beautiful.
And you'll keep your part of the bargain?
A deal's a deal.
He can stop now.
Not on your life.
♪ I should say... ♪
Circe.
Remember when Penguin tried to kidnap that singer?
Ricky what's-his-name?
So?
I spent a month on stakeout.
Must've heard that song a hundred times.
Is there anything you can't do?
There's one thing I've never been very good at.
Saying thank you.
And, truthfully, it's all still pretty much of a blur to me.
Did I miss anything?
Not really.
The important thing is you're safe.
Yeah. Of course... that's not the only important thing.