clank clank clank
You said "Come back Tuesday."
'It's Tuesday.'
I want my suit.
Patience, brother.
You know how much I care about the details.
It doesn't have to be pretty, Hephaestus.
Where it's going things aren't supposed to be pretty.
Present company excluded, of course.
Just hurry up!
My finishing touch.
[instrumental music]
(Hephaestus) 'The Annihilator.
'Heartless, indestructible'
and ready to feed
on mankind's misery and rage
per your specifications.
Go ahead, Ares.
Give it life.
[grunting]
Enough!
Wrap it up.
I'll take it.
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
[gunfire]
[gunfire continues]
boom
Impressive.
Isn't it?
I knew about advances
in unmanned weaponry, but this is incredible.
Who built it?
Ever heard the expression
"Don't look a gift horse in the mouth"?
Ah, classified.
Now, I've already taken the liberty of imprinting it
to your voice commands.
So, Mr. Nardoc
the only question is
are you interested?
Of course, anything to protect us
from those dogs in the south.
But Mr. Sera
you know how little money we have.
We can worry about that later.
You're joking, right?
No, I trust you.
It's not like you're going anywhere, is it?
With this weapon's help
'no, we are certainly staying right here.'
Follow.
[alarm ringing]
Come on, go, go, go!
[instrumental music]
- Ugh. - Ahh.
- Oof, ow, ah. - Ow.
I try to take a day off
try to have a semblance of a normal life
but you had to pick today to rob a bank.
Unh.
[gunshots]
[clicking]
Oh, yeah.
Like that's going to work.
Wait! Please.
I've learned my lesson.
I promise.
No, you haven't.
Uh! Uh!
Aah!
Uhh!
Your kind never learns.
And it's really starting to get on my nerves.
(J'onn) 'Diana.'
In a minute.
'Diana!'
I'm not finished here.
'I'd say you are.'
[groaning]
Fine.
[sirens wailing]
(J'onn) 'Queen Adria of Kaznia has asked the League for help.'
'Her nation is being torn apart'
by warring paramilitary groups.
Each faction has ties with neighboring countries.
If this escalates
it could easily ignite the region.
What's wrong with people, J'onn?
Hostility's their answer to everything.
You're not one to talk of late.
What's that supposed to mean?
'Diana..
...you and I have both been affected
by our time among humans.'
It's important that we keep ourselves in check.
First of all, those thugs back there
got exactly what they had coming.
As did that band of mercenaries last week.
And those creatures from the Decorin Nebula.
They weren't misunderstood.
They thought we were food!
You're right, Diana.
'None of it has anything to do with you.'
"Before heading to Kaznia"
'you're going to have to make a stop.'
Fine mess here, Don.
Talk to them. You speak Neanderthal?
I think they're done talking.
This is ridiculous.
Just because I disagree with you
doesn't make me unpatriotic.
No, you being a bleeding-heart punk
makes you unpatriotic.
Actually, I've got to agree with him on that one.
(male #1) 'Too late trying to side with us.'
You're both taking a beating.
- Unh'! - Uhh!
Look, we got off on the wrong foot.
But don't you think we could find
plenty of things we all have in common
if we just tried?
- Nope. - Hank, say something.
Preemptive strike.
Aagh!
Hawk.
Dove.
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
Boo.
[grunting]
Uhh!
Aww.
Aah.
Oh, you so wanted to do this.
Don't blame me.
You're the one who couldn't keep your trap shut.
[grunting]
Now, how about you calm down
and I'll let you go.
How about you kiss my a.. Aah!
Argh.
thwack
Uh.
You didn't answer your summons.
Look around, princess.
'Had our hands full.'
Enough to go around if you want a piece.
Out.
Now.
'Ahh, uff.'
The northern tribes have infested
our motherland for too many generations.
Kaznia is ours.
By the blood of our fathers
and our fathers' fathers.
[muttering]
Right now, they're preparing a new weapon
a weapon with fearsome power.
We've got to attack now.
To protect your farms and your families
from their vicious hands.
[cheering]
Move out.
And may fortune be with you!
[engine starts]
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
Why not just let them obliterate each other?
If people can't control their own country
they don't deserve to have one.
(Don) 'Way to oversimplify.'
These folks live in poverty.
And when you have so little
it's easy to be swayed into blaming your neighbor.
Almost all aggression can be cured with education.
Yeah?
Then how come some of the best
educated guys in the world
work at the Pentagon?
Down there.
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
- Ahh. - W-Whoa.
Who is that?
'These people don't stand a chance against it.'
Hawk, you're with me. Dove--
I'm on it.
[grunting]
Both of you. Scram.
boom boom boom
Unh.
Huh-uh.
There's no one inside that thing.
How do you fight that?
You hit it till it breaks.
- Ugh. - Ugh.
- Uhh. - Uhh.
[groaning]
[rock music]
Whoa.
Hey.
What are you doing?
You pulled us right out of battle.
She just saved our lives, Hank.
Two yards would have done that.
This is what's called a retreat.
There was no point continuing.
We were having no effect on that thing.
If anything, it was getting stronger.
There's got to be a way to stop this war.
If we could just get the two leaders
to sit down together.
Oh, 'cause that happens all the time
in these situations.
Unless, you want to just kidnap 'em and make 'em talk.
- I wish. - Then go for it.
At least it'll buy me some time.
Why? What are you doing?
I've got to see a man about a suit of armor.
You let them go.
Why didn't you push ahead
and take their camp?
They have enough arsenal there to launch
an assault against the capital.
I have no designs on the capital.
We won, Mr. Sera.
The animals attacked
and we ran them out of town.
I didn't give you the Annihilator
so you could run your enemies out of town.
I gave you the Annihilator
so you could annihilate them!
Forgive the insult, sir.
But you think like a South Kaznian.
'They want to destroy us all'
'but my brothers and I only wish'
'to keep our land.'
Perhaps I could take their camp
but the price would be too great.
Shall I win a country but massacre my people?
Yes, you idiot!
I think like a South Kaznian?
Has it even entered your skull
that they think like South Kaznians?
And you better start thinking that way too
if you want there to be a northerner left
in this rat-infested dirt heap you call a country.
All any of you mortals are good for
is to slaughter one another.
To fight and fight, until the bones of your enemies
are strewn across the battlefield!
Only to rise again
'in the next generation'
'like a well-tended crop.'
That's what the Annihilator is for.
But no-o-o.
You're using it to play tag.
You know what?
You're crazy and I wash my hands of you.
I'll thank you to get out of
my rat-infested dirt heap now.
And you can take your robot with you.
Better idea.
I stay.
You go.
clank clank clank
I made that armor for your mother.
Did she ever thank me?
No.
I love your mom
but she didn't have your build.
I didn't come here to talk about my armor.
There's an armored suit fighting in Kaznia
that needs no wearer and bears your mark.
The Annihilator.
Then you did make it.
Who else does such fine work?
Ares liked it.
Ares.
Of course.
How do you stop it?
Aww.
You knew to ask.
I do leave a small weakness
in each of my creations.
An Achilles' heel, if you will.
It's so no one ever gets too powerful.
You know what they say
only Zeus is perfect.
And what's the Annihilator's weakness?
Diana, you wouldn't want me
to go around telling people
the weakness in your armor
would you?
Unh.
With that attitude
you'll never figure it out.
Come back when you have more time.
I'll let that suit out a little.
[mumbling]
Sorry, kid. You'll have a headache later.
But on the bright side, if this works
you'll live to see 20.
Don't be afraid.
My name is Dove.
I'm not here to hurt you.
I'd like you to come with me.
It's time to try a new path.
And what path is that?
Peace.
Hmm, not really my thing.
But if you're into it
I can arrange for you
to have eternal peace.
After I'm done with you that is.
[snoring]
Ever run away from home?
It's fun. You'll love it.
Brother and me used to do it all the time.
Except he'd always wuss out
and run home to mama.
[explosion]
[shouting]
General. The northern forces are--
[mumbling]
boom
[instrumental music]
[grunting]
I see Don's social skills
had their usual effect.
[groaning]
[grunting]
boom
[groaning]
Uh.
Aah! Unh! Uh!
[gunfire]
Huh-ah.
Lay down your arms.
You're being used.
Uh.
[gunfire]
What in--
Have a nice day.
Uh ah.
(Hank) 'Unh!'
Ahh.
[gasps]
screech
Don't let them take the camp.
Our arsenal..
You must stop this.
I must do nothing.
I don't take orders from women.
[instrumental music]
The Annihilator.
It's fueled by our rage.
Lower your weapons!
You don't have a chance like that
so try it my way!
Lower your weapons!
Don!
Let go of me.
He's weak.
He'll get himself killed.
Don!
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
[sighs]
Anybody want to give me a clue what just happened?
Sometimes it takes more strength
not to fight.
What's the matter with you people?
Keep fighting!
This is your chance to finish them.
Give it up, Ares.
It's over.
You lose.
Alright.
This time.
But I'll be back
and sooner than you think.
Wherever there's prejudice
ignorance, inequality
I'll be there.
And I'll be waiting.
You see?
Doesn't this prove exactly
what I've been saying for years?
Couldn't tell you.
- I do my best not to listen. - What?
(Hank) 'And another thing, don't go all Gandhi on me.
You think you can pull this every time.'
[instrumental music]
[theme music]