Everybody down!
Down!
Come on! That's not gonna do us any good now.
I'll sure feel better.
But it'll make me a little cranky.
Well, well, the great and glorious Green Lantern.
What, did you run out of alien menaces to beat on?
You gotta horn in on my turf?
You're welcome.
We never heard back from you.
Been kind of busy.
Someone's gotta keep the streets safe
while you and your pals are out there...
- Ready. - zipping around the galaxy...
grandstanding and...
Glad you could make it.
And where am I, exactly?
Among friends.
Each of you brings something different to the table.
Strength, speed, stealth, whatever.
But we're all equal in at least one way.
Each of us is willing to make the sacrifices
a hero needs to make.
Even the ultimate one.
Since there are so many of us
we have a chance to do more
than just put out fires, both literal and figurative.
We can be proactive.
We can do some real good in the world.
But we're gonna have to be organized.
J'onn'll be up here, keeping an eye on everything.
He'll be the one to decide who's going where and when.
I know a lot of you are used to making
those decisions for yourself.
But from now on, we have to be more coordinated than that.
We can't be cowboys anymore.
Or cowgirls.
Ha ha ha...
We sent The Lantern for you
because you never gave us an answer.
Come on, I don't belong up here.
Fighting monsters and aliens and super villains.
I just help the little guy.
And a big club like this?
You tend to forget all about him.
So, gee whiz, I'm flattered to be asked and all
but, no, thanks.
Suit yourself.
Those monsters you don't fight?
They tend to step on little guys.
It's some sort of nuclear accident.
The sensors are showing an enormous release of heat.
I'll get down there and try to contain it.
That's the odd thing, it's not dissipating.
It's moving in a straight line.
Take Captain Atom.
He might be able to absorb some of the radiation.
Right, and I could use some muscle for crowd control.
Take Supergirl.
She's got to start sometime.
Fine.
Use a Javelin.
The radiation's making it impossible
for the transporter to get a fix on the location.
- Um, have to... - Captain Atom, Kara.
About time.
Either of you ever been to Chiang Mai?
It's on the state department's
no travel list.
Class Three felony for American citizens to go there.
Is it anywhere near Daytona Beach?
You're not gonna leave me up here on Mount Olympus.
You can go back the way you came.
Uh-uh, no one's playing pinball with my molecules again.
Alright, we'll drop you off after we're done.
So, you're gonna let me drive, right?
Whoa, wait a minute.
Has she been certified in a Javelin?
Why don't you take the stick out, corporal?
Captain.
Is that a containment suit?
Uh-huh. I'm not flesh and blood anymore.
Just living energy.
That wouldn't be nuclear energy, would it?
With a name like Captain Atom, what do you think?
I think you're what I marched against
back in college.
Looks like we missed the party.
We'll do recon.
If you see anything, don't try to engage.
Roger that.
Uh, you can just say okay.
Okay.
Hey!
State Department sure was right about them
not liking foreigners.
It's crazy. No reason for it.
- I'll give them a reason. - Kara!
We came here to help them, not to fight.
So, you're just gonna stand there
until they run out of RPGs?
If this radiations thing's as bad as it looks
there's a lot of people out there who are gonna get fried.
My apologies for the fireworks.
Colonel Kim here was just a farmer before the revolution.
He doesn't know who you are.
I'm General Kwan.
Most flattered that the Justice League
has honored us with your presence.
But I must ask why.
You had some kind of nuclear accident.
A minor problem.
Fully under control.
If it's all the same to you...
It's fully under control.
If it's all the same to you.
Listen, we came a long way to help, and...
Your help is not needed here.
Thank you for coming.
Now, goodbye.
I'm telling you, J'onn.
It took all the restraint I had not to part that guy's hair
with my ring.
You did the right thing
but the problem is not under control.
It's getting worse.
Don't you get it?
They don't want anyone to find out about the accident.
And they don't care how many of their own people
they have to lose to keep it quiet.
This isn't your concern.
He does have a point.
Maybe the three of us should go back and...
No. We can't just do whatever we want.
We have to respect the government's wishes.
No matter what we might think of their policies.
Lantern.
Green Arrow's gone.
And so is the Geiger counter.
Move it! Move it!
Hurry!
Come on!
I told you to stay away.
Hey, I'm just trying to help.
I told you before
the situation is completely under con...
Looks like I just can't help horning in.
There's some people up the cliff.
I'll try to drain it.
Go! Go!
There was... too much energy.
Well, there's always the low-tech way.
Lantern!
This wouldn't have happened if you'd acted
like you were part of a team.
But I'm not, remember?
So, back off, nuke-boy.
Hey! We've got a giant, out-of-control robot out there.
But if you guys are too busy playing alpha male smackdown
I guess I'll just have to deal with it myself.
Shayera!
You need a plan.
You need to find its weakness.
Those hazmat guys in the village...
they should know something.
Thought you weren't on the team.
Take him.
You'll need all the help you can get.
Okay, but I'm gonna be too busy to cover your sorry...
Wouldn't ask you to.
What are we up against?
He asked you a question.
Don't answer them.
That's classified inform... oh!
I've just about had it with you guys.
You've got to the count of five.
One.
Four.
I'd speak up if I were you.
It was supposed to be our protector.
It was going to protect us from the foreigners.
But then you lost control of it, right?
Is that what happened?
We have carbon rod dampers.
But we couldn't get close enough to it to put them in.
Where's its reactor?
The front of the upper torso.
But it's too hot. You won't make it.
I'll worry about that.
So, what's the plan?
I shove these carbon rods into the robot's reactor.
That should stop it.
I gotta say, that's not much of a plan.
If you get that close, the heat'll fry you.
I know.
But...
If this doesn't work, contact the League.
They'll know what to do next.
Captain.
Try to distract it.
Roger.
Hey! Butane breath!
Say "aah," dirt bag.
You sure he's gonna be okay?
He should be.
J'onn's team picked him up right after it happened
so he didn't lose much of his energy.
At least he got a new suit out of it.
So. Aren't you gonna give me the "You did good" speech?
You're headstrong, unprofessional, and reckless.
If you ever jeopardize yourself or your teammates again
by running off half-cocked without a battle plan
I will personally see to it
that you are kicked out of the League.
I don't care who your cousin is.
And incidentally...
you did good.
Huh.
Well, if it isn't the monster killer.
I was lucky. So was everybody else.
Still don't think I belong up here.
That's the point.
Someone like you will keep us honest.
Gee, Bats, I don't know.
Don't get me wrong, I enjoy a good radiation burn
as much as the next guy but I don't think...
So, see you soon?
You just might.