I've been wondering when you were going to show up.
Terry McGinnis.
Or do you prefer being called... Batman?
How could you do it to me, Bruce?
The only thing that matters is the mission.
You know that.
What about people, Bruce?
Dick, Barbara, Tim, Selena?
They all loved you, but eventually
every single one of them left you.
Ever wonder why?
Not for an instant.
They quit because when it came down to it
they didn't have the heart for the mission.
Are you about to quit, too?
It doesn't really surprise me.
It doesn't?
Of course not.
I've been expecting this day for years.
Why don't you put that thing away, take off your coat
and sit a spell?
I've got some questions I need you to answer.
Of course you do, boy.
Why else go to all the trouble
of breaking into the lair
of the great and powerful Amanda Waller?
You want some green tea? I do.
Full of antioxidants this stuff.
It's supposed to make you live longer.
I don't want tea. I want answers.
Then you're going to have to humor me.
It's been many a year since I had
a handsome gentlemen caller.
Why is it that super heroes are always
so good-looking?
- Drink up. - I don't want any tea!
I'm sorry.
Sorry isn't good enough.
What's this all about?
Your safety. You know how much I care about you.
Sure. Why else keep dating for 15 years?
You know why I can't marry you. If the...
"if the bad guys ever found out I was Batman
they'd try to get to me by hurting you."
Blah blah blah.
- It's nothing to joke about. - You're right.
There could be super villains hiding in the tall grass.
I'm poison, Dana.
Cursed.
You're silly, McGinnis.
It's not silly for me to want to keep you safe.
Every moment we're together you're risking your life.
I've told you a 100 times.
That's a risk I'm willing to take.
I'm taking the choice out of your hands.
What are you saying?
I'm saying we're done.
- I'm sorry. - Oh, that's okay.
I've only had that cup for 70 years.
My mother passed it on to me.
Guess that's what all this is about.
Legacies.
Doubt you can find this pattern anymore.
It's real China, not that synthetic stuff.
How can anyone be their own man living someone else's dream?
It's been years since I've had enough friends to use
the whole set anyway.
How can I escape the curse of Batman?
Even so, one missing piece
and the set's ruined.
Ruined, I tell you.
I would offer my condolences...
but that would be insincere.
That's it. Caper's blown.
Get out of...
Ah, like water. Very good.
Good of you to drop in considering that three-quarters
of the iniquity collective are from your Rogue's gallery.
Well, it's the last time.
I'm not working with you guys anymore.
- What? - What are you talking about?
You can't quit. The Justice League needs Batman.
Forget it. Batman is dead.
When did you figure it all out?
I guess I've always known, but a few months ago
when Bruce's kidney's failed and they needed a tissue donor
to clone him new ones, turned out I was a perfect
histo-compatibility match with him.
Perfect. You know the odds?
111 -1.
Yeah.
So, you ran a DNA test.
Once I worked up the nerve.
I was 16 years old when you started training me, Bruce.
A punk kid with a smart mouth
and potential I didn't even suspect.
I may have pretended otherwise
but I looked up to you, worshipped you.
What you wanted from me, I couldn't give to anyone.
Tell me something I don't know.
My dad wasn't a superhero.
He didn't save the world from the near apocalypse of '09.
He never went toe-to-toe with Mr. Freeze
but he was a good man just the same.
Even after he and mom got divorced
he always tried to do the right thing.
My brother and I were always provided for.
When mom couldn't quite make the bills, he always helped out.
He tried to teach me right from wrong
would have, too, if I'd ever listened to him.
And he never laid a hand on me although
Lord knows I was asking for it.
- What's your point? - What's my point?
My point is I never once doubted that he loved me
with all his heart. My point is all those warm feelings
I had for my dad, turns out they were just another lie.
Another in the long list of things you've stolen from me!
My point is I just found out
that Warren McGinnis isn't my father!
You are!
What do you want from me?
I want to know the whole truth.
Sounds like you already do.
Guess I didn't want to believe you were so incredibly arrogant
that you thought the world couldn't go on without you.
Or someone like me.
It's not arrogance. It's fact.
You set the whole thing up.
How? You were already a teenager
when I first met your mother.
I don't know. Maybe you dug up some of that
old Cadmus nanotech.
Used it to have my genes rewritten to match yours.
That technology's been illegal
for over 40 years.
Didn't stop the Joker from using it on Tim Drake.
Alright, low blow.
Because you'd never lie to me, right?
Fine. Believe what you want.
But you know as well as I do, accident or not
it's a good thing that you're almost a clone of me.
The world does need a Batman and it always will.
The mantle of Batman is an honor, Terry.
You know what, old man?
All those years, turns out everybody was right.
You are insane. Being Batman is no honor.
It's a curse.
Look at all this.
A pill for blood pressure.
A pill for my diabetes.
A pill to replace my pituitary function.
I don't even know what this one's for.
Oh, yeah, Alzheimer's.
Don't pretend you're some dowdy old lady
who can't remember anything.
I've got questions, and you're the only one
left with the answers.
Besides Bruce, you mean.
Bruce can't be trusted.
I should have realized what he was capable of.
Once he settles on a course of action
he won't stop at anything.
If you think that
you don't know him at all.
Let me tell you a little story.
It was a long time ago, when Batman was young and so was I.
The Justice League found themselves cleaning up
one of my old messes.
The second group of villains to call themselves
the Royal Flush gang or the third.
Who can keep it all straight?
Eventually the League took them down.
Most of them anyway.
That's where I came in.
Waller, should have recognized your hand in this.
No time for the usual pleasantries.
Before you go after Ace
you need to know what you're getting into.
I've met her before. She has the power to give anyone
she's in contact with hallucinations
as you can see.
It's worse than you think.
Ace's powers have evolved.
She doesn't create hallucinations anymore.
She telekinetically warps reality.
Please. Are you trying to tell me all this is real?
Real, growing, and permanent
if we don't put a stop to it all.
Cadmus psytechs predict that Ace is days
maybe only hours, from a massive aneurysm.
- Problem solved. - Not that simple.
When she goes, the psychic backlash
could kill everyone in range of her powers.
That's a distance measured in miles.
Take her down before she takes everyone with her.
I'll do it, Shayera.
I'm the only one of us Ace knows.
She might let me get close enough to use it.
Do you understand what you're agreeing to?
The only way to stop Ace for certain is to kill her.
Hey! Huh!
Batman.
Ace.
Did you like playing with my new Royal Flush gang?
Can't say that I did.
Yeah. They aren't any fun at all.
I gave them their powers
and they still hardly ever play with me.
Can't imagine why.
When I was little, Cadmus used to make me play all kinds
of games, but they weren't any fun either.
They'd strap me into their machines
and poke wires into my brain.
"Ace, can you move this object with your mind?"
Yeah, I can move it.
They weren't really games you know.
They were training me.
Turning me into a weapon
for justice, they said.
They got their weapon.
I got cheated out of my childhood.
I know what that's like.
You do, don't you?
You don't have to answer. I've read your mind.
That's how I knew you weren't going to use Mrs. Waller's
weapon on me.
No, I wasn't.
You were going to try and talk me
into fixing what I've changed.
Before I die.
Yes.
I'm dying very soon.
Yes. I'm sorry.
Could you stay with me?
I'm scared.
He sat with her until her time came.
That's the Bruce Wayne I came to know over the years.
You think he showed mercy?
Maybe. But more likely he'd somehow
already deduced that Ace wasn't really gonna hurt anyone.
He always was two steps ahead of everybody.
That's right. Even when it looks like
it's your call, it isn't. Think about it.
Bruce wanted a successor.
Another Batman. He planned it all from the beginning.
I never had a chance.
Honey, Bruce didn't overwrite your DNA with his.
I did.
How? Why?
Because the world needs a Batman.
Not that I always thought so, mind you.
Before you were born
Bruce and I were enemies.
His Justice League was easily
the most powerful force on Earth.
As you know, I was in charge
of project Cadmus.
Over the years
I came to respect Batman, even trust him.
Guess the law of averages means somebody would have to.
Did you know I was the government liaison
with the Justice League for a while?
I met some extraordinary people in that job.
But none of them were the equal of Batman.
Right. Who could be?
Not my point. I saw him save the day dozens of times
with nothing but his wits, body, and will.
But I saw something else as the years passed.
He was getting older, slower.
Soon he'd have to retire, or more likely, someone would
finally manage to kill him.
The thought of a world without Batman
was unacceptable.
So I decided to make a new one.
I used my old Cadmus connections
to gather technology necessary for project Batman beyond.
Bruce's DNA was easy enough to obtain.
He left it all over town.
Not remotely what I meant.
Then I found a young Neo-Gotham couple
with psychological profiles nearly identical
to those of Bruce's parents.
Your father thought he was getting a flu shot.
Actually, it was a nanotech solution
programmed to rewrite his reproductive material
into an exact copy of Bruce Wayne's.
A little over a year later
your mother gave birth to you.
A child sharing half her genetic material
and half Bruce's.
But when you're making a Batman
genetics is only part of the story.
The rest is tragedy.
Stop me if you've heard it before.
You're 8 years old. Your parents have just taken you
to a rousing adventure film.
A grand time is had by all.
But unknown to you
a mysterious figure hides in the shadows.
My plan was simple.
The killer would leap out at you
and kill your family.
The trauma would put you on the path to becoming Batman.
One problem. My assassin wouldn't pull the trigger.
I argued with her
but deep down, I knew she was right.
People say Batman's obsessive
that he'd do anything to achieve his goals
but he'd never resort to murder.
So if I was to honor all he stood for...
Neither could I.
And yet my dad wound up murdered anyway.
Don't you get it? No matter what you did or didn't do
I was gonna end up being Bruce's carbon copy.
It was fate.
You know, the Lord's been a great comfort to me
all these years.
Try not to look so surprised.
Yeah, I have got a lot to answer for when I meet him
but I'd like to believe that for all the harm I've caused
I've also done some good.
Maybe the angels need a sharp sword, too.
Like the good book says, "He moves in mysterious ways."
His plan is a mystery, but here's what isn't.
He gave us free will.
We choose our own fate.
For good or ill.
I've known Bruce Wayne
for over 50 years, and I've been keeping
an eye on you your whole life.
You're not Bruce's clone.
You're his son.
There are similarities, mind you
but more than a few differences, too.
You don't quite have his magnificent brain, for instance.
You do have his heart, though.
And for all that fierce exterior
I've never met anyone who cared as deeply
about his fellow man as Bruce Wayne
except maybe you.
You want to have a little better life than the old man's?
Take care of the people who love you.
Or don't. It's your choice.
- Hello? - Hi.
Terry? What time is it?
- It's just after 3. - Oh, baby.
I have to be up at 5. What's wrong?
I just wanted to know if we were still on for this weekend?
Yeah. Why?
- Something come up again? - No.
I just want to ask you something.
So ask.
No, not until I see you.
- Okay. - So, Friday night?
- Fine. - Goodnight.
- Love you. - Love you, too.
You're in my chair.
Yeah, guess I am.
Where the devil have you been?
I had some stuff to take care of.
Enigma's overrated, especially at 3 a.m.
You could have called. I made you some soup.
- But it's cold. - Sorry.
Didn't mean to worry you.
I was worried about Gotham.
If Batman's not around...
I've got it covered.
Always.
Kent called. Nothing apocalyptic.
He just wants your opinion on a case he's working.
Said you could meet him at the Metro Tower.
Right. Better suit up.
You should eat something first.
- Keep up your strength. - When I get back.
You're a stubborn piece of work, you know that?
Just like my old man.
Did you see that?