[♪♪♪]
Sawyer. Special Crimes Unit.
[BEEPS]
[TRUCK DOORS CLOSE]
A late-night deposit, inspector?
Yeah, some freshly laundered money
we swept up in our latest raid.
Won't those Intergang bums ever learn Turpin's first law?
You play in my backyard,
you play by my rules.
Modest, isn't he?
[LOUD BOOM] Please tell me that's thunder.
Afraid not.
I guess they think they can change the rules.
[ALL YELL]
This is Sawyer. All units.
We need backup, now.
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
Maggie!
[GRUNTING]
Come back, you murdering scum!
Come back!
It would serve him right if we did come back.
THUG 1: Look out!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Fire the nova bomb. Hurry!
[GRUNTING]
Fire!
[EMITTING HIGH-PITCHED NOISE]
[GROANING]
[SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[PEOPLE MURMURING, MOANING]
[WOMAN WEEPING]
[SIRENS GROWING LOUDER]
You shouldn't stay long, Dan.
She's still very weak.
Hi.
Hi, yourself.
Lying down on the job, huh?
Some days you're the windshield,
and some days you're the bug.
Forget it. You'll be back busting my chops in no time.
Any leads on the heist?
Got our best people working on it.
I... I mean, besides you.
[GROANING]
Maggie... I swear I'll find those filthy creeps.
And when I do...
Dan, these aren't simple street punks.
Punks are punks, Maggie. I am gonna...!
No!
Promise me you'll keep that temper in check.
Promise.
You got it.
Turpin's word.
I'm gonna hold you to that, Dan,
because it's all on you now.
Yeah. I know.
MAN: I tell you, it was beautiful, Bruno.
We jacked the loot
and left Superman kissing concrete.
A few more jobs like this, and I'll own Metropolis.
[BEEPING]
Uh... I gotta take this call.
You heard me.
Out!
[BEEPING FASTER]
Darkseid.
We tried out the tank, just like you said.
I did not return you to Earth
so you could indulge in petty theft.
Petty?
We cleared over 20 million!
I play for higher stakes.
Aah!
Do we understand each other?
[GULPS]
Good.
Serve me well, Mannheim, and I'll make you a king.
[SIGHS]
[REPORTERS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
So you're saying not even Superman
could stop this thing?
I'm saying we can't always expect one guy
to save our sorry butts,
even if he is Superman.
This time, we'll have to tackle it ourselves.
Good luck.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER] REPORTER 1: Hey, Turpin!
REPORTER 2: Dan, Northstar Herald here.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
It almost looks... alien.
Sure, Kent.
Maybe it was a Martian strapped for cash.
MAN 1: What is that?
MAN 2: What's going on?
Let's get outta here! WOMAN 1: Quick!
[CROWD YELLING]
Whoa!
[GROANING]
Superman!
Must warn... Superman.
[GROANS]
SUPERMAN: How's our mysterious visitor doing, Emil?
His wounds are healing at a phenomenal rate.
He's fully conscious, and in quite a rage to see...
Superman!
Get me Superman!
Freeze, bucket-head!
One more move, and you're back in intensive care.
Hold it, inspector!
Everybody calm down.
I didn't fight my way through a battalion of Parademons
to be told to calm down!
And they say I got a temper.
You have me at a loss, Mr...
My name is Orion.
I fled from the fire-pits of Apokolips to warn you.
He's coming.
Who is?
Darkseid.
Mother Box can explain it better than I.
She is a living computer connected to the Source.
MOTHER BOX: Let us begin at the beginning.
What once was whole was split asunder.
And in its place, there arose two worlds.
Worlds as different as daylight and darkness,
virtue and evil.
One is called New Genesis.
Unparalleled in its beauty...
It is ruled by the wise and powerful Highfather.
The other is Apokolips, a ravaged wasteland
ruled by the demonic and omnipotent Darkseid.
He psychically feeds on the despair
and misery of others.
Because of their opposite natures,
these two worlds have been locked in eternal war.
However, an uneasy truce was established
when Darkseid and Highfather exchanged their infant sons.
Unfortunately, this has not diminished.
Darkseid's ambitions.
For years he has searched the galaxies
for the legendary Anti-Life Equation,
a formula that would give him complete control
over all living things.
In his endless search,
he has conquered and subjugated
planet after planet.
Now he threatens Earth.
He's already provided human agents
with Apokoliptic weaponry.
The hover tank?
Is just a prelude. [CELL PHONE RINGING]
Turpin.
I'm here to offer my assistance
in the coming battle.
Well, strap on your six-gun, space cowboy.
Your playmates are attacking Sinnott Air Force Base.
[SIRENS WAILING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
What? Take cover!
MAN: Down! MAN 2: Go, go, go!
Blue Leader One,
I just lost contact with the tower.
Cover me.
Roger.
Locked on target.
Fire!
[MEN PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
Scratch one hero.
[YELLING]
[YELLING, GROANING]
By the Source.
[BOTH YELLING]
[GROANS]
Help! Get us outta here!
[GRUNTING]
This ain't happening.
[GROANS]
I take it the battle is not going well.
It's not my fault.
It's that new guy.
[GRUNTING]
Orion.
You know that creep?
Doesn't matter.
We're ready to begin phase two, Mr. Mannheim.
You mean the power plant?
Now?
Now.
Who...? Who are you?
How did you...?
So many questions, so little time.
[SCREAMS]
[SIRENS WAILING]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
[FIRE TRUCK HORN HONKING]
[GRUNTING]
You know, Superman, I play a pretty good game,
but, uh, not in this league.
I don't know what we would have done without you.
I'm not the one to thank.
It was a good thing you showed up, Orion.
It was too easy.
Oh, yeah. A real walk in the park.
Don't mock me.
Darkseid will consider this a minor setback, if that.
I know how he thinks.
Oh?
Yes.
I'm his son.
I was the infant Darkseid gave up
to pay for his... uneasy truce.
I'm sorry.
I had no idea.
It doesn't matter.
Right now, I must return to New Genesis
and report Darkseid's latest aggressions.
You may use this to contact me when you need further help.
And you will need it.
[BEEPING]
BRUNO: The island's been evacuated, just like you ordered.
And the incendiary's all set to take out
the reactor's cooling system.
There it goes.
You know, Darkseid,
you and me, we make a great team.
Hmm. Indeed.
You have served me well, Mr. Mannheim.
And now, farewell.
Ah?
What gives? What about me?
You promised you'd make me a king!
And so you are.
The king of fools.
Darkseid?
Darkseid.
No!
Gotta be a kill switch.
[YELLS]
[MOANS]
Aah!
[GRUNTING]
[SPLUTTERING]
Come on.
[GRUNTING]
[RUMBLING] Yes!
[EXPLOSION]
Holy Hannah!
Orion was right.
It isn't over.
[♪♪♪]