City desk? This is Lois Lane.
Hit the record button and take all this down.
I'm in Crestview Park on the west side...
and this thing from outer space has just landed.
I don't know what it is, but it doesn't look user-friendly.
- You got plans this weekend, Clark? - I'm playing tour guide for my folks.
They're coming to town for Father's Day.
What's their ETA?
Call the SCU. Get them down here. Fast.
Your mom and dad. What time are they...?
Clark?
Lois, get back.
He's ripping it apart.
Transmit the destruct code.
- Now. - Yes, sire!
- That doesn't look too encouraging. - No, it doesn't.
Superman.
My scream machine is a success, great Darkseid.
Is it?
A success in gauging Superman's strength.
Using this data, I can now construct the ultimate device to destroy him and...
That was your ultimate device, Desaad. You have failed me.
Please, sire. All my years of service to you.
Send me back to Earth, Darkseid.
Let me put Intergang back together. I've learned a lot here on Apokolips.
No one gets the chance to fail me twice, Mr. Manheim.
Give me the opportunity to prove myself, sire.
Let me destroy Superman for you.
- No, Kalibak. - But...
The destruction of Superman is too important to my plans.
I cannot entrust it to you.
As you wish, great Darkseid.
How can he even take that gorilla seriously?
No one questions my judgment, Mr. Manheim.
Least of all you.
To work.
Kalibak. You do not have to accept your rejection.
I can send you to Earth to destroy Superman.
And cover your failure, worm?
Well, technically. But if you were to succeed...
Darkseid would honor you.
- You would be his favorite. - Yes.
It is only right that you claim all the glory...
for this great deed. Do not even mention that I suggested it.
Are you certain?
Trust me, Kalibak.
Darkseid will finally accept you as his son.
Your father's thinking of buying a computer for the farm.
I am not. I don't need some fancy gizmo...
to tell me when the chickens have to be fed.
It's your mother who wants one.
She's aching to surf the net, whatever that means.
When I finish a story, I press a button and it goes straight to the editor's desk.
Heck. That could save you five or six whole steps.
Ah, but the editor can send it directly to typography...
seven flights down, and they can send it to the press room, and...
Okay, okay. I surrender.
This is Lois Lane, folks.
Nice to meet you, Mr. and Mrs. Kent.
Please, Jonathan and Martha.
We've heard so much about you from Clark.
- Really? - We feel like you're practically family.
Will you join us for lunch?
Well, seeing as I'm practically family, why not?
Kent! My office. Now.
On my way, chief.
You all go ahead to the restaurant. I'll meet you in a few minutes.
No hurry, Clark. I'm sure Lois and I have a lot to talk about.
Your editor wasn't angry with Clark, was he?
He certainly sounded upset.
No. The chief always sounds like that. It's part of his charm.
My goodness. This place looks expensive.
- Clark shouldn't have... - Oh, hush, Martha.
Let the boy indulge us if he wants.
Is it true Superman is often seen in this part of the city?
- Yes, sir. - Good.
Hurry! Before the roof comes down.
Somebody should take that bruiser down a peg.
Jonathan!
What was that?!
I can't see a thing, but it sounded like a bomb to me.
Kent. Get down there and find out what...
Superman. Clark Kent's father... still inside.
Are you two all right?
Yes. Go save Jonathan.
And be careful!
Don't move. I'm coming.
The only place you're going is to the grave.
Stop! There's an innocent man.
How naive you are.
On Apokolips we are taught even as children that no one is innocent.
You see, Superman, life breeds death.
Anything that lives must kill something to survive.
And I am a survivor.
Whoever you are...
My name is Kalibak.
I'll settle with you in a moment.
I seem to recall telling Kalibak he was not to go to Earth.
I was just about to tell you, sire. He has disobeyed you.
I know now where he comes by such foolish ideas.
Oh?
He wishes to prove himself worthy to be your...
A technicality of his birth.
As far as destiny and I are concerned, I have no son.
There are people on that train.
Maybe hundreds of them.
More of your innocents?
Clear out. Now.
Not again...
The destruction of Superman is too important to my plans.
I cannot entrust it to you.
Entrust it to you.
To you, to you.
- Clark. Look out! - Clark? Where...?
Now, with your death, I shall prove my worthiness...
- to my father. - Father?
No!
So is this my Father's Day present?
Honestly, Jonathan. You've got more nerve than sense.
He tried to stand up to that big brute...
- all by himself. - Speaking of whom...
No matter how many times I see that, I'll never get used to it.
Me neither.
Sire, I know I disobeyed you...
but I thought if I could destroy Superman...
- And did you? - I underestimated his strength...
but he won't catch me off guard again.
That much, at least, is true.
Please, Father!
You'll beg louder than that when I'm done with you.
What have you done to him?
I asked you a question.
Who are you?
Answer me.
That is who I am.
And when the time comes, you and this primitive planet...
will swear allegiance to Darkseid.
Or you will be destroyed.
Great Darkseid, I do not understand.
Why did you let Superman live?
Superman cannot be destroyed with one stroke.
But it can and will be done.
You sacrificed your son... Uh, Kalibak?
One casualty.
How many will there be before you destroy Superman...
and conquer the Earth?
As many as it takes.
[ENGLISH]