Behind the line, Lytener.
Beautiful day, isn't it?
The sunshine is so... energizing.
That's close enough.
Close enough to what?
I'm not even here.
Lytener?
- What happened? - Get a doctor.
- Is he breathing? - I don't know.
So long, warden.
Thanks for everything.
What the..
No, that was it, thanks for clearing up the quote
your honor.
Ow!
- You okay, Clark? - Yeah.
Just a little... weak, I guess.
Bet it's the weather. Knocks me right out.
- Clark Kent. - Kent.
Do me a favor and cover for me
at the animal rights coalition.
Where are you?
Heading over to Truman Island.
Got a tip on Lytener's next move.
What happened to laying low until this guy was caught?
It was driving me nuts is what happened.
And if he takes a shot at you?
Then you'll know who did it.. Aah!
Lois?
Lytener.
Don't feel bad, Lois.
It's not personal this time.
I have bigger fish to fry now
and frankly, you're just bait.
Unh.
Oh, yeah. That makes me feel better.
Ah. Speak of the devil, and here he comes.
Someday I'll have to figure out
how he's always watching over you.
Lois, I can't hang on for long! The tram's too heavy!
Just wait, Superman. This is only the beginning.
- Lytener. - It's Luminus now.
Tell me, Superman, feeling a little under the weather?
Quick! Give me your hand!
Yes, tend to Lois.
This was just a test.
You'll realize what I've done to you in time.
See you soon.
Even if you don't see me.
- Are you alright? - I don't know.
Unh.
What's happening?
It's... red.
Naturally the sun itself is still yellow
but we're seeing it through a force field
emitted by a series of satellites.
This force field is filtering our sunlight
so that only the red wavelengths get through.
Come on, Lex.
Those are your satellites up there
and Lytener's worked for you before.
How do you expect me to believe you have nothing to do with it?
What you believe makes little difference to me.
The fact is I did provide Lytener resources
while behind bars, but only for legitimate Lexcorp research.
I had no idea he'd escape,
and I certainly didn't tell him
to hijack my satellites for his own revenge.
Heck, why not? You'd love to see superman dead.
Oh, please, Lois.
Forget that I'm losing millions in communications revenues.
Do you really think I'd jeopardize
the welfare of the planet just to settle
my personal grudge with Superman?
Check the trades, SEC reports.
See if Luthor's recently unloaded
any satellite control equipment.
If Lex is behind Lytener
he'll have covered his tracks
put the hardware under another name.
And, uh, while you guys are on that
I'm gonna check if there's anything down in microfilm.
Getting weaker, I see.
You must be at, what, half strength by now.
Wanna try me?
A hologram.
Maybe this is the real me.
But then again..
Maybe it's me.
Or me.
Enough, Lytener. What do you want?
To kill you for getting in my way.
For making a mockery of me and my work.
And how are holograms supposed to kill me?
Well, we might only be made of light..
But so are lasers.
One of you is real.
Ah-ah-ah.
Gotcha.
Unh.
Testing time's over, Superman.
Next time we meet, you die.
Ow!
I just can't figure out what happened to Clark.
I still think we should've waited for him.
He snoozes, he loses.
This is the address. Lexcorp Satellite-com.
- Currently out of use. - And out of sight.
There's supposed to be a building here.
Look! Up in the sky!
It's a bird.
Yeah, but what's it sitting on?
Come on.
Ha!
Unh! Ow.
I think I found a doorknob.
It's unlocked?
If you had an invisible door, would you bother to lock it?
Maybe I can find a light.
That better?
I can have the rocket operational within the hour.
Good, if I can shoot a few of those satellites
out of the sky, maybe I can let in some real sunlight.
Sorry, Superman. No space jaunts for you today.
- Where are they? - Want to save them?
All you have to do..
Is follow the bouncing ball.
Superman, you're almost powerless.
He's obviously trying to lure you in.
And doing a good job.
Unh!
Howdy!
I wouldn't bother.
Here's the game, Superman.
Lois and her friend are somewhere in the building.
Find them, and I spare their lives.
I don't play games, Lytener.
Oh, come now.
After all I went through to remove your powers
I do deserve to have a little fun.
Trying to scare me with holograms again?
With the proper use of laser fields
the hologram actually feels quite solid
doesn't it?
Now what?
Avast there!
Prepare to taste cold steel!
Ha!
Into the briny with you!
Just as well that you found your way through.
I'll enjoy finishing this myself.
How does it feel to be mortal, Superman?
To know pain? Well, don't worry.
You won't have to endure it for long.
No!
I can still finish you off!
Uh.. Ooh!
- Superman, how do you feel? - Disable the satellites?
Aah! Get those lights out of my eyes.
You heard him.
Put him somewhere nice and dark.