[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
You know Cignian fighting techniques.
I'm impressed.
I'm not, if that's all you have to show me.
Patience, Maxima.
Sometimes the hunter likes to play with his prey.
Yes. Sometimes she does.
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
[INDISTINCT MURMURING]
The prey is cornered.
The victory is mine, and so are you, Maxima.
My queen.
My mate.
My foot.
[SCREAMS]
[MOANS]
[GRUNTS]
ALL: Oh, no.
Ahh-uh!
Great, another loser.
Isn't there a single warrior in this whole crummy galaxy
who can take me?
At this rate, I'll die a maiden.
My lady, another candidate has been found.
The scouts have brought viso-recordings
of his heroic deeds.
Sure. I could use a good laugh.
Bring them to my room.
Ow!
[ALL GASP]
Ugh. If I find one split end,
you'll be in the stables brushing the horses.
[BOTH GASP]
SAZU: He lives on the planet called Earth,
although our scouts inform us
that he's Kryptonian by birth.
The Earth natives call him "Superman."
Hm, Superman.
I like those shoulders.
And that chin.
Oh. Our children will be
absolutely gorgeous.
Shall I have the ambassador contact him?
No, I'll handle this... personally.
But, my lady,
your counselors are waiting, and...
Let them wait! God knows I have.
And if this one's as promising as he looks...
you can start ordering the wedding pattern.
Mistress, wait.
DE'CINE: So she took the bait?
You knew she would.
She's young, headstrong...
Hormonal. Having second thoughts, my dear?
I feel like... I've betrayed her.
No, she betrayed you.
See how she ran off?
That's how much she cares for her people.
But together, you and I,
we can change things here on Almerac.
No, my...
My lady would never let us be together.
Just leave everything to me.
[MOANS]
Whoa. Not so fast, legs.
Where you headed? Costume party?
I'm here to find a mate.
[ALL WHOOP]
Well, here I am, babe.
Hey!
Did you hear me say you could paw me?
I don't think so.
Hey, who do you think you are?
I am the Lady Maxima.
[SCREAMS]
Warrior queen.
Head of the royal house.
And leader of all Almerac.
[GROANS]
Feel free to bow.
[HORNS HONK IN DISTANCE]
MAN [ON TV] Angela Chen's special report,
"Man of Steel, Man of Mystery,"
continues after these messages.
Fifty cents.
Ahh!
Where is this coming from?
We're in trouble, people.
The Superman piece is coming up short.
We need to fill two minutes. Anybody have any ideas?
Hey!
I said, out of my way.
Excuse me?
I am the Lady Maxima:
warrior queen, head of the royal house,
leader of all Almerac.
And Superman's betrothed.
[WHISPERING] Thank you.
ANGELA [ON TV]: You know, you've just broken the hearts
of about a million hopeful, single women.
But seriously, as Superman's wife...
Not his wife.
His betrothed.
His destined mate.
If he proves himself worthy.
Really?
And how's he supposed to do that?
Why, in battle, of course.
So where is he?
[GRUNTS]
[CREW SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[CRASH]
[INDISTINCT MURMURING]
I want him.
And I want him now.
I'm waiting.
Huh?
Superman.
Yeow!
And you are?
Later for that. Almerac awaits us.
You need only prove yourself, and...
Listen, I'm afraid you've got the wrong idea.
I'm flattered you've taken a shine to me,
but my home is here on Earth.
Are you refusing the royal throne of Almerac?
Are you refusing me?
Well, yes.
Oh!
[GROWLS]
Oof!
I know you're upset, but...
Now, wait a minute.
Someone's gonna get hurt.
Yeah. You!
[CRIES OUT]
Loser.
And I had such high hopes.
Whoa!
[GRUNTING]
So you have some life in you after all.
[STRAINS]
Harry, there's a man and a woman fighting.
Stop spying on the neighbors, Lucille.
[GRUNTING]
Now he's got her tied up.
No one has ever lasted this long with me.
No one.
You are... my equal.
This is the happiest day of my life.
I'm... glad.
Oh, my goodness.
They're hugging.
Just don't get any ideas.
Of course, now you'll have to marry me.
Uh, you can't just barge in and make demands like that.
Why not?
On my planet, I do it all the time.
Well, this isn't Almanac.
Almerac.
Whatever.
Here on Earth, marriage isn't something you can command.
Marriage is a willing partnership
where husbands and wives share
the decisions and sacrifices.
What planet is he from?
You can't force me to marry you.
Watch me.
[SCREAMS]
Sooner or later, I knew you'd fall for me.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[GASPING]
My lady.
Congratulate me. I'm getting married.
Congratulations.
[GRUNTING]
Sazu. Call the Minister of Rituals.
My betrothed and I are ready to...
My lady.
My throne.
Arrest them at once.
No, Maxima. I think not.
Guards.
You sure you're queen?
[GROANS]
So this is what you pick for a mate.
Doesn't look like much.
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
You'll die for this. Both of you.
When my people hear of your treachery...
Your people were only too glad for this treachery.
They call it liberation.
Traitorous witch!
[SCREAMS]
[MOANS]
No, my lady.
It is you who are the traitor.
A spoiled, self-interested brat
more concerned with trapping a mate
than the needs of your people.
Under new leadership,
all Almerac will prosper and grow.
Isn't that right, my love?
I couldn't have put it better.
Mwah.
Guards, send these three to the catacombs.
Three? De'Cine?
Please, Sazu. Don't embarrass yourself.
Just remember how great it was while it lasted.
[GRUNTS]
[LAUGHS] No!
All right, what's for dinner?
[ALL GRUNT]
Forgive me, my lady. He deceived me.
I... I was a fool.
A dead fool.
No.
I'm still queen here,
head of the royal house, leader of all Almerac.
But you can't just go around killing people.
I have the power to do as I please.
And the responsibility to do what is right.
As leader, you serve the people. They don't serve you.
Now, where are we?
Miles underground.
I used to use these ancient tunnels as a prison.
No wonder you're so popular.
Uh...
[SIZZLES] [SCREAMS]
The tunnels are shielded to prevent escape.
Great.
Mistress... Silence, Sazu.
[MOANING]
We should move before the Carnorite hears us.
[GROWLING]
I'm betting that's the Carnorite.
[SIZZLING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
This way.
[GROWLING]
How big is this thing?
Big.
[ALL GRUNT]
We have to try to stun him, fast.
Be ready to strike.
[GRUNTS]
[SIZZLES] [SCREAMS]
[SCREAMS]
Maxima, now!
[GRUNTS]
[SHRIEKS]
[SIZZLES]
[GROWLS]
[GRUNTS]
What a man.
Later.
[ARABIC MUSIC PLAYING]
GUARD: Halt! Hey!
[BOTH GRUNT]
Kill them!
[ALL SCREAM]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
Superman!
[ALL SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
This time, De'Cine, it's no game.
This time, I kill you.
Maxima.
I don't kill him?
I... lock him up?
For a really long time.
Sazu.
Yes, mistress?
Escort the prisoner to one of the really nasty dungeons.
One with plenty of rats.
Yes, mistress.
Well...?
It's a start.
A start. What about us?
You know I can't stay here, Maxima.
[WHINING] Oh!
Very well.
I release you from our betrothal.
You're free to go.
Thanks.
Are there any more at home like you?
No, but as my mother always said,
"There's someone for everyone."
[EXPLOSION]
[GRUNTS]
I'm here to get that fraggin',
scum-suckin', rat-scratchin' De'Cine,
and nobody had better stop me.
Yeow!
[♪♪♪]