I wonder what new toy Luthor's showing off for the brass today.
Whatever it is, I'm sure it's gonna wind up on all their Christmas lists.
I don't need to tell you what this day means to me, my dear.
You do have everything in place?
Of course, Lex. You don't think I'd let you go out there half-cocked.
What would you do without me?
Let's hope it never comes to that.
Ladies, gentlemen. Thank you for joining me...
on this beautiful spring morning.
As I speak, two Sidewinder missiles are being fired toward this very building.
- Are you crazy? - What do you think you're doing?
You can't be serious.
He's gotta have something up his sleeve.
I hope so.
Quiet, please.
The missiles will never make it here, thanks to...
this.
The LexCorp Sky Sentry.
Its high energy magnetic beam is designed...
to knock out the guidance system of any incoming missile.
Activate.
I said, activate!
It's not responding, sir.
The field setting's been reprogrammed.
That's impossible!
Get it off-line and store it in Sector Six.
Hey, Lex. What went wrong?
Premature product launch?
- Yeah, we want some answers! - How about it?
Show's over, boys.
Those jackals are going to crucify me!
- But it wasn't your fault. - I know that!
The question is, whose fault was it?
- I'll get on it right away. - No!
I'd prefer to investigate this matter firsthand and alone.
- Sabotage? - Has to be.
Luthor's too careful to foul up like that.
But who'd want to destroy Luthor?
Well, yeah, but who'd be crazy enough to try?
Luthor.
This morning's incident was not simple equipment failure.
- Who is this? - If you want more answers...
go to the research and development lab in Sector Six.
Computer, trace the last call.
Trace blocked. Origin unknown.
Lex Luthor, cleared for entry.
Who's there?
So we meet again, Lex Luthor.
Brainiac!
In the flesh, so to speak.
I managed to survive your betrayal by downloading into these computers.
They control the Sky Sentry.
Yes. I needed a way of attracting your attention.
There's always e-mail.
Actually, I wanted to greet you in person.
But as you can see, I'm not myself yet.
So far, I've used these drones.
But they're far too primitive to finish the job.
For that, I need your hands and your brilliance.
You flatter me, Brainiac, but I already have a day job.
I'm the head of the world's largest multi-national corporation!
Don't you think someone will notice I'm missing?
No one's irreplaceable.
Ms. Graves, I'm still pursuing my investigation.
Cancel my appointments for tomorrow and no phone calls...
until you hear from me.
- Understood? - Yes, sir.
There. Shall we get to work?
Why are you stopping?
I'm not some infernal machine. I'm human.
I need food and rest.
There's no time for rest.
But if it's food you need...
Hi, Clark Kent, Daily Planet. I need to ask Luthor a few questions.
Mr. Luthor is behind closed doors and doesn't want to be disturbed.
Is that a fact?
Tomorrow I'm gonna print a story...
suggesting possible sabotage within LexCorp.
I think Mr. Luthor's friends at the
Pentagon should find it fascinating reading.
Mr. Kent, wait!
- Lex, I... - I said I didn't want to be disturbed.
But there's a reporter here with questions.
I have no time!
Maybe he should make time.
Hey! One more step and it gets ugly.
What are you trying to pull here? Where's Luthor?
He was right here. You saw him.
This coffee's ice-cold. Nobody's been here for a while.
Well?
I'm afraid you're gonna have to leave, Mr. Kent. Now!
Do yourself a favor, Ms. Graves.
Call me when your lord and master turns up.
Security, I want to review all building tapes from the last 24 hours.
It appears your little deception is starting to unravel.
A minor problem, easily eliminated.
Granted, Lois, Luthor does a lot of strange things.
But what reason could he possibly have for trying to fool his own bodyguard?
Maybe he just needed some space.
Haven't you ever noticed the way she hovers around him all the time?
But that's her job.
It's no wonder why you're still single, Kent.
Hold on, I've got another call.
- Hello? - Is this Clark Kent?
Speaking.
Hello?
Sector Six. So that's where you went.
Have a seat, guys. I'm out of here.
Superman!
What are you doing here?
Someone fired a bomb into Metropolis. I followed the vapor trail.
Where's Luthor?
Come on, Mercy. Your loyalty could end up getting him killed.
According to the tapes, the last place he was seen was Sector Six.
The R&D lab. He never came out.
Wait here.
No! I'm coming with you.
I must admit a grudging admiration, Brainiac.
These microcircuits are more advanced than anything I've ever seen.
Or will ever see again.
You can't kill me until I finish the job.
And I'll rot before I help you anymore.
I believe I can take it from here.
Why are you willing to risk your life for Luthor?
- What does he have on you? - Nothing.
Before I met him, I was living on the streets like a stray dog.
He took me in, made me what I am.
It's not working!
I think I may be able to help.
Lex.
Welcome, Kal-El.
Brainiac.
Reactivated and ready.
- You okay, boss? - Stop him.
I calculated we would meet again, Kal-El.
So I designed some improvements.
Superman, the Sky Sentry!
The magnetic field's going to tear the place apart!
Get out! Now!
Up there.
Lex!
Careful with that thing.
I want the tech boys to analyze every circuit.
That's really a job for the military.
They have no claim on Brainiac.
Every single one of his parts is registered LexCorp property.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have a charity benefit to attend.
I'm waiting.
Just a stray.
[ENGLISH]