Play the song, Lois. Play it.
You wanna hear Beppo sing, Titano?
Okay, here goes.
Daddy's here!
Hello, Lucy. Have you three been having fun?
Lois, honey, it's time.
No. No. I won't let you take him.
But, Lois, you knew one day Titano would have to leave us.
He has to go on his mission now.
Why can't you send Lucy into space instead?
- I'll go. - It's Titano's job, honey.
That's why he was able to come live with us.
Colonel Lane? I'm sorry, but...
I understand. Go ahead, gentlemen.
No. No.
Don't worry, honey.
Daddy promises Titano is going to be just fine.
So, colonel, how are your cadets enjoying the launch?
Fine, sir, though my oldest is still a bit concerned about Titano.
No need to be, my dear. That little monkey's got the might...
and brainpower of the greatest nation on Earth behind him.
The booster misfired. We're losing contact, general.
We lost him.
Titano.
The meteor storm is right where you said it would be, professor...
larger than life and headed straight for the space station.
- I'm going in. - Happy hunting.
Superman, come in. Are you all right?
I set off some kind of chain reaction.
Superman to S.T.A.R., cleanup's all done.
And I'm bringing you back a little surprise.
- How's he doing? - Well, he's alive, and that's a miracle.
But he's been lethargic since he woke up.
You'd think after 20 years he'd be a little hungry.
According to the records, he's twice as heavy as he was when they launched him.
Titano.
Remember me? Lo-Lo?
- Lo-Lo? - I was 8, okay?
Oh, my pretty little baby. You do remember. Oh, yes, you do.
That's the most life we've seen out of him yet.
Baby hungry?
Looks like you're just what the doctor ordered, Lo-Lo.
Yes, I'd say resuming your old relationship with Titano...
- would do him a world of good. - What do you...?
Oh, wait. I have a job, a crazy schedule and a tiny apartment.
You can't expect me to...
No, Titano, put down that vase.
Give me back the remote.
Come down from there!
Sure was easier to have a monkey in the house when Mom did the cleaning.
"My Life with Titano," by Lois Lane.
With photos by the esteemed Jimmy Olsen.
What life with Titano? I haven't been out since he got here.
Jimmy? Think you could keep an eye on him for an hour or two?
- Me? - You've got to take the photos anyway.
- And I know they'll be terrific. - But...
It's just like babysitting. With fleas.
Great.
Take a look, Superman. You might find this interesting.
Gas pockets in the meteor fragments.
Could the gas have caused Titano's suspended state?
Possibly. We're running tests right now.
That came from the lab.
- Look out! - They're growing.
Move!
- What are those things? - Bacteria.
They must have been trapped in the jars with the meteor gas.
The exposure to our atmosphere somehow caused this tremendous growth.
- Oh, good heavens. - Titano.
Lois, you've gotta get back here. Right now.
Jimmy, I haven't been gone 20 minutes. Just throw him a banana.
I don't think that's gonna be enough.
Hello? Jimmy?
Hello? Back to the monkey house.
Good Titano. Nice Titano.
That's right. You eat.
That's it. I'm out of here.
Superman. Hey, you're not gonna believe...
Let me guess. Titano's a growing boy.
Hey, where'd he go?
Okay, Jimmy. What's the big...
Look, Mommy. Monkey.
Yes, dear. There's lots of monkeys.
No, big monkey.
Monkey, monkey, monkey.
All right, Cheetah. You asked for it.
Bad monkey. Bad, bad monkey!
Criminals, madmen and aliens we can handle, but this?
Don't sweat it, Maggie. These babies will put anything to sleep.
Nighty-night, monkey boy.
That was a short nap.
I'm sorry, Lois, but your monkey friend's going down.
Don't hurt him! He's just a baby!
Okay, a really big baby.
- Hello? - Lois, I left for Metropolis...
as soon as I saw the news. Are you all right?
Daddy? I'm okay, but...
Listen, I've got something I think might calm Titano.
Where are the helicopters with the gas?
Can't bring them in yet.
He won't sit still long enough for gas to work.
Right now Superman's our best hope.
I'll take it from here, Dad.
Titano! Titano, look!
Lois, get out of here!
Oh, no. I don't believe this.
Beppo? Oh, Beppo? Where are you?
- Oh, no! - He's coming closer.
You're sure it's in here?
Yes, I'm sure. So shut up and keep squeezing the monkeys.
Bingo.
What the...?
- Is it over? - Let's get out of here.
It's okay. We got him.
He should be fine here, Lois.
Now that S.T.A.R. Labs stopped his growth spurts.
I guess I have to say goodbye again.
Though this time, I don't think I'll miss him quite as much.
[ENGLISH]