- Huh? - Hey, you blind?
No electronic equipment.
Your watch, you forgot to take it off.
Oh!
I guess I did. Sorry.
Psst! Hey, Mr. Clean!
Yo, rap master Danny!
Hey, stupid!
I love a man who knows his limitations.
- What you listening to? - My walkman.
Sounded like Voodoo Connection.
Oh, I'd sure like to hear a cut off of their new album.
I don't think so. I'm not even supposed to be talking to you.
Yeah, you're not even supposed to be listening to music
but you are.
Wait! Don't go. Talk to me.
It's so boring in here. So lonely.
I've been waiting for someone like you to come along.
Someone to help me shake things up a little.
W-What do you want me to do?
How about a little music for Livewire?
Just to get me in the mood.
Sure. Why not?
Whoa!
Thanks, danny boy. That's all I needed.
Hey, these batteries are dead.
Ooh!
Let's see if they're rechargeable.
Aah!
Oh.
Lights out!
Hey, hey, come on!
Hey, watch out!
Later, chumps.
And as I told Superman.
The SCU will be mobilized within the hour
and ready to move out at a moment's notice.
- Dan! - Hey, Turp!
Inspector, is the SCU
really prepared to deal with Livewire?
If that short circuit shows her mug
anywhere in this town, I will personally...
Pucker up and plant a big wet one right on her lips.
Mmm!
Wow!
Now, where's my real date?
Looking for me, Livewire?
Well-timed, superjerk. Let's rock!
Oh!
You're just delaying the inevitable, Superman.
What do you want?
That's right, let's get to the heart of the matter.
I want justice.
I want revenge.
I want your life!
Ugh!
Why won't you die?
Aah!
Uh, uh, uh. Not this time, superjerk.
But I'll be back, and next time
I'll find a way to take you out... permanently!
Okay, folks, let's see if he'll..
Ha, by golly, he's really doing it.
He's drinking milk out of his owner's mouth.
- Bow-wow, Rudy. - Huh?
Is this the bone they threw you?
A big TV?
How'd you like to have some real laughs?
Poor little parasite.
I've been where you are.
Locked away in a cell. All alone.
No one to see. No one to touch.
And all because of Superman.
Superman.
But we could take care of him, you and I.
And then when we're done
maybe I'll give you a little taste..
Of my power, I mean.
Yeah. S-sure. Whatever you say.
- Oh, baby! - Hey, good-looking!
- Come on to my house. - Whoo! Come to me, baby.
- Over here. Come here, kid. - Oh, I'm the one!
Hi, boys. Wanna make sparks fly?
- Certainly, honey! - Charge me up, baby.
I just keep going and going and going.
Huh?
Aah!
Ha!
Don't play with your food now.
Oh!
Do you know how to pilot one of those?
Not yet, but I'm a fast learner.
Aah!
You know where to go.
Ain't you comin'?
I don't do boats.
- Too loud for you? - No.
It's just that every time I see something electric
I keep thinking she's going to pop out.
That sounds like it's coming from Strykers.
I'd better find a phone.
Here, we can use mine.
Clark?
- Superman! - Sorry, Rudy.
I'm canceling your early release.
Aah!
Oh, no, you don't.
Give it up, Rudy. You're only hurting yourself.
Oh!
So, that's the plan, my purple people eater.
I force Superman into your grip
then you drain away his powers
leaving him just conscious enough
to watch me deliver the final blow!
Auck! Uou smell like fish.
So? Hold your nose.
Uh-uh, you can look, but don't touch.
Don't be afraid. I know how to control my power.
That's what they all say.
You stupid sleaze! I'm pure electricity.
186,000 miles per second.
If I say no, it means no!
Now, don't stay up too late, Rud-ster.
Remember, we gotta stay charged for the S-man. Ciao.
How do you like this?
The fun couple makes the front page
even when they're lying low.
How does it look out there?
It's going to get worse before it gets better.
Well, I'm going over to SCU Headquarters anyway.
See if Maggie Sawyer can give me more than the official line.
- Wanna come? - No, I think I'll just stay.
What?
Alright, maybe it's not the latest word in rainwear.
But nothing beats a plain old plastic poncho.
It won't take long for the cops to get here.
Even less for blue boy.
Just enough time to juice up.
Aah!
Knock it off. Can't you see I'm eating?
Look, Rudy, dessert!
Get him!
Hey, he's covered.
Well, what do you know? The boy scout brought protection.
That ain't fair.
I didn't realize there were rules.
Tear it off!
Ah!
Rudy, the tank!
Super sorbet.
Uh-oh, do not use if plastic seal is broken.
Aah!
Ha-ha!
That's it. Drain him!
Not too much, idiot. I want him left standing.
I know what I'm doing.
Yeah, blue boy, this has been a long time coming.
Get ready to snap, crackle, and pop.
Hey, what do you think you're..
I want him alive so I can keep feeding off him.
And you, too.
You said no to me for the last time, baby.
Oh, no, you don't.
Hey, Superman!
Or should I call you Clark?
I remember now.
In fact, I remember everything about you.
How's that pretty little colleague of yours?
Lois, right?
Aah!
I was going to do this nicely, but give 'em an inch..
The janitor's closet. Dead end, Superman.
Believe me, I know.
Oh, now I'm scared.
No!
You bungling idiot!
We could've had it all. All!
Look at me, you dolt.
This is the face that's going to destroy you.
You hear me, eggplant?
Don't waste your breath, Sparky.
Parasite don't even know who he is.
It's a good bet he ain't gonna remember you.
Do you think he'll ever remember?
Nah, he's oatmeal.
You, uh, need a lift?
No, thanks. I'm feeling stronger.
And it's a nice night for flying.