Hi, I'm Angela Chen.
Tonight, a new segment on Metropolis Edition.
"Where Are They Now?"
This evening, we spotlight John Corben
also known as Metallo.
Who can forget his epic battle with Superman
exactly one year ago?
This is the last known recording of the metal monster
who was later lost at sea.
But is he rusting on the ocean floor
or just resting?
Outta my way, Quantum Rider!
This is the last of your evil treachery.
Pow! Unh!
Aah!
Stupid volcano!
Can I play?
Go play with your dolls.
Fine! I'll go buy my own action figures.
On this island? I don't think so.
Stupid island. Stupid brother.
Aah!
Sarita?
It's a monster!
Whoa! Oh!
Whoa!
Aah!
Sarita!
Are you alright?
I think so.
That was cool.
You saved my life.
Who are you?
I..
Don't know.
You don't know your own name?
Hush up, Sarita. What are you?
Where are you from?
Not sure.
He's lost. He has no place to go.
- Can we keep him? - I suppose.
If he doesn't belong to anybody.
He does now.
I'm gonna call you Tinman.
Tinman? Give me a break!
I found him.
Look at him.
He's big, he's strong like Superman.
Superman?
Steelman, like the man of steel.
That's what we'll call you.
- What do you think? - Bobby!
Look!
Oh..
It's gonna fall!
You gotta save him!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh..
Huh?
What?
- Steelman! - Come on. Let's go.
Hey, did you guys read this?
A trucker up in Raknaveek
says he was saved by a robot.
Peddle it to Angela, kid.
She covers the whackos.
Say, Perry, about this robot story
I was thinking you might wanna send somebody...
He is.
Afraid Lois beat you to it.
That's becoming your mantra, isn't it, Kent?
You think it's Metallo, too, don't you?
Let's say things could get a lot hotter
on the island of Raknaveek,
and I'm not talking volcanoes.
Hi, professor.
I'm going on a little trip and thought
I'd bring a change of clothes.
There's a juicer, a granola bar
a peanut butter-and-jelly sandwich
and some grapes.
I told you he wouldn't eat that stuff.
Listen, Steelman,
we gotta get back to our dad
but we'll see you in the morning, okay?
Wait.
Here's something I made for you
in case you get lonely.
Sarita.
I'm coming.
Superman!
I'll be at the observation site all day
so don't wander too far.
If the volcano should erupt...
Yeah, yeah, we know. Come right home.
Now, listen to me, the pressure's building
faster than we thought.
We could be evacuating any time.
But..
Uh..
I thought you'd be happy to get off this stupid old island.
Come on!
Was he wearing a costume?
A cape? Did he say or do anything unusual?
He pulled me out of a burning truck.
I'd call that unusual.
And he didn't say nothing.
He just ran off with a couple of kids.
Hey, I'm not making this up. I tell you, they were kids.
I've started to remember everything.
You see, I'm...
I'm from another planet.
I knew it!
Yes. I came here to deliver
an important message
to the leaders of your world
but there are bad people who want to stop me.
I'll need a disguise to get off the island safely.
The fate of the whole galaxy is at stake.
You can count on us, Steelman.
Hey, what about dad's old coat?
This should fit him.
Sarita and Bobby, right?
Who are you?
My name is Lois Lane.
I'm a newspaper reporter.
I'd just like to ask you a few questions.
- About what? - About that robot.
The one that saved that trucker's life a few days ago.
Someone said you might've been there.
They lied.
I'll just put that down as a "no comment."
Truth is, Superman, most of us
are so tied up in this project
we wouldn't notice a flying cow.
I only ask because the robot was seen not far from your...
Hold on.
Collins, get over here.
Look at that sonar gauge!
This can't be right. She's not due to erupt for...
Good Lord!
Aah! Aah!
Whoa!
- You're evacuating? - You bet.
That little shakeup was just a preamble.
Yes, you did well.
My pursuers will never recognize me.
- I think we met one of them. - What?
A lady. She was asking questions about you.
Aah!
You didn't tell her anything?
No, of course not.
You're hurting me.
You... did the right thing.
But we have to be careful.
These people can be tricky.
Very tricky.
Lois Lane.
I'd give you a kiss
if I still had my lips.
Let go of me, you walking waffle iron!
Now, now.
Not in front of the children.
The evacuation alarm!
Hold on a second.
Okay, hit it!
Thanks, Superman!
Bobby! Sarita! Bobby!
- What's wrong? - My kids.
They must be in the woods.
They're supposed to head back here
the minute they hear the alarm.
You're not going to get away with this, Corben.
Miss Lane, please!
Such cliches.
How did you ever win that Pulitzer?
Let's go.
We can't just leave her here. She'll die.
So what? She deserves it.
Superman wouldn't let anyone die
no matter how bad they were.
I'm not Superman.
It's him! Isn't it?
Nice space suit, when I'm done with you
you'll wish you were on the moon.
It won't work this time.
Hyah!
We have to get these kids out of here now.
Get going!
What are they doing? Why are they fighting?
We got our own problems, kid.
Aah!
Have a drink on me, Superman.
Steelman, no!
Don't do it, Steelman!
Steelman?
Steelman is dead and so are you, Superman.
No!
Hang on!
Huh? Aah!
How could Steelman do those things?
We thought he was good.
He was, while he was with you.
Whatever goodness he had, though
got buried along with the rest of him.
It's so still and dark.
No sound.
No light.
Nothing.
My mind..
I cannot let it drift.
I must remember.
I am Metallo..