Aah! Mmh.
- Hang on, Tommy! - Just climb down!
I'm scared! I can't move.
- What if he dies? - I'm not telling his mom.
- Look! It's Superman! - Tommy! Superman's coming!
- He's gonna help! - It's okay now. I've got you.
Alright. Who wants to explain what you were doing up there?
- They dared me. - We didn't think you'd do it!
I know it's tough to turn down a dare
but sometimes being brave means using your head
and not doing something dangerous
just 'cause other kids pressure you.
You're right, Superman. I'll be smarter next time.
Yeah. Thanks, Superman.
Okay, then. Bye-bye.
- What a dork! - Is not!
Of course he is, with that corny little speech.
- I mean, come on! - Little whiner!
Shut up!
- Hey, Superman! - We love ya, big guy!
Get your hands up!
Aah!
- Take a wrong step, Mr. Kent? - What?
- Clark! - Uh, thanks ...perman.
Maybe you two should leave the dirty work
to the authorities, hmm?
- Uh, I.. - Yeah, right.
Have you ever known me to play it safe?
I suppose not.
We should have a word about that.
Maybe over dinner?
Um, fine with me. 8 o'clock?
Meet you on the roof of The Planet.
It's a date.
A date? Hmm! Must be this new perfume.
Hey, Smallville! You alright?
Uh, yeah.
A little shaken up, I guess.
You go on ahead, Lois. I feel like walking it off.
Are you nuts? We're miles from nowhere.
- What about the story? - You know us country bumpkins.
10 miles to school and all that.
Your loss. My byline.
- Ooh!
Thanks, Superman. We're okay from here.
Excuse me.
I know you're a busy guy, but I am dying
to get your autograph.
Okay. Who are you? What's the game?
There's no point keeping up the act with me.
The question is who are you?
Let me guess. This is all a distraction to keep me busy.
If you say so, but I should warn you
your makeup's rubbing off.
This.. This is a trick.
How are you doing this? Answer me!
Oomph!
Whoever you are, you don't look so good.
Leave me alone!
I... have... problem.
My friend, I would call that an understatement.
But... he looked like me.
I no understand.
It's alright. Calm down.
How? How could he?
I'm Superman. Me!
- Aah! Me. - What's happening to him?
Why isn't he following my orders?
I warned you, the alien DNA was unlike anything
we'd cloned before.
It must be breaking down.
I say we abort. Activate the auto-destruct.
Get rid of them all while we can.
We are not scrapping the project for one glitch.
Take this opportunity to learn, doctor.
Study him... for the sake of the others.
Come. Let's look your over.
What going on?
Me am Superman.
Yes. Yes, of course you are.
At least his programmed memories are holding.
Although the damage has clearly affected
some parts of his brain.
No kidding?
What am me?
Bizarro, that's what you am.
Mercy...
Bizzaro? That not my name.
If the shoe fits, handsome.
No! Me am Superman!
Me am hero.
Me show you.
That's coming out of your pay.
Ah! There! Me save building!
Unh!
Whoa!
Don't ask me. I just catch them.
Me fix bridge!
That prove me Superman!
What the heck is he doing?
I can't slow it in time, sir.
It not break again.
Nooo! You am no Superman!
Me am Superman! You leave me alone!
So now I'm ruining his day.
Whew!
I wasn't sure you'd really come.
Me remember.
Me need Lois help.
Don't be afraid.
Me never hurt you.
I heard about our date, Lois.
Problem is you made it with the wrong guy.
Imposter! Stay back, Lois!
Me protect you!
Unh!
Lois...
Aah! Aah!
Don't worry. Me save Lois.
Me always save Lois.
Me hero.
Me have memories.
Me know am Superman,
but other Superman make me confused.
Me come to Lois... because Lois friend.
Um, I had a late lunch.
Which I'm about to lose.
So, um, Superman. Tell me about these memories.
What is it you remember?
Girl at lab call me Bizzaro
but that not right. Me am Superman.
Did you say lab?
In mountain where me born.
Me show Lois.
Me like take Lois for ride.
Um, sure. Aah!
But use the door this time.
- Okay. - Ow!
This am home.
Cozy.
Oh, my God!
This is some kind of cloning operation.
Someone's making duplicates of Superman.
Not someone.. Me.
It was a-a freak dressed as Superman!
He burst in here with a woman and scared everyone away.
They just sat there for a few minutes, and-and they took off.
But that not right. Me am Superman.
- Did you say lab? - In mountain where me born.
What direction were they headed?
I trust you remember Superman's run-in
with a mechanical dinosaur?
- How could I forget? - Hmm.
He was so weak from the kryptonite
our man of steel actually bled.
My technicians collected a few drops from the floor
and from that humble beginning, we have this.
Your own army of supermen.
All programmed to answer to me.
A charming image, except for this... technical difficulty.
No! Them no Superman.
Me am Superman!
Me am hero!
Sorry, my friend, but you am toast.
Aah!
- Uhh! - No!
Since it's too late to save the others, we should clean house.
Engage the auto-destruct. Mercy, start the chopper.
There. We've got 2 minutes.
You can't just leave him like this!
You're welcome to stay.
Though I wouldn't advise it.
Decide quickly, Lois. The ride leaves now.
Grrrr! Uhh!
Where think you going?
You not get away from Superman.
Aah! Unh!
Aah! Uhh! Now no one leave.
He's destroyed the terminal!
I can't cancel the auto-destruct.
Superman! We've got to get out!
You! Me kill you!
She meant now, Superman!
We're sitting on top of a half-kiloton of explosives.
Enough, I presume, to destroy even you!
Now! Run!
Aah!
Uhh!
Superman!
- Unh! - Superman... save ...is?
- Unh! - My leg.
Me hold. You go.
Me no am Superman.
You am Superman.
Superman save Lois.
You are a hero.
- Do you think he survived? - I don't know.
I've never been in a half-kiloton blast.
I hope he did.
He turned out to have a good heart.
Well, naturally. He came from good stock.