The Phantom Zone.
We're looking through to another dimension.
Previously on Superman...
You wanna return what you stole.
Yeah, yeah. Just put me down, please.
- Beg me. - I think I may have made a mistake.
The images I saw didn't say anything about her being so power-hungry.
Have the projector ready. If Mala doesn't straighten out, we have to send her back.
I will not go back. I'll destroy every being on this planet first!
Professor.
Mala. I tried to stop her.
She took the projector.
Welcome to Earth, my darling.
Believe me, you're going to love it here.
Almost there, professor.
Now, hang on. Here comes the fun part.
My word.
It's incredible.
These are the animals I saved off the Preserver's ship.
I come up every now and then to feed them...
and steal a few moments to be by myself.
- You know. - If anyone deserves their own...
fortress of solitude, it's you.
Fortress of solitude?
Astounding.
I could spend a career studying any one of them.
I'm sure you could, but right now we should hurry.
Yes, of course.
So this is the orb.
- How does it work? - Here.
Stand close. It's activated by my DNA.
Welcome to Krypton.
Brainiac, I'd like you to show us how to build a Phantom Zone projector.
One moment, please.
Better get out your pad and pencil.
Interdimensional teleportation operates on the principle...
that each dimension in the cosmos vibrates at its own unique frequency.
Fossil fuel engines.
Primitive, aren't they?
But so was Krypton centuries ago.
I see great possibilities for these beings, under my guiding hand.
We'll begin our conquest as soon as my power's up to yours.
And we've gotten rid of that one little obstacle.
The son of Jor-El.
Almighty Rao has brought me full circle, Mala...
giving me a planet to rule and a chance for revenge.
Out of the way, snails.
You...
- you're Mala. - It's that woman who fought Superman.
- And there's another one. - Quick. Let's get out of here.
Oh, my God!
My, they are afraid of us.
Would you like a demonstration why, my darling?
Nothing would please me more.
Hey, hey! Get your... Hey, put me down!
Help, somebody, help, help!
Somebody, please let me out! Please, help!
Outstanding.
Coming through.
Something going on I should know about?
Where have you been, on another planet?
Mala's let a friend out of the Phantom Zone, and they're tearing up the streets.
Hold the door!
Somebody, please, help me!
Help!
- Look, it's Superman. - Hey.
So this is Kal-El, son of Jor-El.
Your father was a clever man...
though I see you share his poor judgment in choosing sides.
Glad to disappoint you.
You'll face the general when spoken to.
I must say, it seems a shame to kill the one other survivor of Krypton.
I'd offer you a place in our new order, but...
- something tells me you'd turn it down. - Guess you're not as dumb as you look.
As I expected. Mala, crush his skull.
Thank you, general.
Come on, general.
Let's see if anyone salutes.
Let me down. Let me down.
- Look at Superman. - Get her.
All right, move it back, folks.
That's it, Superman. Harder!
Mala!
Thattaboy.
Thanks, but I think you just lost your dance partner.
- How's it coming, professor? - You're just in time.
We're ready to proceed.
So close.
- What's wrong? - We're missing a crystal...
that vibrates at the Phantom Zone's frequency, the homing signal to the zone.
Without it, we can't send anything in or get anything out.
But the crystal simply doesn't exist on Earth.
Keep trying. Jax-Ur's getting stronger, and they've got the projector.
Somehow, we've got to even the odds.
I'm paying a roomful of crack reporters...
and not one has a clue where Jax-Ur and Mala could be?
Those guys don't exactly blend in, people.
Hey, it's not like you can just look them up in the white pages.
Although, I think I'd call this a lead.
She's the one he cares about.
Let her go!
Tell Superman we're at Mala's cabin.
It must hurt your fingers, clamping down on my throat like that.
I'll live.
Here's your brave warrior, and dressed for battle, I see.
The suit's to protect me from this.
You all right, Lois?
Jax-Ur snuck off when they saw you coming.
I don't think he feels up to your strength.
Here.
- Keep her covered. - Love to.
I know you're here.
Show yourself, madman.
No!
That was almost too easy.
- Feeling better? - There are so many ways to kill her...
I can hardly choose.
No.
Let her live. She's a reporter.
Let her tell her world that Superman is gone...
forever.
I'm gonna personally lead the army that vaporizes you two.
Or vice versa.
Either way, see you soon.
The two Kryptonian renegades attacked the United Nations this morning...
forcing their way into the security council.
When the world's leaders refused to surrender...
Jax-Ur promised immediate retaliation.
Reports of devastation are coming in from all over the world.
Here on the border of the Sahara desert...
Jax-Ur and Mala created a sandstorm that toppled buildings and buried others.
Elsewhere, in Kenya, a stampede incited by the pair crushed...
And the fate of the world hangs on questions I can answer?
Yes, Ms. Lane. Tell me about Superman.
Was he wearing the anti-kryptonite suit when they sent him?
- Yeah, but... - Was the suit damaged at all?
It looked wrinkled. What does it matter?
We treated the suit with traceable coating.
We couldn't lock on to the homing signal to the Phantom Zone.
But we could retrieve our own signal once it was sent in.
You can get him out of there?
If I can find his signal...
Wait! There he is!
Superman, can you hear me?
- Professor? - Hang on.
We're going to try to pull you back.
The signal's weak. I don't know if I can hold onto it.
He's in pain. Do something.
He's being torn between dimensions.
- Superman. - Don't come too close, Lois.
The radiation.
What did they do with the other projector?
I still don't get it. What good is this scrap pile going to do us?
It's in a million pieces.
That's all right. We only need one.
In light of the destruction that has been wrought upon our world...
it is clear that we have no choice but to surrender the planet...
to the High General Jax-Ur.
You should be proud.
One stroke of this pen, and billions of lives will be saved.
I wouldn't sign that just yet.
What?
- Yes, it is. - I think I can negotiate a better deal.
- Superman. - He's back.
Oh, thank heavens.
Impossible.
Look at it this way, Kal-El.
Death is better than the Phantom Zone.
I'll take your word for it.
- Bye-bye. - No!
Parole revoked.
Fortress of solitude.
I mean, it's not exactly lonely up here...
though I am the only Kryptonian.
Lately, I'm thinking it's better we keep it that way.
[ENGLISH]