Wow, this is gonna be great.
Superman's gonna shred that guy from Central City.
Don't bet on it, Jimmy. There's a reason this guy's called The Flash.
Oh, yeah, well if he's so swift, where is he?
Hey!
Sorry I'm late. Just woke up two minutes ago.
Give me five, big guy.
Too slow.
Flash, do you really think you stand a chance against the Man of Steel?
"Man of Steel." Feet of lead.
- May I quote you? - You can do more than that, doll.
How about an exclusive after the race?
Fast worker, eh?
Just watch me. I'll run circles around this superslug.
Save it for the race.
Don't worry about me, pal.
I got more than enough heat to burn your sorry...
Thank you both for participating in this charitable event.
The rules of the race are simple.
The first man to circle the globe 100 times will be declared...
the fastest man alive.
- Superman, 7-to-5. - Flash by a mile.
These electronic bands allow us to track your progress by satellite.
Swanky. But you don't need a satellite to see who's gonna win this race.
Shut up and run.
Gentlemen, on your marks. Get set.
Go!
Awesome.
Go, go, go! Yeah! Go, go, go!
Madre de Dios!
As they finish their 15th lap around the world...
The Flash still holds a narrow lead.
That's right, fools. Run your brains out.
Ben.
You see, Mark, it works. Just like I said it would.
The problem's always been generating enough high-velocity ionic energy.
But the armbands solved all that.
Now Superman and Flash are generating all the ionic energy we'll ever need.
And thanks to you, they don't even know.
Shut up. Get this through your thick head, little brother.
We don't want to call attention to ourselves
yet. Though the time is fast approaching.
Just sit back and watch the show.
Nimbus Tracking Station.
Batten down the hatches, general.
There are stormy skies ahead.
- Who is this? - You may call me The Weather Wizard.
And for my first trick, I suggest you watch
the skies off the coast of Northern Australia.
Is this some kind of joke?
This should get their attention.
Brace yourselves, mates. We're in for a squall.
That ruddy sky was just clear. Not a cloud in sight.
Bring her around, hard to port!
Hurry, man.
Ready to throw in the towel?
Haven't even caught my second wind.
Slow down. A ship's in trouble.
Yeah. Nice try, Supes.
Hey.
Wait for me.
Help! Help us!
Men overboard!
- Superman. - And The Flash. Hold your applause.
The hull split. We can't contain the oil.
Not bad. But he's still leaving a mess.
Believe it or not, he calls himself The Weather Wizard.
Here's his latest message:
You just witnessed a small displa y of the powers at m y disposal.
Unless you transfer $ 1 billion into m y overseas account within the hour...
the forecast will be decidedl y gloom y.
Hey, I know this yahoo.
His name's Mark Mardon. He's an extortionist.
Didn't he threaten to blow up the metro tunnel?
- But I put a stop to that. - But the money was never recovered.
Hey, what do you want? I ran a million miles just to find him.
No way is this guy going back in business. No way.
You coming or not?
Word travels fast.
Oh, well. They served their purpose.
No, you can't.
I... I mean I know that I agreed to let you use the machine first...
but it's just, well... Well, killing? Isn't that going too far?
Grow up.
- Unusual weather we're having. - You had to say it.
Stopped them cold.
Bravo. Bravo.
- But how...? - I vibrated my body till I melted through.
Hot. Now if you're ready...
Sometime this century?
How did Mardon know where we were?
Freezing us at the speed we were going would take pinpoint accuracy.
The armbands.
There's some sort of device in here besides the tracker.
At least your brain's faster than your feet.
- Sorry for the delay, general. - He's on.
You have 15 minutes remaining.
Unless the money's in m y account in that time, I'll unleash a hurricane...
that will annihilate Metropolis.
Please, Mark. I'm begging you.
I made this machine to help people.
And I paid for it to make a profit.
But threatening an entire city?
- I never thought that you'd... - Oh, please.
Don't play innocent with me. You knew my intentions.
You didn't want to believe them. The machine was too important to you.
Not that important. I won't be a party to mass murder.
You want out? Fine.
- Go. - Just like that?
Just like that.
Farewell, brother dear.
Look. What's that?
It's another weather anomaly. And it's just outside Metropolis.
Oh, no.
He's mad. He tried to kill me. He'll try to kill us all.
- Who? - My brother.
Oh, my God.
It's beginning.
Button up your overcoats.
- Where is he? - In a house just up the mountain.
Wait.
This must be the place.
- He's got some kind of lightning shield. - It works pretty good.
Take it easy. I'll try to find another way in.
Superman.
You shouldn't have come here. Your powers are nothing compared to mine.
You should've heeded the storm warning, Superman.
- There's been a change in the weather. - What?
No!
Help!
Mardon's gonna have to be a real wizard to get out this time.
You know, Flash, this morning I thought you were just a hyperactive jerk.
But you're okay.
Give me five.
Too slow.
Hey, we never did settle who's the fastest man alive.
No, we never did.
On your mark.
Get set.
Go!
[ENGLISH]