And the nominees for the Excalibur Award
for outstanding investigative journalism
are Patrice Bandi for her article
on illegal drug traffic..
Mike Hart for his expose on diet fraud.
Julian Frey for his piece.
"No Profit like Nonprofit."
Good luck, Julian.
And Lois Lane for "Lex-scam, Nuclear Danger."
You, too, my dear.
And the award goes to..
Lois Lane.
Lois. Go up.
Did you hear that?
Yes. I can hardly believe it, either.
As if her ego weren't big enough already.
Ladies and gentlemen of the Metropolis Press
uh, colleagues..
I'd like to thank the Excalibur committee
for nominating my work.
I-I would also like to thank the members
of the Daily Planet editorial department
and the entire support staff for their invaluable help
locating and compiling the data for this article.
I would also like to congratulate
my fellow nominees..
Oh, please.
Oops. Better go wash this out before it stains.
When corruption or waste or fraud is uncovered
we all win.
Thank you, all. I will treasure..
Hmm. Some kind of electro-gizmo.
It looks like it's got a...
When did you join the force?
This is police business.
When we have information
you'll get it along with all the other reporters.
I'm not just "one of the other reporters."
This was an attempt on my life, you know.
You really want to be helpful?
Try making a list of the people
who might want to see you dead.
And try to keep it to one page.
What do you think the chances are
of Bowman actually solving this case?
What's his problem?
Oh, about two years ago
I wrote an expose on police corruption.
It cost him a promotion.
He's had it in for me ever since.
Careful!
Don't worry, Kent. I'm always in control.
If you want, I'd be happy to stay
at your apartment tonight.
Somebody did try to kill you.
And he failed. Look, Kent
I'm not worried. You shouldn't be, either.
And now a very special request.
Is there anything else on?
Paldoverdi's version of "You Win, You Die."
It won't change.
Dedicated to Lois Lane.
Yes, Lois, you.
What a shame that an innocent party like Mr. Kent
must also suffer, but you never were one
to let an innocent stand in your way.
What are you doing?
Getting us out of here.
Whoa!
Clark!
Oh, no, you don't, Lois.
Ohh!
Are you alright?
- Yes, but, Clark... - He's fine.
I was able to cushion his fall.
A little something for your insurance agent.
Arm still hurting?
Mm. About the same as yesterday.
I still think we should've taken it to the police first.
Oh, yeah. I'm sure Detective Bowman won't rest
till he finds out where this came from.
At least I know Edward Lytener will be helpful.
Yes, yes, what is it?
Oh, yes. Very helpful, I'm sure.
It's me, Eddie. Lois?
Lois! Lois Lane! Of course!
Of course.
I wouldn't. Ten gigawatts. Real nasty shock.
I'm really sorry to bother you like this.
It's no bother. I've been in this lab
for 24 hours straight without looking up.
I could use the break. And the company.
The circuit patterns are lot like what they're working on
over at LexCorp R&D.
How do you know that?
Eddie used to work for Luthor.
He was my informant on the lex-scam article.
By the way, Lois, congratulations.
Yeah. Thanks.
Hello. What's this?
"L.C."
It's from LexCorp, alright.
Somebody there must really have it in for you, Lois.
Another in a long line of killing machines.
It's not as much fun when you're on the receiving end.
I heard about the regrettable incident
at the Excalibur Awards.
Yes. And this little goodie was in my car.
I have evidence it was manufactured here at LexCorp.
Really, Lois, I wouldn't leave so blatant a trail
even if I were out to get you.
And you're not?
No. Why would I be?
I respect you and what you do
even when you're taking potshots at my company.
But the device...
This disturbs me as much as it does you.
If it came from LexCorp
I'll find out how it ended up in your car.
I promise.
Trust me, Lois.
Trust him? Why would you do that?
He's just trying to keep you from nosing around LexCorp.
Probably. But I believed him
when he said he wasn't behind it.
The way this assassin keeps warning me
it's like he wants me to suffer first.
That's weird, but it's not Lex.
Lois, my dear. Perry has just handed me
some of your, uh, overdue assignments.
What?
He was worried about you falling behind.
I certainly hope I can come up
to your, uh, award-winning standards.
I'm sure you will.
Great.
You're not safe, Lois, not outside
not in your car, not even here at work.
I'll give you exactly one minute
to prepare to meet your maker.
Uhh!
Uh, uh, uh.
Ohh!
Uhh..
Oh!
Uhh!
Aah!
I believe this is your floor.
I'm not having a good day.
Uhh! Uhh..
Uhh!
Uhh! Uhh!
Uhh! Aah!
I just hate this. I can't sleep, I can't eat.
I feel so... helpless.
- Why don't you just relax? - I can't relax.
I feel like I should be out there doing something
not sitting here wondering
what everybody else is up to.
It feels... wrong.
Why? Let other people take the risks for you for a change.
The world can get by without Lois Lane for a couple of days.
Yeah, just enough time for Julian to steal
all my stories and my byline.
Oh, by the way, Angela Chen called.
She heard about your award on the news last night
and wanted to congratulate you.
On the news, huh?
You know, Clark, maybe you're right.
Let everyone else take care of things.
That's the spirit.
In fact, I think I'll go relax
in a nice hot bath right now.
See ya.
- I got a couple more hours. - Oh?
My shift will be over by 10:00.
- Maybe we could get together. - Okay.
I thought if we put our heads together
we could figure out who's behind this.
Of course, I hate to be taking you away
from your work again, Eddie.
Not at all, Lois.
I'm happy to help in any way I can.
By the way, what were you working on
so hard the other night?
Shh. Top secret.
You certainly have the most amazing collection of gadgets.
But... no TV? No radio?
Never. They're a wasteland
of call-in drivel and news trivia.
It would just break my concentra..
What is it?
You know, don't you?
Know what?
Tell me, Lois how did you figure it out?
You congratulated me on my award, remember?
If you were cooped up in this lab all night
with no TV or radio
then how did you know I'd won the Excalibur?
Such a clever girl.
Hello.
Kent. I was hoping to speak to Lois.
She's not here.
Then take a note.
I've traced the materials she was asking about.
It was part of a lot that went missing from inventory
right after her little snitch Lytener was fired.
Did you get that, Kent?
Hello? Hello?
Eddie, why are you doing this?
What have I ever done to you?
That's just it. You never did anything for me.
And I risked it all
my job, my reputation, my research.
I knew what would happen if Lex found out.
You blew the whistle because it was the right thing to do.
Wrong! I blew the whistle
because I wanted you to notice me.
You didn't. But you will now.
Daddy was a black belt.
You're an unusual woman, Lois.
That's why I've taken unusual measures.
A little trap I designed for your apartment.
You see, you wouldn't have been safe anywhere.
Superman!
Aah!
I was expecting you to show up.
After all, if Lois Lane is in danger
can Superman be far behind?
Let her out of there, Lytener.
You're in no position to make demands, Superman.
Let her out, or I 'll...
Aah!
Unh!
Uhh!
This is my favorite invention
a project I began at LexLabs, actually.
It's powered by the solar energy spectrum of a red sun.
Uhh!
Aah!
That's why the punches pack such a wallop
particularly for you, Superman.
Uhh! Ahh!
Unhh!
Aah!
Ohh! Aah! Ooh!
Superman! The controls!
Are you okay?
A little extra crispy, but otherwise fine.
Tell me something.
How do you always manage
to arrive just in the nick of time?
It's a gift.
You wouldn't be keeping an eye on me or anything?
Well... some people need more watching than others.
Thanks.
Someday, though, it'd be nice to see you
when I wasn't about to be killed.
Someday.