The Lexcorp police battlesuit is the last word in law enforcement.
Once Metropolis City Council approves the prototype...
we're prepared to build enough suits to create a police force...
where each individual officer is as efficient as Superman.
Trying to put the Man of Steel out of business, Lex?
I would think, Ms. Lane, that with your knack for getting into trouble...
you'd appreciate a few extra rescuers.
- Touché. - Whose side are you on?
Now I'd like to introduce you to our test pilot...
the S.C.U.'s most decorated officer, Sergeant Corey Mills.
Gentlemen, ladies, prepare to be amazed.
The Series Alpha police battlesuit is a totally self-contained fighting machine.
In addition to being virtually invulnerable...
it sports a powerful cache of weapons...
including black-light lasers.
An impact grenade launcher.
Jetpacks for flight.
Infrared scopes for night vision.
Lex, this is a mistake. It's too soon.
There is a time and a place for dissension, Mr. Irons...
bUt never with me.
And the agility and strength of 20 men.
- What is it? - Five-alarm fire at Cooper Towers.
There's civilians on the roof.
An excellent opportunity to test the prototype in action.
Fighting fires is hardly in the S.C.U.'s jurisdiction.
But saving lives is.
- All right, Mills. - I'm on my way.
What's going on?
Hey, Smallville, how far is your car?
Right around the corner, toots. We going to your place or mine?
Guess we're working together on this one, huh?
Happy to have an extra hand.
What's going on here?
Superman!
- I'll start with the ones on the right. - No time. That roof is gonna collapse.
You're right. The suit's feeding me options.
- Look up there! - What are they waiting for?
Superman!
Move in tight and lie down.
I'll smother the fire!
Where's Mills?
- Do you see him? - Look!
Nice job.
- Impressive handshake. - I was hoping you'd notice.
Honey, you were wonderful.
Looks like he's got them in the palm of his hand.
They'd better be careful he doesn't make a fist.
But, Lex, this goes way beyond biofeedback.
This man's entire nervous system is integrated into the suit.
We've got to consider the psychological effects...
the aggression factor.
If there are problems, we'll deal with them as they arise.
That's not how I operate.
Oh, yes, it is. You work for me, remember?
Not anymore.
We have more dramatic film today of Sergeant Corey Mills...
the man in the police battlesuit, foiling yet another bank robbery.
We caution parents that the footage you're about to see...
may be too intense for younger viewers.
This is what the bank cameras caught on tape earlier this afternoon.
My Lord. Corey, you're on TV again.
Yeah? How does it feel to have a famous husband?
You're so strong in that suit.
Don't you think you should be more careful? Not so violent?
Look, I'm doing a great job for this city. Why can't you just appreciate that?
I know, but...
It's better for the suit. Makes the contact points static-free.
That's just great. You could've at least prepared me.
What do you want? It's my job.
- What's that? - Brochures, for our vacation.
Forget it. I can't go now, not when I'm getting used to the suit.
This is becoming an obsession.
You don't understand, Trish. You don't know how it feels.
The rush, the power. It's so perfect.
And every day we get stronger and stronger.
"We," Corey? "We"?
You talk as if that thing were a person.
Oh, God, what's happening to you?
Nothing, baby. Nothing, it's just the excitement of it, that's all.
Really.
Corey?
Where'd you pick up that one?
Royal and Park. Business is good, huh?
Business is closed.
Who is this guy?
I was hoping you'd do that.
Look out!
- He's crazy! - Come on, man, out of here. Let's do it.
Come on, Pauly. Get it in gear!
Another junkyard rat.
- Help. - Help us.
- Somebody. Please. - Get this thing off me.
Come on, over here!
Superman. That robot guy, he's gone nuts.
I give up. We all give up.
You don't say.
What do you think you're doing?
Mills!
He's interfering with police business, inspector.
Yeah, well, maybe you better explain this police business right now.
Sergeant Mills remains on medical leave pending an investigation.
Until then, the suit will be off-limits to all personnel.
No. The sUit is mine!
We belong together. They can't just take it away from me!
Corey!
They can't.
Gin.
The sUit.
I warned Luthor this might happen.
Mills isn't wearing the suit, he's become the suit.
Taking it away from him is like removing an arm.
He'll never give it up.
Does it have a kill switch?
There's a jamming device. Attach it to the sUit...
and it'll scramble the neural connections, paralyze him.
- Where's the device? - Where else?
Luthor's pocket.
- Hey, hold it. - You can't go in there.
Something I can do for you, Sergeant Mills?
- They're after me. - Who?
Who? Superman, the S.C.U., everybody.
They want the suit, but they can't have it.
I need it. I have a purpose.
Of course you do.
If you remember, I created that purpose.
Then you can explain it to them. You can make them understand.
Of course I can.
We'll go see them together and straighten this all out.
There's no problem I can't solve.
See? Problem solved.
Get me security.
Yes, there's some garbage that needs to be...
- disposed of. - It's been recycled.
I thought we were allies. I thought you were my friend.
We are. I am. I was just... Liar.
You're just like all the other scum in this town, Luthor.
Always picking on the little guy.
How does it feel to be on the receiving end?
I'm not done with you!
Air ball!
You should have stayed away, Superman.
The suit and I grow stronger by the second.
Not even you can stop us.
You'll never take it away. Never!
He's still in withdrawal from the suit.
The doctor said it'll take a while, but he should recover completely.
The suit seemed like such a good idea.
It still is, if someone could find a way to make it work safely.
It'd be nice to have a little help for a change.
[ENGLISH]