[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR: Previously on Superman:
There's nothing out there but death.
A distress signal
coming from the edge of the system.
I'm too late.
[MACHINES BEEPING]
Maybe not.
Yeah, I saw on TV that Intergang's back.
Oh, yeah?
MARTHA: They're a bunch of hoodlums
with terrible weapons.
Don't even blink.
Children, defend your granny's honor.
A super... girl?
You called, Granny?
GRANNY: Girls, this ninny noodle
wants to play rough.
Make her last moments special.
[♪♪♪]
Lashina. Stompa.
Mad Harriet.
Tear them apart!
Run, Jimmy!
[SHRIEKS]
Aw, poor baby.
Let me kiss it and make it worse.
Ew!
Hands off, gruesome.
Pity we have to kill the little dumpling.
She'd be perfect for my Female Furies.
After a little brain surgery.
Aah!
[BOTH SCREAMING]
Nice teamwork, ladies.
Don't just stand there, you ninny doodles.
Finish her!
[CHATTERING]
Hey! We can't let them do that.
Are you nuts? She's dog meat.
And so are we, if we stick around here.
Come on, Amy.
But what about Supergirl?
What about her? I'm outta here.
[GROANING]
[♪♪♪]
That's it, girlie.
Now I'm gonna have to put my foot down.
Aah!
MAN: So we can expect to see quite a display
from Fleischer's Comet as it passes our orbit.
Not too close, I hope.
Well, two-and-a-half million miles or so.
Quite close in astronomical terms,
but not close enough to threaten.
[RUMBLING, PEOPLE SCREAM]
An earthquake in Metropolis?
MAN: Run! Move it!
Sorry, doc, looks like your comet
just got bumped off the front page.
Right, Clark? Clark?
Heads up, and off.
[ALL GASP]
Kara, I thought I told you to stay out of trouble.
Who, me?
I'm not in trouble.
And by the way, it's Supergirl.
See? Super... girl.
Right.
Hello, big boy.
Come to help your little friend?
Ain't that a kick.
Superman! Aah!
[♪♪♪]
Aah!
[SCREAMS]
Stop, or I'll fire!
Play with fire, and you might get burned.
[LAUGHS]
Can I cook, or can I cook?
[ALL LAUGHING]
Well done, my darlings.
He'll make an excellent toy for the master.
Take him now.
Drat. I'm such an old pudding head.
Where did I put my Boom Tube controller?
Allow me, Granny.
Thank you, kitten.
Bless you.
Oh, no.
GRANNY: Good morning, sunshine.
Where's Supergirl?
Still on that mud-ball planet of yours.
We throw the small ones back.
[ALL LAUGHING]
What do you want?
No time for idle chatter, pumpkin.
We've got to get you ready to meet the master.
Lovely.
[YELLING]
AMY: I still can't believe that Granny and all this stuff
are from another planet.
I'm from another planet. It happens.
Hey, isn't this what brought that traveling freak show here?
Looks like it.
It opens those Boom Tubes to Apokolips.
If that's where Superman is,
that's where I'm going.
Supergirl, wait.
Good luck.
Thanks.
I'm gonna need it.
[♪♪♪]
[BEEPS]
What a toilet.
Yow!
Wouldn't wanna meet him in a dark alley.
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
[♪♪♪]
[ANIMAL GROWLING]
Oi! Got something there, boy?
[BARKING]
[♪♪♪]
[SCREECHING IN DISTANCE]
Oh, great.
Uh, listen.
Um, Amy, I just wanted to say thanks.
You know, for helping out.
Well, I helped make this mess.
I figure I should try to square things.
What was Granny doing here, anyway?
What did she want with you guys?
She was always sending us out to get electronics and stuff.
So what did she do with it all?
There's gotta be more than this.
You know, there's a room in back
she always kept locked.
Bingo.
[♪♪♪]
[GASPS]
Geez.
Granny's been busy.
[♪♪♪]
Aah!
Yes!
[PANTING]
[HORN BLARES]
[GRUNTING]
Dance, monkey-boy, dance.
Show a little more spirit.
The master awaits you.
Hang on, Clark.
[CONTINUES GRUNTING]
Kneel before Lord Darkseid.
I said, kneel, you big meatloaf.
Ever proud, eh, Kryptonian?
I must say, I find it wearying.
What was this bootlicker doing on Earth, Darkseid?
I thought your business there was settled.
I never settle.
What I cannot have, I destroy.
If you attack Earth,
it'll be a breach of your treaty with New Genesis.
I am well aware of our agreement.
However, if the Earth were to be destroyed
by a natural disaster, say...
a stray comet...
well, then I could not be held accountable.
That comet isn't coming anywhere near Earth.
It will now, pork chop.
Thanks to my darling Doomsday Magnet,
which I built on Earth myself.
An old lady needs her hobbies.
[MACHINE BEEPING]
What are you looking at?
It's some kind of clock mechanism.
[BEEPING]
Don't look at me. I didn't touch anything.
[ENERGY SURGING]
Uh-oh.
This is not good.
Definitely not good.
What are you doing?
Making up for past mistakes.
Aah!
Where's a superhero when you need him?
DARKSEID: The die is cast.
Within the hour, the comet will collide with your paltry planet.
The impact will create a dark cloud
that will cover the world, snuffing out all life.
Ooh, the devastation.
Can you just picture it?
SUPERGIRL: I can.
[♪♪♪]
I've seen one planet die,
and I'm not gonna stand by and watch it happen again.
Noble sentiments, my dear.
Aah!
Kara!
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
No.
Darkseid!
Aah!
You've got a lot of guts coming here, blondie.
And we're gonna spread 'em all over Apokolips.
[GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
[GROWLS]
[SCREAMING]
Okay, sugar. The main event.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
DARKSEID: Most impressive...
but ultimately futile.
There is no escape.
Maybe. Maybe not.
Superman!
The Doomsday Magnet.
JIMMY: You know what this is?
Yeah, it's scrap metal.
Supergirl, don't...
Some fireworks, huh?
Now, what'd I do wrong?
I might have been able to use the magnet
to repel the comet back into space.
Oops.
Now I'll have to do it the hard way.
Wait!
It's entering their atmosphere.
Nothing can stop it now, master.
Nothing!
[♪♪♪]
Stay back. I'm gonna try to deflect it.
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
Well, girl, you always wanted to save the world.
[♪♪♪]
Kara!
Awesome.
Oh, great and powerful Darkseid, I...
Furies, teach Granny the price of failure.
No, my precious girls.
Don't!
Don't hurt your beloved Granny.
GRANNY [SCREAMING]: No!
[♪♪♪]
You keep staring at your byline, you'll burn a hole in it.
What? Oh, uh, heh. Yeah.
It just looks so... good.
It's a big story.
You should be proud.
So tell us, Jimbo, is she as cute as her picture?
See for yourself.
All right!
There she is. Hey.
[♪♪♪]
That reminds me, Jimmy.
My cousin's in town, and something tells me
you two would hit it off just fine.
[♪♪♪]