[♪♪♪]
My name is Orion.
I fled from the fire-pits of Apokolips to warn you.
He's coming.
SUPERMAN: Who is? Darkseid.
He's already provided human agents
with Apokoliptic weaponry.
Maggie!
We're ready to begin phase two, Mr. Mannheim.
You may use this to contact me when you need further help.
Orion was right.
It isn't over.
HAMILTON: We've been monitoring the hot zone by satellite.
The explosion triggered a meltdown
in the power plant's central reactor.
It's burning straight through the substrata now.
And it will get hotter and hotter
until it reaches the Earth's core.
What then?
As this simulation shows, it will explode,
setting off a series of violent eruptions
which will cover the earth with more burn holes.
I've never seen anything like it.
Yes, you have.
We all have.
On Apokolips.
Your plan worked, Darkseid.
Earth is ours.
Your enthusiasm is premature, Kalibak.
Superman will still try to resist me.
Then send me.
I'm ready.
I'll crush him this time.
Don't remind me of your ignominious defeat.
You'll stay at my side where I can see you.
Father, please.
No! This prey requires a more experienced hunter.
Steppenwolf.
I look forward to adding a new trophy to my collection.
The radioactive hole is now only a few hundred meters deep.
But that's going to increase, and quickly.
TURPIN: Shouldn't you be paging
your new best friend the buckethead?
I was just thinking about Orion.
What's the matter?
Fried.
Must have been the pulse from the explosion.
We're on our own now.
If the reactor melts through the top mantle,
we'll never stop it.
[♪♪♪]
[ENERGY CRACKLES]
This will be good hunting.
You picked the wrong time, pal.
Ah!
[CREATURES SNARLING]
Para-Demons, attack!
Argh!
[HORNS HONKING]
Jeez. We've got a meltdown on Ayers Island,
a war at Sinnott Air Force Base.
What next? [GASPS]
Ah!
[SCREECHES]
Whoa.
This wasn't in the forecast.
[SCREAMS]
GIRL: Look at that, Mommy. BOY: I know.
[GRUNTING]
GIRL: Superman.
[GROANS]
Superman!
Now, to the kill.
[CROWD SCREAMING]
WOMAN: Oh, my God!
No!
[GASPS]
Stop him!
[EXPLOSION]
Pull around for another shot.
This guy's about to be an oil slick.
Looks like the big guy could use a hand.
Giacoia, move in!
Come on.
Thanks, inspector.
Hey, don't you have a fire to put out?
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
You're a magnificent opponent, Superman.
But even you must realize it's hopeless.
Darkseid.
I could easily destroy you now.
And once you're gone,
the pathetic beings of this planet
won't have the will to resist me.
The few who survive, that is.
[GROANING]
However, if you join me as my loyal vassal,
I could guarantee a modicum of restraint.
Think of it, Superman.
The power you have now,
it's nothing compared with what I'm offering you.
You know I can't do that.
Pity.
Still, if you won't be my knight,
you will be my pawn.
[SUPERMAN SCREAMS]
MAN: Citizens are warned to stay away from Metropolis Plaza,
where police are still trying to contain the situation...
Gotta get down there.
Whoa, cowgirl, what are you gonna do?
Hold a gun in one hand and your IV in the other?
Forces have been mobilized and are en route to Metropolis.
Dan.
Where's those choppers? I need cover. Now!
[♪♪♪]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Outstanding.
[GASPS]
[HISSES]
[SNARLS]
[WHIMPERING]
Thanks, inspector.
Get back!
What do you think you're doin', kid?
This ain't no stunt show.
I'm with the Planet. I'm their photographer.
That a fact? Well, get ready to shoot.
Hey, you overgrown parakeets!
Take a snort of this!
Royer, Colletta, cover me!
That's right, chief.
Turpin and his boys are holding their own.
Maybe even more than that.
[BEEPS]
[CARS HONKING]
[RUMBLING]
What is it?
It ain't no street sweeper.
[CROWD SCREAMING]
What is that thing?
Oh, my Lord.
[WHIMPERS]
[♪♪♪]
Holy Joe.
[GROANING]
Okay, back off. I get the point.
People of Earth,
I am Darkseid, lord of Apokolips.
Here is your savior, cowed and broken.
I have crushed him as easily as I have crushed
all who have dared to oppose me throughout the cosmos.
I am power unlike any you have known:
absolute, infinite and unrelenting.
You have no choice
but to prepare for a long, dark future as my subjects
and my slaves.
In a pig's eye!
[CROWD SHOUTING]
This is our world, ugly.
You won't get it without a fight!
You hear that, Darkseid?
The people of Earth aren't like your slaves on Apokolips.
They don't take kindly to dictators.
If they resist, I will not hesitate to destroy them.
You want a piece of me? Come on! Come on, rockhead!
[CROWD CHEERING]
Jeez. Is he crazy?
Yeah.
Don't they know this is suicide?
Better a quick death in battle than a slow one under your heel.
Darkseid, we've detected military aircraft
heading this way.
I don't care how many crummy planets you've conquered.
You ain't gettin' this one.
No!
[CROWD CHEERING]
That's one for the home team.
Let's finish it.
Very well.
This world dies now.
Darkseid.
High Father has decreed this planet is under his protection.
Any further aggression will breach the peace treaty
and be considered an act of war against New Genesis itself.
The decision is yours, Darkseid.
It is good to see you after all these years, my son.
I've observed your boldness and ferocity for some time
not without undue pride.
Though you're misguided in your loyalty,
I won't quibble
over this insignificant speck in the universe.
I would hate to spoil our reunion with bloodshed.
Return.
Go on, you mangy buzzards.
And don't come back.
Savor your moment of triumph, Superman.
But remember, victory has its price.
[SCREAMS]
Dan!
[CROWD GASPS]
[GASPS]
Murderer!
[GROWLING]
[SCREAMS]
[YELLING]
[BLOWS THUDDING]
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry.
[SINGING IN HEBREW]
♪ Amen ♪
Goodbye, old friend.
In the end, the world didn't really need a super man,
just a brave one.
[♪♪♪]