Need a hand, professor?
No, thank you. I think I'd like to beat this one myself.
There seems to be a compartment in here that I hadn't noticed before.
I think you'll find this very interesting.
The Phantom Zone. Believe it or not, we're looking through to another dimension.
- Incredible. - I saw this in Brainiac's orb.
On Krypton, this is where they imprison dangerous aliens.
Amazing. I do wish the image were clearer.
Oh, dear.
Stay behind me, professor.
Oh, no, you don't.
- What is that? - Look out!
Hurry, professor.
Whatever you turned last time, turn it the other way.
- You okay? - Yes.
Just making a mental note to label that knob.
Help me! Please! Release me!
I've served my sentence. Where is the council?
- Hello. - Have you come to release me?
- Who are you? - Mala.
- Where is the council? - The council isn't here.
- My name is Kal-El. - Kal-El?
Please, bring Jor-El. He will know.
- Jor-El? Wasn't that your father? - Yes.
Help, please.
Hey, fellas. Keeping warm?
Welcome to Krypton.
- Tell me about Mala. - One moment, please.
Mala, at the peak of her career, was second-in-command of Planetary Defenses...
answering only to the high general himself, Jax-Ur.
And when our defenses have been diminished to a pitiful strike force...
who will save Krypton from its enemies?
Jax-Ur and Mala, brilliant warriors each, stood together in service...
to the council for years, till the thirst for power corrupted Jax-Ur's mind.
The council has grown weak.
Krypton needs a strong leader to reclaim its former greatness, and I am that leader.
Together, we will usher in a new age of strength and order for all.
Don't move.
Jax-Ur and Mala seized the ruling council, and would surely have held on to power...
if not for one young scientist who had learned of the traitors' plans.
- Jor-El. - Father.
At their trial, Jax-Ur defiantly claimed sole responsibility for the insurrection...
and was exiled permanently to the Phantom Zone.
Where is Jor-El? Does he not have the backbone to face his condemned?
Bring me Jor-El. Let me spit at him with my final breath.
But the council was sympathetic to Mala...
who they believed was only following orders...
and her sentence in the Phantom Zone was reduced to 20 years.
Professor, I know it's risky, but it's the right thing to do.
Get the Phantom Zone projector.
We're letting her out.
Where am I? Who are you? Start talking.
I'm Kal-El, the one you spoke to.
- You're on a planet called Earth. - Why? Why aren't we on Krypton?
I'm sorry. Krypton was destroyed a long time ago.
You and I are its only survivors.
- No. - This is a lot to absorb.
I should take her somewhere safe until she gets her bearings.
There's no one at the STAR Labs retreat...
- if you'd like to use it. - Thanks, professor. Now, hang on.
- People on Earth can fly? - Actually, just me.
And you too, once your body absorbs enough yellow sunlight.
Tell me more.
And we're the only two people with these powers on the planet?
And you, you're defenseless against us?
Yes. I'm just a human being. In fact, I bleed more easily than many.
Please, put me down now.
Marvelous.
But you have to understand, there's a condition on your staying here.
You can't ever use your powers to hurt people.
Of course. I'll always respect...
your benevolent ways.
You promise?
Wholeheartedly.
Well...
I guess we're ready to try a night on the town.
Right there. Just look through the wall.
I see them. They're like insects raiding a nest.
Here we go.
Where are the other two?
You go after those two. I'm gonna stop that chase before people start shooting.
- Slick move, chief. You're the man. - I told you, always have a back door.
What the heck?
You wanna get out of the way, sweetie.
Hey!
Guess who's next.
You wanna return what you stole.
Yeah, yeah. Just put me down, please.
- Beg me. - I'm begging you. Please.
Mala, put him down.
This one's confessed, and promised restitution.
But, Mala, you can't...
Did Superman do this?
What's with the woman?
- Are these Earth troops? - Sort of.
I am Mala, Superman's second-in-command.
I offer you my promise to this world...
that I will follow in Superman's tradition of just rule with a fair hand.
And I thought I was career-minded.
Mala-mania has even hit Metropolis mogul Lex Luthor...
who had this to say about the ex-con from Krypton:
Now the truth comes out.
Superman and this woman fancy themselves our rulers.
No doubt they plan to populate the earth with Kryptonians...
reducing us to slaves or pets.
An enticing notion.
If Superman really cares about the human race...
he should send her back to where he found her...
to that Phantom Zone dimension.
I'm never going back!
Never!
I think I may have made a mistake.
The images I saw didn't say anything about her being so power-hungry.
The fact is, I wonder if even Brainiac knew the whole truth about Mala.
Might there be a way she could repair the damage she's done?
Maybe. I think it's time she spoke to the press.
Have the projector ready.
If Mala doesn't straighten out, we may have to send her back.
I misunderstood Superman's role on Earth. I...
I don't want to rule your planet. I only want to help people...
as Superman himself has sworn to do.
Yeah, right. And I'm Wonder Woman.
- Excuse me? - Nothing. So tell me...
are you guys an item?
- No. - Yes.
It's not like that.
What?
You'd spurn me?
The last woman of your own kind?
Oh, I see.
You prefer the touch of these inferior creatures.
Hey, who you calling infer...?
You've seen your last yellow sunrise, woman.
Mala.
I will not go back. I'll destroy every being on this planet first!
You okay?
Talk about high-maintenance.
I think I found your weakness. You care about that twig.
I care about everyone, though you're pushing it right now.
If Jax-Ur were in your place...
- the planet would be ours by now. - I'm not Jax-Ur.
No, you aren't.
Professor.
Mala... I tried to stop her.
She took the projector.
Welcome to Earth, my darling.
Believe me, you're going to love it here.
[ENGLISH]