This is a lot lighter than the last one, Uncle John.
You ready to go out and whup some bad guys now?
Got to do more testing, Nate. Lots more.
But that's all you've been doing ever since you quit working for Mr. Luthor.
Grandma and I hardly ever see you anymore.
Once I get it right, things'll be different.
- Back to the way they were before? - Yeah, except for the Luthor part.
- You gonna be home for dinner tonight? - What are we having?
Pork chops and bean curd in a cilantro sauce.
Hey, you're the one who bought Grandma a California cuisine cookbook.
Maybe I should be building myself a cast iron stomach.
We interrupt this program to bring you a channel six special bulletin.
Now from our studios in Metropolis, the Six Scene news team.
Daily Planet media reporter Angela Chen has just located a witness...
to today's multimillion dollar diamond district robbery.
- We go to her now, live. Angela? - This is nonfat decaf, right?
- I don't wanna be up half the night again. - Angela, you're on.
Yes, Angela Chen here, and I've just found a witness to the robbery.
His name is Mr. "B. Bibbowski."
Exactly what did you see today, Mr. Bibbowski?
Oh, yeah. I couldn't believe it.
This guy in a mask, see...
he comes over to the side of the bank and he gives it a karate chop.
Bam! Just like kung fu.
Are you saying that was done by one karate chop?
Yeah. That mook was almost as strong as my favorite guy, Superman.
You know, I remember one time we was fighting this big monkey...
Well, there you have it. One witness but no suspects in this fast-breaking story.
Angela, we understand from earlier reports that this super strong thief...
may have ties to Intergang.
- Really? - Cut!
Superman was right. Plenty of crime to go around.
How about a little target practice before dinner?
All right, everybody. Down!
I don't know the combination. Really. I don't even have key to the men's room.
Shut up!
- Hey, we could use a hand here. - I don't do grunt work.
You do what we say. You owe us.
After today, I'll owe you nothing.
I'll catch up.
Let's go!
Whoa. That's one part of the suit that doesn't need any more testing.
- Wait here. - Hey!
Tell Grandma we're gonna be late for dinner.
Gonna have to address this problem. Maybe later.
Look, it's a dead Samaritan. Say good night, chump.
Good night, chump.
That's putting out the trash, Superman.
My pleasure, Mr. Irons.
Guess you really do know him, Uncle John.
Working on the prototype again?
You said if it could work you'd be glad for the help.
And I meant it. But be careful. You're not invulnerable, you know.
Well, I'm working on that too.
Hey, look!
Time to throw in the old towel. You were just too much for us.
Metallo.
In the flesh.
My new friends from Intergang found me right where you left me.
Dug me out and fixed me up as good as new.
Some might say better.
Keeping your distance. Wise, but pointless, I'm afraid.
My friends at Intergang have done much more than a simple repair job.
They've also added a few improvements.
- Get to the van. - But, Uncle... Now!
You don't expect me to walk all the way up there, do you?
Remember how you left me, Superman? Buried in rock.
I couldn't move. I couldn't see. I couldn't hear. But I could think.
And all I thought about was how I was going to make you pay.
Goodbye, hero.
YoU still here?
- A lovely shade of chartreuse. - You can't.
You ought to be paying attention, my friend.
The tabloids will be all over you.
You're about to become famous: "The man who watched Superman die."
- We have to go after them. - How? The truck is toast.
Here comes our ride now.
We've got company.
- Better let me drive. - No time, Uncle John.
Nate, what are you...?
Uncle John, we're out of gas.
Must have busted the fuel line when you hit Metallo.
- I'll remember to aim better next time. - You did great.
Need some help, sister?
I could make it run good.
All I want you to make is some space.
- Coming through. - Hey, who's he got there?
- It's Superman. - Superman.
You sure you don't need help?
Well, I could use a head start.
- Somebody call the police. - Somebody help him. Call an ambulance.
- Something happened to him. - Where's he going with him?
- What's that? - It's a full-spectrum light generator.
I'm gonna give him intensified yellow sunlight.
Might help him recover, if it's not too late.
Finally. Go tell them about Superman.
- I don't think so. - What's the matter with you?
Officer! Hey, officer! We've got an emergency...
- Indeed you do, madam. - What is this?
All right, people. Where's Superman?
Watch out!
Somebody speak up or I'll tear this neighborhood apart...
brick by brick.
We got nothing to say to you, Robobutt.
- Uncle John, what are we gonna do? - You're staying here with Superman.
Where are you going?
For a test drive.
Want me to do that to you? Now, where's Superman?
Try the planet Krypton.
I'm going to ask you one last time. Where is he?
There's a good lad.
Looks like the erector set's got a big brother.
- Well, what have we here? - Call me...
Steel.
Steel, Metallo. The meeting of the metals.
Well then, Mr. Steel, may the best alloy win.
Yeah!
Don't think I'm going to be as easy as my men, Steel.
Sorry, Steel, I've still got some business in the 'hood.
Come on, Superman, this ain't no tanning salon.
Nice air show, Superfly, but I have a few aerobic moves of my own.
A hammer. Nice touch.
Bet you think you've got me. Well, surprise.
He's got Superman. He's gonna kill him.
Not on my watch he's not.
No escape, Superman. Not this time.
You can drown me. You can bury me.
You can send your foot soldiers to do your dirty work...
but I can take anything you can throw at me. Anything.
Yo, Metallo. Take this!
- He got him. - Yeah.
- Look. - That was the end of him.
Hey, Steel!
Steel, huh?
Well, Steel, you're gonna be getting this a lot...
so you might as well hear it from me first.
What?
Thanks.
[ENGLISH]