He's in a better place now...
where he'll be rewarded for the kindness and thoughtfulness...
he showed so many of you.
I didn't know him myself...
but based on what I've heard...
I wish I'd been lucky enough to have met him.
He seems to have led an exemplary life
filled with courage, dedication and modesty.
Luck.
That's what it boils down to, doesn't it?
The smallest break one way or the other.
It can save a life or destroy one.
And you can't fight it...
no matter how strong you are.
But we mustn't let this tragedy dominate our memories of him.
We mustn't forget the good times and warm feelings we have...
for a colleague and a friend named...
Clark Kent.
It seems like an eternity now.
A few days ago, Perry asked me to interview Ernest Walker.
He was a smalltime thief who was convicted of murdering a woman...
during a burglary five years ago. He'd soon pay the ultimate price.
I'm telling you, I wasn't there. I never touched her. I never saw her.
- I didn't take nothing! - But, Ernie...
- you tried to fence the victim's necklace. - I found it outside my door!
It was a setup.
Look, Mr. Kent, I stole. Yeah, lots of times...
but I never hurt no one. Never.
You gotta believe me.
You're my last hope.
His heartbeat was steady.
His eyes never wavered.
I was beginning to wonder.
There you go, Kent. The file on the Walker case...
and the trial transcript.
Thanks.
Kent, a word of advice:
Walker's got a rap sheet longer than my tie.
I know. I was on the case.
Don't lose too much sleep.
Halfway through the transcript...
I was starting to think Detective Bowman was right.
Give it a rest, Smallville. Time for dinner.
Can't, Lois.
Only a couple of days left before...
Before what? They execute a killer?
Everyone knows he did it, Clark.
Everyone thinks he did it, Jimmy.
Come on, kid. He's a sucker for lost causes.
Let's get some burgers.
Dinner was hard to pass up.
I hadn't eaten all day.
Not that I needed to.
But old habits die hard.
I figured Ron Troupe wouldn't mind if I got rid of his leftovers.
Then it hit me.
On the night of the murder...
Walker claimed he was home alone watching TV, eating pizza.
Not much of an alibi...
but his public defender didn't even bother to follow up.
I found the place closest to his old apartment...
and prayed the delivery boy had a good memory.
Five years ago? Forget about it!
I'm lucky if a delivery boy lasts five days.
Is there anyone else here who might remember?
Excuse me.
Round Th' Clock Pizza.
Yeah.
Yeah. I got your address right here, Mr. Caan.
Be there in half an hour.
Tell me, did you have that computer five years ago?
Yeah, but we purge the database of old customers every year.
Walker wouldn't be on...
Wait a second.
We got backup disks somewhere.
There.
Walker's deliveries could be on these...
along with a million others.
It looked like I was gonna lose some sleep after all.
- Hello. - Hey.
Score one for the sucker.
Kent?
I found Walker's alibi.
It's all here on a little computer disk.
You can clear Walker? What? How?
Sorry, Lois. I gotta make a quick trip to the governor.
You can read all about it in the afternoon edition.
According to the computer disk, Walker got his pizza...
almost the exact moment the murder was committed...
which proved he was innocent.
I could have flown to the governor as Superman and given him the disk...
but that could have raised some questions.
Maybe there was some ego involved too.
I wanted this to be Clark's victory, not Superman's.
I had to get out of the water and get back as Kent...
but there was one little problem.
If the fisherman saw me come out as Superman...
he'd know my secret.
I was in hot water, all right. But more importantly...
how was I going to save Walker without the evidence?
Who else but the real killer would have done this?
- He was afraid Kent was getting too close. - Kent was a reporter.
Who knows how many enemies he had? This might come as a kick in the pants...
but nobody likes you guys.
Any sign of him?
- What if he made it to shore? - From that?
He could have gotten blown out.
Then where is he?
Maybe he's lying low. I mean, someone did try to kill him.
Lane, listen. See that guy?
He was out there fishing at the time. He saw the whole thing.
When Kent's car went down, nothing came up...
except the bubbles.
Mind if I ask him a few questions?
If it gets you off my back.
All right, everyone, let's not waste too much time here.
I think it's a sure bet we've seen the last of Mr. Clark Kent.
Yes, detective, I heard you.
My son's car blew up and went into the ocean.
But are you sure you understand?
I mean, this is serious.
I know. I guess the shock just hasn't set in yet.
If you hear anything else, give us a jingle. Bye, now.
Well, this is a fine mess.
It's not like he's really dead, Martha. He just can't be Clark anymore.
But I am Clark. I need to be Clark.
I'd go crazy if I had to be Superman all the time.
There must be a way to bring back our boy.
I don't see how. Not with an eyewitness and all.
Don't forget, there's someone else to consider.
Pa was right. I still had to help Walker. I
couldn't let his friends go through this...
even if it meant that I had to tell the world that Clark Kent is Superman.
Well, so much for sentiment.
I figured I'd change into Clark one last time...
and go to the governor and tell my story.
If he asked me how I survived the wreck? Well, I was ready to show him.
What are you doing here?
Same as you, I imagine.
Trying to figure out who killed Clark Kent.
He told me he had some evidence on a disk.
I was hoping he'd made a backup.
Wish I'd thought of that.
Wouldn't have done any good. Clark's computer is gone.
Somebody's been through here.
Apparently, but look what they left.
I found it in Clark's phone.
A bug. I've seen others just like this one.
Lois?
I always teased him.
But I had so much respect.
And I liked him too. I really did.
Wish I'd told him.
Well, maybe he'll show up yet.
I thought for sure he would...
especially after I talked to that so-called eyewitness.
- The fisherman? - Yeah.
I found out he has 20/200 eyesight.
He wasn't wearing his glasses. It's a wonder he saw the ocean.
Then Clark could have made it to shore after all.
Yeah, but he would have contacted someone by now.
That's the real proof he's dead.
Superman!
Bowman.
Detective Bowman? I need to talk to you a minute.
What do you want, Lane? I'm busy.
You're the busiest cop on the force, aren't you?
You were the lead detective on the Walker case.
- You caught him fencing the necklace. - Good police work, that's all.
Good? I think it's downright unbelievable.
Like how you were the first cop at Clark's wreck.
Tonight, you just happened to be near his apartment when the bomb went off.
Coincidence.
The bug in his phone wasn't a coincidence.
It's the same model you cops use for wiretaps.
I don't know anything about it.
Come on, detective.
Just between you, me and the wall.
You framed Walker. You killed that woman, made him a scapegoat.
And when Clark started looking into it, you put a bomb in his car.
And tonight, you burned his place, just in case he'd hidden evidence there.
Keep talking, lady. I smell a big libel suit.
Not when we see whose fingerprints are on this.
Give me that.
Hey! Let go!
What took you?
You were going to get Bowman to incriminate himself, remember?
I think this qualifies.
But it wasn't over yet.
Luck still had to play its part.
He's not here? We've got the real killer.
I'm sorry. At the last minute, the governor decided to attend the execution.
It is an election year.
We barely had time for him to make the phone call.
No!
- What's going on? - What's going on?
- It's Superman. - Somebody stop him!
The gas!
Great story, Lois.
Thanks, Jimmy. But the fun's sure gone out of it.
I know what you mean.
Lane here.
What?!
After I swam to shore, I guess I must have found a phone...
and called Lana.
You've been sitting here in the lap of luxury while I'm out risking my neck.
He was recuperating.
Poor thing. When I picked him up, he could barely remember his name.
But he sure remembered yours and your telephone number.
Clark and I go back a long way.
Are you jealous?
Yeah. Jealous of his endless luck.
It's time.
How did he survive that car bomb? How?
He's Superman!
[ENGLISH]