This? Nah.
Pretty.
"I am power beyond your dreams...
call to me."
Yeah, right. Singing "Polly Wolly Doodle" all day.
Who's there?
Control, we have an intruder in building three.
Hey, buddy, watch where you're...
- Please, help me. - Get away from us.
- Hey! - Watch it. Oh, my...!
Man, what happened to him?
Hey, fella, you seem to be causing quite a disturbance.
What's going on? Who are you?
I...
am...
Karkull!
Free again.
And forever!
- What's going on? - I don't know.
Freeze!
What...?
Who are you? What do you want?
Stay out of this, mortal.
Still here?
But when I showed Perry the photos, he said they just weren't "front page."
What do I need a picture of?
- Luthor kissing a donkey? - I got something even better.
You're strong, for a mortal.
But a mortal is all you are.
You don't have the tools to defeat me.
I, Karkull, claim the protection of the Lords of Chaos...
for myself and my own.
There's your page one, Jimmy.
If we live to see it.
Fire!
Cut it. Our luck's no better than yours. What do you think it is?
Some kind of alien force field?
- I wish I... - It's an incantor.
You know, like a spell of protection. It's pretty awesome.
Hey. Behind the line, girlie.
Wait. Who are you?
My real name's Doris, but my elf friends call me Rainsong.
Okay, Tink, back to Neverland.
That thing inside calls himself Karkull. Ever heard of him?
I read about him in this book we sell down at my store, The Dancing Hobbit.
It's that little place next to the Coffee Hut.
- What did the book say? - About Karkull?
Oh, he's bad. The worst.
Seventh level lord of the inner pit. Seeks to transform all human life...
into his bestial demon slaves.
So how are we supposed to deal with that?
Well, if you give me a couple of hours...
maybe I could get my white Wicca coven together and...
Never mind. I know someone who can help.
Fate!
Superman.
- Inza, I have to see your husband. - You've been hurt.
Come.
I don't suppose you can sew too.
Entry level spells. Wouldn't be much use against whatever gave you that.
It was something called Karkull.
- That's why you wanted to see Fate? - Is he here?
Right behind you.
Same old Dr. Fate.
- You heard? - Yes.
Then what are we waiting for?
Not this time, my friend. I've quit.
What do you mean? We need you.
This thing has magic only you...
I know all about Karkull. I fought him a century ago.
Thought I'd won. But if there's anything I've learned from a lifetime of combat...
it's that victory is an illusion.
No matter how thoroughly you exterminate the evil...
it creeps back like a cockroach.
Well, it's time to step on him again.
Not for me.
I've removed myself from the battlefield.
This is my domain now.
The metaphysical realm.
I've moved beyond good and evil.
But there are people trapped.
I'm sorry. I truly am.
Superman.
You and I are alike, you know. We're masters of our destiny.
Don't waste your life in endless battle as I did.
Not when the universe beckons.
You're wrong, Fate. We're nothing alike.
Superman, my own powers would be useless against Karkull.
But this talisman might help you.
Thank you.
You've just sent him to his grave.
What do you care?
We've searched everywhere, even the vents.
There's no way out. Is he still at it?
Like the guest that won't go home.
- Holy...! - Bad choice of words, Jimmy.
What gives? Where's your pal?
He's not coming. However, I have this.
What's that supposed to do?
We'll all find out together.
It's opening.
Come on!
- Great! - Hey, mister.
We're ready. Where do you want us to chant?
Oy.
Jimmy!
I don't remember inviting you.
Kill him!
Careful now, it could be someone you know.
You continue to surprise me, but as I said...
you don't have the tools to defeat me.
But I do.
Fate, I thought our dealings had come to an end long ago.
No such luck, I'm afraid.
What magic do you have that's powerful enough to defeat me in my own lair?
The artifact of Lorta. I destroyed it!
What has been made can never be unmade.
No!
The artifact! It's the only power that can trap him. Get it!
- But you... - Go!
Fate!
Don't let go!
Did we miss something?
It's okay.
Hold on.
The healing balm should do its work.
- What made you change your mind? - You.
- Something I said? - Something you did.
You went back.
You didn't stand a chance, but you went back.
Till then, I thought it was only the forces of evil that wouldn't give up.
I was wrong.
Your helmet.
I'll be needing it.
[ENGLISH]