So how's it work?
- I wish I could tell you. - Top secret, huh?
No, it's Kryptonian technology, based on the Phantom Zone projector.
We don't fully understand it yet.
Can you really look into other dimensions with it?
In theory, it should be a kind of window.
But all we've been able to get so far is static.
You see?
Hey!
- Professor, it's different. - What is?
The glass is cracked. You can see it between the posts.
It works. We're looking into another dimension.
Lois!
Looks like you still got a few bugs to work out, profess...
Professor? Jimmy?
Anybody?
Oh, my God.
Well, at least some things are the same around here.
Where is everybody?
Hey, could you help...?
Nice guy.
This is new.
Luthor?
"The men who saved Metropolis"?
It's 10:00. Curfew time.
Superman wishes you all a pleasant evening and a restful sleep.
Good night.
Let's have a look at that curfew card, ma'am.
Turpin.
That's what it says on my badge.
Now, where's that card?
Oh, yeah, it's right here in my pur...
Oh, whoops, no purse. I'll just run home and...
I don't think so.
Look, there's been a mistake.
And you're the one who made it, lady. Now come on.
This is Turpin. I'm at Lexcorp Research, Ninth and Ross.
Some of them rebels just blew in a door. Send backup.
All right, dirt bags. Time for a taste of law and order.
- Jimmy? - Lois? But you're... Look out!
- It's him! - Blast him.
Get him!
Stay back.
Drop the gun.
We're not taking any more orders from you.
You get one warning.
Come on.
Come on!
Stay in the shadows. They got surveillance cameras everywhere.
We're just lucky Superman didn't follow us.
He... He's so different.
Different? What about you?
- What do you mean? - You're supposed to be dead.
You were working on that Intergang piece.
They put a bomb in your car. Remember?
Sure, but Superman saved me.
He didn't save you.
He got there a split second too late.
I saw the photos.
That's when everything changed. He started wearing the black costume.
Then he teamed up with Luthor. Said he wanted to make the city safe again.
Here's the result.
Who are they?
People who've lost their jobs, their families,
because they wouldn't go with the program.
We're part of the resistance now.
It's your turn to explain. How'd you survive?
- Jimmy, it's a long story, and... - Jim!
We were listening on the police scanner.
We thought Superman got you.
- I was the lucky one. - Did you get it?
Superman's not gonna be a problem much longer.
All we need is the right opportunity.
Everyone, against the walls.
Adults to Detainment Center C. Children to the Lexcorp orphanage.
- My baby! - Mommy!
Let go of me. Let go.
It can't be.
I'll interrogate this one myself.
Get up. He wants you.
Naturally, I was quite skeptical...
when Commander Graves said you were still alive.
But according to this DNA scan, you are Lois Lane.
No question who you are.
You're the one thing that's exactly the same.
The insolence, the outright rudeness.
She's definitely the genuine article.
- But how? - It doesn't matter.
If he finds out she's still alive, who knows what he'll do.
He's hard enough to work with as it is.
So you want me to...?
Yes, but not here.
Hey, I'm not finished!
I beg to differ.
Get your hands off me!
Hey!
Find some other street to walk on, you two-bit tart.
Angela?
Lois? Lois Lane?
My God, it's you. It's really you. You're alive, after all these years.
Can you loan me a dollar?
Out of the way!
Don't do anything stupid, Lois.
This is Graves at Lexcorp. I need...
She's inside the monument.
She's on the roof now!
I'll shoot, I swear!
Lois?
You.
So I am Lois Lane, but I'm not the Lois you knew.
Ever since you... She died...
I've wondered if there were other dimensions out there.
Other versions of me and you.
Hold it. I may be a lot like your Lois...
but you're nothing like the Superman I know.
He's no tyrant.
I had to take control. There was no other way.
For too long I fooled myself into thinking I was doing a simple cleanup job...
that if I did enough good, people would follow my example.
I didn't realize it was a war.
And suddenly, you were a casualty of that war...
and I knew I had to stop it by whatever means possible.
You did this because of me?
You never knew how I felt about you.
I never knew...
till you were gone.
You could've said something.
We could've talked about it, figured it out.
Now look at you.
Married to Luthor.
I needed someone with the organization, the technology.
But Luthor?!
He just takes care of the day-to-day duties.
He knows that if he ever tried anything, I'd crush him.
I hate to disillusion you, but he just tried something.
He tried to kill me.
A holding cell.
There are others. The jail cells are below.
I swear, all I ever wanted for them was peace, order, tranquility.
Hey, look. It's the alien.
Why don't you come down here, creep?
- Fascist! - You should've died on Krypton!
- Where's my baby? - Get off the planet!
At ease.
Something troubling you?
I'm having trouble with your job performance.
All I've ever done is give you what you wanted.
Not anymore, Luthor. Show's over.
Maybe for you.
A gift from your adoring public.
No!
- They'll never accept you. - Oh, no?
I'll tell them how you forced me to enslave them.
How I stood between them and your terrible wrath.
Then, when I toss them your poisoned, green carcass...
I'll be more than their leader, I'll be their savior.
Olsen!
I'm glad you're all here.
You can bear witness that I've been on your side all along.
Save it, Luthor.
How do you think they got here?
I had Superman stop by on the way over.
They had a nice, long talk.
Mom!
S.TA.R. Labs used to be a place for ideas and hope.
It can be again.
But will the people ever trust me again?
It'll take time.
I've got the time. For them and for you.
Lois!
Hamilton sent me to bring you back.
Hurry, there's not much time.
I never thought I'd lose you twice.
Will it change anything?
For me, but not for Metropolis. Not this time.
Lois!
- So that was me? - Yes. And no.
It... It's complicated. I could explain it over dinner.
Dinner? Aren't we getting a little personal?
Better now than never.
[ENGLISH]