Turn your vehicle around. No one's allowed past this point.
Luthor has buried his connection to that cloning lab long enough.
Do you wanna be his stooge, or help a free press?
Lady, you had one warning. My orders are to...
There a problem here?
Yeah. This beefhead...
No problem at all, as long as the lady turns around.
Don't bother. I checked already. There's nothing left up there.
I guess that includes Bizarro.
He must have been completely vaporized.
Just think what it would have been like for him if he'd lived.
First finding out he wasn't...
well, you, and then his home...
his whole world destroyed in one day.
- Could you imagine? - Yeah, I think I can.
He'd probably feel a lot like I did when I learned I wasn't human.
You don't know who you are...
where you belong...
why you're here.
Well, I'm up here training for the Olympics...
- Who's that? - It's a monster!
- I'm out of here. - Let's get out of here. Run!
This no am home.
After all this time, Metropolis still knows so little about...
the real Superman.
Only one person is known to have pierced the iron wall...
around the Man of Steel:
Professor Emil Hamilton of S.T.A.R. Labs.
Rumor has it that he's even been to Superman's secret hideaway...
a mysterious fortress hidden somewhere near the North Pole.
I tried asking Hamilton if this was Superman's home...
but the professor declined to comment.
North Pole? Home?
Why am you locked up?
Me bet you do nothing wrong.
Doggie, you am new friend?
Welcome to Krypton.
What is it you wish to know?
Who am me?
Where am home?
One moment, please.
This is your home... the planet Krypton.
A majestic world of scientific achievement and prosperity.
You are Kal-El, son of Jor-El.
Your father was a world-renowned scientist...
and member of Krypton's ruling council.
An only child, you were born shortly before the end...
of Krypton's seventh age.
Who let you out? Don't tell me we've had visitors.
Oh, no.
Me make Krypton.
Then me am home.
Too many chairs.
Me make room.
He's up there!
He's wrecking everything in sight.
Dada?
Dada. No be scared, me am Kay-Lil.
Me take you home.
That's just dandy. Now we got a hostage situation.
I want this area locked down.
Get those people out of there.
Scram, Lane. This is a police matter.
Yeah, Turpin. Like that really works with me.
Loiz?
- Bizarro? - You know this guy?
Figures, all the wackos come to you.
Me show Loiz new home?
Hold it, bub. You're not showing anyone any...
- Hey! - Wait.
I'll go. I'd love to.
I can't let you do that. It's too dangerous.
And duking it out with him is safe?
Superman will be here soon. I'll keep him calm in the meantime.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, great. Now we got two hostages.
This my house. What you think?
It's you.
Hey, you scare Krypto.
But me forgive you.
Let me guess. Bizarro?
- Any idea what he's doing? - Remodeling.
He thinks he's me, so he's trying to create...
- his own version of Krypton. - Naturally.
That building won't last long.
I'll be right back.
If Krypton is what Bizarro wants, that's what he's gonna get.
I had to take this beat. Humans weren't nuts enough.
- Loiz sit? - SUre.
- So, what is all this? - It am Dada's house on Krypton.
Krypton? You remember Krypton?
Shiny ball show me.
It say me am Kay-Lil, and it show me baby me.
Unfortunately, shiny ball was confused at the time.
Superman! Me am happy to see you.
Likewise, but why don't we continue this reunion outside.
Me not give up home.
No, of course not. In fact, I brought you a housewarming present.
Catch.
Pretty. Thanks.
Kryptonite didn't knock him out.
Our cell structures must be too different.
Time for plan B.
Superman play with Krypto. Here, fetch!
No!
Superman!
This am nice.
Superman, Krypto, Dada, Loiz, all here with me.
Krypton pretty.
So sad now it have to blow up.
Wait.
- Superman! - Superman!
Help!
Superman! Can you hear us?
- Which way? - Like a bullet.
The Fort Sherman Missile Base.
Get people underground. He wants to blow up the city.
Call me crazy for asking, but why would he wanna do that?
To play out the end of Krypton.
Naturally.
All right, men, just hold your positions. Hold your positions.
Hold your fire, hold your fire!
You no stop missile. Krypton need missile.
Bizarro, you've gotta listen.
You'll kill millions of people.
That how Krypton end.
But this isn't Krypton.
Me make it Krypton. Now Krypton explode.
And what about Lois? If you do this, Lois will die.
Loiz?
Loiz not on Krypton.
Right, but she's down there now.
Me save Loiz.
Lois.
- Loiz no want to be saved? - Sure she does.
It's all right. Lois is safe.
I'm fine. See?
Now, how would you like to know what happened after Krypton exploded?
After?
This can be your new planet. A place to protect.
Me hate planet. It am empty.
How can me be protector when no one here to protect?
Actually, I thought of that.
Krypto!
Me am happy now.
[ENGLISH]