[♪♪♪]
SUPERMAN: Personal journal.
After following the coordinates
from my ship's initial flight recorder,
I've finally retraced the ship's escape route
from my home planet:
Krypton.
[BEEPING]
Nothing.
There's nothing out there but death.
[LOUD BEEPING]
A distress signal,
coming from the edge of the system.
No traces of Kryptonite radiation.
Let's drop in.
[BEEPING]
[HUMMING]
I am Kala In-Ze, chief physician of Argo City.
Five years ago,
Argo was a thriving, vibrant world.
But then, without warning,
KALA: our sister planet, Krypton,
was destroyed in a giant chain of explosions.
Krypton's destruction tore Argo from its orbit.
The resulting devastation destroyed most of our world
and sent it moving slowly,
inexorably, away from our sun...
leaving a few desperate survivors
slowly freezing to death.
There was nothing my people could do
but pray our distress signals would be answered.
But now, I can wait no longer.
I have taken a desperate last chance
to save my surviving family.
To my knowledge, we are all that is left of Argo.
Please help us.
I'm too late.
Maybe not.
WEATHERMAN [OVER TV]: It's gonna be a gorgeous spring day
in the nation's heartland,
with temperatures reaching the high 70s.
So all you folks in Smallville, Kansas,
get out there and enjoy that great, big, beautiful sun.
[GEESE HONKING]
Hey!
That's enough of that, Kara.
Hey, Clark. It was such a nice day,
I thought I'd just, you know, "vroom."
What did we talk about?
No "vroom" during the daytime.
I'm sorry, Clark.
I mean, it's great staying here with your folks and everything,
but I feel so cooped up.
I understand, believe me.
On Argo I dreamed about saving my mother
and helping my friends.
And now that I have the power to help people,
why won't you let me?
You need to adjust to life here a little bit more.
Just be patient.
So, Clark, will you be staying the night?
Sorry, Ma, Metropolis is having a sudden crime wave.
Yeah, I saw on TV that Intergang's back.
Intergang? What's that?
Nothing you have to worry about.
Who's worried? I was just asking.
They're a bunch of hoodlums with terrible weapons.
Oh, yeah?
They caused Clark no end of trouble.
Really?
Thanks, guys. I gotta go.
You be good.
Yeah, yeah. Feet on the ground, I know.
So, Pa, Intergang, huh?
We got a new Intergang running riot through town,
and what does Perry ask me to cover?
Some techno geek show.
Somehow I don't smell Pulitzer here.
Ooh.
[SNIFFS]
Or soap, for that matter.
Oh, at least the chief treats you like a real reporter.
I mean, when's he gonna give me a break?
First rule of reporting, kid: never count on breaks.
You want a story? Go get one.
It won't just drop in your lap.
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[CROWD GASPING]
[PEOPLE GASPING, SCREAMING]
I stand corrected.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
WOMAN: No, no!
WOMAN 2: Get out of the way!
Let's go!
They're heading back outside.
[SIREN WAILING]
Freeze! Or we'll fire!
Tell you what, rent-a-cops, you freeze...
[BOTH GRUNTING]
And we'll fire!
[GUARDS SHOUTING]
You see, Metropolis, nobody can beat Intergang!
Nobody!
Well, then, just call me "nobody."
Let him have it.
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
Dump it!
[GROANS]
[GROANING]
[SCREAMS]
Whoa!
[ELECTRICITY ZAPPING]
[GASPS]
Hey, Supes!
Catch!
[SCREAMING]
Let's get the heck out of here!
From now on, I'll leave the flying to you.
[PLAYING ROCK MUSIC]
Yeah! We took Superman on and trashed him!
Excuse me, who trashed him?
Excuse me, who did he slam into a parked car?
GRANNY: Now, now, what's all this fluttering, my ducklings?
Your loving Granny doesn't like her babies to quarrel.
BOTH: Yes, Granny.
An obedient family is a happy family,
and a happy family means a happy Granny.
ALL: Yes, Granny.
WOMAN: Mr. Kent.
Yes?
Your cousin to see you.
Cousin?
It's me, Kara.
I know.
You saw through my secret identity?
Ah!
How'd you get here?
You told me not to "vroom," so I ran.
Listen, I saw a report about Intergang on TV,
and I thought you could really use my help.
Look, I appreciate your concern, Kara,
but I don't want you to rush into something
you're not ready for.
I didn't save your life so you could throw it away
fighting some ray gun-toting punks.
But... No buts.
I gotta get back to work.
Here's a key to my apartment.
Wait for me there.
We'll talk later.
And walk.
But, Lois, I was right there when Intergang hit.
Why can't I help you with the story?
Too dangerous.
Stick to the darkroom, kiddo.
But, Lois...
Can you talk some sense into him?
I've had my fill of teenagers today.
Look, I think one of 'em might have dropped this.
It's a game token.
All we have to do is hit every video parlor
in Metropolis... Good. You go, Jim.
Have a free game on me.
Okay, fine.
She said go, I'll go.
She doesn't think I can do it, I'm doing it.
I'll just go it alone.
Can I join you?
Nah, same size, but not the right color.
Come on, let's try the one across the street.
Hey, slow down.
You said your name's Karen?
Yeah.
And you're an intern?
I thought I knew all the interns.
I, uh, just started today.
And like you, I wanted to make a good impression.
So let's get that story.
Bingo!
What's that mean?
They're the same.
Oh, yeah.
Bingo.
TROUBLE: Hey, hey!
Didn't I tell you to keep out of my way?
Uh, hey, man, i-it was an accident.
Just like your face.
Chill, Trouble.
We're in public.
Granny wants us to be good little boys and girls.
[SCREAMS]
[BEEPING]
That guy's got some kind of laser weapon.
What?
Over there.
How can you tell?
Uh, his jacket was open.
And you could see it from all the way over here?
Yeah! Come on!
Granny said she doesn't want us calling attention to ourselves.
And you see what she does to people who break the rules.
Ahh, I'm too smart for that old bat.
Where do you think they're going?
To Grandmother's house.
Wait up!
We're getting warmer.
I didn't see how they opened the door.
Did you see it?
Yeah, I think it was right here.
Come on!
[DOOR CRASHES SHUT]
Oops.
Don't even blink.
Now, why have you nosey, little mice come calling
on poor old Granny Goodness?
Uh, my chick and I heard Intergang was back in biz.
Sounded like a good gig.
Thought we'd join up.
Bingo!
Let me tell you tadpoles how I work.
I seek out the lost, little lambs
society has cruelly abandoned.
I take them lovingly under my wings,
give them the power to face the cold, heartless world
and kick its butt!
We're in!
But you hardly seem the type.
So bright-eyed and soft-skinned.
Life has not scarred you as it has my other goslings.
Still, we can remedy that.
All right, I've seen enough!
Don't you realize you're being duped?
You think you're getting power,
but she's just turning you into her own personal goon squad.
What are you doing?
What do you think? I'm shutting down this psycho witch!
Eh! Such language!
Children, defend your Granny's honor.
Kill her!
[GANGSTERS GROWLING, YELLING]
[GASPS]
I don't believe it.
A super... girl?
Believe it.
[SCREAMS]
Oh, you naughty little monkey.
Granny will spank you good.
[GROANING]
[GRANNY SCREAMING]
Take a nap, Grandma.
Outstanding.
No, ho, ho, ho.
It doesn't end that easily, my little gingersnap.
What the heck is that?
She's from Apokolips.
Where?
The surprises are just beginning, muffin.
You called, Granny?
Girls, this ninny-noodle wants to play rough.
Make her last moments special.
[♪♪♪]