Lex, stop it!
You will blow us all to pieces!
Not now, woman! Something's happening.
It's... it's...
It's just one more steaming flop.
Baby...
Nothing works!
Lex, forget bringing back Brainiac.
I don't need input from some crystal-gazing parasite!
One who's confused a wench's grip on power
with the real thing!
This is the real trouble-maker for us.
It's pure wild goose chase.
Look, I will prove it.
I will show you what is in there.
Don't be stupid.
This is science. What good is your sorcery?
Unless you plan to turn stone into gold?
Or maybe a frog?
Such ignorance.
Transmutation is what you want to do!
Transmutation is...
What are you waiting for? Do it!
- Okay! - Okay!
By the slaughter of the innocent
by pestilence and plague, reveal the hidden unto me.
There, you see? Just a rock.
A worthless piece of...
What?
It's not important.
Show me!
Critical system failure in three seconds.
Two seconds.
One second.
No, keep the image!
There is still Brainiac in the universe.
There is no way to tell where it happened.
Wrong.
I saw enough of those stars
to determine the explosion's coordinates.
It should be a simple matter.
You saw the wild goose again.
Concentrate on us, baby.
Space is too far.
Together, we can rule this world.
If you like this world so much, keep your fool mouth shut.
Then maybe I'll let you keep it.
Me, I'm going to be a God again.
Speed it up!
Sinestro, don't forget the floor.
I want radiation shielding
from every direction.
Rampage...
Help Bizarro.
Don't distort the metal, moron!
I don't even know why we're doing this.
Killer Frost, if Weather Wizard here
doesn't shape up I'm holding you accountable.
Whatever.
Structural integrity is crucial.
Okay! Got it.
Geez.
Soon, people, the Secret Society
will no longer exist.
Instead, you'll become the new ruling class of the universe.
You are the lucky few, the chosen
witnesses to the moment I seize my Godhead.
Luthor, what kind of game is this?
Because so far, it's no fun.
Bear with me, Toyman. You'll get the hang of it.
You're going to help me collect
some newly discovered pieces of Brainiac.
Swell.
So you merge with a living computer, like you did before.
You become more powerful than all of us put together
but what do we get?
You'll all be my lieutenants in the new order.
Of course, if you don't like those terms
you better stop me now while you still have a chance.
But you'd also better remember what happened to poor Goldface.
I'm already more powerful than all of you put together.
Excuse me.
Don't take this the wrong way, but what exactly are we doing?
I was coming to that.
I reconfigured Grodd's cloaking field into a hyperspatial drive.
You're not serious!
Little bit.
Why is my headquarters moving?
Hey! What's going on?
I demand to know what's going on!
Quiet, Grodd.
You.
Come to gloat at me again?
I'm not some monkey in a zoo throwing...
Shh.
Listen, I've been very, very bad.
I backed the wrong pony.
It should have been you.
Oh, you finally sussed it out.
That hairless sweetheart of yours isn't a leader.
- He's a thug. - And how.
I don't like to compete for Lex with a dead computer.
I want you to be my man in charge, like before.
So, baby, what do you want?
Oh. Why, only you, my dear.
And Luthor's fat head on a plate.
That's one mother of a laser show.
Toyman?
We should be reaching the Brainiac remnants soon.
By the way, thank you for making me your navigator, Luthor.
I always love learning a new controller.
Just keep us on course.
The slightest error, and we're dead.
I wouldn't worry about it, Neanderthal.
The way I see it, you're dead either way.
I'd like to complete this transaction
with as little bloodshed as possible, Lex.
Now, put your hands up and have Toyman turn us around.
Don't look at him, big boy.
Grodd is leader.
Luthor?
Finish that off!
Giganta, you're out of jail.
How's your head?
Pretty good, considering you tried to fry my brain.
Don't get grabby, thunder thighs.
Grodd is mine now.
Hey.
One creepsicle coming up.
You are so annoying.
Trapped like a rat.
It's very weird.
You were never so much fun when we were together.
You wouldn't believe what this cost me.
Around the world.
Rock the cradle.
Sleeper.
Luthor! Look out!
Give it up, Lex.
You're only delaying the inevitable.
You're right.
if it's all the same to you
I'd rather snap your neck with my bare hands.
You know, this mutiny was easy.
The Secret Society hates you.
Ah! Like they love you.
Idiotic simian!
Half-baked objectivist!
You're ill-equipped to lead, Lex.
A lower primate, masquerading as an intellectual.
I'm the more accomplished, both physically and mentally.
Took you long enough.
I was beginning to think I'd figured you wrong.
Now, bow down to me.
Who is master here?
You... are.
Get up.
Take six steps forward.
Get in.
I should have let you rot in jail.
Goodbye, Grodd.
It could have gone the other way.
It really could have, couldn't it?
No.
But why speak ill of the dead?
You twisted pink rat-hole of a hominid, I'm not done with you!
I'll get out of this, and when I do...
Can any of you give me one good reason to let you live?
Killer Frost, you've got a future.
Get rid of the rest.
You got it.
We're here.
Darling, Grodd must have used mind control.
Okay, maybe not.
But, baby, you don't ever doubt that I love you, correct?
I-I-I know I did something bad.
I'm a sick person.
You don't know what it's like to be me.
Don't be afraid, darling.
You still have a big role in my plan.
In fact, I can't do this without you.
I used to think magic was unknowable
unpredictable, and not to be trusted.
You've taught me so much, Tala.
Even my wealth of scientific knowledge
would never have been up to this task.
You will be the mystic conduit
that will siphon Brainiac's essence from the debris.
I'll be able to reconstitute him from that energy.
But I doubt you'll see it.
You planned this all along. Even before I...
I'm a sick person, too.
Luthor, the collection panels are in place.
Lex, please!
I beg you!
Hold that thought.
Do it!
I said, do it!
He cannot hear you, Lex Luthor.
Time has stopped.
We exist between two ticks of the clock.
In my travels through the myriad paths of infinity
I have seen the first and the last.
But what you do today threatens the entire universe
past, present, and future.
I should hope it does.
Look, I didn't catch the name.
Metron, scientist and chronicler.
Well, Metron, I'll soon be ready for anything
the universe can throw at me.
I'm about to become a God.
You don't know what a God is.
Or what you are unleashing.
Tampering with forces beyond my ken, and so forth?
Nice try.
If you want my power, make your move.
Otherwise, you can get lost.
You will regret your decision.
We all will.
♪ Twinkle twinkle Brainiac ♪
♪ Tala's gonna bring you back ♪
Lex!
Brainiac, I'm coming.
People, meet your new lord and master!
It seems I have you to thank for my resurrection.
Though your world will suffer slowly
I grant you a quick death.
That rodent thunderbar thinks he can rule Apokolips
in Darkseid's stead.
We'll be the ones who deliver
his pestilent corpse to Granny Goodness.
Welcome home, oh, mighty Darkseid.
Arise, my children.
Let this meaningless battle for control end today.
Of course, lord.
We had thought ourselves bereft forever.
Only the slimmest of chances
has allowed me to overcome my death
at the hands of Superman.
But let the universe howl in despair
for I have returned.
What is your will, my lord?
As ever, to search for the Anti-Life Equation
that I may bring order to this aimless universe.
But first, Superman must suffer for killing me.
His adopted world will die screaming.
Only then will I seek the ultimate end.
Forgive me, lord, but an attack on Earth
would violate your pact with Highfather.
New Genesis would doubtless retaliate.
Where do you think I'm going next?
Superman!
You'd better get outside, quick!
We have a little problem.