- Ha ha. - Come on!
- Disaster. - You don't know the half of it.
We'll be lucky if we can make the rent on this toilet.
- That's it? - Nobody's betting.
Who can blame them?
It's no good. There isn't enough.
The last remnant of Brainiac but there isn't enough to work with.
Perhaps if you constructed a positronic event chamber.
Yes, yes, that could work, but where would I get the money?
Between the government freezing my assets
and the cost of running this secret society...
He's talking to his imaginary friend again.
You're a resourceful human, Luthor.
I'm sure you'll find a way.
What do you want, Sonar?
You busy? Roulette wants to...
I'm more than capable of speaking for myself.
Lex, darling, I'm having some serious financial problems
and I'm afraid you're to blame.
Well, don't look at me to bail you out, Roulette.
I'm the one who skims you.
You know I don't like to complain, Lex
but you are taking a much bigger cut of the gross
than Grodd ever did and Meta-Brawl receipts are down.
I've seen the books.
Now, don't think me ungrateful but you've been poaching
the best fighters for your so-called secret society.
Pity. Cut to the chase, Roulette. What do you want?
If I could only have a few star attractions in the ring...
Bizarro, Sinestro...
Maybe Bizarro versus Sinestro.
Back off, hot pants. Give the man some space.
You're playing with fire, witch.
- Who's playing? - Tala!
Come on, let 'em go at it a minute.
There's not going to be any fighting.
At least not here.
Sonar, I think you've given me the solution
to Roulette's problem and mine as well.
Of course, the new Meta-Brawl. All-girl fights all the time!
We'll call it The Glamour Slam or The Belles Of The Brawl.
Chickapalooza!
With the right backing, it's a million-dollar idea. A cash cow!
But even this won't work if the girls are all
second-string villains.
Who said anything about villains?
Nowhere to run, nowhere to hide.
- Need a hand, Canary? - Not from you.
Suit yourself.
I've never seen you so sloppy. What's the deal?
Get out of my way.
I don't need your help, Huntress.
Right, you were doing a fabulous job
of getting your butt handed to you.
What did he do, anyway?
- Stole a wallet. - Shut up!
You got creamed by a pickpocket?
- You sure you're okay? - Worried?
- Curious. - Right.
I didn't think you cared about anyone.
I'm telling you, Q, Canary's totally off her game.
I think she's moonlighting?
Maybe she's stepping out on Green Arrow.
The deeper mystery here is why do you even care.
Isn't this the woman who beat the snot out of you
a few months back?
She got a lucky shot in.
Okay, five or six lucky shots.
Anyway, that's not the point...
Aha! As I suspected.
Thirty two flavors.
There's something wrong here, Q. I can feel it.
I'm the conspiracy theorist and even I don't see anything.
So what are you wearing?
Blue overcoat, fedora.
You really stink at this.
Orange socks.
Piece of...
cake.
Going down?
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to another ultra-exclusive evening
of Meta-Brawl Glamour Slam.
My name is Roulette, and I make the rules.
Prepare to see the biggest, baddest, super-powered struggle
for dominance that it has ever been my pleasure to present.
A no-holds-barred fight between two legendary ladies
of the League, Fire, the blistering babe from Brazil
and the sultry siren of the Sonic Smackdown
the undefeated queen of the Glamour Slam, Black Canary.
Place your bets, ladies and gentlemen.
Let the pain begin.
Ha-ah!
And the winner is...
Jeez, what's wrong with you? You almost killed Fire back there.
Are you undercover? ls Roulette blackmailing you?
Talk to me.
You've got worse than that coming.
You better call the League in on...
Terrific.
What's-what's going...
Thanks for saving us the trouble.
We really appreciate it.
How was I supposed to know you snapped out of it?
I mean, I couldn't be sure.
They've had you up every night working the arena.
No wonder you've been fighting like a girl.
You know what I mean.
You don't remember, do you?
You did that to her.
No way.
Where do you think you got that burn?
It wasn't your fault.
They must be using some kind of mind control technology.
Grodd's.
Wherever it comes from
that stuff's a little too efficient for my taste.
Your earpiece was wrecked in the fight.
We can't phone for help.
Yeah, yeah, I think you're right.
The League comlinks.
That must be how Roulette was controlling you.
If she dies, Roulette, I'm taking you down
hard, I promise you that.
Now why would I let such a valuable commodity die?
On the other hand, you two aren't under my control
which means I'm going to have to eliminate you.
In the ring, of course.
Why just snuff you when I can sell tickets and lay odds?
You're scum.
No, no, my dear. I'm an entrepreneur.
Let's face it, with some A-list heroes to do the jobs
your deaths will net me millions.
An extra-added attraction tonight, ladies and gentlemen.
Black Canary had so much fun, she's come back for more.
And she's brought the Huntress with her.
But they won't be fighting each other.
They'll be fighting together.
Huntress and Black Canary versus two new contenders.
Vixen, the beauty with the beast powers
and the Thanagar thrasher, Hawkgirl.
Ladies and gentlemen, place your bets.
Looks like we're in this together.
If you call me girlfriend
I'm gonna dropkick you into the next county.
Now, don't go all sentimental on me.
No, no, no, little bird.
Watchtower...
What?
Let me give you the short version.
Huh!
I don't wanna hurt you, Shayera.
But I wanna hurt you.
Just when we were starting to get along.
Huh?
I don't think I wanna know.
We're all in a cage match fighting to the death.
Yeah, see?
Is that all you got?
Oh, no.
I've saved the very best for last.
Yes, that's really Wonder Woman, ladies and gentlemen.
It is on!
Can even these four beautiful bruisers
stand up to the Amazon powerhouse herself?
- Anybody got a plan? - Yeah, try to stay alive.
Anybody got a good plan?
We're getting creamed here.
Let me try. Cover you ears.
Keep her busy so I can take her from behind.
Oh, nice move.
That's all I got.
Control center's gotta be up there.
Hang on.
I should have taken you down last time. My mistake.
I know your kind, Roulette. You like to watch.
But when it comes to getting your own pretty hands dirty...
Didn't think I was that good, did you?
Breaking news, I'm even better.
- Who's better? - You.
- You! - You got that right.
In another 30 seconds, your brains will be so scrambled
I'll be able to serve 'em up with bacon.
Okay, I give up.
Do I kill the signal or you?
I hope you two have an explanation for this.
Slow steps. That's it.
- I did what? - I know how you feel.
You know, if you want, I can talk to the League
and get you back in.
Nah, I do fine on my own.
Thank you, Helena. If you hadn't...
You would have done the same.
You know, I was totally whipping your butt
back when they caught us.
Pfft! In your dreams.
Like I'd waste my dreams on you.
We could settle this right now.
After all the mindless brutality we've seen tonight, no, thanks.
Yeah, I hear you, bad enough most people think
superheroes solve all their problems with their fists.
Like we're all a bunch of muscle-headed stereotypes.
- We're better than that. - Way.
- Two falls out of three? - You're on.