Looking good, Diana.
- Big date? - No such luck, Ollie.
I'm representing Themyscira at the global warming conference.
Way to go, man. Save the planet.
More like save my relationship with my mother.
Hey, at least you're speaking again.
It's the first thing she's asked me to do
since we mended fences.
I'd rather take another day trip to Tartarus.
I think you'll make a great diplomat.
Leave your sword.
I'm serious. I really don't want to go by myself.
J'onn, how about you come along and keep me company?
The Justice League currently has 23 active missions in progress.
Only I can properly deploy what remains of our resources.
Oh, please. Mr. Terrific can fill in.
He's smart enough to do monitor duty
and the Sunday Times crossword at the same time.
Go ahead, J'onn. I'm already finished with the crossword.
You did it in ink again, didn't you?
Mr. Terrific is more than capable
but I insist on remaining where I'm needed.
Turn around and talk to me.
You've been cooped up like a hermit in the watchtower
for almost two years now.
I can better serve the League...
We're not even going to have that argument.
You're a super strong
nearly invulnerable, telepathic shape-changer.
The reason you aren't on the ground protecting humanity
is because you don't want to be.
You don't actually like humanity all that much, do you?
I don't... dislike them.
You're not the only newcomer to this world around here.
People have strange ways and take a lot of getting used to.
But it's worth the effort. They're worth it.
She's got your number, J'onn.
You need to mingle, maybe take a meal
in the commissary every once in a while.
My Martian physiology doesn't require
as many meals as a human.
You know what he means. You must be terribly lonely.
I've gotta go, but we're not done talking about this.
Progress report, Mr. Luthor.
As promised, I've used various technologies to augment
the powers of dozens of our associates.
I've had notable success with Atomic Skull.
- And Devil Ray? - Ready for action.
- I feel stronger than ever. - That's because you are.
The increased strength is the least of the gifts
I've granted you, your stingers...
Perfect timing, Lex.
I've got an assignment that's right up Devil Ray's
new and improved alley.
Where to?
First, I want to tell you a story.
In Scandinavia, early in the tenth century
lived Prince John
the greatest warrior of his era.
His tremendous skill and valor brought him fame
throughout the world as the legendary Viking prince.
His adventures were epic, as were the legends that grew
around his exploits.
This much, we know to be truth.
On a frozen battlefield, Prince John, sole survivor
of a bloody war, its purpose lost to time
met a Valkyrie, a messenger from the Norse Gods
sent to escort the souls
of fallen heroes to their reward
in the halls of Valhalla.
Impossibly, they fell in love
and swore their hearts to each other.
But Odin, king of the Norse Gods
discovered their illicit affair
and enraged, banished John from Valhalla.
The Viking prince pleaded with Odin for mercy
begging to be allowed to remain with his love.
Odin agreed, saying that if John died a heroic death
he and his love would again be united for all eternity.
But Odin was a crafty God and cruel.
Before exiling John, he gifted him with invulnerability
to harm from metal, wood, fire and water.
The Viking prince soon realized
that he would never die a hero's death
because no weapon on Earth could slay him.
He trod boldly across a troubled world
in search of adventure and an honorable death
growing ever more distant from humanity.
Eventually, weary of the endless fight
for justice and despairing in his loneliness
he sailed north
beyond the boundaries of the known world
and passed from the knowledge of man.
That is, until now.
That Viking ship they found in a glacier last month.
You think it's his.
I know it is.
That's the standard of King Rick, his father.
The Viking prince is on that ship.
And?
I want you to steal his corpse.
You want me to reverse engineer
the secret of his invulnerability.
If we gained that power, all of us
we'd have nothing left to fear from the Justice League
and would be that much closer to achieving my ultimate goal.
Which, I note, you haven't seen fit to share with us.
Patience, my friends.
The grandest prizes are worth the wait.
The proposed accords are far too drastic.
With all due respect, princess
we're talking about committing hundreds of billions of dollars
and nobody's even proven the existence of global warming.
My mother's government fully supports the findings
of her scientists and those of the vast majority
of scientists here in man's world.
My government does not accept those studies.
Then, accept the evidence of your eyes.
There's a Viking ship at the bottom of this mountain
hidden in ice for 1100 years.
If it weren't for global warming
we wouldn't even know about it.
Yes, and it was clever PR
for our host to hold the talks here, but it is not proof.
You have to take this seriously.
Atlantis has already withdrawn
from the World Assembly over this
and they aren't the only country considering action.
Are you suggesting Themyscira might do the same?
If your pollution continues to affect my home
my mother is less likely to withdraw
than she is to attempt a military solution.
As a last resort only of course.
Excuse me.
Agent Faraday, what are you doing here?
- Not smoking. Want some? - No, thanks.
I'm here with the special security team.
The vice president is attending, but you know that already.
I saw you reading him the riot act earlier.
I'm not much of a diplomat.
Don't sell yourself short, lady.
You're an international incident waiting to happen.
By the way, if you raise your voice to the VP again
my men are under orders to shoot you.
Smack
You did not just shoot at me.
You have to stop.
If you pull that ship free, half the mountain's gonna come down.
So?
So I'm not going to let you do it.
Out of my way, Jumbo.
That hurt.
Cheater. You're cheating.
It's a poison stinger, sweetheart.
It'll kill you, eventually
slowly, painfully, but today's your lucky day.
I'm gonna put you out of your misery right now.
Move it, you goldbricking yahoos! Pour it on!
- You okay? - Arm's numb.
Stomach's not all that great either.
Easy, princess. Let me look at that.
Stinger's still in there.
- Pull it out. - There's a barb.
If you want a bullet to bite, there's plenty lying around.
Now. Uh!
That's all. It's out.
Then, let's take them down.
You are a beautiful man.
I think I'll keep you.
We should retreat.
I'm not backing down from a fight.
Your bloodstream's full of poison.
I can't believe you're still on your feet.
It's only a matter of time until your system shuts down.
I guess calling for support isn't backing down.
I gotta say it ain't.
J'onn, I've got a situation.
Watchtower sensors have picked up the Earth tremors
from your location.
I knew you were on the scene and assumed you could handle it.
Well, I can't. I'm outnumbered and I'm not feeling well.
We're still shorthanded.
I could spare Green Arrow and Mr. Terrific.
Bring who you want, J'onn, but I need you!
Well, that bites.
What's the matter, honey, break a nail?
- Green Arrow? - And I brought company.
Smack
And Black Canary said a buzz-saw arrow was self-indulgent.
They've had every opportunity to escape, but they keep fighting.
What makes that ancient vessel so important?
if I can get my lasso around one of them
I can make them tell.
Good idea, but save your strength.
He gifted him with invulnerability to harm.
Close enough.
J'onn, what happened? Are you okay?
Didn't get it all, but we can't allow them
to take that ship, they...
Fire.
You're a sight for sore eyes.
Not to say that ain't always the case.
Oh, what's happening?
♪ Da da da ♪
Hey, buddy!
What are you doing in here?
Well, for one thing, it's freezing outside.
You're coming with me.
Hey, watch the hands.
This is just too good to be true.
Let me give you a hint.
You want to try holding your breath as long as you can.
Let me go, freak, or so help me, I'll give you frostbite
in places you didn't even know you had places!
Use your powers.
Stop the avalanche or all the people inside will die.
Why should I care?
When it hits, I intend to see
that we're both standing right here.
I don't even know if I'm powerful enough
to stop a whole avalanche!
Let's find out, shall we?
if you move, we're gonna have to mop the floor.
- You've done well. - Kiss my frosty butt.
I don't suppose you boys want to talk about this?
That's probably for me.
Attention unidentified craft.
This is Special Agent King Faraday
Your vessel is currently surrounded
by three United States navy sea wolf-class submarines.
While I strongly suggest you surrender immediately
and prepare to be boarded
I really enjoy firing trident missiles
at tiny little subs, so the decision's entirely up to you.
- How's the shoulder, Diana? - Better.
The anti-toxin I found in Devil Ray's belt did the trick.
I still don't get what all this was about.
They think the Viking prince's corpse
will give them the secret of invulnerability.
That was their plan or as much of it as I could learn
before something shut down Giganta's mind.
Green Lantern said the same thing happened
when he tried to question Metallo.
So these guys were working with Metallo?
And perhaps with others.
We can't leave Prince John's body here.
Whoever else is involved will just try again.
The legend of the Viking prince is known even to my people.
If this is really him, he deserves to be laid to rest
according to tradition.
I'll take care of it.
Meanwhile, something's definitely not kosher.
Strange thefts, super villains with their heads hotwired
to short out if you question them.
We've got a real mystery developing here.
True, but it's a mystery you'll have to solve without me.
I've been thinking about what you said
and about the horrible despair of Prince John's life.
I'm a Martian. I'll live far longer than he did.
And unless I find a way to connect with humanity
I'll live out that time totally alone.
I can't learn what I need to learn on the watchtower.
And now, all in my own countree, I stood on the firm land.
The Hermit stepped forth from the boat
and scarcely he could stand.
"Oh, shrieve me, shrieve me, holy man."
The Hermit crossed his brow.
"Say quick," quoth he.
"I bid thee say, what manner of man art thou?"
Forthwith this frame of mind
was wrenched with a woeful agony
which forced me to begin my tale and then it left me free.
Since then, at an uncertain hour, that agony returns.
And till my ghastly tale is told
this heart within me burns.
I pass, like night, from land to land.
I have strange power of speech.
That moment that his face I see
I know the man that must hear me.
To him my tale I teach.