This stinks, Brainy
I hate running from a fight.
They'll never think to look for us here
that gives us a chance to mount a counterattack.
Attack how?
There's only the two of us left.
Yes, I've been giving that problem some thought.
Oh, no, I know you're a level 12 mega genius
but you are seriously out of your mind.
There's no other option.
All of our teammates have been captured.
To save them, we'll have to break the laws of time
and recruit heroes from the past.
But messing with history?
That's risky, even for us.
Incomplete records from the 21 st century
show that three members of the legendary Justice League
once came to the future.
My research indicates now is that time.
I did my homework, too, Brainy.
The histories say three heroes came to the future.
But only two of them ever made it home.
You're ready, Supergirl?
Dude, I was born ready.
That tickles.
Kaboom
I'll take that, thanks.
So, Queen Bee and Dr. Cyber?
Not much of a workout.
Hear that, Ollie? Kara thinks it's too easy.
Well, we wouldn't want her to get bored.
I hate you.
Some kid, huh?
Today's her 21 st birthday
but she'd rather be here practicing
than go out on the town with me and Dinah.
Good for her.
Hey, at least we wanted
to spend some time with her.
You ever think about how she must feel?
She's always an outsider.
I know a little bit about that myself, Ollie.
Just a little. You came to Earth as a baby, grew up here.
Kara spent most of her life
on a planet with technology
hundreds of years ahead of ours.
She's got to feel like she's
trapped in the stone age.
I've tried to make her feel at home.
How? Seems to me, you treat her just like another cape.
I was never happy about Kara going into the family business
but now that she's decided it's what she wants to do
I've tried to step back and let her develop into her own person.
I didn't want her living in the shadow
of being Superman's cousin.
This may shock you, but she's proud to be your cousin
she even changed her costume to look more like yours.
Yes and I'm very proud.
But don't tell her.
No, that's a job for Superman.
- Well? - Well, what?
Aren't you gonna give me notes
about all the stuff I screwed up?
No notes, Kara.
I've got nothing left to teach you.
Not bad, kiddo, you set a new record for the simulation.
Kara!
I'm certain that this must be disorienting for you.
- My name is... - Brainiac!
Yes, how did you...
Please, calm down
I'm not going to hurt you.
Whoa, sparky
let's hear what he has to say.
Thank you.
Yes, I am a Brainiac
but I'm not a machine.
I'm organic.
The universe conquering Brainiac
you knew is my distant ancestor.
Over time, he learned how to pass
his code down biologically.
I am Brainiac 5.
Think of me as the black sheep of my family
dedicated to doing good to make up
for my ancestor's legacy of evil.
And you demonstrated that by kidnapping us?
We'd have never done it if the situation wasn't so dire.
Where are we, anyway?
Approximately 1,000 years into your future
in what you'd call the 31 st century.
Time travel, swell.
It's a real thrill for me to meet you, sir.
You're the famous John Stewart, father of...
You wanna shut up before you create a time paradox?
Sorry.
Chuck Taine, codename, Bouncing Boy.
Why did you bring us here?
We're part of a group called the Legion Of Superheroes.
A galaxy spanning force, none unlike your Justice League.
A team of criminals called the Fatal Five attacked
our new headquarters and captured all our teammates.
They must have something big planned
to risk taking on the Legion.
But we can't figure what it is.
We needed help, so we set the time bubble to bring back
some of Earth's greatest heroes.
But why us?
It-it was random, we'd have taken anyone.
Okay, so how can we help?
Whoa, time out.
Just because he's seriously cute
doesn't mean we should trust a Brainiac.
I'm not getting a bad vibe off the kid.
Apparently neither are you.
Seriously cute, huh?
The date we pulled her from
is exactly when Supergirl vanished
from the historical records.
Brainy, she's going to die.
We have to tell her.
No, telling her could change history.
Keep quiet, Chuck. That's an order.
You know, Brainiac, being organic and having
a heart, not the same thing.
We're in. What's next?
The lab's this way.
The tech is out of date, but we should find enough...
A Green Lantern, that's a rare sight in this galaxy these days.
Take a good look, he won't be here long.
So what's your power? Super strength, speed?
I have a 12th level intellect.
Great, you can knock them out with your diploma.
That was unnecessary, my belt protects me from any impact.
Maybe I was just trying to cop a feel.
Empress.
You'll find the Emerald Eye of Ekron more than a match
for your ring.
On your feet.
Ohh, what?
You've got to free the others...
Forget them, we have the Green Lantern, let's go!
Ohh, what's going on?
Can you track them with those things?
Not yet, but I've identified the technology.
They're Scion receptors.
Hey, that soda machine in the lobby still works.
Oh, thanks.
Back on Argos, we use Scionic technology
for our remote controls.
When we lost one, you just had to think at it, and it'd beep.
Don't know why we bothered
they were always in the couch cushions.
Good idea, but it won't work.
The Fatal Five are masking the carrier wave somehow.
So, I have to know.
Why'd you save me first?
My decision was based on pure logic.
Really?
Because Green Lantern's the most powerful.
No offense, but I really don't think you could follow
the reasoning of a 12th level intellect such as my own.
Guess not.
Hey, Kara, wanna get me one of those drinks?
Oh, sure.
Admit it, genius, you're in love with her.
Ludicrous, we just met.
Moreover, as a Coluan, I'm ruled by intellect, not emotion.
So in love with her.
Increased sweat gland production, shortness of breath
inability to concentrate...
I thought it was guilt, but I am in love.
How did you know?
Just call me Cupid, junior.
I never miss.
I'm gonna raid this dump.
See if I can't upgrade my arrows
with some future tech.
I'll be gone for a long time
so you two are stuck with each other, alone.
For a long time.
You had the superior weapons
and the advantage of surprise.
Explain to me how you failed to capture Brainiac 5?
Watch your tone, half a man, I'd hardly call capturing
a Green Lantern a failure.
He's more powerful than a dozen Brainiacs.
Perhaps, but that was never part of the plan.
You have to learn to improvise, Tharok.
We're better armed than ever
to strike against the United Planets.
After that, the universe will be ours for the taking.
What's that?
A legion flight ring
all of us have one.
So, does this mean we're going steady?
Trust me, a thousand years ago, that joke was hilarious.
I thought since I couldn't trace the control disk
maybe I could trace the missing Legionnaires' rings.
But it was another dead end.
It's a shame our Justice League comlinks don't work here.
We could track Green Lantern by his transponder.
Come to think of it, we still could if we had a...
Quantum tunneling RF transponder.
Hold that thought.
Yeah, this looks like it could do some damage.
Get up here, Brainiac's found GL
His signal is coming from this ship.
They're headed right towards the capital of the United Planets.
The Fatal Five has tried to destroy it before.
And now with GL and the entire Legion
under their control, they just might succeed.
The good news is my personal cruiser runs rings
around their ship. We could still beat them there.
Then what?
We improvise.
Nice ship.
It's strictly no frills, but it's fast.
What do you pilot back home?
Usually just a pickup.
A pickup, is that a type of star cruiser?
Yes, yes, it is.
We're going into orbit.
And we've got company.
You guys get aboard that mother ship
and shut down the control devices.
What are you gonna do?
Hold off John and the Legion
until you snap them back to normal.
You won't stand a chance against them.
Maybe, but I'm the only one who does stand a chance
of protecting the capital.
You can't go, because I lo...
Because I lied to you.
Kara, I don't even know you but history says you never
return from this battle.
What?
And you knew that all along?
I'm sorry.
I had hoped it wouldn't come to this.
I wanted to spare her.
There's still a planet full of people down there
who need our help.
Do your job, and I'm going to do mine.
But...
In case I don't see you again.
Hey, genius.
Hi, how about putting that big brain of yours
to work on a plan to get us aboard the mother ship?
I'll get us in.
I love the direct approach.
The rest of the mission won't be so easy, let's move.
You can do this, Kara.
No biggie, just another practice mission.
Shoot.
I know, I was hoping
they'd be out looking for us.
No, shoot!
Obliterate them.
Okay, big guy, that's as far as you go.
You can't stop Validus with that toy.
Rusty, I got him right where I want him.
No!
John, stop... Fight it.
Oh, Kara!
I knew what I was doing, but I couldn't stop.
Where are we?
Last thing I remember was...
Oh, no.
Just so you know, the sharp
part's on the other end, chief.
Believe me, that's coming.
Tear him to bits.
Slowly.
We wanted to say thanks
by making you Honorary Legionnaires.
It's very nice, but I already have a ring.
Don't worry about it, GL, you can't keep it anyway.
If you took it home, the future
technology could pollute the time stream.
I'm keeping mine.
I'm not going back.
Kara...
History says Supergirl never returned from this mission
because she decided to stay in the future.
Whatever abducted them didn't leave
any traceable energy signature.
Maybe Dr. Fate or Zatanna?
Where's Kara?
She asked us to give you this.
Tell ma and pa I love them.
And I love you, too, Clark.
Don't take this the wrong way but I found a place
where I can make a difference.
Where I'm more than just Superman's kid cousin.
I... I feel I belong here.
Also, I met this boy.
You should've seen her, she was amazing.
She's a grown woman now, capable of choosing...
Kara's headstrong, but she's always made good decisions.
I trust her judgment.
But you were right, Ollie.
I wish I had told her.
It's okay, Clark.
She knows.
Now, this boy, Kara likes so much...
does he have a name?