Previously on "Justice League Unlimited..."
You are the mystic conduit
that draws cosmic essence from the debris.
I'll be able to reconstitute
Brainiac from that energy.
Let the universe howl in despair
for I have returned.
Superman must suffer for killing me.
His adopted world will die screaming.
We have a little problem.
Let's say, just for the sake of argument
that I believe a single word of your story.
How did you survive the explosion?
By the skin of my teeth.
But stranded more than a power ring's charge from home
we found ourselves dependent on the kindness of strangers.
A resident of the nearby planet
New Genesis, drawn by our ship's explosion
offered his help.
We accepted, of course.
You've got some nerve coming to us for help.
Darkseid took Brainiac away from me.
I can't hear his voice in my head anymore.
Enough of the crazy talk, Lex.
Darkseid said he was coming to Earth to destroy it.
You guys were supposed to keep that from happening.
We'll do just that, lady.
Thanks for the heads-up.
And what about us?
You're all going into holding cells.
You think so? Ain't no way we're giving up without a...
Watchtower to Metro Tower.
- We've got a situation. - What's going on up there?
Multiple hyper-spatial incursions
but they're planet-side.
I'm sending telemetry.
- Boom tubes. - He's right.
Can you hear it? Like thunder?
Attention, all Justice League personnel
this is an Omega-level threat.
- Get to the Javelins. - No time.
All members, prepare for emergency teleport.
Send us first. Give the others a chance to get their pants on.
You got it.
Okay. Let's get these people locked up.
It sounds like we've got a fight on our hands.
If you think you're locking us up
while the whole world's under attack
you got two fights on your hands.
She's got a point.
We'll need all the bodies we can throw at this.
Oh, come on. It's Lex Flippin' Luthor.
Why should we trust him?
Hey, it's our world, too.
Let's be clear about this.
We're not here to help you save the world.
You're here to help me get revenge on Darkseid.
When this is over, it's back to business as usual.
Wouldn't have it any other way.
- You get all that? - Yeah.
- You guys sure about this? - Trust, but verify.
Put the bad guys on teams with regular leaders.
Search through the telemetry on the attack groups.
Find the best protected mother ship.
That's where Darkseid will be.
- That's where I wanna go. - I imagine so.
It's in Metropolis hovering over "The Daily Planet."
Stand by.
Back off.
Is there a plan here?
Take out the small fry until we attract
the big fish's attention.
Ah, with everything going on
I'll bet he never notices us.
You're on.
I'll take some of that action.
I hope you appreciate, Kal-El
that everything that happens from this point
is on your head.
The skies will rain fire.
The oceans will boil.
The streets will run red
with the blood of billions.
Only then, after your last
pitiful hope is extinguished
will I end your life.
Let's go.
You destroyed Brainiac
and I'm going to make you pay.
Unlikely.
I'm more powerful than I've ever been.
And the last time we met
you barely managed to hold your own.
Funny. That's not how I remember it.
Allow me to refresh your memory.
- I have to go help. - I know.
Find shelter. I'll be back as soon as I can.
Blue Devil got me close enough to get a good look.
Those big burrowing machines are Magma Tappers.
At least now we know what they're trying to do.
The invaders are setting up drilling machines
to tap the heat at the Earth's core.
They're trying to create fire pits.
If they succeed, it's apocalypse on Earth.
They won't succeed.
Your primary targets are those drills.
Destroy them at all costs.
You heard the man. Rock 'n' roll.
Looks like the main power coupling.
Cover my backside.
Get out of here. It's gonna blow.
Yeah!
We gotta find a way to take this out for good.
Why don't you just throw it to the sun?
Yeah, I guess it was a pretty stupid idea.
No. Maybe you're onto something.
But I'll need more leverage and a trench.
On it.
Now what?
Oh, cool.
Doesn't look like it quite made escape velocity.
Nope.
Good effort though.
Don't leave us yet, Kal-El.
I want you to see your adopted home world
bow down before me.
Only then will I allow you death's sweet release.
Parademons, dispose of these annoyances.
Excuse me.
Get away from here. It's not safe.
Don't worry. I'm here to help.
I appreciate your intent...
Hera!
- J'onn! - Good to see you, Diana.
I've got a lot to tell you about.
- We'll catch up later. - Wouldn't miss it.
First things first.
- Problem? - I'm out.
- Take my extra. - Not my style.
Suit yourself.
I'm planning to live through this.
Flea.
Impressive.
No one has ever avoided my Omega Beam.
I wonder if the other one is as agile.
- Excellent strategy. - Luthor!
Your friends have abandoned you or fallen before my might.
Super or otherwise...
you're merely a man...
and I am a God.
You, Metron, you knew this was going to happen.
This outcome was the most likely possible result
of your foolhardy actions.
You can help me.
I demand that you help me!
You are in no position to make demands of anyone.
I warned you that you were dabbling
in forces beyond your comprehension.
You'd be surprised what I can comprehend.
For instance, if you know so much about Darkseid
I'll wager you know how to beat him.
There is one possibility.
One thing in all the universe that might...
But no. The risk is...
I know a little something about risk myself.
Care for an object lesson?
Very well.
I will take you where you want to go.
You still try to fight.
Can't you see that it's hopeless?
That man won't quit as long
as he can still draw a breath.
None of my teammates will.
Me? I've got a different problem.
I feel like I live in a world made of cardboard.
Always taking constant care not to break something.
To break someone.
Never allowing myself to lose control
even for a moment or someone could die.
But you can take it, can't you, big man.
What we have here is a rare opportunity
for me to cut loose and show you
just how powerful I really am.
- Had enough? - Not quite yet.
It's called the Agony Matrix.
Direct neural stimulation of pain receptors. All of them.
Imagine the worst pain you've ever felt in your life...
times a thousand.
Now imagine that pain continuing forever.
Oh, that's right. You don't have to imagine.
Behold the source wall.
Behind it is the single greatest
secret of the universe.
This is as far as I dare to go.
I warn you one final time.
Only a 12th-level intellect has the slightest hope
of surviving what you're about to experience.
Then I'm overqualified.
Still alive.
You impress me, Kryptonian.
More, your valor has touched my heart.
Oh, yes.
There is still some small part of me
that knows mercy.
I will end your pain with something special
I've been saving for just this occasion.
I'm going to carve out your heart
and put it on a pike in my throne room.
As much as I'd enjoy seeing that
first you've got some business with me.
Sorry it took me so long.
I had to go get my power suit.
You would dare challenge me?
Insanity.
Oh, I'm not here to challenge you, Darkseid.
Quite the contrary.
I've got something you want.
The only thing you want.
The Anti-Life Equation.
My gift to you.
- Lex, don't. - It's too late.
It's beautiful.
Isn't it?
Yes. Yes, it is.
This has been the scene all over the world.
In the wake of Darkseid defeat
his attacking forces have withdrawn
presumably back to wherever it is they came from.
Thanks to Luthor, of all people.
In many ways, Lex Luthor represents
the worst mankind has to offer.
But he died saving us all.
I doubt that either of them died.
- We saw it this time. - You saw it last time, too.
What's the old saying? "Believe half of what you see."
"And none of what you hear."
They'll be back.
And we'll be ready for them.
Meanwhile, it's past time
that Luthor's partners in crime were locked up.
Wait a minute.
We helped you guys save the world
and we don't even get any consideration?
You're right. Five minute head start.
Five minutes? Are you kidding?
Four minutes, fifty seconds.
I should be back in time for dinner.
- I love you, too. - These are the end times.
A head start.
You're getting soft in your old age.
Don't you have a tall building to go leap?
And the adventure continues.