Trap's all set.
Eat my sparkles, turtle.
Wait for GL, Star Girl!
You'll give yourself a hernia.
I got him, Pat.
Anytime, Lantern!
Stall it, S.T.R.I.P.E. I'll be right there.
Stall it, he says.
He's almost in position.
On my signal...
As if. Big boy's mine.
Courtney!
Arigato. Thank you.
Arigato.
Arigato. Arigato.
How'd she get here anyway?
What's with all the wannabes?
Probably here for the convention.
Convention?
When we get back to the Metro Tower
you and I are going to have a talk about grandstanding.
Tell that to her. The little showoff stole my thunder.
Don't you talk about Supergirl!
Supergirl can melt you with her eyes!
Big whoop.
My stepdad here is a mecha.
Mecha so last year.
She's very big in Japan.
Why can't we just fly straight home?
Over the North Pole is the straightest route... rookie.
She's always blah blah blah my cousin.
Blah blah blah blah my cousin.
Like we don't know who she means.
Check me out. I'm Supergirl.
Ask me, the only thing that matters is we all pull through.
Shut up, Pat. It wasn't World War III.
It was a giant turtle.
If I was you, I wouldn't talk
behind somebody's back when they got super hearing.
- Kara, easy on the yoke! - I'm not doing anything!
- Watchtower! - Watchtower!
Be my guest.
J'onn, it's Kara.
- Nothing. - Hmm.
My ring says we're still at the North Pole.
Maybe somebody's North Pole.
So where the heck are we?
I can only guess we're way, way underground.
And the exit would be...
- Through them. - Not a problem.
You guys! My powers aren't working.
Aw.
I'm serious. I'm at, like, half strength, maybe less.
Oh, damn!
Heads up!
Cover Supergirl!
What are you waiting for?
Zap 'em with your star thingy!
Oh, may I?
Cause it would be such an honor to help
the great Supergirl out of a jam.
Come on!
You are so loving this.
Scan the area.
Yep, that's the last of 'em.
Oh, wait.
Travis Morgan, warlord of Shambala.
Been expecting you.
Welcome to Skartaris.
Sorry I can't put out more of a spread.
Times are tough.
Morgan, I don't believe you brought us here just to feed us.
We are in dire need.
My daughter, Jennifer.
Our world must have champions.
I used my magic to reach out
and bring you here to the center of the Earth.
And I'd call the whole thing a load of crab cakes
if I wasn't here to see it.
And even seeing it, I still ain't a hundred percent.
If you want something to believe in, come on.
Geez. You call that an army?
Most of these folks have lost everything
to Demos, so you know, feel free to dump on them.
What I meant was...
She means we'll do everything
we can to help.
Tell us about Demos.
Yeah, nasty wizard.
Those were his Dinotroopers you met.
He used to try and shake down a kingdom here and there.
But a few months ago, he started this big push
to take over the world.
And that was about the same time
he discovered energy weapons.
All of a sudden, the wizard's gone hi-tech.
Somebody's supplying him.
Back when I was in the air force
that energy stuff was science fiction.
That explains why Morgan the barbarian packs an auto-mag.
Came through the portal and made myself at home.
Look around you.
These are some of the last free people in Skartaris.
Demos has us pinned between his army and the great stone.
I'll bite. What great stone?
The monks keep it in a tabernacle
deep inside the mountain.
They say it's got magic properties.
Demos wants it... bad.
Lord Demos, the alien force escaped us.
Describe them.
My Lord, it happened so fast.
How many were there?
Did they have weapons?
Did they address each other by name?
One wore a coat of arms!
Well...
you're my military advisors.
Do you recognize this crest?
Yes, I know it well.
- Morgan. - Machiste.
Best guy I know. King of Kiro.
Machiste knows as much about the great stone as anybody.
Machiste, this is Green Lantern.
Hey.
When the blood death came upon me
my case seemed hopeless...
until the monks of the tabernacle placed me
before the great stone and let me bathe in its rays.
- It's a curative? - Only for the most desperate.
It can cure or kill.
And Demos isn't the healing type.
Behold!
The great stone!
You okay?
I've never seen a piece of Kryptonite
that big before.
If this place wasn't messing with my powers...
I'd be dead already.
- Shakera! - Oh!
Demos is here.
It's the end.
For Skartaris!
Let's get this done.
Supergirl, you stay...
- Yah! - Fine.
Not coming off.
Silver Banshee.
How the heck did you get...
Tell the outworlder to come get his rock.
You need a new plan.
My magic is strongest, girl.
Your breath is strongest, dude.
That's about it.
Such a pretty child.
But then they're always pretty when I begin.
Demos!
You and me, pal.
Morgan, I was hoping to kill you today.
Touch it and you're tinfoil.
At this distance, the Kryptonite cell that powers me
would bring your cousin to his knees.
I'm immune to Kryptonite, metal mouth.
Give up!
if you're immune, love, why do you need that staff?
You filthy brat! Where are you?
Ha ha ha.
You think you've won?
No freedom-loving warlord will ever unite the lands
and bring peace, justice.
A foolish dream.
Maybe so, wizard, but it's the one dream worth fighting for.
You lied, little one.
I can see the illness creeping over you.
You have none of Superman's strength.
But I got brains.
I can't move without my Kryptonite battery.
But it's killing you.
I won't quit.
You don't have to.
Will there ever be another time such as ours?
The Great Stone is safe!
Demos is defeated!
Now and forever, Skartaris is free!
John Corbin alias Metallo.
Fancy meeting you here in the center of the Earth.
Muling Kryptonite with Silver Banshee.
You could pretty much run forever
on this one little chunk.
And without it, what do you have?
Fifteen minutes of reserve power? Ten?
Tell me, why do you want so much?
There's enough in that tabernacle to satisfy
a 100 Superman haters.
There's a scary thought.
You won't get anything out of me.
Pretty soon, you aren't gonna have the breath to talk.
Who knows, five minutes? One?
Alright.
I joined forces with...
Whoa, Nelly!
This isn't Silver Banshee's work.
Somebody else didn't want Metallo to give them up.
You'll take that thing with you.
Definitely and the Great Stone too.
Let GL whip it into the sun.
Wait!
This is the one place where
Kryptonite can do some good.
That is a fact.
We don't want Silver Banshee coming back after it.
So the only way I'll let the stone stay here
is if we seal the portal to Skartaris permanently.
Fine by me.
I got everything I need right here.
There. I doubt even I could get back through.
How are you feeling? Need a lift?
No. I'm good.
Courtney, you slow your butt down!
- Uh, my dad. - I know.
Superman tried to keep me on the farm.
Made me hide there for three years.
Big deal. I've still got a curfew.
Enough cosmic energy to trash a city
and I can't stay out past ten.
Three years on a farm.
In Kansas!
We'll have J'onn probe what's left of Metallo's mind.
I wanna know what he was going to say.
Something's going on, ain't it?