I know you are here, Boston Brand.
What's the point of being a flipping ghost
if you can't even sneak up on people?
For that matter, what's the point of me
being a ghost, period?
It's been over a year since I caught the man who murdered me.
So, your work here is done?
You are ready to pass on to the next level?
I don't know what ready means.
But I feel like I've done my time.
And yet, here you are.
"Here you are"?
What kind of lousy wisdom is "Here you are"?
If you seek knowledge, you have but to ask.
I've avenged my own death.
Why am I still here?
Your destiny is not to avenge your own death.
Your destiny is to avenge mine.
What?
Grodd never sends us anyplace nice.
His humble one begs your forgiveness.
But to enter this sacred place, the right must be earned.
Keep the change.
His humble one begs your forgiveness...
but no outsider is permitted in the temple of Nandeparvak.
That's cute, kid. Get out of the way or I'll spank you.
This would also not be permitted.
Little Bruce Lee's got your number.
Lucky thing you got us for backup.
This humble one would not presume to fight you alone.
Now things are getting interesting.
Take them down.
Bizarro, you despise me, right?
Uh-huh. Bizarro hate Luthor.
He do anything for him.
Good. I mean, bad.
Anyway, take care of those monks.
Okay.
Stand aside or you're dead.
In the fullness of time, we are all dead.
This is not the way to end my life.
Master!
Do not waste your time, Boston Brand.
This portion of my journey has come to an end.
But...
We will meet again.
I'm gonna make you pay!
Rampage, what's wrong with you?
She has been possessed.
Oh, undead spirit!
What just happened?
This is it, the heart of Nandeparvak.
We have what we came for.
It's time to leave.
I have done as you asked, Lord Grodd.
Get off your knees, woman.
Not until my master says so.
Excellent work, my dear.
You may rise.
You're pathetic, debasing yourself like that.
I owe Grodd everything.
I would still be trapped in that mirror if he hadn't freed me.
When Giganta gets out of prison, she ain't gonna appreciate you
hanging on to her boyfriend like that.
That's her problem.
Giganta's not nearly enough woman for Grodd.
True.
If you're quite finished demonstrating what an alpha male
you are, maybe you'd care to explain what you intend to do
with that thing.
I already told you, but you won't accept it.
You don't believe in magic.
It's not a matter of belief.
I'm just unaccustomed to working
with something I don't fully understand.
As long as the amplifier you built for me works...
It does.
Then consider this an exotic power source.
You don't need to understand anything more.
You can't produce a carrier wave of the amplitude
you're talking about with this building's
cloaking-field generator.
So you've convinced me.
I don't intend to use our field generator.
You're planning to build one?
Luthor, Luthor, Luthor.
Why build when we can take what we want.
Gentlemen, shall we go?
Rama Kushna, just like you to show up too late to help.
Your impertinence is refreshing as always.
But have a care, the Gods are capricious.
What do you want from me?
The master is dead.
They're all dead.
Do not presume to lecture me on the nature of reality.
The monks have not yet passed from this plane.
They're in some kind of coma?
That is as close to the truth as you
are capable of comprehending.
You must retrieve the heart of Nandeparvak
or they will remain in their current state for all time.
I have spoken.
How the heck am I supposed to do that?
Is that really everything?
We're done.
- All reports filed. - Good.
What do you guys say we get something to eat?
We hardly ever spend time together when we're not working.
Sounds good to me.
I'm tired of commissary food.
I'd like to, Diana, but I've been away from Gotham too long.
Come on, Bruce. I know a burger place in Metropolis
that has the best fries on the East Coast
and the milkshakes are so thick...
- I need your help. - That's pretty thick.
I'm serious. I need your help on a mission of vengeance.
Now, don't be alarmed, but I'm not Superman. I'm...
A ghost, inhabiting his body.
Is that you, Boston?
Hiya, Bats.
When I'm working, people call me Deadman.
You know this... ghost?
Yeah, Batman helped me solve my own murder a while back.
Now, I need your help again.
If you hurt Superman, I'll...
Relax. He doesn't even know I'm in here.
We can't see or hear him otherwise.
Once he leaves, Superman will be fine.
It's like he says.
Why are you still around?
I thought once your murder was solved, your exile was ended.
You and me, both.
You know how they say no good deed goes unpunished?
I guess I shot my mouth off to the wrong deity.
What's this about?
A bunch of Supervillains busted into Nandeparvak
and stole a mystic totem filled with the souls
of hundreds of monks, and they killed the master.
Batman?
He knew the master even before I did.
He was one of my martial-arts teachers.
With all the power in this body, it'd be easy to punish
the men responsible, if I could find them.
That's not the master's way... or yours.
We'll find them and we'll see
that justice is done, not vengeance.
Yeah, fun to think about, though.
Let's go up to ops and see if you can't pick the bad guys
out of a photo array.
You're sure that's not the magician you saw?
Nope. All the rest of 'em are right on, though.
First sign of Luthor since Shayera saw him
on Blackhawk Island.
What's he up to?
This seems like it might be bigger than Luthor.
Agent Faraday told me Devil Ray escaped from prison.
And Bizarro showing up again?
And all the odd teams
of previously unaffiliated villains?
Whose brains have conveniently been shorting out
when we question them.
Do you guys remember the one bit of information J'onn was able
to pull out of Giganta's mind before it shut down?
Grodd.
Think he's put together a new secret society?
Except this time, he's doing a better job
of keeping the secret.
So, how do we find them?
I wish I could help.
I can feel the psychic screams of the souls they stole.
But I can't pinpoint a location.
All I get are images of Africa.
I know, a continent doesn't much narrow things down
but it's all I can...
Gorilla City.
He's gone back home.
Solovar, this is Batman.
What a coincidence. I was just about to call you.
Wanted to give you a heads up.
We've got reason to believe that Grodd's headed your way.
You don't say, that might explain the armies
of supervillains attacking the city.
How bad?
All but taken over.
They're already holding the central control building.
We could use some help if you have any to spare.
Can't chat.
Signing off.
Gorilla City?
A hidden city of super- intelligent talking gorillas
with technology far beyond anything humans have created.
No, really?
You're the ghost from the Himalayas
having trouble believing this?
Point.
You know, when they beam down on that TV show, they never miss.
We didn't miss either.
It's a force field, but it also hides the city from prying eyes.
Looks like a job for Superman.
You're wasting time.
Go in as a ghost, find the central control building
and shut down the shield generator.
We'll follow as soon as we can.
Yeah, okay.
You have to eat them with a spoon.
What am I doing in Africa?
You two, Devil Ray wants you outside right now.
Go on, I'll take care of things here.
You'd think the thing would be a big, red button
or at least have a sign on it or something.
The heck with it.
That's our cue.
Skull, what do you think you're doing?
I gotta say, I don't have a good answer for ya.
It's the ghost.
He's here again.
But this time, I will take care of him for good.
I cannot destroy him.
Can you at least get him out of our hair for a bit?
Yes. I banish you from this place, evil spirit.
We lost shield power for 41 seconds
before the backup kicked in.
We have to assume...
That the Justice League is here.
They're headed this way.
We need more time to complete our work.
Then, it won't matter.
I'm on it.
Bizarro.
Superman is your best friend.
Do you understand?
Bizarro understand.
Superman am friend.
Bizarro must kill him.
You killed my teacher, my friend.
You'll have to be more specific, lady.
I've killed a lot of people.
The old monk.
What are you waiting for?
You want revenge? Take it.
No. That's not what he would have wanted.
Next time, ask permission!
Tala, we're ready for the heart.
Good.
Then, all I have to do is install this mind-control module
and you'll be able to project your will over the entire world.
Present company excepted, of course.
Actually, that's just what I wanted you to think.
My true plans are far more grand.
Tala?
Some sort of genetic reconfiguration matrix?
You show impressive intellect for a homo sapien.
Using the massive carrier-wave that, thanks to you
Gorilla City's shield generator can now produce.
I'm about to send a signal that will rewrite human DNA.
A devolution ray that will turn every man, woman
and child on earth into an ape!
You okay?
Yeah. Let's wrap this up.
Oh, come on!
Why am I not surprised?
Don't bother.
It's too late.
Tell me how to stop it.
Get us out of here, Tala.
ls everything okay?
Well, I'm sort of missing flash's obligatory joke
about how Grodd made a monkey out of us.
Just couldn't let it go unsaid.
Obligatory.
That's it, guys, yuck it up.
You saved the world, but I failed.
Everyone in Nandeparvak is gone...
forever.
We're in your debt again, Justice League.
If only Luthor and Grodd hadn't gotten away.
If it's any consolation, we picked up nearly a dozen
of his superpowered cronies, with more to come, I'm sure.
No, I didn't mean it.
Bruce, Deadman took over your body.
It wasn't your fault.
Let me explain.
He would have shot her. I didn't have a choice.
Boston Brand, your actions led to the death of another.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Intentions are immaterial.
You were gifted with power to be used
to balance the scales of karma.
Because of your actions, the scale now is unbalanced.
Unbalanced?
Thanks to Devil Ray and his team
the master and all the other monks are dead.
Incorrect.
When the heart was shattered
the essence of the monks was set free.
Even now, their souls return to their rightful places.
No one dies in Nandeparvak but the scales are unbalanced.
Your work in this world is not yet done.
Since there's only one monkey left around here
I'm assuming that the Justice League found a way
to stop the carrier wave.
There's more than one way to peel a banana.
Next time...
I wasn't going to do this for another few weeks
but seriously...
turning all of humanity into apes?
That was your master plan?
Listen up.
From now on, I'm in charge of this operation.
Anybody got a problem with that?
No problem at all, baby.