The delegates from Kasnia are just arriving.
Any sign of trouble?
Nothing here.
Zilch. Not even a sleazy politician.
Are you sure we need to be here?
According to my sources,
Terrorists have targeted this international peace summit.
Flash: They would have to do it during the playoffs.
J'onn: What if these terrorists are already inside?
I've got that covered.
[all talking at once]
Look, Lois, I know you'd give your eye teeth
For this assignment,
But someone had to cover that sanitation strike.
[Lois speaking indistinctly on telephone]
Don't blame me! Talk to Perry!
Green Lantern: Hey there.
Hey, yourself.
Aren't you supposed to be patrolling the north end?
I thought I saw trouble over here.
There's no trouble.
Sure there is.
And I'm looking right at it.
[kiss]
You're bad. You should know.
And you should get back to work.
But after we're done, let's get some take-out
From that Chinese place near your apartment.
Great. But this time, no eel heads.
Lightweight.
Woman: General Welles.
I'm picking up an unidentified bogey
Heading toward Washington.
I've tried contacting it, but there's no response.
Scramble interceptors.
I want visual confirmation.
Man: Roger that.
Weird.
Radar says it's there, but I can't see it.
Still no response?
No, sir, and it's entering D.C. Airspace.
Take it down.
Direct hit!
Holy...
G.L., report!
Not exactly your garden variety terrorists.
It's a Gordanian class-7 cruiser!
What? Watch out for the plasma cannons!
Aah! Aah!
[screaming]
I'll draw their fire.
We'll take out the rear stabilizers.
Wait! Don't!
Aah! Aah!
Any other suggestions?
Out of the frying pan, into the fire.
Hawkgirl: No! Wait!
You know these guys?
Yes.
Welcome to Earth, commander.
Thank you, lieutenant.
Care to tell us what exactly is going on here?
This is commander Hro Talak, of Thanagar.
Save the introductions for later.
I must meet with your world leaders.
The fate of this planet may hang in the balance.
Talak: Friends, we are here on a mission of great urgency.
5 years ago, we secretly sent an advance agent to Earth
To learn more about your people and to study your defenses.
That agent was lieutenant Shayera Hol,
Better known to you as Hawkgirl.
You mean she's a spy? Cool!
She was spying on us.
Oh, yeah. Huh.
Unfortunately, she discovered that Earth's defenses are sorely lacking.
With your limited technology, you are totally unprepared
For what is about to come.
The greatest evil in the universe.
Our mortal enemies, the Gordanians.
For generations, we on Thanagar have been locked
in a bloody war with these monsters.
[distant moaning]
Across the cosmos, they have committed unspeakable atrocities,
Decimating world upon world.
And now, they are coming here.
This will be the fate of Earth, unless you accept our help.
[murmuring]
I know you'll need to discuss this amongst yourselves,
But be quick about it.
We are your only hope of salvation.
All this time... Why didn't you tell me?
John, there were so many times I wanted to.
But?
This was a military mission.
I'd sworn an oath of secrecy,
And I couldn't tell anyone.
Sorry, but not even you.
You're a soldier. I'd think you'd understand.
So... What else aren't you telling me?
Well, actually--
Talak: Shayera.
There you are. Hro.
Darling. At last.
Sorry. Hro Talak.
John Stewart.
The Green Lantern.
Shayera has told me so much about you.
Has she?
And you two are...?
Hro and I are promised to each other.
It's like being engaged.
Congratulations.
I'm sure you two must have a lot of catching up to do.
I thought he'd be taller.
Man: You saw what one Gordanian ship can do.
What chance would we stand against an entire fleet?
But can we trust the thanagarians?
We don't know anything about them.
We know they came here and risked
Their own lives to help us.
Like angels from heaven?
Sorry, princess. I'm not buying it.
It does seem almost too good to be true.
But if Earth really is in danger,
We can hardly afford to turn away help.
I can't believe they're still discussing this.
It's such a no-brainer, right?
Yeah.
Batman: The most mysterious creatures in the universe.
Sorry? Women.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
You didn't know she was spoken for.
How did you--
It wasn't hard to figure out.
The point is, these things happen.
You just have to deal with it.
Thanks. I'll keep that in mind.
Believe me.
I know how painful it can be when two people who are so involved--
Who's involved?
Wait. You and Hawkgirl?
Get out!
Really?
Imagine how hard this situation must be for her.
She's been here, alone,
On a strange planet, far from home.
Who knows what she must have gone through?
Maybe you should have read her mind.
Actually, it's strange, but I never could.
In fact, I can't read any of their minds.
Not exactly Thanagar's finest,
But I tried to make it feel like home.
Hungry?
Alonse kidneys, Korshian oysters.
Don't you like them?
I remembered they were your favorites.
No. It was very thoughtful.
Mmm! Awesome!
And when was the last time you had this?
Plume nectar!
I remember we were on leave together on Aloria.
How long ago was that?
5 years. 5 long years.
My Shayera!
[angrily] what is it?
Commander Talak.
Kragger! I left orders not to be interrupted.
I'm sorry, sir, but we're receiving
A transmission from the humans.
Commander Talak, the world leaders
Have come to a decision.
Earth gladly accepts your assistance.
Very good. We will begin immediately.
I'm sorry, darling.
Duty calls.
But I want you to come with me
And act as an official liaison with the natives.
Your experience with them may come in handy.
Of course.
Commander, a word with you?
I'm meet you in the landing bay.
Sir, with all due respect,
Do you think it's prudent to let her go down there again?
She hasn't been properly debriefed
Or psychologically assessed.
Living among those humans for so long may have--
You worry too much, Kragger.
I've always been overly cautious.
Still, you might want to keep an eye on her.
Oh, I'll be watching her closely.
Very closely.
And you will mind your own business.
Is that understood?
Yes, sir.
[goat bleating]
Move those civilians out of here.
We need this entire area cleared and leveled.
I'm on it.
John, we have to talk.
Nothing to talk about.
But I wanted to explain about Hro and me.
I'm a little busy right now, lieutenant.
This generator-- when we're finished,
It's going to be the size of a city.
A big one. It has to be.
It's got to sustain a force field strong enough
to protect Earth from the Gordanians.
I don't get what you see in that guy.
I mean, sure he's big and strong
And ridiculously good-looking, but so what?
That doesn't make him some kind of hero.
[goat bleating]
Here. Look after this little one.
[bleats]
Fine... But I still don't like him.
Wonder Woman: What exactly are you trying to prove here?
Think about it.
A single ship attacks a major city.
Then the thanagarian armada coincidentally shows up to save us.
I don't believe in coincidence.
So how is this going to help?
You don't know anything about Gordanian physiology.
No, but I know a frozen liver when I see one.
What?
The crew of this ship was dead long before
The thanagarians shot them down.
I think we've been set up.
Kragger: Welcome aboard.
Since you are now our partners in this great endeavor,
Commander Talak has asked me to show you our ship
And answer any questions you might have.
It's easy to get lost, so please stay close together.
I thought we'd start with the bridge
And then move on to our fully equipped medical facilities.
I'm sure you'll find these quite interesting.
Easy now.
Connect the absorbing plate to the integration unit.
Good.
This technology is amazing.
How does it work?
The circuits utilize Nth metal,
An element with properties you couldn't begin to understand.
Which properties wouldn't I understand?
The hyperconductivity or the mason-graviton inversion?
Man: Sector 17...
Second man: Received and understood.
Talak: Talak to comm center.
Link me to the high council.
Man: Right away, sir.
Commander Talak, what progress can you report?
Talak: We are on schedule, my lord.
With the help of the humans,
We should be operational within days.
Not a moment too soon.
As you see, the Gordanians
Have launched a new counteroffensive.
They have sealed off our expeditionary forces,
And their entire fleet is pressing toward Thanagar.
Man: You there!
How did you get in here?
I'm sorry.
I seem to have gotten separated from my group.
Don't move!
Lieutenant, I found one of your visitors in the comm center.
Kragger: Did he see anything?
I'm not sure.
Then don't take any chances. Lock him up.
Come with me. No, thanks.
[grunts]
Security! We have an intruder on level 5!
Batman: Diana, I was right.
The Gordanians are nowhere near Earth.
The thanagarians are-- aah!
Batman! Come in! Can you hear me?
Keep an eye on this one.
Commander, our security has been breached.
I was hoping to avoid this.
Deploy our contingency forces now.
By your command.
Wonder Woman: Superman! The thanagarians are lying.
Batman's been captured aboard their command ship.
[loud crash]
Great Hera!
They're here at the Watchtower!
The landing bay's opening!
They must have our access codes!
Aah!
Ugh! Ugh!
Superman: Diana's in trouble!
Get to the Javelin! Fast!
Aah!
Woman: I'm afraid we can't allow that.
[grunting]
What are you doing?
Talak: Can't let your friends jeopardize our mission.
Man: General Welles, the hawkmen are attacking the Justice League!
It's a double-cross!
Launch a full strike counterattack.
10 seconds to impact, sir.
[shouting]
[clicking]
Man: What happened? It's jammed!
[chatter]
Surrender or die!
Take them out! Fast and hard!
[shouting]
You wanted to learn about our technology?
Aah!
[grunting]
J'onn!
Now!
[weakly] feels like kryptonite.
Fire the gravity beam!
Kragger, seal off the area!
Kragger: Activate force field projection. Now!
Don't fight us. We're trying to help you.
Do you ever stop lying?
It was for your own good.
You've got to trust me!
Why? Whose side are you really on?
Don't you know?
[grunts]
I'm sorry, John.