Previously on Justice League...
We meet again, Kal-El.
What do you want?
Even as we speak, Apokolips is being assimilated
By the kryptonian menace known as Brainiac.
Once he's finished siphoning
The memory banks and technology of my planet...
He'll annihilate it.
Good.
We know he used you, humiliated you. Get over it!
All right. But I need you to do something for me.
Who are you?
They call me Forager.
Do you know someone named Orion?
Orion is a god who is far above us.
Hold still. We won't hurt you.
No, you most certainly will not.
Man: Superman has played his part.
Now it's our turn.
You imbeciles are letting Brainiac get away.
Oh, my stars.
What is that thing?
J'onn: We'll know soon enough.
No response.
The controls have been overridden.
So what do we do now?
What can we do, but wait?
[loud hum]
Welcome, Kal-El.
Once I offered you the chance to join me
In carrying on the legacy of Krypton.
Today I renew that offer.
You must be joking.
Why do you reject your great heritage?
The entire history of your planet,
Its knowledge and splendor,
Its awe and mystery
Are encoded within me.
Superman, don't...
I am Krypton.
You're a perversion,
Dishonoring the very memory of my father
And all my people.
And this is your final decision?
Read my lips. Go to...
Unfortunate...
But predictable.
Move!
Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah!
Uh!
Aah!
[yelling]
Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah!
Someone had to do it.
No problem.
Then it's over.
Brainiac: Again you've miscalculated.
It hasn't even begun.
Man: It's hard, isn't it?
But we must lovingly tend our garden
If we want it to grow strong and tall.
I hate this.
What's wrong, child?
I've tried, Highfather.
Really I have. But look.
Patience, my dear.
Everything has a purpose
And a place.
Everything?
Given time.
Man: Highfather.
I have urgent news from Apokolips.
Indeed.
We're friends of Superman.
He sent us to warn you that Darkseid is under attack on Apokolips.
Do not speak that name in front of the children.
You'll frighten them.
They should be afraid.
For too long, the shadow of Apokolips
Has threatened New Genesis.
Come with me.
Would you excuse us, children?
Orion: Well, let me mount an army.
While Darkseid is under siege,
We will attack and end
His reign of terror once and for all.
Superman asked for your help.
He doesn't want to start a war.
Don't be so sure.
Highfather: You forget.
In the name of peace,
We swore not to interfere on Apokolips.
We made a pact.
As long as Darkseid is in power,
There can be no real peace.
There is truth in what you say.
Then give the order.
No!
Though I love you like a son,
You are too young to remember
The endless bloodshed we endured.
Before making such a terrible decision,
I must commune with the source.
You will await my verdict.
Yes, Highfather.
[growls]
[yells]
Hyah!
[growling]
Darkseid.
Aah!
[screaming]
It appears our stratagem was a success.
Yes.
As promised,
I've delivered Superman into your hands.
Those people we met
Down below... who are they?
They're not important,
Just bugs.
And where are you going?
To face Darkseid.
But Highfather ordered you to wait.
Why are you so eager to fight?
I have my reasons. Now stand aside.
We can't let you go.
Try to stop me.
[beeps]
Next time I let Superman take charge,
Just hit me real hard.
Remember the terms of our bargain.
In exchange for Superman,
You promised to spare my planet.
Agreed.
But I still can't fathom why you need him.
Surely not for simple revenge.
It is quite elementary.
Observe.
Over the years,
I have roamed the universe, collecting data.
As my appetite grew,
I changed and evolved into what you see today.
From this central core,
I can send countless drones
To the farthest corners of the galaxy
To gather more data for my collection,
But it is not enough.
I have reached the limits of my programmed functions.
To evolve to the next level,
I must extract living D.N.A.
From the last kryptonian.
[screaming]
Now I become a true life form...
The likes of which this universe has never seen.
Brainiac: Wait.
What have you done?
Darkseid: Just a minor modification
To override your control circuits.
You are now the instrument of my will.
[screaming]
Brainiac: You deceived me, Darkseid, used me.
It's what I do.
J'onn, wake up.
What hit us?
It was Darkseid.
Then Superman was right.
This was all an elaborate trap.
Where is Superman?
I can't locate him.
He's either unconscious or...
All these worlds that Brainiac has visited.
Somewhere in here there might be information about Thanagar.
There's no time to think about that.
Superman needs us.
Why are you doing this?
Before Brainiac had the power to devour planets.
Now he can consume an entire universe.
[screaming]
He is my solution to the ultimate problem...
The anti-life equation.
This isn't Apokolips.
No. But Mother Box senses Darkseid's hand here.
But why?
You, of all people, should know,
The universe is filled
With chaos, confusion, and uncertainty.
I will tear it down to nothing
And then rebuild it,
Bringing order and discipline at last.
Think of it, Superman...
A new universe created in my image.
[rumbling]
What?
By the source.
Highfather, what is it?!
Darkseid.
Get everyone to the escape pods.
What?
We have no choice.
Evacuate the city.
Darkseid, I calculate that this reaction
Will soon reach critical mass.
If you don't release me,
There will be no stopping it.
Precisely.
Hawkgirl: Then I guess it's up to us.
Aah!
Brainiac, stop them!
I have no desire to save you,
But I am compelled to obey.
J'onn: Get back!
No way!
Hyah! Hyah!
Aah!
No!
Uh! Ungh!
Finish them now.
What?!
Hello, father.
Don't I get a hug?
Having fun?
Yes.
Come on!
Cover me.
Ungh! My pleasure.
[wind]
By the gods!
[yelling]
[yells]
[groaning]
Brainiac: Warning... circuit incomplete.
Critical system failure.
Hyah!
Where's Darkseid?
I don't know. But we've got to get out of here.
I'm glad to see growing up with Highfather
Has made you soft and weak.
You make an old man proud.
But I won't let you or anyone else
Stand in my way.
Spare the rod.
Superman: Any minute now, Brainiac will explode.
And guess what. You're going with him.
No, Darkseid.
To get off this rock, you'll have to go through me.
You really are a glutton for punishment.
Time and again, I've beaten you,
Humbled you.
What makes you think today's outcome
Will be any different?
Because this time,
I won't stop until you're just a greasy smear on my fist.
Let's go.
It seems you need
Another lesson in humility, boy.
Wonder woman: Wait!
Where's Superman?
That idiot. I'll get him.
The rest of you, take off now!
But...
Just do it!
I hope he knows what he's doing.
This is where you belong, Superman:
Under my heel.
Uh! Uh!
Uh!
Superman!
Go! I'm finishing this!
Kent, don't be a fool.
Get out of here now!
[beep]
No!
[scoffs]
Loser.
Nothing could have survived that,
Not even Darkseid.
You know something, Bruce?
You're not always right.
[raspy breathing]
[Lightray approaching]
Any sign of the others?
I've searched everywhere.
There's nothing.
Then all is lost.
[children giggling]
Listen.
I'll race you!
Highfather, Highfather!
It's a miracle.
How did you survive?
He found us and hid us in his hive
Until the storm blew over.
You did this?
Forgive my presumption, Highfather.
No. Forgive me...
For forgetting that everything has a purpose...
And a place.
Today, here at our side,
You have found your place.
Perhaps someday, you will find yours, as well.
Some day.