Narrator: Previously on Justice League...
We're looking at another dimension.
It's just like ours.
Batman: Almost. But their Flash is still alive.
So is their Luthor.
Green Lantern: Their world is the mess ours used to be.
Hawkgirl: Too bad we can't help them.
Batman: Who says we can't?
J'onn J’onzz: And the dimensions appear to be collapsing on each other.
Flash: So it's agreed, then.
Let's do it. I'm in.
[all screaming]
Uhh!
J'onn J’onzz: Look at that thing.
When we stop it, they'll be so grateful,
They'll roll right over for us.
Uhh!
[moans]
Reporter: And what's with the new costumes, guys?
We just felt it was time for a change.
[moans]
[beeping]
One question:
Why?
Because you and your friends
Couldn't do what needed to be done.
There are mercury switches at your hands and feet.
Any motion, and I'll know about it.
You've thought of everything.
No.
Just everything you'll ever think of.
[grunting]
Huh?
What are you looking at, huh?
Calm down.
You'll appreciate this someday.
Yeah? I don't think Hawkgirl is going to appreciate it too much.
That was an accident.
She's in our best hospital now, and--
I don't want to hear it.
Believe me, the last thing we want is to lose another...
Another what?
Batman: I think he likes you.
Must be my magnetic personality.
More likely, it has to do with what happened to this world's Flash.
You mean he's--
All this had to have been set off by something.
But to go this far,
Even over me...
It isn't that far from what we do...
If you think about it.
I'd rather not.
You figured a way out of here?
No.
Don't you mean, not yet?
No. I mean, not going to.
[grunting]
I can't believe they left it so unprotected.
We did... For a long time.
And how often did it come back to bite us?
[beeping]
[beeping faster]
Flash! Flash!
Uhh!
You'll appreciate this someday.
What are you doing?
Trying every possible combination.
9-1-9-3-9.
[beep]
How'd you know?
They're the numbers I use. How'd you get out?
I sped up my heartbeat till it looked like it flatlined.
I didn't know you could do that.
Neither did I, but I had to come up with something
If you weren't going to.
I couldn't, not with him
Anticipating everything I could ever think of.
But who could anticipate you?
I don't know about the rest of you,
But I'm ready to kick some serious--
You're gonna have to wait on that.
They've got Hawkgirl in a hospital somewhere.
You need to find out which one she's in
And get there before they hear about this.
This is your city. You know the hospitals better than we do.
I've got a portal to find.
I'll go with you.
Sorry, I have to do this alone.
Flash: Hospitals, hospitals.
Superman: They'd never keep her in that one.
There's no security.
And this one doesn't have the right equipment.
Wait a minute. In this world, we are the bad guys.
So?
Where would you send a sick bad guy around here?
Wait here. You're dead, remember?
Hey, the costumes will tip them off, anyway.
We'll just say it's a fashion choice.
[sniff sniff]
We need to see one of the inmates.
Why, certainly, Superman.
Right this way.
Oh, one little thing.
Today's password...
J'onn J’onzz, thinking: Applesauce.
Applesauce.
Right.
But Wonder Woman was supposed to say it.
[alarm ringing]
Weasel.
You must be stopped.
A robot.
I built mine to take over for me when I had to be away.
Green Lantern: Looks like the other guy had the same idea...
In spades.
Uhh!
Aah!
I knew you'd come here.
Just like I know you're going to... Do that.
What are you hiding for?
I do my best work in the dark.
I used to think that, too.
But what have you ever accomplished from there,
Aside from scaring a few punks half to death
And putting a few more in jail?
It all adds up.
Not fast enough.
If you really want to make a difference--
If you want to change the system instead of just patching it,
You can't be subtle.
You've got to step into the sunlight,
Take over, like we did.
[grunting]
Violent behavior will not be tolerated.
Nor will a bad attitude.
Woman: You're not supposed to pick the flowers.
Sorry, I couldn't resist.
It's all right.
It... is?
With me, anyway.
This kind of thing just doesn't bother me anymore.
In fact, nothing really bothers me anymore.
But you might want to watch out for Superman.
[explosion]
[electrical crackling]
Will you excuse me?
Ok.
[woman humming]
Think about it.
A world where there's no crime,
No victims, no pain.
And no choice.
Who elected you anyway?
Who elected you?
The problem with democracy is,
It doesn't keep you very safe. It has other virtues.
But you seem to have forgotten.
I didn't forget. I just chose peace and security instead.
You grabbed power!
And with that power,
We've made a world where no 8-year-old boy
Will ever lose his parents
Because of some punk with a gun.
[metal clanking]
You win.
[beeping]
Your friends are tearing up Arkham.
Then shouldn't we stop them?
I'm going in for her.
Ha! Ha! Ha!
Thanks.
I can't believe this is Gotham.
Where's the litter?
If you want people to respect the big laws,
You've got to enforce the small ones.
What are you doing?
The small laws, remember?
I'm not paying for this.
Bad food, lousy service,
And then you add up the check wrong.
Sir, you're disturbing the other customers.
Look? 5 and 5 make 15?
Would you come with us, please?
Get your hands off m--
Wh--? I didn't mean it.
I-I'm sorry.
I'll pay it, whatever it is.
And the food-- it was good, really.
They'd love it here, don't you think?
Who?
Mom and dad.
They'd be so proud of you.
Just drive.
Don't make any sudden moves,
Or we'll vaporize the entire lot of you.
Hold it.
These are my prisoners, and I'm taking them back.
You're in the right costume, but how do I know
You're not one of them?
Are you questioning my authority, lieutenant?
Put your guns down. Now.
[guns clicking]
We'll go out the back.
You fooled 'em.
Even I thought you were him.
I am him.
So without your Flash, the Justice Lords went rogue?
It wasn't quite that simple.
Hey, he was the conscience of your group,
And that means I must be--
Green Lantern: Come on, Jiminy.
[thunder]
Batman: They're as strong as we are
And just as smart.
But they're willing to kill.
What are you saying?
That we have to be willing to kill, too?
I won't cross that line.
How else can we stop them?
You're the smart one.
You figure it out.
We can't do it,
Not unless we cross some kind of line.
[beeping]
It's Luthor.
Escaped again? Yes.
And he's taken a hostage, and--
Don't do it.
Why not?
It worked pretty well back home.
But here, they're not ready for it.
We'll see about that.
Maybe we should all go.
All right, I'm patient.
[explosion]
Where's the hostage?
There never was one.
Sorry.
Aargh!
[screams]
[moans]
[scream]
Do it!
Ha!
[groan]
[gasp]
Whoa!
Uh!
Uh-oh.
Right here, big guy.
[groan]
[scream]
[moan]
Wow, Supes,
You really know how to bring down the house.
Can't do it. Can you?
I'm the last piece of your conscience.
And this is the one thing you'll never do.
I've done a lot of things
I thought I'd never do these last two years.
One more won't hurt.
Hold it!
Nice company you're keeping.
Must be your true colors.
It's just one of the hard choices I've had to make today
Go for it.
Oh, yes.
Aagh! Aagh!
[grunting]
[moan]
Aah!
It's a power disrupter,
And yours are now gone.
[gasping]
[groans]
This would be so sweet.
But a deal's a deal.
What deal?
A full pardon, in exchange for his help.
Everything he does from now on
Is your fault!
It's a high price,
But it's better than the alternative.
I knew you wouldn't be able to change his mind.
Yeah? How?
Because I've felt the same temptations he has.
They're pretty strong.
So you're not such a boy scout after all?
Never even made it to my first merit badge.
But I can't take full credit.
I never would have been able to reconstruct the disrupter
Without Superman's high-speed assistance.
Where is it now?
I believe Superman has it.
That was part of our arrangement.
Where do you go from here?
Back to running LexCorp?
Oh, the business world doesn't seem
As challenging as it used to,
And there's no poetry in it, either.
I have been giving some thought to...
Politics.