Previously on "Justice League."
This is commander Hro Talak.
In the name of the thanagarian authority
We claim your planet as a garrison
And have instituted martial law.
It would have been difficult to storm their Watchtower
Without the access codes you provided.
But if we open a hole in hyperspace,
It will destroy this entire planet.
Sadly, yes.
For Thanagar to live,
Earth must die.
The so-called Justice League
Is in violation of our marshal law.
They are to be considered an enemy
And dealt with on sight.
We've lost track of the Justice League.
They've blended with the populous.
It will be difficult to find them--
Unless, of course, you know where they are.
You've got a lot of nerve showing up here.
The situation is worse than you think.
I have a fix on their location.
This time...
They will not escape.
Captioning made possible by Warner bros.
Welcome back, lieutenant Hol.
You're in my way. Likewise, I'm sure.
Come with me.
I don't take orders from--
Construction is nearly complete.
The bypass generator will be operational within the hour.
Evacuate our troops.
I want the bypass activated as soon as it's ready.
[grunts]
What do you think you're doing?
I'm sorry, sir.
She's guilty of high treason,
Espionage, and consorting with the enemy.
They're building a hyperspace bypass.
When it's activated, it will destroy the planet
And everything on it.
Where did you get this?
From the holocam I planted on her.
Wait, it gets better.
I did what I thought was right then.
And that's what I'm doing now.
Hro...
Get her out of my sight.
Commander, I hated to be the one to tell you.
[grunts]
Assemble your strike force and deal with the leak.
This time, don't bother taking prisoners.
Ingenious.
Yeah, I'm impressed.
Let's go wreck it.
How? It's behind a force field.
Force field controlled from the command ship.
Go shut it down.
I'll take care of the generator.
That thing's the size of a city.
What are you gonna do, throw a batarang at it?
Something like that.
Good heavens!
[explosion]
[grunting]
Spread out.
They're hiding here somewhere.
Uh-uh!
All through hiding.
Come and get some!
Hyah!
Oof!
[screaming]
Let's use our inside voice.
Oh!
Oof!
[grunting]
Tails, I win!
Your weapons are pitiful!
Wait for it.
[screeching]
[grunting]
Oof!
Let's go.
Mind the glass, sir.
I want you, Superman, and Wonder Woman
To go to the command ship and shut down the force field.
And the rest of us?
You're going to help me retake the Watchtower.
It's crawling with thanagarian soldiers.
How are you planning on getting inside?
With that.
Well?
I have no idea how to fly this vehicle.
What's this do?
[boom]
That's not helping.
I'll need one of the hawkmen.
You think I'd tell you anything?
I'd sooner choke on your bones.
Ok by me.
Start with these.
We're running out of time.
I'll take the information from him.
I thought you couldn't read their minds.
I'll just have to try harder.
[screeching]
Ow! J'onn!
[grunting]
[groaning]
[screaming]
Ugh!
I have what we need.
I've asked master Bruce to refrain from leaving trash in the yard.
Why, Shayera?
Why would you do this?
I'm trying to save lives.
So am I.
Tens of billions of thanagarians.
So we trade the humans' lives for our own?
War makes for hard choices, lieutenant.
It's them or us.
The man I fell in love with
Would have found another way.
Are you talking about me,
Or Green Lantern?
I didn't want to believe it.
Shayera, I love you.
I can forgive your treason.
I can forgive everything.
Make this all go away.
Just tell me what I need to hear.
It was a meaningless flirtation.
You were lonely.
Tell me I'm the one you love, not him!
If you want me, I'm yours.
All you have to do is spare the Earth.
Perhaps you'll forget him once Earth is nothing but a memory.
Shuttle Epsilon 16 requesting entry.
Confirm docking code.
Docking code confirmed.
You are cleared to come aboard.
We weren't expecting you, sir.
There's been a change in plans.
[growling]
[grunting]
Ugh!
Oof!
Commander, the Justice League is approaching.
Kragger's strike squad has failed.
Launch interceptors.
Pretty bad odds.
Yeah.
They don't stand a chance.
Ok. The Watchtower's ours again.
So, where's your secret weapon?
You're standing in it.
Wait.
You mean we're gonna--
Take the Watchtower out of orbit
And drop it right on top of their little science project.
Get them to the escape pods.
Is that the last of them?
Yeah, the tower's completely pest-free.
Good.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Can't risk having the Watchtower
Burn up on reentry.
I'll have to guide it in manually.
Gentlemen, it's been an honor.
[screams]
Intruder alert!
All available security forces to engineering deck!
Belay that!
Green Lantern is mine.
[grunting]
Ooh!
[metal clanging]
[screaming]
I should leave you to burn.
The force field control is over here.
That is what you came for, yes?
You want it,
All you have to do is get by me.
It'll be a pleasure.
No-- this won't be like the last time
You took something that belonged to me.
Anything I took was freely offered.
Maybe you should take better care of your stuff.
[grunting]
I've beaten you, little man.
Any last words?
Yeah, you can kiss my ax.
[grunting]
Oof!
[yelling]
[groaning]
Mistake.
[screaming]
Hro, enough!
The fight's over.
You're a soldier, not a murderer.
I'm a fool...
For ever loving you.
It didn't have to be this way.
Yes...
It did.
[grunting]
We're cutting it a little close.
Have you shut off the force field?
Not yet. Where are you?
Aboard the Watchtower, guiding it to target.
That's insane! Get out of there!
Negative. I'm staying with it.
Batman!
Was he worth it?
This isn't about him,
It's about us.
Don't kill these innocent people, Hro.
Find another way.
[screaming]
There's no us anymore, Shayera.
[grunting]
Just a fallen traitor
And a soldier with a job to do.
She won't save you again, Lantern.
No woman's skirt to hide behind.
No ring.
What are you going to do now?
I was thinking of introducing you to my friend here!
All construction personnel now en route to mother ship.
Good.
Begin activation sequence.
[grunting]
That all you got?
My grandma hits harder than you.
No!
Always have to be the hero, don't you?
Right back at you.
[men grunting]
Who's next?!
Stand down!
Lower your weapons.
Commander?
Our mission is a failure.
There's no more reason to fight.
Let them go.
I hope you're pleased with yourself.
It will take years for us to rebuild elsewhere.
Then you'd better get started.
This is Snapper Carr reporting.
In a stunning turn of events,
The thanagarian forces have ended their occupation of Earth,
Departing for locations unknown.
Once again, the world owes a debt of gratitude
to the selfless heroism of the Justice League.
[click]
They've been in there a long time.
Yes, miss, they have.
If I may be so bold,
I'm neither a superhero nor a soldier,
So I'm hardly qualified to judge your actions by those standards.
But I do know this:
Without the great sacrifices you've made
We wouldn't be here to share this nice pot of tea.
Whatever they decide in that room,
In my eyes, you'll always be a hero.
She exploited our weaknesses,
Betrayed us--
Come on!
She was in the ultimate no-win situation.
But when push came to shove,
She came through for us, just like always.
She's a pariah to her people.
We're all she has left.
Believe me, J’onn,
I feel for her,
But after everything that's happened
I honestly don't know if I could ever completely trust her again.
We're arguing in circles.
It's time to take a vote.
They've sent for you, miss.
Thank you, Alfred.
Hawkgirl--
Before you start, I have something to say...
I came to this planet as a patriot.
I had a mission, and I carried it out.
What I couldn't know was that I would come to care for the Earth
And her people--
That I've come to care for all of you.
I've spent the last 5 years torn between my feelings
And my duty.
I won't ask you to do the same.
Therefore I am resigning from the Justice League,
Effective immediately.
Great.
No Hawkgirl, no Javelin,
No Watchtower.
What's gonna happen to the League now?
Do we all just walk away?
No, we rebuild,
Starting today.
J'onn's right.
Earth still needs us,
And we'll never let her down.
It's our duty.
You never asked how we voted.
It doesn't matter.
So, where are you gonna go?
I don't know.
Someplace where the fate of the world
Isn't in my hands,
Someplace where there are no more secrets,
No more lies.
Was it all a lie?
I love you, John.
I never lied about that.
I love you, too.