Aargh!
[people yelling on radio]
Re-route plasma flux to starboard defense screens!
Helmsman, get us out of the gravity well now.
Not enough thrust, general. We just lost reactors 5 and 6.
Then boom us out of here, Blastio.
Too late, they've locked us in a simbio-beam.
Great Darkseid, the fleet ambushed us as soon as we hit the troposphere.
Starkiller 2 is gone, and we are in full retreat.
They were waiting for us.
You knew going into that sector
Was a violation of our treaty with New Genesis.
It was a calculated risk.
You have served me well, general.
Take as many of them with you as you can.
As you command, my lord.
We've lost contact.
General Steppenwolf, come in.
Steppenwolf!
I'm afraid the general isn't returning any calls today.
Orion.
Your invasion force is shattered. It's over.
Please accept this parting gift with Highfather's compliments.
Aah!
[grunting]
We know of your mad ambitions, Darkseid.
This is your final warning.
Break the treaty again, and you will be destroyed.
J'onn: Magnificent, aren't they?
Yes, yes, they are.
You miss your home world very much?
It doesn't take a telepath
To see what's troubling you.
I suppose not.
Forgive me, I didn't mean to pry.
J'onn, wait. It's all right, it's just...
Well, it's a long story.
Earth doesn't seem to be in peril at the moment.
[groaning]
Man: Faster, dogs,
To restore the glory of great Darkseid.
You underestimated Highfather,
And again, it cost you dearly.
The solution to the anti-life equation
Was almost within my grasp.
But at what price?
Our forces are decimated, our defenses weakened...
It was a fool's errand.
Er, what I mean to say is...
No one questions me, Desaad.
No one.
Father, father, did you see?
Be still, fool, I'm not blind.
But what is it?
It's death.
I tracked the criminals back to their fortress,
But like a rank amateur, I stumbled right into a trap.
By all rights, I should be dead.
Their particle beam ripped my molecules apart,
And shot them halfway across the cosmos.
And you have no idea where home is?
J'onn, Thanagar is so far away.
We've never even come into contact with the Green Lantern Corps.
What?
I was just thinking, you, me, Wonder Woman, Superman,
We are, all of us, orphans and exiles.
Maybe we should call ourselves the "just us" League.
[loud rumble]
What the devil...?
Batman: Sensors are picking up a powerful energy surge.
But I've never seen a signature like this.
I have. It's a boom tube.
[loud rumbling]
We meet again, Kal-El.
You!
Stop him before he knocks us out of orbit.
Superman, don't!
Let go!
I see you haven't forgotten me.
What do you want?
Though it pains me to admit it,
I need your help.
My latest skirmish with New Genesis has left
My military forces at considerably less than full strength.
Why should we help you?
Because my enemy is your enemy.
Even as we speak, Apokolips is being assimilated by
The kryptonian menace known as Brainiac.
You are lying. I destroyed him.
Apparently, he is harder to kill than you realized.
You know his pattern, Kal-El.
Once he's finished siphoning the memory banks
And technology of my planet...
He'll annihilate it.
Good.
Superman! What! You can't mean.
You may not care what happens to me or my world, but know this:
If Brainiac isn't stopped, countless millions more will perish.
Think about it.
Hawkgirl: So, what are you saying?
You'd sacrifice millions of lives
Just because you don't like this guy?
You don't know Darkseid like I do.
Batman: We know he used you...
Humiliated you... Brainwashed you...
Wound you up like a tin soldier,
And turned you loose against earth.
Cry me a river.
On the outside chance that this isn't another one of his schemes,
We have to take action.
So I suggest you get over it.
Brainiac has already destroyed countless civilizations,
And now he threatens another.
Do you want this to be the legacy of your people?
I'm telling you, there's something wrong with this whole scenario.
All right. We'll play Darkseid's game,
But I need you to do something for me.
Fire!
Aah!
Uh!
Don't let up.
My lord, Superman and the Justice League
Have agreed to come to our aid.
Transport them here, now.
There!
[dialing]
Looks like Darkseid was telling the truth.
Looks can be deceiving. Just stay sharp.
[groaning]
That was fun.
Let me get this straight.
Orion is Darkseid’s own son?
New Genesis and Apokolips
Have been at war for centuries.
Apparently, Darkseid and Highfather
Exchanged sons as part of some kind of peace treaty.
Sounds whacky to me, too.
But with a conflict on this scale,
We could use some backup.
So, where do we find this Orion?
[rumbling]
Aah!
[roaring]
Ah!
Batman!
[grunting]
Are you all right?
Peachy.
[coughing]
Uh.
This way. That buzz bomb won't hold him for long.
You should be safe here.
Uh.
Who are you?
They call me forager.
Do you know someone named Orion?
Orion? I am just an unworthy bug.
Orion is a god who is far above us.
You are too modest.
You've shown courage, compassion...
No, no, you don't understand.
All of the gods are far above us.
I'm going to need a longer grapple.
Darkseid: Idiot.
You're wasting your time.
I suppose you have a better idea.
You should know by now.
I always have a plan.
Such grandeur.
It even outshines Themyscira.
I've never seen the like.
We can take in the sights some other time.
Let's concentrate on finding Orion.
What have we here?
I've never seen bugs like you before.
We're not bugs.
Well, you're certainly not gods.
Hey, come back here.
Only if you catch me.
He's worse than the Flash.
Stay on him.
Hey!
Uh.
Hold still. We won't hurt you.
No, you most certainly will not.
Superman: Brainiac!
Kal-El, what brings you so far from your adopted home?
I'm here to end you.
If your father, Jor-El couldn't stop me,
What hope have you?
Drop that force field and find out.
No, I don't believe that will be necessary.
Ah!
Superman has played his part, now it's our turn.
Now!
Aah!
It appears you've won this round, Kal-El.
No!
Behind you!
Aah!
Oh.
You ok?
Uh, I've had softer landings.
Ow.
Darkseid: You imbeciles are letting Brainiac get away.
What are you waiting for? Finish him.
Sure, but only because you asked so nicely.
Here's our ride.
Still think Darkseid was up to something?
Hawkgirl, I'd bet the farm on it.
Gone! But that's impossible.
J'onn: Some kind of warp drive?
No, according to the navicomputer,
He should be right below us.
Oh, my stars. What is that thing?
Ah!
We'll know soon enough.