Narrator: Previously on Justice League...
Uh! Oh!
We're not working together as well as we could.
What are you suggesting? - Practice.
Aw, man.
You're trying to set up another Injustice gang, aren't you?
We call it a society...
A secret society.
No!
You've got to trust your partners.
I do, but the fact is,
I'm the invulnerable one.
Are you saying we can't cut it?
That's what it sounds like to me.
Why didn't you let us finish him?
In a warehouse? That's far too small a stage.
I've had better luck handling whole armies.
And you know why?
Because I didn't have to worry about anyone but myself.
Then why don't you go back to that?
The least he could have done was put up some bail for us.
All Shade cares about is Shade.
We'd still be in the joint
If it hadn't been for your mom.
How is she gonna pay back all that money?
She'll just have to keep dancing for a few more years.
Sounds like Shade isn't too popular with you either.
Tell me where he is,
And I'll see that he gets what's coming to him.
You want Shade?
That's what I said.
Go look under a tree.
[laughing]
[engine starts]
[tires screeching]
I can do this on my own.
I don't need the League.
Fool.
Maybe, but I owe him quite a lot.
If it hadn't been for a certain "accident" he caused,
I never would have gotten my new mental powers.
That's why they broke up so easily.
You willed them to.
Even my mind isn't that powerful.
For months, I've been reading their body language
And facial expressions like a book.
They were holding back
Considerable resentment for each other.
All I had to do was get those feelings to come out.
How'd you do that?
Parasite, have you ever said something
You knew you shouldn't have,
Something really hurtful?
Sure.
What made you do it?
Too little sleep? Low blood sugar?
Maybe you were just in one of those moods
You get into every so often.
I hear that.
Precisely. This blessed organ of mine
Can send out thought waves that affect those moods.
They open the door that most people keep locked.
So, what's next?
We've already divided. Now we conquer.
Who do you think you are-- Batman?
It's been a long night.
Just tell me where Shade is, ok?
Look, buddy, I know Batman.
I once ratted out a counterfeiter to Batman.
And believe me,
you are no Batma-a-a-an!
[screaming continues]
You were saying?
All right! All right! All right!
Oh!
Sh-shade... He's setting up another job.
He's got this place
At the old North Hills subway station.
Not much of a trap.
I can go on like this all night.
My beams are as fast as you are-- light speed.
Yeah, but you don't think that fast.
Oh! Ooh!
Yo, bats. Come on, pick up. I know you're there.
What do you want?
I bit off a little more
Than I can chew with Sinestro.
You got to give me some help here.
I thought you didn't need any.
Well, I do now.
I'm at the old North Hills subway platform. Hurry!
Looks like I didn't need you after all, yo.
But you can help me tie him up.
Catch.
Uh!
The real Flash would have been too fast for that.
Aah!
What gave me away?
You overplayed your part, yo.
Grodd: Everyone's a critic.
We could have been
The greatest fighting force
In the history of the universe.
How do you walk away from that?
You were asking too much.
A little practice? That's too much to ask?
You wanted us to stop being individuals.
We're all just soldiers to you, interchangeable.
You don't care about us as people.
That's not true!
I care.
You don't care about me.
What are you talking about?
I'd give my life for you.
You don't know what you're saying.
Spy cam?
Who are you broadcasting to?
Hawkgirl, it's Lantern.
I don't have anything more to say to you.
Listen. Something weird is going on.
Meet me at the practice ring.
Well, where is he?
You know Batman. Always has to make an entrance.
Batman? Lantern was the one who called me.
I heard from Flash.
Down!
Out of the way! Everybody!
Hah! Ooh!
Careful!
I told you to get out of the way!
Aah!
Uh!
Superman.
Don't do it! It's Clayface!
Go!
Ha ha ha.
[crash]
Freeze him!
We did it. We got him.
But what about the Lantern?
Only a matter of time.
Soon we'll have the complete set.
Then the real fun begins.
Remember those old spy movies I used to act in,
where the villain would catch the hero but wouldn't kill him,
and then the hero would always get away?
I'm not much of a moviegoer.
My point is, we should get rid of them now.
What happened to your sense of drama, Mr. Hagen?
This is something that has to be done in front of the whole world.
Do your part, and I'll let you bring down the final curtain.
Don't underestimate us, clay.
We could have taken the League
even if Grodd hadn't been messing with their moods.
Clayface: We shouldn't overestimate ourselves either.
Right. What are we going to do about the Lantern?
I don't know. What are we going to do
About you, Mr. Stewart?
Can't hide from this.
Look out! Move it!
He's getting away!
Perhaps not.
He was mine.
Grodd: He's ours.
They all are now.
Announcer: And now,
For your local halftime entertainment,
Her last 2 albums have gone triple platinum,
And she's here tonight to sing her smash hit,
Gimme gimme all your love,
From her newest album underbelly.
Ladies and gentlemen, tina Squires!
[cheering]
[music playing]
Aah!
[audience murmuring]
Now that I have your attention...
We've come to this arena
Because it's where the strong routinely defeat the weak.
How you so-called higher primates revel in that.
Yet outside these walls, you do everything you can
to shackle the mighty and prevent them from fulfilling their destiny.
That's all about to end.
Just a small demonstration of our might.
Not convinced? There's more.
There they are... Your heroes,
Who violate every law of nature
By coddling the weak and cowards.
We say it's time for a new order.
But it can't arise until the old one departs.
Ready for your closeup, Mr. Hagen?
Why'd he do that?
Of course.
The Martian tricked us.
You froze the wrong one.
Grodd's been messing with our minds.
Great. How do we fight it?
We get over it. That's how.
Grodd: This isn't exactly the show I had in mind,
But in a way, it's going to be even better.
Don't forget your training.
Get 'em.
This time, I got the right one.
Never learn, do you? Uh!
Actually, I have learned a few things.
Aah!
Antifreeze, anyone?
Please, no jokes. Just get her.
Can't... Breathe!
[gasping]
Really?
Uh!
Wouldn't hit a woman, would you?
I would!
[audience cheering]
I knew this wouldn't work. I knew it.
I could have--
What?
Thanks.
[loud cheering]
That's a wrap.
Just about.
There's still a chance for us, you know.
What are you talking about?
We're the superior ones, you and I.
We should be running the world.
I don't think so.
Pity.
Aah!
You had your chance.
Now you can feel the pain.
I've... felt... worse.
Oh.
[cheering]
Whoo!
Back in business.
Aren't we?
A lot of things were said.
Yeah, but that was all mind control.
We didn't mean-- - We meant every word.
So, what do we do?
All we can do is say we're sorry and move on.