Wonder Woman: Previously on Justice League...
What brings you to the city of lights?
I never miss a good party.
Diana, I'd like to introduce you to my fiancé.
Vandal Savage is a Nazi war criminal.
He was-- my grandfather.
Vandal Savage III.
A pleasure to meet you.
Look at what we've got so far.
A Kasnian operative stealing military secrets.
Kasnia spearheading the International Space Station.
Good cover to circumvent
the weapons embargo they're supposed to be under.
Man: Platform one is ours.
Different man: It's Wonder Woman.
Why don't you have a word with her?
Aah!
It's the king. He's had a stroke.
If my father cannot rule, my duty is clear.
For the good of Kasnia, I must assume the throne
Until my father is able again.
The people need reassurance
Of the royal family's continuity.
Our wedding will take place immediately.
Ahh. Ohh.
Easy.
That's quite a shot you took.
I miss anything?
Plenty. Your friend Audrey’s moved up the wedding.
It's happening right now.
Like Hades it is.
You go there uninvited,
You'll be breaking international law.
I get my hands on Savage,
That's not all I'll be breaking.
You coming?
Hera!
Huh!
[beeping]
Aah!
[organ playing here comes the bride]
Dearly beloved, we are gathered here
In the presence of god and this company
That princess Audrey II of Kasnia
And Vandal Savage may be united
In holy matrimony.
This relationship
Is an honorable and sacred one
Designed to unite two sympathies and hopes into one,
And it rests upon the mutual confidence and devotion of husband and wife.
Therefore, it is not by any to be entered into
Unadvisedly or lightly
But reverently, discreetly, soberly,
And in the fear of god.
Into this holy estate
These two persons present come now to be joined.
If anyone has cause why this couple should not be united in marriage,
Let them speak now or forever hold their peace.
Aah!
[murmuring]
Audrey, stop!
I won't let you marry him.
Aah!
Does anyone else have any objections?
Introducing for the first time her royal highness queen Audrey
And her husband prince Vandal Savage.
[fanfare]
[waltz playing]
What was Diana thinking?
Has she lost her mind?
Well, it's obvious she's grown quite attached to you.
I'm fond of her, too, but her behavior is inexcusable.
Banish it from your mind.
Today is your wedding day, my beautiful queen.
I know that you only married me out of duty,
But when I look into your eyes,
I want to give you the whole world.
Sometimes, I almost believe you would if you could.
We'll see.
Vandal?
Where is my husband?
Attending to a minor diplomatic matter.
I'm to tell you that he will return shortly.
If her majesty requires anything,
I can send a chambermaid for it.
If I need any assistance taking a walk,
I'll let you know.
[buzzing]
[footsteps]
How dare you burst in here and ruin my wedding.
Aren't you even curious about what Savage is up to?
He's dangerous.
Why? Do you think he might throw a tank
Through my wall?
Grow up. He's obviously using you.
He's amassing military and political power.
For what?
What do you think?
He's got to be stopped!
You're a raving lunatic.
Not to say you weren't fun to go clubbing with.
This isn't a joke, Audrey.
I think Savage is responsible
For your father's sudden illness.
And I think you've just crossed a line.
Don't walk away, Audrey.
You're making a big mistake!
I can do whatever I please.
Surely you've noticed by now.
Busy?
Merely fortifying our defenses.
Wonder Woman penetrated them too easily.
She just accused you of being some sort of power-mad monster.
Did she?
We go out live in two minutes.
Vandal, what?
Shh!
You'll spoil the surprise.
[grunting]
Batman to Watchtower.
Hey. Hope you're having fun.
I'm up here watching the paint dry.
Wonder Woman's being held captive.
She's too well guarded for me to extract her.
Need backup? I'll grab the two Johns, and we'll--
J'onn J'onzz: Flash, Green Lantern,
Join me in the monitor room.
We have a developing situation.
What is it? I've got bats on the other line.
Well, look who's back.
Today, the world changes.
Kasnia is at the forefront of that change.
Crucial to these changes was Kasnia's contribution
To the international space station,
Platform one...
A contribution somewhat larger
Than you've been led to believe.
No. Even he wouldn't.
This device is called a mass driver,
But I prefer its more colloquial appellation, a railgun.
It's all very complicated.
Perhaps a demonstration is in order.
The asteroid is mostly iron ore.
The large coils are a magnetic accelerator.
The target is anywhere I say.
At this time, where is the U.S.S. Avington carrier group,
I'd pick up my pace substantially.
With our railgun in orbit,
Kasnia has the ultimate high ground.
I am now the dominant military power on Earth,
And there are going to be some changes.
Item one...
J'onn J’onzz: That weapon must be destroyed.
Its destructive potential is unimaginable.
I don't have to imagine it.
I saw the Yungar of Omega Centauri use one
To blow an inhabited moon out of orbit.
You get all that?
Batman: Most of it. We'll have to fend for ourselves.
Taking out that weapon is top priority.
What's the plan?
Plan? We blow that thing out of the sky.
It is possible that there are still hostages on board.
Astronauts are military. They know the risks.
Still, if we can save them, we should.
I concur.
If I were them, I'd want you to save the world,
Not waste time coming back for me.
Yeah, but we'd come anyway.
[beeping]
Spotters identify the bogey as the Javelin-7.
May we...
By all means.
[grunting]
I can't control this thing!
Counterpull. Avionics are off-line.
Brace yourselves. We're going down.
[beeping]
Target destroyed.
Vandal, what do you think you're doing?
Destroying the Justice League, building a railgun,
Assuming total dominion over the nations of the Earth.
You're ranting like your grandfather in an old newsreel.
Ha ha ha!
Sweet, foolish child.
Wonder Woman was right all along.
Ridiculous. You'd have to be over 100 years old.
I'm far older than that.
Savage: The first time a meteor granted me power
Was over 25,000 years ago.
While my fellows cowered with fear,
I dared approach the strangely glowing rock.
It was warm, and the night was very cold.
I slept curled up next to it,
Not realizing what its rays were doing to me,
But over the millennia that followed
As I watched those around me grow old and die
While I remained unchanged,
I discovered the truth
And came to accept my destiny.
Destiny?
I live to rule.
Delusions of grandeur aside,
I rule Kasnia.
That's why I married you.
It's also why I poisoned your father.
You... Poisoned?
Aah!
Unh!
[gasp]
Guards, confine this brat to her quarters.
Ohh!
Unhand me! I command you!
Let me go! Unh!
You have any idea what this is gonna do to our insurance premiums?
I don't suppose anybody brought the keys.
Oops.
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Secure the control room.
I'll find the hostages.
[clang]
[beeping]
[rapid beeping]
Unh!
[man speaking Kasnian]
That won't distract them for long.
Unh!
Hold these, would you?
Sucker.
[grunting]
Aah!
Ha ha ha!
[buzzing]
Is this everybody?
Yeah.
Stay with me.
Once we shut this place down--
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Let me out, do you hear me?!
I demand that I be set free immediately!
Oh. Hi.
Audrey, we need your help.
I can't even help myself.
Vandal's usurped my father's throne.
You're the queen. You have to take command of the situation.
How?
You can start by taking us
To the control room.
They're stalling, Vox.
Sir?
The nations of the world.
Instead of paying me tribute, they're stalling and plotting against me.
They'll have to be taught who's in charge.
It's a shame really.
I rather enjoyed Paris.
Hang on, buddy.
[whooshing]
Ohh!
He's inside.
Stay here.
Can I borrow your earrings?
Heck of a time to accessorize.
[gasping]
Breathe easy. You're gonna be ok.
Yeah? Wish I could say the same for them.
Ooh!
You find the control room?
Yeah. Follow me.
Ohh!
Unh!
Unh! Aah!
Vox: Apparently, you didn't get the message.
Let me make it loud and clear.
Unh!
Not another word.
They really are a girl's best friend.
You're in my way.
Can't you shut this thing off?
J'onn J’onzz: Batman, we couldn't prevent the railgun from discharging.
Me neither, but I did manage to change the targeting coordinates.
Where'd you send it?
Right here.
[alarm sounding]
[speaking Kasnian]
[men yelling in Kasnian]
[men yelling]
Hey, we can't just leave.
What's to stop somebody else
From taking control of that thing?
That.
You've got a great deal of rebuilding to do.
I never liked the palace anyway.
Drafty.
But maybe this is a chance for me and Kasnia to make a new start.
[groaning]
Aah!
You sure can pick them.
Seize that thing.
I don't know how you survived,
But I promise that you'll pay
For your crimes in full.
Do your worst, child.
I'm immortal.
I can't be killed.
We'll see.
[groans]
You know, we never did get to finish our dance.
I don't know what you're talking about.
If you say so,
But you're still taking me dancing.