We have all been wronged by the same man.
We have. We have.
We all seek the same redress.
We do. We do.
We agree to work together
To achieve our ultimate goal.
We will. We will.
Speak your names.
Toyman.
Livewire.
Weather Wizard.
Kalibar.
Metallo.
Speak the word and seal the pact.
Together: Revenge.
[sirens]
You said he'd come.
A matter of time.
He's unaccountably fond of this dump.
The cops seem fond of it, too.
Toyman, isn't that thing ready yet?
Toyman: Just finishing up.
Everybody down!
[shouting]
Nice.
I'm sensing something's moving
Through the local air mass, heading this way fast.
The rat's taken the cheese.
You ready, Toyman?
You bet. This will be fun.
Uh-oh. Wrong rat.
Watch out for iron giant.
Those darts are no joke.
Xxx: Copy that. I'm only a few minutes away.
Be careful. This is obviously an ambush.
Livewire: Those guys travel in bunches.
Maybe we should call this off.
Excellent advice.
Aah!
Grr! Oh!
Incoming!
Windy.
I gathered.
There are so many reasons
Why that shouldn't have worked.
Our next priority is to get rid of Metallo.
I got an idea.
Hang on.
J'onn, make yourself scarce.
Aah!
Looks like Supes is gonna miss the party.
Give us some more cover.
The Amazon's mine.
[screaming]
Maybe you should get a strap for this.
That all you got?
Not quite.
Impressive, little man.
If you stand down right now,
I'll let you live to tell the story.
I just flattened Wonder Woman.
You really think you can beat me?
I'm not trying to beat you.
I'm trying to stall you.
Stall me? For what?
Ah... Ooh!
For what it's worth, I don't think
You could have taken Batman, either.
Rain, rain, go away.
Little Johnny wants to play.
[machine whirring]
Give it up, Toyman.
You'll never hit me with that thing.
Maybe not, but what about your friends?
No!
Aah!
Superman go bye-bye.
Stay back. It's full of acid.
Aah!
Do I look like I'm playing games?
What are you gonna do to me?
I'm gonna punch a hole in your head.
We don't do that to our enemies.
Speak for yourself.
I'm trying to speak for Superman.
This is Snapper Carr, returning to our continuing coverage
of the death of Superman.
I'm here at first Metropolis cathedral,
Where just hours from now,
services will be held for the world's greatest hero.
In addition to friends, colleagues, and loved ones,
Heads of state from over 400 countries
Are expected to attend today.
In the streets of Metropolis, as in cities all over the world,
Thousands have gathered
To pay their last respects to the Man of Steel.
Our all-day live coverage will conclude
following Superman's ceremonial interment later this evening.
Afterwards, our panel of commentators and pundits
Will debate the question on everyone's lips--
Without Superman, can there be a Justice League?
Our coverage of the death of Superman will continue.
I must admit...
I'm also concerned about the League's future.
I never expected to hear
That kind of talk from you, J'onn.
How many battles did we win
Simply because he was there?
Yeah. I used to be able to goof around so much
Because I knew Superman had my back.
Now all I've got is his example,
And that's gonna have to be enough.
What is it, Alfred?
I'm afraid it's time, master Bruce.
I'm not going to the funeral.
Why?
Because he's not dead.
What tipped me off was the lack of evidence.
Sir?
I brought all this from the crime scene,
And I've examined it every way I know how.
And you found?
Absolutely nothing.
No scorching, no residue, no radiation.
Objects were here, then they were gone.
I'm afraid I don't understand.
Matter can't be created or destroyed,
Just changed from one form into another.
As you say, sir.
I believe I heard something about that
When I attended grammar school.
So, unless the law of conservation of mass has been repealed,
There's still hope.
That's... wonderful news, master Bruce.
Nevertheless, don't you think
You should make an appearance?
What for?
I've got work to do.
Batman hasn't arrived.
Have you spoken with him?
He's still not answering calls.
He doesn't handle loss very well.
[excited murmuring]
Is that him now?
I can't see.
I can.
Luthor, how dare you show your face here?
Lois, I--
You've come to gloat.
You've tried to get rid of him for years.
Are you happy now?
Isn't this what you've always wanted?
I hate you! I hate you!
[sobbing]
Believe it or not, I'm going to miss him, too.
J'onn: Though we gather here today,
Bound together in sorrow and loss,
We share a precious gift.
We are all of us privileged to live a life
That has been touched by Superman.
The Man of Steel possessed many extraordinary gifts,
And he shared them with us freely.
None of these gifts were more remarkable
Than his ability to discern what needed to be done
And his unfailing courage in doing it,
Whatever the personal cost.
Let us all strive to accept his gift and pass it along,
As an ongoing tribute to Kal-El of krypton,
The immigrant from the stars
Who taught us all how to be heroes.
[laughter]
And Superman holds the grenade in his hands like this.
So it blows, and he doesn't even move.
And I say, "are you all right?"
And he says--
This is the best part.
He says, "fine. And you?"
[laughter]
To Superman.
Together: To Superman.
Perhaps this isn't the best time,
But we need to consider replenishing our forces.
A new member? Who? Aquaman maybe?
Metamorpho.
Is Supergirl old enough?
Before we look outside, we should start with family.
Batman, this is Diana.
Go ahead.
We're discussing the future of the Justice League.
We're hoping you'll make it official
And become a full-time member.
I'm busy. Batman out.
Yeah, Aquaman could definitely pick up
Batman's slack in the pompous jerk department.
He's grieving. Give him time.
What's with all the long faces, justice dweebs?
It's like a wake in here.
Lighten up. The answer to all your problems has arrived.
Since we're going to be working together,
you can call me Lobo.
You are not welcome here.
This is a private gathering.
Yeah, yeah. Superman kicked the bucket.
That's why I'm here.
I don't know you, but I'm pretty sure I don't like you.
Good instinct. His name's Lobo.
He's a lowlife bounty hunter.
The main man happens to be
The best bounty hunter in the known universe.
You could ask Superman,
If he weren't busy pushing up daisies.
Hey, don't talk about him like that.
Superman was our friend.
Mine, too. I saved his life once, you know.
That's not how he told the story.
Whatever. The point is, Superman bit the big one,
And the main man's here to take his place.
You're no Superman.
The ladies say different.
Stay down.
On the contrary,
Get up and leave.
The Justice League
Does not require your services
At this or any other time.
Now I get it. You clowns don't think
The main man is tough enough
To join your little girl scout troop.
Easy mistake to fix.
You want an audition?
Come on, ladies. Let's dance.
[faint beeping]
Another dead-end.
I'm beginning to wonder if I might be wrong.
I've got some things to say.
I should have said them when you were here, but...
Despite our differences,
I have nothing but respect for you.
I hope you knew... Know that.
You showed me that justice
Doesn't always have to come from the darkness.
I'll miss--
[distant explosions]
What did you always call it, Clark?
"the never-ending battle"?
[woman screaming]
This is hopeless. We may as well
Be throwing candy corn at them.
So, what do you want to do--
Give them the city?
You think your pitiful human prison can hold me?
This looks like a job for Superman,
But I don't think he's coming.
Heh heh heh!
Hyah!
Yah!
Aah!
Uh...
[distant sirens]
Too bad. He was kind of cute.
Come on, Green Longjohns. Let me out of here
So I can go upside your head.
[whistles]
[engine revving]
Remember to look both ways before you cross me.
Huh?
You talk too much.
Oh...
You want to settle down now?
Please say no.
[whistles]
I got it.
Whoo-hoo!
Ah! Ah! Ooh! Ah!
All right, that's it!
Flash: I'm ok!
All right, already. I guess I'll let
You all stay on the team with me,
But I'm the leader.
Ow!
The Justice League is about more than physical power.
It's about ideals, caring, helping.
Buy me a ticket to Pukesville.
All right, all right.
Say what you want,
But the Justice League needs the main man.
Green Lantern: He might be right.
Reporter on screen: Metropolis is under siege.
Following a mass jailbreak,
Dozens of supervillains are running amok downtown,
Apparently in celebration of the recent loss of--
Lobo: You ain't gonna be sorry you brought the main man.
Right. Like we were going to
Leave you alone in the Watchtower.
But long as I'm here,
I get to bust heads.
You will do precisely as we instruct--
No more, no less.
Sure thing. Finders keepers on any bounties, right?
You need to be quiet now.
Get your own money.
There's plenty.
Guess that was a little too much to hope for.
[screaming]
Aah!
Uh!
Lobo: Hey, hat hair!
Want a piece of me?
Wuss.
[groaning]
I'm gonna grind you into paste.
Awful brave talk for a dead man.
I'm not dead yet.
You're right.
My watch is about 10 seconds fast.
[groaning]
Uh!
Aah!
Does that account for everyone?
Say it. Say it.
Uncle.
I can't hear you.
He's beaten. Put the car down.
I was gonna.
Pretty good, huh?
When you got Lobo on your team,
Who needs Superman?