Previously, on Justice League...
Kilowog: John, they got her.
They got Kat.
Take care of him.
It's called the Legion of the Third Eye,
A fanatical cult from the planet Kalanor.
Flash: And what about this Katma Tui?
I'm not sure what happened to her.
She was the Green Lantern who trained John.
They must've been close.
Despero, I presume.
A new order to the universe is coming,
One that will be written in fire...
And with the blood of all who oppose me.
Aah!
[grunting]
He's preparing to start a massive war of conquest.
You'll stay here and coordinate with them.
But I--
Mmm...
Despero: O flame of Py’tar,
Infuse me with your power
So that I may carry out your will.
Go!
The conquest begins now!
Emblazon my word and will across the cosmos!
Despero's created one of the most formidable forces I've ever seen.
He's out to control the galaxy,
And I think he can do it.
The galaxy is a big place, Kat.
Despero doesn't have the manpower.
He'd spread his forces way too thin.
Not if he pulls in new recruits from each world he conquers.
Katma's right.
Despero can subjugate a people using only his mind.
His army will grow with each world he conquers.
All right, then. Enough talk.
Let's mobilize the corp.
I doubt these amateurs can hold their own
Against a few thousand Green Lanterns.
Despero's got some kind of dampening field around this planet.
Communications with Oa are impossible.
Then sit tight.
I'll be back with the cavalry.
We are betrayed!
And you led them here!
Sorry, honey, I'm too good for that.
[grunting]
What the--
Stewart, what are you doing?
My ring. I can't get it to work.
There's too many of them.
Regroup at the secondary site. Hurry!
Ok, everybody out.
The other way!
Trapped!
Then we'll make our last stand here.
Hyaa!
Hey, G.L., did you miss me?
Like a toothache.
[grunting]
John, Katma. Are you guys ok?
Ah, you must be the mystery woman.
And you must be?
Delighted to meet you.
That's a bit old-fashioned.
I'll explain later.
We gotta move before reinforcements arrive.
There seems to be a recurring theme here.
You can read these?
You mean you can't?
These chambers are ancient.
No one knows who built them.
These icons suggest that your world
May have had a flourishing ecosystem at one time
Much different from the barren desert conditions of today.
Legend does say that Kalanor was once a paradise.
This same tree seems to repeat throughout.
Apparently, it holds some significance.
The only image I recognize is the flame of Py’tar.
That tells me that this evil has been on Kalanor for centuries.
Radocko: Ancient drawings by cavemen, that's all they are.
Are we just going to sit here and talk or do something?
Patience, Radocko.
We might as well accept that the cause is lost.
Forgive him. He is young.
But I must admit... It does look hopeless.
Only if you believe it to be is it so.
Katma: Try again.
I don't get it. Is the ring...broken?
Power rings don't break. But something else did.
You mean me? That's nuts.
The broken wills of over a million Kalanorn speaks to the contrary.
So Despero somehow got to me.
He did something inside my head.
That would explain this feeling,
Like a piece of me is missing.
An important piece.
But if that's gone...
Then we start over.
I trained you once. I can do it again.
Back to basics? I don't think so.
The problem with half the Corp, you included,
...is that once you learn to use your rings like jackhammers,
you forget the subtleties
Of manipulation and control.
I know. I know. The mind is the weapon, not the metal.
At least you remember that much.
It's time to relearn what you've learned.
Now you sound like Yoda.
Look, you have two choices:
Let me help you retune your mental disciplines,
Or you can live with your emerald impudence.
Impotence?
Uh...Right. I-- I was just going over there.
Ok. You win.
Guess it really will be like old times.
Don't presume too much, John Stewart.
Krizblack, do you have news from the Ministry of Conversion?
Lieutenant Franzee has a report, lord.
Step forward, my son.
Our forces stormed the enemy headquarters.
Unfortunately, the nonbelievers escaped.
I failed you.
I see.
And naturally, you've come to beg for forgiveness.
I know I'm unworthy.
This is true.
What must I do to atone?
March into the desert dressed in simple robes and without provisions.
Stay there and await a vision from me.
Only then will you be cleansed
And ready to reenter my kingdom.
Thank you, lord Despero.
I praise your name. Thank you!
Despero is the beginning.
Despero is the end. Despero is all.
Tell lieutenant Franzee's forces that he won't be back.
Then send them out again.
These nonbelievers must be brought around to my truth.
Yes, lord. But if I may be so bold,
Your power is great and theirs is small.
Surely they pose no threat.
A lone voice in the darkness
Can rouse many if not snuffed out.
My word is absolute and must be accepted by all.
Of course, lord.
Remember, surface thought is only the initiator.
The inner governing thought
Maintains the integrity through power of will.
This is key when multitasking,
Especially if you're in space.
[grunting]
Aah! Oof!
If that was your life support field,
We'd be picking you up with a vacuum now.
Let's take it from the top.
This is useless.
Where do you think you're going?
I need some air.
I didn't say you could go.
Excuse me?
You're as bad as that Rayner kid you sent me to train.
What's your problem?
I think the problem is yours.
I'm not a kid anymore!
She's got a bit of an edge to her.
You're kidding, right?
Just an observation.
It's like she thinks I'm still a raw recruit.
We tend to cling to images of people
From when we knew them best,
Forgetting that they do change.
Ok. So as someone who knows John Stewart in the here and now,
How would you handle me?
As a friend and equal,
I'd say get back in there and try again
Or I'll knock you into next Tuesday.
Somehow I fail to see the difference in your approach.
Oh, there's a difference.
You just haven't figured it out yet.
Now get back in there.
Ooh!
Despero must have a weakness.
We need to discover what it is and exploit it.
[chomping]
Got any more of that?
Not exactly Bob and Terry's.
No kidding.
But with a hypercharged metabolism,
I can't always be choosy.
Especially if we're going into action.
Kilowog, your rings and Lantern batteries
Are all fed from a much larger power source, correct?
That's right. The central power battery on Oa.
Its energy is almost infinite.
Despero is channeling a great deal of power himself.
It stands to reason that he may have
A similar energy supply and distribution system.
How about that flame of his?
My thoughts exactly.
Somehow Despero draws power from it.
Then he channels it through his third eye.
So if we take out the flame--
The Pytar's comprised of pure nuclear plasma.
You can't just blow it out like a candle.
You can with a carbon bomb.
A what?
Of course.
Carbon can be used to arrest nuclear activity.
And I can build one in a few hours.
Ladies and gentlemen, I give you Kilowog,
The man of a thousand talents.
Oh!
Aah!
Soon, great Py’tar,
We will receive word from our forces
On our latest conquest.
[clears throat]
Some better news this time, I trust.
Indeed, lord.
Speak.
Lord Despero, the unbelievers and off worlders
Have regrouped in the city's ancient catacombs.
I can show you where to find them.
And why should I take your word?
What do you gain from this betrayal?
I only wish to be part of the winning side.
Ha ha ha!
Well, young one,
You've assured yourself a position there indeed.
Prepare your forces.
I will show this resistance the error of their ways.
They will accept the light of Py’tar,
Or they will die.
I'm afraid he's finished.
When this mission's over,
We'll have to recall Rayner
To take over John's sector.
Just like that?
He's given up on himself.
He's not the only one.
But I guess that's what happens
When a toy loses its luster.
Are you going to need all those power cells?
If that's what it takes.
I can still pull my weight, you know.
There's more to me than just a fancy ring.
I've always known that, John.
There's an exhaust port that few know about.
It will take us into the throne room.
Excellent.
You sure this thing'll work?
Thermal mechanics was always my best subject.
We have every confidence in your abilities, Kilowog.
[blast]
Aah!
Don't just stand there! Light 'em up!
Aah! Oof!
Aah!
Hey, what's Katma doing?
Buying us time. We must go.
Say what?
We have the carbon bomb.
If we are captured, all hope is lost.
J'onn's right, little poozer.
We got a job to do.
[grunting]
Hawkgirl: J'onn, are you ok?
I'll let you know when my head stops throbbing.
Katma?
She's still out cold.
I admit I am puzzled as to how you survived the Py’tar,
But it's just as well.
Killing you is a waste
When I can make better use of your talents
In my army.
We're not interested.
It's not like you have a choice.
I've just launched a second invasion wave.
Soon, I will launch another.
You three will be part of it.
Prepare to embrace the power of the Py’tar.
[grunting]
Aah!
This would seem to be it.
Allow me.
Now, who's next?
Unh...
Keep away from her!
The wings give her an exotic quality,
Wouldn't you agree?
I don't think I'll put her in the army.
I have just the place for her
As one of my personal attendants.
Don't even think about it.
Aah!
Yeah!
[grunting]
Round two, freak.
Ooh...Oh...
[beeping]
Fire in the hole!
Wait! Stop!
Unh!
[straining]
Aah!
What are we waiting for?
The Py’tar. It's a sentient being.
A what?
It's alive. In pain.
It wants to make contact.
Unh!
Not this time.
I can almost connect with it.
[screaming]
J'onn!
Ok. We are officially spooked here.
Hear me, o children of Kalanor.
Behold, I am the Py’tar, the living soul of this planet.
Despero is a great deceiver.
He has misused my power for his own petty ends.
I say unto thee the Py’tar is not a source of hatred,
But a beacon of hope.
In times gone by, Kalanor was a paradise.
It can be again.
But thou must reject the dark ways of Despero
And step into the light.
The choice is thine.
[groaning]
Py’tar, do not forsake me.
Oh!
Oh, Py’tar.
Now I see...
Paradise.
It's a miracle.
It's just the normal life force of your planet
Reasserting itself after centuries of entrapment.
And you won't have to worry
About Despero anymore.
Where is old 3 eyes?
He finally saw the light.
Well, ok, then. We've saved the day.
Can we go home now?
There's still a lot that needs to be done to rebuild Kalanor.
We could use your help.
Sorry, Kat. Duty calls.
Good-bye, Shifflet. Good luck to you all.
Hey, Kilowog!
Bratwurst, my place, next week.
You're on, poozer.
What's a bratwurst?
Phew!
That Katma’s quite a woman.
Yeah. A good teacher, too.
But some things can't be taught.
Some things you only get through experience.
Like?
Clarity.