Previously on Justice League...
Mercy, I'm...
Sick? Dying?
And you couldn't do it somewhere else?
Now, where's professor Ivo?
When will the professor come back?
Luthor: Never.
You're going to take care of me now?
You're going to have to take care of me, too.
Otherwise, I'll go to sleep
And never wake up again.
Luthor: Looks like Ivo was right on the money.
His duplication program seems to be working
Rather well.
A psychic sweep.
Of the whole city.
Once the gate is opened, it might not be so easy to close.
[all talking at once]
Superman: J'onn, are you all right?
Leave me alone!
This thing can copy us...
Flash's speed, Wonder Woman's strength,
Even my ring.
Aah!
You come here, and all you'll do
Is make him even stronger.
Unh! Arr!
Unh!
Unh! Unh! Ugh!
Stay back. I'll take it from here.
You don't have any powers.
I have this.
[gasp]
[groaning]
It's a package deal.
You get our strengths...
But you also get our weaknesses.
You always carry kryptonite around with you?
Call it insurance.
And they say I'm scary.
[knock on door]
Well, did you finish them off this time...
Oh. Look who finally showed up.
Like you were really expecting me.
I was but not quite this soon.
People can be very predictable
In their wants and needs.
The only reason I'm here is to let you know
That two of your friends came by.
You tell them anything?
No, but how long can it take
Before they figure out you're here?
Aah!
Are you just going to stand there?
Nothing.
Superman: I scanned downriver.
Not even a trace.
And we still have to find Luthor, too.
G.L., let's follow up with Ivo.
The rest of you, keep looking for the android.
Wonder woman: What about J'onn?
Good question.
We're not sure what's going on with J’onn.
See if you can find him.
Of course.
Has anyone checked the sewers yet?
Uh, maybe g. L. And the big guy
Need some backup.
[thinking] The hatred shouldn't have surprised me,
But the selfishness,
The sheer volume of it,
The cheap attempts to disguise it.
What do you know?
A fresh rabbit every now and then,
And you're happy.
At least you're honest.
What am I fighting for?
Who am I fighting for?
[growls]
Jennifer!
Slow... aah!
Unh!
Next time, I let you go first.
Grab whatever you can
And watch out for the wind.
What wind?
Aah!
I managed to pull these out.
Maybe they'll give us a lead to Luthor.
Any sign of old egghead?
No. There was no one in here.
[sigh]
You'll be ok here for a while.
It's still got the shielding you put in.
You mean you didn't sell the lead for scrap?
What would your accountant say?
Lex, I'm doing you a favor here.
No, you're not.
You're doing this because you need to.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Face it, mercy. You missed me.
You missed the excitement,
The sense of transgression,
Not to mention certain other things.
You're not good for me, Lex.
That much I know.
So finish your suit
And get out of here.
Sorry, but I'm going to be around
For a long, long time. Get used to it.
You've got the whole Justice League after you.
I've got an ally of my own now,
And soon, it's going to be
Just like old times around here.
Maybe better.
[gasp]
Lex.
You've got the wrong... dude!
Not again.
You had to buy the cheapest wiring you could find?
How am I supposed to get any work done?
Will you stop yelling?
You're lucky to have a place at all.
[crash]
It's all right. She's ok.
She's way more than ok.
Mm-mm.
What?
Just something he must have picked up.
Remember that ally I told you about?
This? You're kidding.
I'm serious.
Deadly serious.
Just ask the Justice League.
Right, my friend?
Right?
Why did you leave the house?
I had to look everywhere
Until I heard you yelling and...
First things first.
Did you finish the Justice League?
No.
Then what are you doing here?
Get back out there.
Why?
Because I'm telling you.
That's not good enough anymore.
Any sign of her?
Sorry. Nothing.
Nope. Not a trace.
Nothing? No tracks?
A piece of clothing maybe?
All right. Let's move on.
[thinking] I'm freezing my butt off,
And I don't even know the kid,
But I know how I'd feel
If she was my little girl.
[speaking] hey. Wait up!
Man, thinking: I'll stay up all night if I have to.
Man: I don't care what it takes.
Woman: I wish it were me instead of her.
Man: Only 6 years old.
Guys, over here.
Professor Ivo, I presume.
The water washed away some of the dirt
That was covering him.
I don't think he's going to be telling us
If Luthor's been here.
Come on. This whole scorched earth deal.
Of course he's been here.
Green Lantern: And guess who else has.
Batman was right.
Ivo, the android, Luthor...
They're connected.
Yeah. It's all making sense now,
Even to me.
There's more.
The reason Ivo worked out the duplication program...
It was so the android could evolve.
Evolve? Into what?
You don't want to help me get rid of the League,
That's fine.
I'll do it myself.
It won't be easy, one against 7.
I could get killed,
But it's better this way
For both of us.
You have your own life to live now.
I've done all I can for you.
Go. Be happy.
Oh! Ohh!
Go.
I'll do it for you.
I'll do it.
Are you out of your mind
Messing with him like that?
He could flatten you like an ant.
Ha ha ha!
Your concern is touching
And not entirely unexpected,
But professor Ivo took that
Into account when he built it.
This is a kill switch.
There's a bomb at the base of his brain,
And all I have to do is press this little button.
Does he know about that?
He doesn't need to.
He's going to do what I want
Out of love, not fear,
But unfortunately,
Love seldom lasts forever.
Man, thinking: We've got to find her.
Man: We've got to keep looking
No matter how cold it is.
Man: We'll find her. I know we will.
Woman: Please, lord, let her be all right.
Woman: She's got to be here somewhere.
Man: I'm not giving up.
Man: Come on, baby, where are you?
Jennifer: Mom, I'm sorry I ran away.
Please come and find me.
I'm so scared.
[crying]
Don't be afraid.
All right, everybody.
Let's fan out and...
It's her!
We found her!
She's fine!
I don't believe it.
Look at her.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
You're great.
Whoever you are, thank you.
Such a blessing.
It's so wonderful.
How'd he do that?
Where did he go?
Wonder woman: You're not getting away that easily.
Batman, I found the android.
Where?
He's flying over downtown.
Keep on it. I'll tell the others.
And one more thing...
Don't go near him.
Batman: The android's over downtown.
We'll be right there.
You better hang back.
I'll be using the kryptonite again.
Superman: I hear you.
Got it. See you in a few minutes.
It's showtime.
[groaning]
Unh!
Aah!
Unh! Ohh!
Batman: Some people never learn.
[groaning]
I guess that goes for androids, too.
I learn, but I also adapt
And evolve.
Aah!
Ohh!
Ohh.
Flash: Hey. Here I am.
No. There I am.
Come on, chump. Over...
Here?
You're just too fast for me, bro,
But not him.
Oldest trick in the boo...
If that thing copies your powers,
We'll never be able to take him down.
But I can't just...
You have to.
Aah!
Ohh.
Let's finish them.
We are not your enemy.
You know what to do.
Yes. You know.
Nothing can stop you now.
You have all their powers.
Use them well.
So you lied to me.
What?
It was all a lie, wasn't it?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Then let me spell it out for you.
I can read your mind, Lex.
If that's true,
Then you know what this is
And that I'm willing to use it.
Now it's my turn.
[groaning]
I say we let them waste each other.
Since when do we do what you say?
Wait.
Unh!
Ohh!
Oww!
Aah! Unh!
No!
No, please!
So small.
All of you.
And so meaningless.
Ohh!
There's nothing I want from you anymore.
None of you has anything to offer me now.
Where's he going?
Where gods belong.
Luthor: Oh, stop.
He's just a machine.
I don't care how much power he has.
He's no god.
Then why do I have a feeling
That if he ever comes back
You're going to be doing a lot of praying?
Perhaps we'll all be praying.
[telephone ringing]
Luthor: They're only giving me one phone call,
So listen carefully.
I need the best lawyers in the country.
I don't care what you have to pay for them.
And doctors. I need them, too.
Bring them in from Europe if you have to,
And... are you listening?
Hello? Hello!