Tie them up.
Make sure everything's secure.
A guard over at Prime Tech
Is reporting a robbery in progress.
Sounds like a friend of ours
Is back in business.
Shade.
How'd you... I keep forgetting.
Finished?
Uh! Ooh!
Uh!
I'll try upstairs.
I'm sensing him in the laboratory.
I'm close.
Tiny chip, big money.
[loud rumbling]
I've got him. I've got him.
Oh! Uh!
You should have held back.
I had him.
I'm not the mind reader, am I?
[sirens passing]
Need a ride, handsome?
Don't mind if I do.
The name's Giganta.
Appropriate.
It's not a problem for you, is it?
Quite the opposite.
My place would have been closer.
But my friends are here.
Friends?
Yah!
[bats screeching]
Yummy. Ah...
[burps]
Now I get it. You're trying to set up
another Injustice Gang, aren't you?
We call it a society...
A secret society.
Call it what you want. It won't work.
I know. I've tried...
Twice.
Voice: What's that old saying?
The third time's the charm.
That chip could have done
A lot of damage in the wrong hands.
Indeed. So we had to make sure
It stayed in the right ones.
It's lucky you were around.
We do what we can.
[reporters shouting questions]
We've got an appointment.
You'll have to excuse us.
I can't stand that hero-worship stuff.
But isn't that what we are?
Not tonight.
Not when two of us can't stop someone like Shade.
What's the problem?
Us. We're not working together as well as we could.
Come on. We're batting close to a thousand.
A lot of that has been luck.
We've taken some pretty bad hits along the way.
What are you suggesting?
Practice.
[groaning]
It's that or more of what happened to us tonight.
What do we really have to lose?
Time.
A little more teamwork wouldn't hurt any of us.
Looks like you're outvoted.
You gonna do it? You sure?
I told you I would.
You know what'll happen to you if you don't.
Just get on with it.
Yeah!
Your turn.
I don't think this is such a good idea.
Don't be such a girl.
But, I mean, I'm a little heavier than I look.
Trying to get them to trust each other, huh?
Not the easiest thing for loners,
Sociopaths, and psychos.
[crash]
Giganta: Ow.
Imagine the childhoods they must have had.
Imagine what's going to happen when someone makes them a better offer.
None of us is in this for the money.
Sinestro's sworn a blood oath against all Green Lanterns.
Parasite simply hates Superman.
Giganta is totally devoted to me.
What about the other one?
Killer Frost? She just likes to kill.
And me? I suppose you got that figured out, too.
You're a master criminal, Shade.
But you could be a master of the world.
I've tried. I'll settle for where I am now.
How are you going to feel in 10 years,
When you're still being chased
Around warehouses and rooftops,
Joints aching, lungs burning?
This is a chance to rid ourselves
Of the League once and for all,
To see how far we can go
When there's no one in our way.
The League's just so powerful.
How do you stop them?
By watching lots of television.
[bird screeches]
No!
Not bad.
It's not over yet.
So far, so good.
Hawkgirl: Behind you!
Don't! Wait!
Aah!
Ooh! Uh...
[groaning]
It was booby-trapped.
How was I supposed to--
Either of your partners could have told you.
One's psychic, and the other's got x-ray vision.
You're right. Good lesson. Can I go now?
Go? We're just getting started.
What country is this?
It's not a country.
One man owns the whole island--
Morgan Edge, collector.
Of what? Art? Jewels?
And other things.
He keeps it all in the main house.
Allow me.
This just gets better and better.
Aah!
Next time, look before you leap.
Frost.
Sinestro.
Time to let those destructive impulses loose.
Hey! That was my bad guy.
Happy?
Call me when it's important... And not before.
[screaming]
Huh?
I believe it's time for another cold snap, my dear.
Cool.
The water. Only the water.
Aw...
I'm just a chef here.
In alligator loafers?
Mr. Edge, he gives me his old shoes and--
Ah!
Aah!
Now, where are the canisters...
Mr. Edge?
Whatever's in those canisters
Better be good if we're passing up
All this other stuff.
Will you do the honors, my dear?
Hey, can't you see the label?
This stuff's dangerous.
That's exactly what I'm counting on.
Go ahead.
Mud?
Living mud.
Grodd: Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you the final member of our secret society...
Clayface.
[panting]
Impressive.
Thanks.
But did you really need to take all that abuse?
I could have used my mace on it,
If you'd given me a chance.
And it never would have been able to lay a glove on me.
When have I heard that before?
Hey!
They're making a good point.
You've got to trust your partners.
I do, but the fact is,
I'm the invulnerable one.
Every punch I take is a punch they don't have to.
Are you saying we can't cut it?
That's what it sounds like to me.
Now hold on. We're a team.
But we're not all equal.
You can't deny that--
Everybody, knock it off!
We're going to keep doing this till we get it right.
Should have used your heat vision.
But nothing appears to have been stolen from the island.
Police have called in a HAZMA-T team
To investigate 4 mysterious empty canisters found at the scene.
What kind of guy would lock somebody up
and keep him as if he was property?
Edge was sick, honey.
But you don't have to worry about him anymore.
Nobody has to.
I'm grateful to you. Don't get me wrong.
But I'm not really one of you.
See, all I want is to be normal again.
And give up all your power?
I can offer you the best of both worlds.
Yeah, right.
This is Giganta.
She was a lovely child,
Don't you think?
If I could do that for her,
Think what I can do for you.
[man and woman speaking spanish]
Uh... Ah!
[speaking spanish]
Aah!
Always trying to find a cure, aren't you?
Can you blame me?
No, but it's made you predictable.
This is the only company in the world that makes what you need.
Now, where's Shade?
Over there.
You didn't think I'd come here
Without reinforcements, did you?
Wish I'd thought of that.
Oh, wait. I did.
I'll take the big one.
I'll take her.
Aah!
John!
Come on!
Why didn't you let us finish them?
In a warehouse?
That's far too small a stage.
It was 7 to 6. We had the advantage.
Where'd you go? I was counting on you.
Lantern was hurt,
And I recall you saying
That you could take her.
So much for practice makes perfect.
I thought we were practicing teamwork,
Not one guys tells everybody else what to do.
Somebody has to be in charge,
And it couldn't very well be you.
You know, I'm getting really sick of--
Will you both shut up?
I've had better luck handling whole armies,
And you know why?
Because I didn't have to worry about anyone but myself.
Then why don't you go back to that?
You think I haven't considered it?
This whole stinking group was your idea,
And now you don't want to do it anymore?
You men. Unless you do it on your own,
It doesn't count.
It's not just the men, you stuck-up--
Stop it! Stop it right now!
I arrived here not knowing a soul,
and you took me in.
You became my new family.
But what's the use of a family
If it diminishes us as individuals?
Well... What are you...
I'm saying I survived the loss of one family,
And I'll survive this one, too.