[gunfire]
Almost there. What about you two?
Man: Oof!
Coming.
[gunfire]
I'll catch up in a minute.
Wait for me.
Uh! Uh!
Wonder Woman, over radio: Superman!
Can you hear me? Wait!
We've waited too long as it is.
They couldn't see the beauty. No imagination.
They'd rather fight.
Even this wasn't enough for you, was it?
You had to have it all.
Now we're on the brink of a war
That could destroy the whole planet.
Could have been so perfect. Paradise.
And I let it get this far because of the law...
And the will of the people.
Ha ha, the people? This is all their fault!
And they're going to burn for it.
Burn!
You're nothing but a mad dog now, aren't you?
Ooh! A threat!
But this old dog still has a few teeth.
There are at least 6 different ways I can stop you right now.
But they all involve deadly force, don't they?
And you don't do that.
No, you need me.
You wouldn't be much of a hero without a villain,
And you do love being the hero, don't you?
The cheering children, the swooning women.
You love it so much it's made you my most reliable accomplice.
Accomplice? What are you--
You could have crushed me anytime you wanted,
And it wasn't the law or the will of the people that stopped you.
It was your ego. Being a hero was too important to you.
You're as much responsible for this as I am.
So, go ahead, fix it somehow,
Put me on trial, lock me up, but I'll beat it.
And then we'll start the whole thing all over again.
I did love being a hero,
But if this is where it leads, I'm done with it.
[whirring]
Oh! Oof!
Unh!
Thanks.
Do you smell something?
Hera!
Well, it had to be done.
Are you ok?
I'm great.
Man: Sector 7-- all clear.
Second man: Sector 10-- alert terminated.
Woman: Sector 11-- all clear.
Sector 19-- all clear.
Third man: Sector 33-- all clear.
Fourth man: Sector 50-- all clear.
Sector 42-- report delayed.
Why the delay in sector 42?
A storm.
Is there anything we can do?
No, everyone's been evacuated.
Oh.
Let's continue, then.
Sector 30.
Man: All clear.
Second man: Sector 35-- all clear.
I'm sorry. We can't allow it right now.
You're just not ready.
But it's kind of a fall tradition, you know?
Like Halloween and football.
Folks aren't gonna be too happy.
They seem happy enough to me.
And an election isn't like football.
There's a lot more to lose.
True enough.
So when do you think might be a good time to have one?
Patience, Mr. President. Patience.
I keep expecting him to come zipping in any minute.
And then say something really stupid, right?
Well, there was that.
But when things got serious, so did he.
I miss him too, John.
Man: Sector 42-- all clear now.
Second man: Sector 31-- civil disturbance.
What's going on?
Just a small protest at the college.
We're there.
Not necessary.
The police are handling it.
It only takes one spark to start a fire.
All right, if you want to go so badly, be my guest.
And as long as you're down there,
Please try to get Batman out of that cave of his.
Even I find it depressing.
Deal.
You coming?
It is your hometown.
I've got a dinner date.
You're sure you don't want to help us out?
Batman: Too much to do.
Come on, for old times' sake.
Batman: I hate old times.
[police sirens]
Crowd, chanting: Elections now! Elections now!
[click]
[coughing]
Crowd, chanting: Elections now!
Crowd: Elections now!
Elections now! And cops off campus!
And cops off campus!
And cops off-- uh!
Hold it, hold it!
Let's get out of here.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Punks. Remember when everyone liked us?
Since when does that matter to you?
Since I started seeing the fear on everyone's face.
You want to talk about fear?
When I was a kid, I went to bed every night scared
That the whole world was gonna blow up.
That's the way things were back then.
And folks just accepted it.
They didn't think there could be a better way.
But we found one.
So, do you sleep better now?
You know I do.
[commotion]
[whack]
Ah! Oof!
Unh!
[grunting]
[ching, ching]
Cold.
It's gazpacho, it's supposed to be.
I wasn't talking about the soup.
You gonna tell me what's wrong?
After two years, you don't know?
Here we go.
The world's on permanent lockdown,
Free speech is all but dead,
And you don't know what's wrong?
Lois, we've been over this a thousand times.
Why can't you see the bigger picture?
I can see just fine, thank you.
You're the one who can't see where this is leading.
Lois, we're doing everything we can--
[beep]
Ah... Just a sec.
Yeah?
Go ahead-- finish.
You're doing everything you can to what?
Make sure everyone bows down to worship you,
Is that what you were going to say?
Superman: That's not what we want!
Can't you just listen for a second?
Ah, love.
Sorry to interrupt, but I need to see you and the others.
I'm busy.
Batman: Now!
I gotta go.
Lois: We're not done with this!
I know. Believe me, I know.
You can't just write me off like--
Like I'm some kind of hysterical--
Sorry, miss lane, but you know the rules.
No leaving the premises, no unauthorized guests, no phone calls.
Can't speak my mind, can't think.
It's only temporary, ma'am.
They gave us their word.
Sucker.
Green Lantern: What is this?
Some old video of us?
Except we never had a fight like this with Luthor.
Batman: You're right.
We never did.
But they're having one... Right now.
They?
We're looking at another dimension.
Live.
It's just like ours. Almost.
But their Flash is still alive.
So's their Luthor.
There's something else.
They don't call themselves the Justice Lords.
They're the Justice League.
It's sad.
Yeah. Their world's the mess ours used to be.
Too bad we can't help them.
Who says we can't?
You've been a busy little bat, haven't you?
What else is there to do around here anymore?
This can take us into that other dimension.
If we decide to use it.
Why wouldn't we?
You're talking about helping them.
But would they accept it?
Our kind of help.
Ugh!
Don't take your eyes off him, I said.
Not even for a second.
Hey, I had to go, ok?
And there's some things I just can't do
In the blink of an eye.
What is that?
Breakable, I hope.
Oh! Oh! Uh!
Ooh!
Watch. I'll be out in days.
Not with a broken leg, you won't.
Sorry I messed up back there.
Apology accepted...
As soon as the damage is fixed.
Got a sec?
Who-- who are you?
I'm you.
And the dimensions appear to be
Collapsing on each other.
Our Batman built this portal
To try to find help.
But what can we do?
We're not sure yet.
But my dimension seems to be at the center of it,
And that would be the best place
To start looking for an answer.
Have you read his mind yet?
Martians don't do that to one another.
Can't... or won't? - Both.
So it's agreed, then. We go?
Sure. Ok. Right.
Let's do it. I'm in.
J'onn? Batman?
Agreed.
Hey, don't you guys believe
In doors and windows?
I'm sorry.
[screams]
They'll thank us later.
Uh-oh.
[straining]
Ah!
Ah...
[groan]
[growls]
[sirens]
Man: And despite the best efforts
Of the special crimes unit,
So far, the creature has proved unstoppable.
The question everyone's asking is,
Where is the Justice League?
Hold on, Janet.
We're now getting unconfirmed reports
That the president is considering a unilat--
Look at that thing.
[growls]
You wanted excitement.
And when we stop it, they'll be so grateful,
They'll roll right over for us.
If we can stop it.
Argh!
[monster roaring]
[groan]
[grunt]
[train whistle]
Ugh!
Whoo!
So, Larry, how are the wife and kids?
Fine, Mr. Luthor.
And they love that big-screen TV.
They'll love their new S.U.V. Even more.
20 bucks on the ugly guy.
Watch out!
Uh!
What do you want?
Same as you, I imagine.
Power.
Control.
But I had to see the best this planet had to offer.
I am not impressed.
Aargh.
Man: Run for it!
[moan]
You think that can hurt me?
My skin can withstand a nuclear explosion.
My bones are-- my...
Bones...
Uh...
[sirens]
[police radio]
[groan]
Superman? That was incredible--
Superman! What happened?
What happened to that creature?
What happened?
Any comment?
You... Lobotomized him.
What's your question, Lois?
It's-- it's so out of character.
It's about time, if you ask me.
Yeah, right. Absolutely. Yeah.
And what's with the new costumes, guys?
We just felt it was time for a change.
What's next, for you?
Where's the Flash?
It's not them.