Previously on "Justice League..."
5 years ago, we secretly sent an advanced agent to Earth
To learn more about your people
And to study your defenses.
You mean she's a spy?
She was spying on us.
The greatest evil in the universe,
The Gordanians--
They are coming here.
This will be the fate of Earth
Unless you accept our help.
Hro and I are promised to each other.
It's like being engaged.
This generator-- when we're finished,
It's gonna be the size of a city.
It has to be.
It's got to sustain a force field
Strong enough to protect Earth from the Gordanians.
Diana, I was right.
The Gordanians are nowhere near Earth.
The thanagarians are--
Ugh!
-Unh! -Aah!
Activate force field projection... Now!
Unh!
Ooh!
Unh! Unh!
Don't fight us. We're trying to help you.
Whose side are you really on?
Unh!
I'm sorry, John.
[grunt]
All ICBM commands are reporting zero fire capability.
All triton subs inoperative, sir.
General Welles, France is reporting total failure of its ballistic systems.
China's ICBM are all nonresponsive, sir.
Russia reports the same.
All long and intermediate-range missiles are inoperative.
Patch me through to NATO command.
Gentlemen, we are faced with an unprecedented situation.
There has been a simultaneous catastrophic failure
Of defense systems around the world.
In the face of the thanagarian threat,
We need to form an offensive strategy
If we have any chance of--
[static]
Get that line back up!
Can't, sir. It's being jammed.
This is commander Hro Talak.
In the name of the thanagarian authority,
We claim your planet as a garrison
And have instituted martial law.
Your world faces a crisis from which only we can protect you.
But to be effective,
We must be free to act and move without interference.
Cooperate, and our stay will be brief
And without incident.
Stand against us,
And our wrath will be unforgiving.
[murmuring]
Commander, we ask that you release us immediately.
Ask? We demand it.
You have no right to keep us here.
You are the ones without rights.
Your militaries are useless.
Your Justice League is defeated.
Your only options are cooperation or death.
Choose wisely.
Now... You are free to go.
You've lived among them.
Do you think they'll cooperate?
I think they got the message,
But what about the Justice League?
What are you going to do with them?
For special guests,
I have made very special arrangements.
Traitor!
[grunts]
Look at them--
Weak...
Useless...
[Flash groans]
Broken.
It would have been difficult to storm their Watchtower
Without the access codes you provided.
Also, your analysis of their weaknesses
Was most helpful.
That one will be the least trouble of all.
He's nothing without his toy.
Don't underestimate them.
You're right.
Perhaps we should make sure they are not a threat.
Better still, perhaps you should.
The point of this occupation is to keep peace
While we finish our mission.
If we kill Earth's heroes, the natives will revolt.
Our best plan is to build the shield, then go.
Make sure they're well taken care of.
[beeping]
How am I supposed to feed myself
Tied up like this?
Not my problem.
It will be if Hawkgirl finds out you disobeyed her orders.
I know my duties.
Then I guess you'll have to feed me.
Don't be afraid, little man.
I won't bite.
Mind your tongue, woman.
I fear nothing.
Eat.
Aah!
Ohh!
Hyuh!
Aah!
Ptui!
Security breach in cell block 7.
Diana! The force field!
Free the others.
Unh!
Aah!
Hmm. I feel like I just ran a marathon on Jupiter.
You can rest later.
Hyah!
Ohh!
The lights.
Lean on me.
Unh!
Here. Try this.
Took you long enough.
Behind you!
We're losing altitude fast.
We need to go now!
Commander, there's been a security breach
Aboard the prison shuttle.
The Justice League has escaped.
How did it happen?
They're the Justice League, that's how it happened.
Take a strike squad back to the surface.
Search every house, every building,
Look under every rock.
Find them!
By your command.
Go!
Onward.
We've got to move, people.
Everyone inside.
Could you give me a hand with these?
Still not back to full strength.
Much better. Thanks.
Diana, cover our tracks.
That x-ray vision working yet?
Just enough to see hawksoldiers still patrolling the skies.
They'll have the whole city covered by now.
Who knows?
Maybe they'll get tired and go home.
Yeah, I know,
But a little optimism at a time like this couldn't hurt.
This is the voice of the thanagarian occupational authority.
Your so-called Justice League
Is in violation of our martial law.
They are to be considered an enemy
And dealt with on sight.
Any person found aiding or harboring them
Will be summarily punished.
Ok. So much for optimism.
For the time being, we're gonna have to go underground.
How exactly do we hide
When the entire planet is looking for us?
They're looking for the Justice League.
Without our costumes, we are merely ordinary citizens.
Hold on a second here.
What about the whole secret identity thing?
I mean, I trust you guys, but I'm not sure I'm ready to--
Wally west, Clark Kent...
Bruce Wayne.
Show-off.
Red hair. It suits you.
You think?
Change. Now.
-We need to split up.
They'll be looking for 6 of us, not pairs.
A rendezvous point?
We're about 30 miles from Gotham city.
We can regroup at my house there.
But try and keep a low profile.
30 miles through hawk-infested territory.
No problem.
The construction proceeds as scheduled.
We have added humans to the workforce.
Are they of any use?
They have no technical expertise to speak of,
But they can lift and carry as well as any animal.
We should complete the project by the target date.
Be aware that the Justice League has escaped.
Stand ready for an attack.
Let them come.
It would only be suicide.
Keep me informed of your progress.
And, Paran, let nothing delay you.
By your command.
Humans working as slaves?
Unfortunate but necessary.
We are on an unforgiving schedule,
And if we're going to finish the hyperspace bypass in time...
Bypass?
I thought we were building a force shield.
That was merely the cover story.
So when were you going to tell me your real plans?
Or didn't you think you could trust me?
Come.
For decades, the Gordanian homeworld
has been protected behind an impregnable defensive line,
But this chain of hyperspace bypasses
will allow our armadas to jump behind their defenses
and make a direct assault on the heart of their empire.
Earth is the last link in that chain.
Once the chain is completed,
We can attack and wipe out the Gordanian threat forever.
But if we open a hole in hyperspace,
it will destroy this entire planet.
Sadly, yes.
For Thanagar to live, Earth must die.
Lieutenant Kragger, we may have found something.
Maintain your position.
We found these,
And the lock on that door was broken.
They were here.
The Justice League has tried
To pass themselves off as civilians.
Search door to door. Question everyone.
Do not let them slip away.
We are here to serve the people of Earth.
We serve the people by making certain
That you do what is in your best interest.
What is in your best interest is to do as we say.
Only by obeying us can we serve you.
Your identification.
Oh!
Hey, leave her alone!
Unh!
Diana, no.
You would stand here and do nothing?
We can't risk a confrontation here.
Hey, birdheads,
Go back to where you came from!
Get off our planet!
Oh!
Unh!
Over there! It's the Justice League!
So much for blending in.
In here.
Please. Hurry.
We can't stay here.
If they find you helping us...
Here. Sit here.
We're looking for a dark-haired man and woman.
If, perhaps, you could be more specific...
Has anyone entered here recently?
No.
What about those two?
Ah, the lovebirds.
Been here for hours.
Let's move on.
Sorry.
Don't be.
I can't believe bats is really Bruce Wayne.
You'd think a billionaire playboy
Could crack a smile every once in a while.
I can't believe how easily they've taken over.
Look, G.L.
Hawkgirl fooled us all.
You-- you can't blame yourself for what's happened.
I don't.
I blame her for what's happened to Earth.
I only blame myself for ever caring about her.
Be prepared to show identification
Or be detained.
I think we wanted the non-hawkpeople line.
If we run, they'll see us.
Well, staying here is no good, either.
If you've got any ideas, I'm open.
Uh-oh. Trouble.
Too many civilians.
If we try to help them, someone could get hurt.
Keep moving.
Have your identification ready.
What are we gonna do?
Excuse me!
Clark Kent of "The Daily Planet."
We understand the thanagarians are doing construction
At a restricted location in the Gobi desert.
Can you confirm this?
Get that contraption away!
And just exactly how long
Do you plan on enforcing martial law?
No more questions.
Go away immediately!
Can I quote you?
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I have never seen anyone stare at nothing so intently.
I know this must be difficult for you.
Do you?
What is obligation can sometimes feel like betrayal,
But our only true obligation is to Thanagar.
There must be another way.
Can't you reroute the bypass
Through some uninhabited planet or moon?
-Any alteration would set us back more than 5 years,
And every moment we delay is equaled in the blood of our people.
That still doesn't give us the right!
There are billions of lives down there!
We are at war.
Have you forgotten why we fight?
Or what horrors the Gordanians are capable of?
Have you forgotten my long years rotting
In their stinking prison camps?
I haven't!
I have forgotten nothing,
But this war is no excuse to--
I am your commander!
You will not question me!
I don't even know you anymore.
Ahem.
What is it?
We've lost track of the Justice League.
They've blended with the populace.
It will be difficult to find them,
Unless, of course,
You know where they are.
You're a long way from home.
If you ever want to see it again, then I suggest you tread lightly.
[gasp]
Ohh.
She never really answered the question, did she?
[doorbell rings]
Uh, we're looking for Bruce Wayne.
We're friends.
Of course. Master Bruce is expecting you.
This way, please.
So, jeeves, do you come with the place,
Or does master Bruce rent you just for parties?
I've been in service here since the master was in diapers.
Now, there's a picture.
Your guests have arrived, sir.
You're late.
Nice to see you, too.
Hey! That's a giant dinosaur.
And I thought Batman was the detective.
We were just speculating
Why the thanagarians are really here.
Obviously not to protect us.
But if the Gordanians aren't actually anywhere near Earth,
Why do they need to build that force field?
If it is a force field.
Then what is it?
I can tell you.
You've got a lot of nerve, showing up here.
We should thank you.
It saves us having to hunt you down.
I didn't come to fight.
I came to help.
Hawkpeople all over the planet,
Martial law,
Us getting chased like dogs--
I don't think we can take much more of your help.
The situation is worse than you think.
They are building a hyperspace bypass.
When it's activated, it'll destroy the planet
And everything on it.
Here. This has all the information on the project.
Believe me.
I didn't know the magnitude of Talak's plans.
We'll check it out.
There's the door.
Aren't you going to turn your back on me, too?
Last time I let my guard down, you sucker-punched me.
It wasn't personal.
Keep telling yourself that.
I did what I thought was right then,
And that's what I'm doing now.
We're triangulating her position
From the tracking device you planted on her.
I have a fix on the location.
Ready the strike squad.
This time, they will not escape.