[thunder]
[grunting and moaning]
The world's greatest heroes.
[thunder]
And I thought I'd actually have to break a sweat.
Superman: I'll be doing the breaking.
Yes, indeed.
You break very nicely.
Ha ha ha!
Well done!
Extraordinary!
Congratulations.
You've done what even I couldn't do, Mr...
Dee. John Dee.
Ew. We'll have to do better than that.
Let's see.
Dee. Dee.
Destructor?
Demolisher!
Time for that later.
First Mr. Dee has to tell us
Exactly how this thing works.
Dee: The materiopticon?
Sorry. It's a trade secret.
That all right.
Grundy like you anyway.
You one of us now.
Easy. Easy.
Easy.
Huh?
Your turn in the barrel.
What's so easy, John?
You were talking in your sleep.
I was just dreaming about my parole.
I think it's really gonna happen this time.
I wouldn't bet against it.
You're not like the other guys here.
You got a future.
Yeah, I got a real date with destiny.
Captioning made possible by Warner bros.
3, 2, 1.
And stop.
That's it?
I don't feel any different.
You're not supposed to.
Just let your mind go blank,
And tell me what comes into it
When I look at these cards.
Uh... A car maybe.
A tree.
A cow.
A house.
Sheez. So it's true.
This thing really can give people E.S.P.
Only for a little while,
And I'm still charting the side effects.
But think of the potential.
I'd sure like to keep working with you on this.
Even after they let me out.
See what this baby can really do.
What it could do is fry your brain.
Hey, sometimes you have to take a chance.
You know, for science.
I appreciate your zeal, but...
[knock on door]
John, your parole report's in.
It's just a little setback, that's all.
You said that last time and the time before.
Listen, I'm working on something new.
It's gonna change everything.
You've said that before, too.
Baby, this time it's going to happen, I swear.
John, I found someone else.
You can't do this. I'm so close.
You can't do this to me!
Where's that happy face today, Dee?
Shut up.
Ooh.
[alarm]
Sounds like somebody's getting out of here today.
[shouting]
You ok, doc?
What are you doing here?
I was worried about you.
Sometimes they take hostages.
Better lock up.
Right. Right.
Oof!
[groaning]
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Stop that.
It's ok. I don't think he's home right now.
What's he working on, anyway?
I don't know, but it's probably important,
So leave him alone.
But aren't you even...
Batman: Forget him.
Get over here.
Crankier than usual.
So?
Prison break.
Grundy. Copperhead.
Luminous. Volcana and Firefly.
Say no more.
I wasn't intending to.
What about J’onn?
I'm ready.
So what were you working on?
Nothing. I was taking a nap.
Something's blocking it.
Dr. Brooks? You in there?
[grunting]
Dr. Brooks!
Bill!
Ohh...
Warden.
John. John?
[mumbling]
Get him to the infirmary. Hurry.
Yes, sir.
[police radio chatter]
Volcana, Firefly, you're completely surrounded.
There's no way out.
How many times have I heard that in my life?
Almost ready?
Oh, yeah.
That's your flamethrower?
Wait till you see how I use it.
That's all right, honey.
I think I'm in love.
I got your back.
Good. Now I can really concentrate.
[grunting]
Oof!
Ugh!
Huh! Oh!
Are you good for anything?
You think this can hold me?
Knock yourself out.
[gasping]
What's happening?
Fire needs air.
And you just burned up all of yours.
Man: Two down, 3 to go.
[yawn]
Pretty routine stuff for you, isn't it?
Sorry. Third night in a row with no sleep.
Maybe you should...
Man on telephone: Warden, Dee’s gone.
What are you talking about?
He's catatonic!
How could he be gone?
You better come to the infirmary.
An E.S.P. Machine?
Kind of a dangerous thing to have in a prison, isn't it?
Where else are you gonna find volunteers?
[groaning]
[mumbling gibberish]
[gasp]
Mmm...
It's probably too late,
But you should have someone check the laundry room.
But... but what happened to everybody?
Some kind of poisoning?
[beep]
Yeah?
We've got the other 3 pinned down
At the old west side refinery.
We'll be right there.
I'm staying.
What for?
You don't know if Dee did this.
I don't know that he didn't.
Look, whatever he is,
He sure isn't in the same league
As Grundy and the others.
He's a nobody.
Ever read the odyssey?
After Odysseus was caught by the cyclops,
He told that his name was nobody,
So when he poked its eye out
And its friends asked who did it,
All the cyclops could say was "nobody. "
Point taken.
What do you know about John Dee?
I'll get his file for you.
I might be able to help.
[gasp]
[sigh]
Trouble sleeping?
[gasp]
[glass shatters]
Maybe it's your conscience.
Oh, I forgot. You don't have one.
How'd you get in here?
I can go anywhere I want now.
Rick! Rick!
Get up! Get up!
Sound sleeper, huh?
What did you do to him?
Nothing.
But there isn't much he can do for you.
Not even the Justice League can save you now.
John, please...
You know, I never liked that name.
It's so... Ordinary.
Especially for someone who has such big things in store.
You know, a destiny.
Oh. Destiny. I like it.
Dr. Destiny.
What do you think?
You're crazy!
I think you're finally seeing the real me.
[gasp]
And now that I'm a doctor,
I think I'll perform some surgery.
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Aah!
What? What?
Hey, you're just having a nightmare, that's all!
Aah! Aah!
Penny, it's only a dream. Wake up.
Aah!
[screaming continues]
Luminous!
Hold it!
Hold what? This?
Huh!
Ha!
Unh!
Huh! Huh!
[grunting]
[panting]
I heard you knocking.
It was Luminous.
Don't feel too bad about it.
He's fooled others a lot worse.
Hey, you ok?
Fine.
This way.
Grundy say this way.
But...
Man: Hold it right there, Grundy!
This is as far as you go!
[roar]
Are you crazy?
No. Mad.
I'm so dead.
[grunting]
Whoa!
[roar]
[grundy roars]
You can't leave now.
You haven't seen the ending.
This is supposed to scare me?
They're just illusions.
Unh! Unh! Unh!
[grunting]
They do pack a wallop, though.
I can make light solid, chump.
[Flash grunting]
We just need to take out the real one.
But which one is it?
That one.
Lights out.
[roar]
You're flying me out of here now, lady.
[grunting]
Well, get me out of here.
And what if I don't?
I'll give you your last kiss.
And you fall 40 stories.
Didn't really think this through, did you?
[roar]
He's as strong as we are,
But there's one thing he can't do.
He'll live. You won't.
I'm not scared.
Then maybe this'll help.
You do anything to her,
And you won't even make it to the ground.
Oh!
Good bluff.
Who was bluffing?
So who's left?
No one. There were only 5, remember?
Oh, yeah. Right.
Just testing.
Let's call it a night.
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
[screaming continues]
[whimpering]
I got here as soon as I could.
Do your thing.
[yawning]
You look beat.
Come on. Time to hit the sack.
Uh, I mean. You know, I'll...
I'll take first watch.
No. I'm good.
But I could use some caffeine.
Hey, no prob.
One triple mocha frappe coming right up.
That'll be $7.50, pl...
Oh!
J'onn?
He calls himself Dr. Destiny now.
He came into her dreams,
Did this to her.
Why can't she wake up?
It's a delusional state.
I'm going back in to see if I can bring her out of it.
He wants us, too.
Us?
Why?
I never even heard of him before today.
Ha ha ha.
[laughing continues]
Captioning made possible by Warner bros.
Captioned by the national captioning institute... www. Ncicap. Org...