Hah!
Aah! Unh!
[grunting]
Aah!
Oof!
I don't need any help.
You're welcome.
Aah!
Unh!
Yaa!
Aah!
[screaming]
Come on!
He can wait.
Woman: Then fire them.
In fact, get rid of the whole division.
I don't care what Luthor would have done.
I'm in charge now,
And if you can't accept that, I'll...
Mercy.
[groaning]
Help me.
I'm... I'm...
Sick?
Dying?
And you couldn't do it somewhere else?
After all I've done for you.
You mean letting me, a lowly chauffeur,
Run your company while you were away?
Oh, was I flattered.
But then I realized
There was no one else
You could trust to give it back...
Only me, your loyal dog.
Well, let me tell you something.
This dog took LexCorp out of the hole you dug
And brought up the stock 38%
All on her own.
So if you think I'm ever gonna let you...
Unh!
[gasping]
Looks like there's some life
In the old suit after all.
Now where's professor Ivo?
[gasping]
I... I fired him.
You what?
He was one of our best scientists.
How could you do that?
Well?
I... I was trying to save money.
He's probably at his place in mountain view.
Unh!
Good girl.
[breathing heavily]
[screaming]
Superman: G.L.'s already patrolling the city,
And Hawkgirl will join him
As soon as we're done here.
Batman and I are going to follow up some leads,
But I just don't know if it'll be enough.
So... A psychic sweep.
Of the whole city.
Is it possible?
I've never tried anything like that before.
Once the gate is opened,
It might not be so easy to close.
I realize it's a lot to ask,
But Luthor...
I know.
He must be stopped.
Smart guy.
Ivo, it's Luthor.
You've got to help me.
Will you get up? I'm d...
[gasp]
Looks like the cigarettes finally got you...
And maybe me, too.
[gasp]
Well, what are you waiting for?
It's not like I won't be dead soon enough, anyway.
Woman, thinking: I want him to love me...
But I don't think he even likes me.
Man: I wish she'd wear some vinyl.
Different woman: I smell bad. I just know it.
20 showers a day. I still can't get rid of it.
Man: Bald? How could anyone say I'm bald?
I just have a high forehead.
Different man: I should ask her out,
But what would she want with me?
But I should try, though.
Woman: Rotten kids.
They don't appreciate me.
Man: I just need a roof over my head.
That's all...
And a drink. Yeah.
Woman: It's funny.
[all talking at once]
[voices stop]
[breathing heavily]
[all talking at once]
Man: I'll sue the pants off him!
Woman: I'll take him for everything he's got!
Man: She thinks she's so special.
Woman: What do I have to tell anyone?
Man: Looks like a gorilla.
[all talking at once]
[groaning]
Aargh!
A little help here.
When will professor come back?
Never.
He has to.
You miss him.
So do I.
He was one of my best friends.
He was?
Almost like a brother,
And he would have wanted me to look after you
If anything ever happened to him.
So... You're going to take care of me now?
Mm-hmm.
But you're going to have to take care of me, too.
Otherwise, I'll go to sleep
And never wake up again.
Thank you.
Now, there's one other thing I need...
Fuel.
[buzzer]
Stay back, freak.
Aah!
Ohh!
Whoa! Whoa!
Hold it, big boy.
Yah!
Now, what did you want this for?
Hah!
Didn't figure on that one, did you?
Aah! Unh!
Mmm.
Aah!
[door opens]
[door closes]
Well, it looks like Ivo was right on the money.
His duplication program seems to be working rather well.
I assume you ran into Hawkgirl?
Girl with wings. Yes.
And seeing that you were able
To get away with this,
I take it she didn't fare too well.
Is she still alive?
Yes.
Aww.
What's wrong?
Let me tell you a story.
It's about a young man
Whose dream was to build a great empire.
He succeeded.
Then he lost it all
Because of 7 very bad people...
Hawkgirl and her friends...
The Justice League.
That young man was me, of course,
And now I have another dream.
It's to take back control of that empire.
And then, when the time comes,
I want to hand it down to someone who will continue my work...
The son I never had.
But none of that can happen
Until you give the Justice League what they deserve.
Mercy: He's the most deeply twisted man
I've ever met.
Of course I'll help you.
Good. If he contacts you,
Let us know.
You have my word.
He hasn't already contacted you, has he?
Don't you think I would have told you?
The two of you were very... Close.
I'm a different person now.
Right.
She was a little too cooperative, wasn't she?
You're learning.
I wouldn't mind hearing what she's really thinking.
[all talking at once]
Superman on radio: J'onn? Any luck yet?
No.
Where are you?
I can't talk now.
Are you all right?
Leave me alone!
Grr!
It was some kind of android.
It had wings built into it
And a mace, too.
Scary, huh?
Sounds like whoever made it had you in mind.
Yeah. It even acted like me.
Now, that's scary.
The android...
It's about 10 feet tall, gray skin?
How'd you know?
Unh!
Aah!
Ohh!
[sirens]
Aah!
You forgot to mention he's as strong as I am.
Hawkgirl: He wasn't like that before.
Aah! Aah!
Unh!
Ooh!
Unh! Unh!
Aah!
Unh!
[groans]
Hah!
Didn't figure on that one, did you?
Unh!
[telephone ringing]
Ohh!
Ohh...
[grunting]
Another business call?
She fired Ivo months ago,
And he's an M.D.,
something Luthor should be needing right about now.
One more thing...
Ivo's specialty is nanotechnology.
Green Lantern: Batman, it's Lantern.
We've found Hawkgirl's robot.
Where are you?
Don't even think about it.
Somehow this thing's copying all our powers
Just by looking at us.
We can't just stay here.
That's exactly what you're gonna do.
You come here,
And all you'll do is make him even stronger.
Aah!
Lantern!
Unh!
Hera help us!
She'd better.
No one else can now.