Announcer: Previously on Justice League...
[commotion]
Oh! Unh!
No!
[buzzing]
Aah!
Unh! Oof!
Martian Manhunter: We need to consider replenishing our forces.
Flash: A new member? Who?
Rah!
[thud]
[boom]
When you've got Lobo on your team, who needs Superman?
Oh...
Unh...
Oh!
Ugh...
Hello?
Anyone here?
[beep beep] Superman to Justice League.
Looks like we've somehow been transported to a planet with a red sun.
My powers aren't working.
I'm picking up your homing beacon, but I'm not getting audio.
I'll leave this channel open and attempt to move closer to your position.
Unh.
[gas flowing]
[engine revving]
[growling]
[clang] ha!
Ha!
Unh!
[clang clang]
Ugh!
[engine revs]
[tires squeal]
[thunder]
[engine sputtering]
Should've taken the compact.
[growling]
Down!
[barking]
Stay!
Unh!
Oof!
[grunting]
[barking]
Just you and me, huh?
Guess this is where we find out who's top dog.
Yah!
Hyah!
[whining]
[growling]
[beep beep]
If I'm interpreting this thing right,
We're very close to each other.
I'm bunking in for the night and heading out again at dawn.
Maybe we'll see each other tomorrow.
Whoa!
[beep beep]
End of the line, guys.
[whimpering]
Get! Go on!
Oof!
[beep beep]
[growling]
[panting]
No!
Computer: Commlink--02. Recognized.
Authorized user: Superman.
Access granted.
Hello! Is anybody in here?
Hello!
Computer: Warning! Watchtower now running on reserve power.
System sleep in 30 seconds.
Override.
Unh!
What happened to everybody?
Man: They died, Superman.
Thousands of years ago.
They don't build them like this anymore.
What?
It didn't lose orbit until only 75 years ago.
Remarkable feat of engineering.
What happened here?
I think you've already guessed.
This is Earth.
Yes.
Thousands of years in your future.
That simpleton Toyman never truly understood what he had created.
The disintegrator beam he hit me with...
An energized tacchian stream.
That's what sent you into the future.
Hello.
How'd you get here?
The old-fashioned way.
I'm immortal.
I'm the sole remaining survivor of the human race.
All the people? Gone.
The Earth belongs to the cockroaches now.
Oh, and me.
I picked up your comm signal a few weeks ago.
I used it to track you down.
You could have just called!
I was afraid you might be holding a grudge.
If you'd switched off, I might never have found you.
Grudge?
You tried to take over the world...Twice.
In the long run, not so important.
Take it from someone who knows.
You're insane.
True. But that doesn't mean I'm not good company.
Say, you want to come over to my house?
Like you've got something better to do.
Before we go inside, I want you to see this.
This is Metropolis.
Was. I restored it myself.
Archaeology is one of my hobbies.
Your funeral was lovely.
It was on all the networks.
I used to have the DVD.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
As a matter of fact, I did.
But I've had 30,000 years to reconsider.
It took you that long to figure out that you're a power-mad despot?
It took me that long to figure out that my lust
For power and control was meaningless.
I don't know what kind of con
You're trying to run on me,
But you're wasting your time.
I should never have done it.
Done what?
This.
I destroyed the world.
It was only a few months after you disappeared.
I had just perfected an invention
That gave me total control over gravity.
I proclaimed myself master of the world.
The Justice League would never have allowed that.
True. They put up quite a fight.
Green Lantern was the most difficult.
I killed him right here.
No... It was over there.
In any case, I destroyed the entire Justice League that day.
But that wasn't all.
My newfound powers disrupted
The gravitational balance of the entire solar system.
This is the result.
Ugh!
Oh!
Ha!
I should smash your skull.
Go ahead. We both know it wouldn't work.
Aaugh!
What now?
Lunch.
Sorry about the mess. I tried to tidy up a bit.
Superman: You did all this?
Savage: Every bit. I've had a long time to tinker.
You have to keep busy, or you'll go mad.
Self-help books. You don't seem the type.
I read whatever I can find.
Anyway, I've got issues.
What with my destroying the Earth and all.
Hope you're hungry.
Like it?
I grew all the food myself.
House, garden view.
Some garden.
I spent quite a lot of time
Rediscovering the principles of agriculture.
Something to do.
Like the rocket ship, I suppose.
Star ship.
I'd intended to leave the Earth
And search the universe for other life,
But I never did.
Too difficult?
Not at all. I decided I deserved to be punished.
Savage!
Savage, wake up!
What? What is it?
You've got a time machine!
I spent several decades working on it.
Then I lost interest.
Why didn't you finish it?
No attention span, I suppose.
No point, either.
There is a point. Don't you see?
You could go back and stop yourself
From destroying the world.
No, I couldn't
This design doesn't allow me to travel
Back to any time where I already exist.
Yeah, but I'm already dead.
On your feet, Mr. Wizard. We've got work to do.
It's not working.
It's working perfectly.
We just don't have sufficient power to keep it open.
You told me this place was powered by its own hydroelectric dam.
10 dams wouldn't be enough
To open a time warp for more than a few seconds.
I take you've got something in mind.
About 30 years ago some of the roach creatures
Broke in and stole my zero point generator.
It's the only power source in the world
Capable of running my time machine.
Can't you just build another one?
I'm working on it. I'll be finished in another 50 years.
Care to wait?
Superman: What do the roaches want with a power cell?
For all intents and purposes it's a miniature sun.
They use it to provide warmth to their central mound.
We go on foot from here.
This is gonna be fun.
Trust me, it isn't.
Ah!
[roaring]
[footsteps]
So much for stealth. They know we're here.
Haa!
Aah!
Go! Go!
Look out!
Aah!
Superman! Aah!
[triumphant music]
You know, I suspected the radiation
From the device might restore your powers.
But I didn't want to needlessly raise your hopes...
Or mine.
You're ready to send me back?
No. But I will, anyway.
You have to stop me by any means necessary.
I promise.
4 days from your arrival,
My younger self will steal a piece of dwarf star matter
From a scientist named Ray Palmer.
If you prevent that theft,
I'll never be able to build my weapon.
Ray Palmer. Got it.
What happens to you?
Redemption, if I'm lucky. Don't worry about me.
Return to your friends. Do what you do best...
What you were born to do:
Save the world.
Say it. Say it.
Uncle.
I can't hear you.
He's beaten. Put the car down.
I was gonna.
Pretty good, huh?
When you got Lobo on your team,
Who needs Superman?
Bang. You're dead.
Aah!
Superman!
You're alive!
Are you ok? I don't believe it.
I'm fine. Very glad to be home.
Flash?
[sniffling]
Something in my eyes.
Yeah. Tears.
It's ok, man. We all feel the same way.
Superman, how can you be...
Alive?
Toyman sent me to the future.
Then Vandal Savage and I
Fought some giant cockroaches and...
It's complicated.
I love the beard. Keeping it?
Not a chance.
You were greatly missed, my friend,
By all of us.
Don't let him fool you.
Your death hit him as hard as it did any of us.
Really?
No. I never believed you were dead in the first place.
I guess that's sort of a compliment.
Ain't this great?
The whole team together again. All 8 of us.
Count again. You're fired.
What?
You're not Justice League material, Lobo.
Go chase a bail jumper.
I don't care what you do, just clear out.
This is the thanks I get? What a stinkin' rip.
Next time you lollipops need help,
Don't bother askin' the main man!
We didn't ask you this time!
Guess you'll want to get cleaned up
And find a new set of clothes.
Not yet. We've got a job to do.
Come on, I'll explain on the way.
Thank you, my friend.