What's bomb squad doing in there?
We can't have much time left.
- Well? - Can't ID The green stuff.
But the wiring's the real deal.
They're definitely rigged to blow.
And the word game?
'That kind of thing wasn't exactly covered'
'in basic training.'
'Yin, get everyone out of there already!'
Right away, chief. I'm right behind you.
You know we can't let them see us together.
If they do, just tell them I'm your prisoner.
"When you do not know what I am, then I am something
"but when you know what I am, then I am nothing.
'What am I?"'
We'll be nothing if we don't leave right now.
I am a riddle.
Okay.
No one needs to see us run out of here together
and I get to keep my badge.
'Bravo!'
Uh, someone is very bright.
Step into the light..
So The Riddler can see you.
♪ The Batman ♪
Uh, someone is very bright.
Step into the light..
So The Riddler can see you.
I was expecting my worthy opponent
to be... taller.
Introduce yourself.
Yin. Detective Ellen Yin.
Where's the boom?
'Hello, Gotham PD!'
'I am The Riddler'
'and Detective Yin here has just proven herself'
'qualified to play.'
Play? Play what?
A battle of wits, a duel of intellects
a night of riddles scattered throughout Gotham
'for you to solve'
and you alone.
'Hear that, chief?'
'You'll never know when I'll be watching'
'or listening.'
'And if I hear anyone help with answers'
or see police uniforms anywhere near Detective Yin.
'Gotham loses big time!'
What's your deal, Riddler?
Why are you doing this?
Uh-uh.
I'm the one posing the riddles here
and I have another just for you.
Ready to play?
To cross the water, I'm the way.
For water, I'm above.
I touch it not, and truth to say
I neither swim nor move.
Swim nor.. Uh, I hate riddles!
And I don't play games with madmen!
Follow her!
Screech.
Gotham Bridge. A two-year-old could've figured that one out.
You know, we can't let Riddler see us together, either.
Or hear us. Riddler may have hacked the police frequency.
'But he can't crack Batwave.'
Two heads are better than.. Huh?
My keen detective skills tell me this is..
Ah, you made it, detective.
'Pity about your hard drive over here'
'but the bridge is set to blow'
'and only you can prevent it.'
Good luck.
What? Riddler, where's the riddle?
'The screen. The riddle's a puzzle.'
'Try the center square.'
Top row, center.
'Steady, all part of the game.'
beep 'Well, well, detective.'
You're quite the gamesmith.
Just keep playing by my rules.
What's this?
Yin, what are you doing?
I don't see any explosives here.
Under the bridge.
Uh-uh. I said, no help, chief.
Time to learn a lesson about following rules.
'Detective Yin still gets a chance'
'to solve the puzzle'
'but if you don't get far away from here tout de suite'
'I will blow Gotham Bay Bridge by remote'
'and everyone on it.'
'Bottom right corner.'
crash.
'Column four, row three.'
- 'Column one, row... ' - I got it. I got it!
'Well done, Yinsy.'
The bridge survives
but will you?
And only you can answer that riddle.
Thud.
Nice save.
Detective, what a surprise!
You must have a guardian angel
watching over you.
Ready for your next riddle?
No! No more riddles!
What do you want, you maniac?
'I prefer brainiac.'
As you've been learning knowledge is power.
Thud.
'Your other left.'
'"The key to this puzzle you will find'
'at last from riddles past."'
From riddles past?
'A piano has 88 keys.'
"Everything in me..
Everything in me is ancient?"
These riddles hurt my brain!
Chief, we located Yin heading for the museum.
"Everything in me is ancient?"
Ah, how did she get museum out of that?
Hm. Neanderthal exhibit.
'You're getting warm, detective'
'yet you're ice cold.'
'But if you don't solve the next riddle soon'
'the entire city block will be blown back to the ice age.'
You better hope I don't solve it, Riddler
because I'm going to find you
and I'm going to bring you down.
You couldn't be further from the truth, detective.
Oh, now, you're boring me.
On to the final riddle.
'A man builds a house'
'with all four sides facing North.'
A bear walks past the house.
What color is the bear?
Facing North?
'What color is the bear?'
Knowledge is power.
Pity about your hard drive over here.
You're ice cold.
You couldn't be further from the truth, detective.
Oh, now, you're boring me.
Boring.
Like a drill.
Riddler can't resist leaving riddles
even ones he shouldn't be.
Four sides facing North.
Ah, the house is at the South Pole
so it's a polar bear. The answer is white!
Taking a risk, aren't you?
There are no bears at the South Pole.
This riddle has no answer.
- Riddler cheated? - Riddler quit.
He's through playing.
Dessert gelatin?
Riddler's been leading us away from the main course
further from the truth, all night long.
Which is?
Beneath the last place we'd think to look..
Again.
Almost done?
Just a few more gigabytes, Riddler sir.
Then drain the brain.
'Freeze, Riddler!'
Knowledge is power, huh?
A fitting heist for a brainiac
don't you think, Yinsy?
If I need money boom, instant access
to Gotham's bank account numbers.
If I want to shut down Gotham's transportation grid
boom, instant access to the technical specs.
Information!
It's all here in the city's mainframe
soon to be uploaded into mine!
But aren't you the smart detective
to see the riddles within my riddles?
We can trade IQ scores
when you're behind bars, Riddler.
Would that be your IQ or The Batman's?
- I don't know what you're tal... - Please!
Do you think I went to all the trouble
to distract Gotham PD from my real crime?
It was The Batman who concerned me.
Isn't that right, Batman?
The game ends now, Riddler.
I'll say, for the two of you.
Gotham's infamous vigilante
working hand-in-hand with a cop?
Scandalous.
Tell me, Batman..
What question can you never answer yes to?
Are you asleep?
Ah, look who decided to join the party.
Welcome to my lair, Batman
where questions are answers
and Yin is yang.
Cute, Riddler. Where are we?
Why, the same place you've been all night long, Yinsy..
Inside my brain.
Stop speaking in riddles. Why are we here?
There is a living riddle walking amongst Gotham
that everyone wants answered.
Who is The Batman?
You want to know, don't you, Yinsy?
Too easy.
Instead, we'll play a game.
Oh, you're gonna love playing shuffleboard
in Arkham, Riddler!
Shh..
The game is 20 questions twenty yes or no's
from which my brilliant mind
will deduce the true identity of The Batman.
'Now, see the lie detector?'
Answer falsely, Batman, and Yinsy here
'gets more than just the shock of learning your identity.'
Don't tell him anything, Batman!
Question number one.
Do you have blond hair?
He has pink hair. He's from the moon.
Blond, yes or no?
Yes.
'Consider that a sample.'
With every false answer, the voltage spikes.
Question two, Bat-brunet.
Were you born here in Gotham City?
- 'Yes.' - 'That's the spirit.'
The riddles ended.
Yin vanished in thin air
and the museum's caked in lime jelly?
'Chief Rojas, the entire City Hall database'
'was stolen earlier tonight.'
But we were there! Is this a joke?
So you do have a day job.
I'm beginning to get a sense of the real you, Batman.
Are you a policeman?
Riddler, enough already!
You wanna know who The Batman is? Ask me!
- You don't know. - I do know. He's...
No! No, no, no, you'll ruin my game!
The true identity of The Batman is Ethan Bennett.
Duh, I can't hear you!
Riddler, the answer to am I a policeman..
Yes.
No one outsmarts The Riddler!
We are in Riddler's brain.
His men must be uploading the stolen data.
You find them, I'll take Riddler.
Drive 09, begin upload.
'Sorry, fellas.'
You have a virus.
Since I can't have Riddler, you'll do.
Riddle for you.
Who's next?
'Are you a singer? Are you a celebrity?'
Are you wealthy? Are you wise?
Huh?
What's black and blue and green all over?
Game's not yours yet, Batman.
Hm, and here I thought
this was going to be a battle of wits.
Pretty swift, Yin.
Maybe one day you'll put that big brain of yours
onto the whole "Who-is-The-Batman thing."
Uh, chief, you may be interested to know
someone on your payroll works hand-in-hand
with The Batman.
Oh, yeah? Who?
Ask not who in your force
works with The Bat ask why in.
Yin, answer it.
Why in, chief, why in.
My name, Yin.
Riddler says it's me.
Get this lunatic out of here!
Huh?
How would he know?
- 'That crazy psychopath!' - Whoo.
The Batman wasn't anywhere in sight tonight!
Nowhere in sight.
♪ The Batman ♪