'Hello, kitty.'
The only known animation cel in existence
from 1923's "Kitty-Cat Follies."
Cute, cuddly, and priceless.
Hiss.
Did someone say cute and cuddly?
- Who are you? - I'm Ragdoll.
♪ The Batman ♪
You, my minx, are a doll.
Might we have this little frivolity in common?
It's fate. It's destiny.
It's feline, so it's mine.
Now, crawl back to your toy box, floppy.
Skipped charm school, did we, precious?
- Gotcha. - Whoa.
Hm, the price tag on this pup
might make a cat person of me yet.
'After tonight..'
I guarantee you won't be a bat person.
The Batman.
Competition, eh?
Oh! My arm!
Neat, huh?
Screech.
'Toodles.'
'I lost my precious animation cel'
'to that triple-jointed contortionist.'
meow.
If Ragdoll ever plays in my sandbox again
I'll claw the stuffing out of him.
Meow meow meow.
Okay, come on, Selina.
Cat always land on their feet.
Time to prowl for fresh prey.
'Old money.'
'Older money.'
Oh. Hm.
New money. Me-ow.
- One water with.. - One water with.. Oh.
Uh, two waters with lemon, please.
I wonder what else we have in common, Miss..
Kyle. Selina Kyle.
- I'm Bruce... - Wayne, I know.
But who knew Gotham's most eligible bachelor
had such a grip.
You're not so bad yourself.
Your grip.
A firm handshake is a must in my line of work.
- Which is? - Fundraising, for charities.
Ah, you find wealthy philanthropists
such as myself and spend our money.
- Only on good causes. - Define, "Good."
Over dinner. Your place?
I'll phone my butler and have him whip something up.
Yummy. I'll grab my coat.
One of those with lots of twists.
'Perfect.'
'Wow, you're really into dog art.'
You like it, huh.
- It belonged to my father. - Dessert, Ms. Kyle?
Your famous nachos will be hard to beat, Alfred.
Mind if I desert you boys for a minute?
The ladies' lounge is down the hall to your right.
Miss Kyle is most pleasant, sir.
More importantly she's intimate with all of Gotham's charities.
You are made for each other.
Saved by the bell.
'Everything but cats.'
Why is it the only man in Gotham
with my sense of style is Batman.
A delivery? At this hour?
Special delivery.
Oh!
Oh, an original Nolbino.
Hello.
The looks on your faces.
Priceless! Perhaps I'll snatch those too.
Sir, considering the mixed company
perhaps Ragdoll's best left for the proper authorities.
Just need to make sure Ragdoll's reachable.
Buddy, I suggest you leave the heirloom behind.
And I suggest you not to play with dolls.
I-i-it's cool. Just take it.
You won't get away with this.
Oh, aren't you're a tigress.
You have no idea.
Toodles.
Wow! I, uh, I better call the police.
Well, perhaps Miss Kyle would like a spot of tea?
You know, for the nerves.
Why don't you brew some for Bruce?
He looks like he could use it.
Goodnight, Alfred.
Oh, if only you knew the real Bruce Wayne.
From Ragdoll to riches.
What're you doing here?
Funny, I was about to ask you.
Clank clank.
Sorry, handsome. Ragdoll's mine.
Gotham ain't big enough for the both of us, Raggedy.
Oh, kitten has claws.
Ooh!
Kitten has a whip.
Meow Ooh!
Now, we're even. Toodles.
So kitten likes to play rough.
About time I ended this game.
Yes, puddy, I know it's horrid.
But you know, the thrill of the hunt
is far more important to me than the payoff.
Too bad Bruce Wayne's belongings don't thrill me at all.
'In local events, billionaire Bruce Wayne has announced'
he will open his most famous property
'the Gotham clock tower for a rare public tour.'
Well, speak of Mr. Boring.
Built over 150 years ago by Wayne's great-grandfather
the tower remains the source of many legends.
The cat's eyes.
And what of Frankie Scolacci's Cat's Eyes?
The emeralds that mobsters supposedly
hid somewhere here back in the 1930s?
Well, the tower's been searched dozens of times.
But who knows? Could be we missed a nook.
Suddenly old Bruce is lookin' pretty good.
Catwoman won't resist the bait.
And Ragdoll won't resist getting even with Catwoman.
'The interior of the clock'
consists of 341 moving parts
including these giant gears
which were forged from over 20 tons of iron.
Now, if you'll follow me..
Dog art collector and clock expert.
Well, aren't you just the whole package, Bruce Wayne?
Selina, I'm, I'm sorry about the other night.
Don't apologize for being burgled.
Apologize for not calling.
I've been distracted.
Bruce, don't tell me you've been courting
another charity fundraiser.
No, Selina, a whole different breed of person
has been on my mind.
Rattle rattle rattle.
What do we have here?
No, they're not in here.
Listen up, Raggy.
If those emeralds are here, they're mine.
'I can't leave you two alone for a second.'
Whoa!
Tick tock, Batman.
When it's your time, it's your time.
Save yourself, Batman.
Lose the mask, I would.
Screech.
What? And ruin his mysterious allure.
Thanks.
You may wanna think twice next time
you consider tyin' me up.
Whoa!
Really irons out the kinks.
Hmm. Oh, and lookie what I found.
No.
Bet these will fetch six figures.
If it's money you want, rob a bank.
Those emeralds are two of a kind, ragface.
Speaking of, three of us, two of these
I guess we'll split them one way.
Hey.
Hey!
Ha!
The reach of Ragdoll is quicker than the..
Eye.
Wa-wow.
- Finders keepers. - They don't belong to you.
Who then? Bruce Wayne?
We are in his clock tower.
Don't bring him between us, handsome.
Mm, I love a man in uniform.
Carry on.
That's tight.
Help me out here and I-I'll split these with you.
I don't accept handouts.
But I'll always take what I've earned.
Come on, don't be a sour puss, handsome.
The cat's eyes were a legend, right?
No one will know they're missing
because they are not even supposed to be here.
Um-mh. Not even one?
Argh!
I'll get my cat's eyes.
Even if I have to claw them from Bruce Wayne's fingertips.
Uh.
Little help?
'Because you love my cooking, madam.'
Ooh, the famous Pennyworth nachos.
Now, you've been quite the danger magnet
these days, Bruce Wayne.
Clock tower incident's all over the news.
Actually there was an upshot.
The found emeralds were bequeathed to me.
Oh, let me guess.
You displayed the cat's eyes besides
your cherished velvet painting of dogs playing poker.
Nope, I sold them..
'...for 100 G's.'
And the Wayne foundation would be honored to have you donate
the proceeds to the charity you feel could use it most.
I can't tell you what a... thrill this is.
- 'Sir.' - 'I'm on hold with the bank.'
Oh, really, Master Bruce?
I think this sudden distrust of Miss Kyle
is terribly misplaced.
I have a weird feeling that's all.
Selina left here in such a mood.
It was? To whom?
I see. Yup.
- Thank you very much. - Well..
Well, Selina donated the check after all
to the Gotham pet shelter network.
Intriguing choice for a woman
who doesn't seem to care much for dog art.
Selina Kyle is a fascinating creature.
'Could be there's more to her than meets the eye.'