Clang.
Mm, meow.
Paws off, puddy.
Hello, it's a cat. The jewel's mine.
I beg to differ, my feline felon
and so do my companions.
Ha!
Ha..
Hm.
Now, how could I say no
to those beady blue eyes?
Well, Mama Cobblepot did always say
I was a handsome one.
You know, perhaps
we can come to some sort of arrangement.
Hm? What you have in mind, good-lookin'?
This gem happens to be one of a pair.
The cat is all yours if you help me steal
the true object of my desire.
A partnership! Mrreow.
♪ The Batman ♪
Millions of dollars worth of art and valuables
skipped over for a jeweled cat.
This heist has all the earmarks of Catwoman
except for the other point of entry.
She had help, a second perp.
I want everyone to recanvass the exterior.
Let's move.
Whirr
beep beep.
The tome you requested, Master Bruce.
A second perp doesn't fit her profile.
Catwoman works alone.
Well, partnerships do appear
to be all the rage these days.
Detective Yin is a good cop, Alfred.
I'm glad she decided to put her trust in The Batman.
Beep beep.
Dander of an eastern European raven.
It's one of Penguin's birds.
But why would Catwoman team with Oswald Cobblepot?
'Here's why.'
The relic stolen last night is one of a pair..
'...with Ra, the Egyptian Sun God.'
The very same relic currently on loan
to the Museum Of Natural History here in Gotham?
A cat and a bird.
Two jewels, two villains.
And one crime-fighter capable of stopping them.
Caw.
Digital surveillance
state-of-the-art electronic security.
Hm, the museum's a tough nut to crack
but I know where the soft spots are.
Ooh, with my birds and your know-how
the two of us will be sitting in the ol' catbird seat.
Sounds cozy, Penguie baby
but cats and birds are natural enemies, you know?
Well, with enemies like you, cat-chickie
who needs friends?
A little privacy, puh-lease!
Yes. Why don't you go fetch me a saucer of Moo Juice?
A-ah! Manners!
Fine! Good riddance! And don't come back!
Alone at last.
Oh, Ozzie, you've stolen my heart.
Too bad I'm gonna break yours
once I steal both those jewels.
Vroom.
Hm?
Caw.
Hey!
Uh, uh..
Surveillance down.
What about that state-of-the-art security?
Well, don't you worry
your pretty little head, Penguie.
The Catwoman knows a trick or two.
Ah, phenomenal.
You know, according to Egyptian legend
the cat goddess enabled ol' Ra here
to harness the power of the sun.
How nice for them.
And where is my kitty, cutie-cakes?
Such a shame to break up the set.
Oh, The Batman!
You never call, you never write.
Three's a crowd, Bat jerk!
You two want souvenirs of your visit
try the gift shop.
Thud thud thud.
Quite a pair.
Oh, about that, sweetie
I prefer to work alone.
I was referring to these!
You double-crossing me?
So sorry for stringing you along, sugarplum
but you're not my type. They are.
I trusted you.
Huh?
I brought this pretty bracelet
especially for you
but since you two pointy-ears
make such a cute couple his and hers.
I'll just hang on to the key
and the jewels.
Crash
thud.
Now what?
Relax.
Oven timer?
It's ready to explode.
It's been a blast, Batman.
It's tamper-proof.
Oh, well, you're stuck with me.
We need the key.
Hm, yet another reason for a Penguin hunt.
Growl.
- This way! - This way!
Fine. You lead.
Screech Mm, meow.
Hm..
I'll drive.
- Whoa! - Hey!
'Catwoman?'
I don't believe it.
'This baby really purrs.'
'Looks like you have Penguin to blame'
for putting me in the driver's seat.
Hm, what's this do?
Curiosity killed the cat.
Mm, kitty's curious about more than just your wheels.
'What's under your hood, handsome?'
Ladies first.
Vroom
tap tap tap.
Trust your instincts, Yin.
So, Bat beau, when we find the waddling worm-eater
I'd like to have at least two minutes alone with him.
You'll both have plenty of alone time
when you're together in the Gotham State Penitentiary.
- Batman. - What do you know? It works.
Uh, hi.
I thought I'd put our new partnership to the test.
Oh, gives his number to all the girls.
What's up, detective?
I'm stumped.
'I can't ID Catwoman's mysterious partner.'
Thought you might have an idea.
I'm tracking a few leads.
- Meow. - 'Excuse me?'
Uh, static on the Batwave.
I'll have to get back to you, detective.
So he's a little strange, Yin.
He dresses like a bat.
'All-points bulletin.'
'The Batman and Catwoman'
'were seen fleeing together'
'from the museum crime scene.'
The Batman's the second perp?
To think, this could have all been mine.
'Penguin's been doing some research.'
According to these artifacts
'when the two jewels are properly configured'
they're capable of harnessing the power of the sun.
You read ancient Egyptian?
The pictures help.
And so you think.
Penguie's looking to reduce his utility bill?
Whoever said cats and birds
are natural enemies?
Detective, squad room.
Something big's going down.
'That's right, I demand one billion dollars by dawn'
'or Gotham suffers the wrath of the sun.'
Sun? In the middle of the night?
This Penguin guy's nuts.
'Oh, allow me to demonstrate!'
Lights..
Camera, destruction!
'Oh, you gotta love those ancient Egyptian engineers.'
'Wire the money to my Swiss Bank account by sunrise'
'or my next target will be full of civilians.'
clang
vroom.
- My, who's the popular one? - Batman.
'Cat's out of the bag, partner.'
'I know you're with Catwoman.'
He is.
Trust me, detective. It's complicated.
'I have to trust you. You're needed.'
Penguin's holding Gotham hostage with some sort of..
'Ancient Egyptian light machine.'
'I know, and I know where to find him'
the only bird's-eye view of Gotham
with a powerful enough light source.
If Penguin sees us coming, he might get trigger-happy.
Well, there's only one stairwell.
We don't need stairs.
Uh, aren't seagulls usually white?
They're Penguin's birds.
Here comes Miss Congeniality.
Uh... up you go.
I never did get my saucer of milk.
Ew! Nails on a chalkboard.
I could dance all night, partner.
Let's shake a crow from his nest.
Ah..
Thud Huh?
Well, well, look what the cat dragged in.
It's over, Penguin.
Bye-bye, birdie.
Any closer
and Gotham Children's Hospital is rubble!
I possess the power of Ra!
I, Penguin, Pharaoh of Gotham!
Squeak.
The cat.
You mean, after all we've been through?
Come on. Throw a dog a bone.
Well, alright!
Sorry, handsome!
Not so fast, kitty-cat!
The triple-crosses end here.
We had a deal, fish breath! No!
Hey!
Hm, made for each other.
Come on!
Thud.
Hang on! Here's our ride.
Bye-bye, Bat!
Now, take us to your spare key.
Huh? What spare key?
Batman?
The coast is clear, detective.
But I highly recommend keeping the relics separated.
I know this may sound shady
but it might be best if I held on to one
'for safekeeping.'
Go right ahead, Batman.
'I trust you.'
♪ The Batman ♪