Tweet tweet tweet Come to me.
Tweet tweet tweet flap flap flap.
Return to your cage.
Tweet tweet.
Now, if I could just get one of these to work on my kids.
Beep
tap tap tap.
Hey there, little fella.
Tweet tweet.
Aah! Ah! Aah!
Rawk rawk hoo hoo hoo
beep beep hoo Out poaching for Penguin?
Hoo
rip rip rip
whack
swoosh
caw
crackle crackle
hoo caw caw caw hoo hoo
beep beep
hoo hoo hoo.
♪ The Batman ♪
Grrr!
What took you so long?
Hoo hoo hoo You are late! Again!
Caw.
Zip it! I'm through with you birdbrains.
You are not wise enough!
You eat too much meat!
You are always crowing about something or other.
And you, Finch!
Don't get me started on you and your bird pies!
Splat Ohh! Indoors?
Bleh-achk!
I have had it with you slobs!
Well, you and your doo-doo are going the way of the dodo.
So, say hello to your replacement!
Raaawwwk.
A rare condor
so vicious even I can't train it.
But with this specialized sonic thingy
I can command any bird to do my bidding.
Clang Observe.
I am your master.
Come to me.
Hmm. Come to me-e-e!
Come... to... me.
'I am your master.'
'Come to me!'
'Come to me-e-e.'
'You'll see.'
It's a matter of time before I recreate my formula
which will allow me to once again
rule Gotham's night skies as Man-Bat!
Okay. Do you want these chimichangas or not, Langstrom?
'Come to me!'
'Come to-o me-e!'
Aaaaaah!
The noise!
Aaaaah!
What noise?
Yaah-aah-aah!
Turn it off! Please!
Get it out of my head!
Screech Aah!
Grr..
Raaaarrh!
'Come to me-e-e!'
crash.
I said come to me already!
Rawwwkk Aah!
Thud Alright! I'm sorry!
Clang Lousy hunk of junk!
Swoosh crash Raaaarrh!
Aah!
Who the, what are you?
And what do bats have against me anyway?
Get away, you!
'Get away!'
flap.
Get away?
Screech.
Come to me.
Fan me.
Raaarrh!
I said, fan your master.
Pity this won't work on birdy.
I'll just have to make do with a ferocious
giant bat monster instead!
A flurry of moths, sir?
Penguin's pets.
Didn't have a shot at tracking them
to their master's whereabouts
but it doesn't add up.
'Oswald Cobblepot's always been after the big payday'
'jewels, gold, money..'
But a tech robbery?
Sonics?
Batwave.
An alarm has been tripped at Gotham National Bank.
Now that's the Penguin I know.
Screech.
Oh, dear.
Beep beep Intruder alert?
Evacuate the cave. I'm on my way.
'That will be most unnecessary, sir.'
I believe I can handle our masked intruder myself.
Blast!
Screech.
Either Penguin's been working out..
Or he needs a manicure.
Splat
thud.
Man-Bat.
Wouldn't a blood bank be more your style, Langstrom?
Screech.
The money.
Bring me the money.
Screech.
'Score!'
Look! Superbat's proving you tweeters are for the birds!
Huh?
Flap flap flap
thud.
Stop fooling around!
'Get rid of the Batman!'
thud.
The Batman, not the money!
Swoosh
screech.
Down, boy.
Creak creak.
Since when does Man-Bat rob banks?
Since Penguin started stealing sonic technology.
Blast.
- Our intruder? - Uh, not to worry, sir.
My grip on that scoundrel tightens as we speak.
I'm on a wild animal hunt myself, Alfred.
And I have a hunch our bird heist
will shed some light on our bat heist.
Rest up, my giant bat pet.
More crimes to commit for El Penguino tomorrow.
Raah!
Screech.
You! You! Get out of my head!
Huh? Where's my bat pet?
I am no one's pet!
I'm Dr. Kirk Langstrom, scientist
and one of the greatest minds in Gotham.
No! I, Penguin am one of the greatest.
So that's the wretched device which controls me.
Its frequency must have triggered my
echolocation bat hearing
and reactivated dormant traces of the serum
in my system, transforming me into Man-Bat!
Yeah, whatever.
So I just gotta flip this puppy on
to turn nerd guy back into Man-Bat?
I shall allow you to live, Penguin
if you hand it to me now.
Hand what to ya, huh? This? This?
Then be sure you never lose it
for the first opportunity I get
I shall clip your flightless wings.
'I've repaired the device, Alfred.'
Diagnostics indicate it's a sonic emitter
encoded to communicate with birds.
But it can be adjusted to emit different frequencies.
'My guess is the one Penguin ended up with'
'was configured to control bats.'
Man-Bat may have the physical advantage
over the Batman, but if we can use
'this device to capture Penguin's frequency'
we might have a shot at breaking.
Penguin's spell over his slave.
Gad! That wretched creature
'made off with the bait.'
It may be time to use
Wayne Industries media connections to lay some bait.
' "Golden penguin statue?" Wow.'
Now, how could they bring something like that to Gotham
and not expect me to steal it?
Idiots!
'Hmm.'
And it's already boxed for takeout.
Click.
Penguin's about to take the bait, Alfred.
I await your signal, sir.
Alright, Fido..
Screech ...time to fetch.
Raaawk!
Alfred, I've captured Penguin's signal.
Got it, sir.
That wave is translating its frequency.
Whack whack.
'That's what I'm talkin' about!'
Sinewy strands of monster muscle!
Could you do that, vulture?
'I didn't think so.'
cheep cheep cheep
screech Ah! Please don't break!
Please don't break, please don't break!
Screech thud.
Bowling balls?
It's a trick!
'So! You like pinatas, Batman?'
Let's find out what you're filled with.
'Man-Bat, attack!'
screech Standing by, Alfred.
Frequency transmission complete.
Prepare to receive, sir.
Clang screech.
Sir, can you hear me?
Blast!
Stop.
Stop!
Screech thud.
Alfred, do you copy?
Crackle crackle Hold on, Master Bruce.
No reception. I'm flying solo.
Gotta buy some time.
Pound him into bat guano.
Raaaarrh!
Thud screech.
How about a game of hide 'n seek?
Oh, the shadows won't conceal you, Batman.
My Man-Bat can hear in the dark.
Raaaarrh!
Smash
thud thud thud
bang bang.
Not too fond of confined spaces?
Screech screech screech.
Power? Where's the backup power?
How can one hungry ball of hair do so much damage?
Ah, these are terrible seats.
I'm missing all the fun.
Screech
boom
screech.
Almost... there.
Thud thud.
Raaaarrh!
Beep We have transmission!
Raaarrh!
Stop.
Phew!
You really did bring this upon yourself, you know.
And the champion returns.
So the mighty Batman is finally..
Whack.
Ooh, boy.
'Bring me Penguin..'
'...by whatever means necessary.'
Please! Help me!
Ow! Someone please!
Next time, Penguin, stick to birds.
Oh, hi, Dr. Langstrom.
Ow!
Now that Penguin and Langstrom are roosting
in Arkham where they belong
'we may want to think about installing'
'an anti-rodent barrier.'
'Nice mask.'
In case you were considering taking on a sidekick, sir.
I think Penguin and I
are through with pets for the time being.
♪ The Batman ♪