Trick or treat?
My, what wonderful costumes, Virginia.
Yes, they certainly are, Georgia.
But what are you doing trick-or-treating? Hmm?
Hello. It's Halloween.
Not just any Halloween.
Tonight is Grundy's night.
'There, the swampland.'
'The birthplace of Solomon Grundy.'
It was 150 years ago, on this very night
in that very same swamp
that a monster rose from the muck
and slouched toward Gotham
to wreak havoc against the very architects of our city.
But the lives Grundy ruined that fateful night
weren't enough to satisfy him.
Grundy vowed to haunt the descendants of his victims
by returning on the darkest of all Hallows Eves.
Tonight, during a total lunar eclipse.
'Grundy will rise again.'
How do you know so much about this?
Because we are the granddaughters of Emmet Bolton
one of Grundy's victims.
And Grundy could come for us at any moment.
- Let's get out of here. - Let's get out of here.
Don't you want any candy?
To grandfather Emmet
who left us so much money.
And wonderful stories to scare children with.
- Aah! - Aah!
Destroy!
♪ The Batman ♪
- Trick or treat! - Trick or treat!
Sorry if I scared you, Holmes.
It's Grundy's night, you know?
I am well aware.
Any good costumes this round?
If you consider Joker, Catwoman, and Penguin good.
I guess it's more fun to be the bad guys.
You sure you didn't see a ghost, Alfred?
I was a bit spooked by the chaperone's Solomon Grundy mask.
Well, it is Grundy's night.
Not all legends are legend, Master Bruce.
The Batman's faced a lot of things
that go bump in the night, Alfred.
But swamp zombies?
The Batwave.
Oh, it would appear something has gone bump, sir.
What would Halloween be if I didn't get to wear my costume?
What happened here?
Ahh, a vampire.
T-t-the police will be here any moment.
I'm here to help you, not harm you.
Who or what did this?
It was him. He came for us.
Solomon Grundy.
Look how strong he is.
He did this with his bare hands.
All part of his revenge
just as the legend told.
Grundy would return on darkest night..
To deprive the descendants of all in their sight.
Our home, our assets.
We're fortunate we still have our lives.
Revenge. Ladies, I know you're frightened, but...
If you don't believe us, look.
He came for us. He'll come for the others, too.
Who are these others?
No.
Winslow, run.
Grundy must have his revenge.
Grundy must destroy.
Ugh!
Destroy.
Yah!
Grundy wins.
Ohh... ahh..
Whoa!
Huh?
No candy here, fellas.
My home, everything I own, gone.
Spiffy costume.
Boo.
Ah. Sir, what happened to you?
Your Gotham legend happened.
Solomon Grundy?
There was a resemblance.
Your bruises didn't make themselves, Master Bruce.
'Was your attacker a seven and a half foot tall'
swamp zombie or wasn't he?
I just don't wanna have to believe
in the boogeyman, too, Alfred.
You would be wise to listen closely, sir.
The legend may provide a clue to lifting Grundy's curse.
It says here that Gotham swamp wasn't always a swamp.
Once, it was lake
home to the mostly Eastern European laborers
who built Gotham city.
But three businessmen, Bolton, Winslow and Parish
conspired to make the area a dumping ground
for the industrial waste
created by Gotham's construction
turning the lake into Gotham swamp
rendering the area unsuitable for habitation.
Several of the laborers who lost their homes
were versed in magic from their native countries.
On all Hallows Eve, during a lunar eclipse
they used that magic to form Solomon Grundy
from the very waste of Gotham swamp.
Since the laborers and their families
lost everything they owned
so, too, would Grundy haunt Gotham's founding fathers
and their families, through the years
leaving them destitute.
Oh, poetic justice it is most spine-tingling.
'Sir?'
I see you have no patience for old butler's tales.
Not true, Alfred.
But tonight I'll let science
dictate what is and isn't supernatural.
'I'm looking for a follicle, a sliver of dead skin'
anything in this mud that might contain a trace of Grundy's DNA.
Call me when the results are in.
And you will be where?
It's nearly witching hour.
If Grundy's allowed to strike his last victim
he could disappear for another 150 years.
Do hurry back, sir.
We wouldn't want you turning into a pumpkin.
Hey, goodnight, Mr. Parish.
Happy Halloween.
Gotham's oldest attraction
and Halloween night, its biggest money-maker.
Pretty fast for a swamp zombie.
Waah!
Whoa there, buddy.
I'm just messin' with ya.
Hey, didn't see you at old man Parish's shindig.
That's quite a Batman costume you got there.
Listen, I'm looking for a... friend of mine.
Big guy, dressed like Solomon Grundy.
Hmm, haven't seen any swamp zombies
but if I do, I'll let 'em know the Batman's looking for 'em.
The Batman. Waah..
'Master Bruce.'
Go ahead.
The Batwave traced DNA alright
mutated human DNA.
'The odd thing is, it wasn't on any follicles or skin.'
But in the mud itself.
How on Earth could you possibly have known that?
Grundy may not be supernatural
but his threat is real alright.
Grundy will destroy you.
Argh!
Raaahhh!
Revenge.
Halloween's nearly over, Grundy.
Time to lose the mask.
Trick or treat, Clayface.
Can't blame me for having some Halloween fun
can ya, Bats?
Terrorizing the descendants
and destroying their homes was your cover
but it was their money you were after.
Leave 'em destitute, like the legend says.
Raahhh!
No one would think of chasing after Grundy for the money.
They'd have to dredge Gotham swamp.
And I'd be long gone with my loot
taking any face I wanted, alive, dead, or nonexistent.
I knew I couldn't lose a 500-pound zombie that easily.
I may not have tricked you, Bats
but I'm still gonna collect my treats.
'A shapeshifter in a wax museum.'
Great.
Grundy. Too obvious.
My leg.
Sorry, Bats. I'm the one providing the chills tonight.
Clang.
The problem with this mask, Bats..
No air holes.
Aah!
Thud.
'Try and find me, Batman.'
'I'm just another face in the crowd.'
Oh, you win the door prize
the waxworks hot wax special.
Face it, Bats.
You'll be the most realistic dummy in the place.
No!
Oh, another all Hallows Eve come and gone.
Well, at least Grundy's curse is lifted.
What makes you so certain, sir?
You're kidding, right?
Just because an arch-villain masqueraded as Grundy tonight
does not mean the zombie doesn't exist.
'Well, what can I say, Alfred?'
'You make a compelling argument.'
If there was a Grundy, we'd have seen him by now.
Yeah. Those old ladies were kooks.
Let's bail.
It's Grundy.
Run!
♪ The Batman ♪