'We're experiencing what experts are calling'
'the harshest winter Gotham's seen in a hundred years.'
'So with the roads iced over and six more inches due'
'turn that radiator up and the alarm clock off'
'because you're not gettin' to work tomorrow'
'unless you can fly.'
slam.
'Come down with your hands up!'
You shouldn't play with Firefly.
- Phew! - Phew.
- Uh! - Ah.
Screech.
Those guys okay?
Yeah, they're alright.
In this town, I'm the heat.
You're all sizzle and no steak.
Burn, Batman!
Creak.
Uh!
Crash
pew pew pew.
So how'd you plan on getting me down?
You'll have to land when you run out of fuel.
Well, let's fill her up, then.
Pew
boom.
♪ The Batman ♪
thud Unh!
Forget Firefly.
We just scored chief's public enemy number one.
I'm really not feeling the love here, fellas.
Beep.
Whoa!
Screech
bang bang bang swoosh
click click.
'Detective Yin.'
You and Firefly threw quite the winter barbecue.
It was a blast, do we know what he took
from the technologies firm?
Working on it.
'Firefly's always been work-for-hire.'
If we knew what he took
maybe we'd know who he took it for.
Thud whoosh.
Honey, I'm home.
Creak Brought you a present.
Gotham city... in the palm of your hand.
Is this a joke?
Saw it in a window, Boss Frost.
Thought of you.
Grrr!
Cool your jets. I got the other thing, too.
Nice.
You don't know the half of it.
I also fried the bat.
And you saw his cold remains?
Well, I didn't exactly see where I left..
You risked putting the Batman hot on our trail.
Okay, okay, chill. Bat showed.
What was I supposed to do?
Nothing must stand in my way when I..
When we extend Gotham's
harsh winter into permafrost.
The city will be ours to shake up
or shake down anytime we want.
Nine-piece band, check.
Decorations, check.
Dinner napkins..
Oh, it would seem that, despite the cold
the Gotham Police Gala has become quite the hot ticket.
Though I must say, Master Bruce
I find your hosting of the event a bit ironic
given the Dark Knight's vigilante standing
with the blue knights.
It's the least I could do for Gotham's finest, Alfred.
Or perhaps it's your way of seeking what the Batman
cannot have, the approval of Gotham's finest.
Slurp.
Yes, yes, I'm fired. I know.
The Batwave.
A break-in..
At Wayne Industries?
Thud.
"Liquid nitrogen. Do not touch."
Creak poof.
Ahh..
Clang.
I was expecting someone with a little more flair.
Such a chilly reception, Batman.
Crackle crackle crackle.
Aah! My eyes!
Crash.
Hmm, how shall I ice you, Batman?
Allow me to pick your frozen brain.
Whirr.
"Liquid nitrogen."
Boom.
Yah! Ha-ha-ha-haa.
Rumble rumble
crash
thud.
So what could the unlikely pair of fire and ice
be building together?
It is time to swap one dark suit for another, Master Bruce.
The policemen's gala begins shortly.
Uh, the roads are iced over, Alfred.
Sounds like the perfect alibi for a no-show to me.
Now, now, you are the celebrity host.
Do you think it's wise to risk
'rousing the suspicion of hundreds of police?'
I'll put in some quick face time
deliver my toast, and duck back out.
Crackle crackle crackle
beep beep whirr.
The vents are rerouted, Boss Frost.
'The heat that flows through these vents'
'warms every building in Gotham.'
With my cryo-accelerator..
We can do something about that.
The guy obviously thinks he's some kinda crusader
but he's doing more harm than good, Wayne.
You're lucky the bat only trashed your lab.
The bat is lucky I wasn't there.
I would've opened a can of hurt on him
and personally dragged him to your doorstep.
You're my kinda guy, Wayne.
Cider, Chief Rojas?
Huh? Oh, uh, sure.
Don't mind if I..
Uh..
Whoo! Appreciate the save, Ellen.
You looked like a man in need of a rescue.
Wow, they tell me just about every badge
in Gotham's here tonight.
Makes you wonder who's protecting the city.
Uh, I'd better rehearse my toast.
Wayne.
I know your secret.
Excuse me?
It's been quite an act.
You really had me snowed.
Uh, I'm afraid I don't know what you're...
Need me to spell it out for you?
There are two sides to Bruce Wayne.
Most people look at you and think rich party boy.
Does the whole charity thing just for the PR.
But I can see..
This isn't a front.
You really care, don't you?
Boy.
You've got my number.
Guilty as charged.
Whoosh.
The freeze-o-matic 9000's ready to blow.
As the cryo-accelerator amplifies my powers tenfold.
Gothamites will have nowhere to turn, as block by city block
they are frozen out of their homes.
And what better block to beta-test
than where the entire police force
fortuitously assembles tonight.
'I can hear 'em now.'
How did these ice cubes get in my shorts?
Let us begin.
Whirr.
Fire up!
Rumble
crash Arrrhhhh!
And we sleep warmer in our beds
knowing that you are there.
That is why I am pleased to donate..
Huh, radiator must be on the fritz.
Hiss crackle crackle crackle
click
swoosh screech
crash.
Where there's frost, there's fire.
Next.
Second stop on the freezer burn tour..
'...City hall.'
The Batman!
Don't sweat it, chief! I got him!
Pew
crash
zap crash
pew.
Uh-oh.
Crackle crackle kaboom.
Idiot! You've damaged the cryo-accelerator!
We'll fix it. Chill!
You chill!
Aah!
Huh! Ugh!
Thud
beep.
Your demise, Batman may warm even my heart.
Pew pew.
Ugh!
That was cold, Jack!
Pew pew pew.
'Time to bring the heat.'
whirr.
He has started the boiler!
Yeah? Well, some like it hot!
Aah! My fuel tank!
Unh!
Bye-bye, Batman.
Aah!
'Feed a cold, starve a fever.'
- Ooh.. - Aah..
Uh, I remember Wayne's speech and then zip.
What happened?
'Hey! Check this out!'
Freeze and Firefly did this?
Well, they won't be giving us any more trouble.
- Nice work, boys. - It-it wasn't us, chief.
It was him.
Swoosh.
Ugh-uh! G-g-get him!
The Batman? He saved us.
And he saved the city.
♪ The Batman ♪