Caw caw
splash
clang clang clang
clank.
Alright, we lay low until the heat's off.
Then we move the rocks. Clear?
- Crystal. - Um, speaking of heat..
Oh, man. Is that the Bat?
Thud.
Boys, I'm a whole different breed of animal.
And one butt-ugly hood ornament.
Looks like you had a busy night. That's good.
Cause you're all working for me now.
Gentlemen, show the walking freak show
who's boss around here.
You city boys need to learn yourself some manners.
- Who are you? - Name's Croc.
Killer Croc. But you can call me boss.
♪ The Batman ♪
Gotham has a sudden burst of nine
seemingly unrelated heists.
With stolen goods ranging from explosives to jet skis.
There has to be a link between these crimes.
Huh?
Apologies, Master Bruce.
Just a bit of spring cleaning.
Clang
beep.
Uh, Alfred, where are you taking the evidence?
These cases are closed.
They are now history in every sense of the word.
It would be criminal to not preserve
these items for posterity.
So I've chosen to archive them.
A private museum, if you will.
After all, the Batman may someday enjoy
a more favorable place in society's view.
Yeah, I won't hold my breath.
Water.
Actually, I'd prefer a spot of ice tea
if you're headed to the kitchen.
No, the link between the robberies, water.
A half dozen within spitting distance of a canal
'and three on Gotham Bay.'
thud.
Boss wants this swag loaded. Pronto!
The Batman.
I'd like to have a word with this boss you fellas mentioned.
Clank.
My daddy used to say you want something done right
best to do it yourself.
Clank swoosh
swoosh swoosh
crash.
You look to be this Batman legend I keep hearin' about.
Well, folks are gonna start hearin' about
how Killer Croc stopped you good.
Bam grrr
splash
thud
clank.
Boss Croc definitely does not have both oars in the water.
Yeah, he calls this slime pit headquarters.
Well, maybe you two should mention that to Croc.
Me, I like my teeth just where they are.
Yeah, well, first chance I get, it's after a while, crocodile.
Sure do hate to see my boys so unhappy.
Oh, not me, boss, I'm happy... as a clam.
Good, because this time tomorrow
the tops of skyscrapers will be our lily pads.
And downtown Gotham will be our oyster.
Master Bruce, your Batsuit may be drip-dry
you, however, are not.
Next time, I'll be sure to keep Croc on my turf.
Dry land.
Beep beep beep.
This was the scene moments ago
as Gotham's financial district was hit
'by the largest flood in the city's history.'
thud thud.
What?
'Emergency crews are now'
'arriving on the scene to assist'
'with the evacuation of local residents.'
'The cause of the flood is still unknown.'
beep beep beep.
'Three bank alarms in Gotham's waterlogged financial district?'
Your amphibious acquaintance?
Water, water everywhere!
How about a little game of chicken? Cajun style.
Splash Mind your cowl now.
Croc's story, spill it.
He's ex-military, I think. Mercenary type.
Some think he's a genetic experiment.
A cross-breed soldier or something.
Others think he messed with
the wrong kind of voodoo in the bayou.
Me, I'm thinking circus freak.
Facts, not folk tales.
What's to tell? Croc's new in town, he's got big plans.
Bigger than robbing banks?
Uh... Croc said today's flood was just a dry run.
If I wanted to do some big city Croc hunting
where would I go?
Oh, no way.
Boss Croc's cold-blooded, man.
I talk, I wind up fish food.
You don't talk, we could all wind up fish food.
Splash.
Schematics of Gotham's canals.
'You sure got a lot of bloodhound in ya'
for a bat. What do you think?
A dry little spot to catch my breath between heists.
And right beside the overflow pumps
for Gotham's canal system.
They were designed to drain the canals
into the bay in case of flooding.
But I did some thinking.
If you reverse the pumps..
They draw water in from the bay filling the canals
until they submerge any part of Gotham
situated below sea level.
Just about all of downtown
where the good shopping is.
Tens of thousands of lives could be lost.
And I'll shed a crocodile tear
for each and every one.
Swish swish
swish
splash.
And speaking of..
My pets haven't had a decent bite since we arrived.
Now, if you'll pardon me, bat snack
I've got some more pumps to reverse.
Clank clank clank
swish
beep beep beep boom
beep beep beep hiss hiss hiss.
Nothing like good old elbow grease.
Rumble rumble.
Huh? You are peskier than a fly in a..
Thud
splash
swish swish swish.
Catch of the day.
Splash.
You gotta put your back into it, boy.
You best give it up, Bat.
By the time they figure out what caused the flood
downtown Gotham will be my personal swamp.
Thud
splat
splash
bam
thud splash.
Boy, you are beginning to stick in my craw.
A dry little spot to catch my breath between heists.
Your amphibious acquaintance?
Clank
thud
clank
thud.
'Crocs may like water, but they're no fish.'
So, either of you up for giving lizard-lips
a little mouth-to-mouth?
Huh, didn't think so.
What are you looking at?
This ain't over, Aqua Bat.
Gotham is gonna be my backyard bayou!
I won't hold my breath.
Clank.
You missed a spot.
And I just mopped that floor.
What did you bring me?
Evidence.
I shall archive this right away, sir.
♪ The Batman ♪