Mustard, no sauerkraut. "Metropolis Gold Exchange"?
Wonder if anyone's tried to rob it.
This place? You'd need a tank the size of Pittsburgh.
Good thing we were in the neighborhood.
Hold it right there!
I want this area sealed off.
Dan, we should move these vehicles back, establish a perimeter.
There's no time.
Don't you just love this town?
See you back at the ranch.
Hey!
From my viewpoint, the Special Crimes Unit might as well save their ammo.
Wait a second.
I think the sides just evened up.
My tank! Look what he's doing to my tank.
Looks like Superman's turned the SCU into a cleanup crew.
That was pretty expensive machinery. You think Intergang's behind this?
All I can tell you now is that we're following every lead.
Whoever it is, you can bet my Aunt Patty's pension they'll be going down real soon.
Translation: you expect Superman to drop them in your lap like he always does.
- What are you saying? - I'm saying your highly-paid department...
can't seem to bust a jaywalker without old blue boy.
The SCU is always grateful for the help of any citizen of Metropolis...
including Superman.
Useless! Worthless! A joke!
- Careful, boss. - I keep telling you guys...
Intergang needs real armaments. Weapons of mass destruction.
And all I get are toys.
What was that?
- Who are you? - My name is Kanto, Mr. Mannheim.
I've been authorized to offer you some assistance.
By whom? Start talking.
Please, put away your so-called weapons. I can assure you they're unnecessary.
I come bearing gifts.
That's tempered steel. It's melting like cheap margarine.
Okay. I'm impressed, but I still don't get it.
Someone sent you here just to give us these things?
Including this. It's called the Armature.
When activated, it forms two hands of raw energy...
hands which perfectly simulate the motions of the gloves.
The energy hands, of course, possess a greatly amplified strength.
Okay, I want them. What's your boss want in return?
- Nothing, for now. - It's my experience that nothing...
- can get very expensive. - Consider this a free sample.
Your benefactor will explain everything at the proper time, a time of his choosing.
Good day.
Call the boys. It's time for another job.
Then the guy disappears into thin air like bad gas.
Strange stuff's going on, Maggie. I never seen anything like it.
You shouldn't have gone. You could've been in terrible danger.
That's why I'm called Terrible Turpin.
I'm serious, kiddo, we got rules here, procedures.
I can't have you peeking over fences like a schoolboy.
- Maybe you'd like it more if I could fly. - You're way out of line, Turpin.
All I know is the tank had Mannheim's mitts all over it.
This department's gonna collar that dog if
I have to grab a leash and drag him myself.
Look sharp. Here it comes.
All units, radio alarm received from the 4:20 money train.
Repeat. Radio alarm received.
You coming? Or do you wanna wait for Superman?
Coming through!
Big train wreck. Someone was on the tracks...
and right now I wish it was the guy who built this stupid elevator!
Hey, Superman! Over here!
Come and get it!
They're working for Mannheim. Let's get the SCU tanks and...
And what, knock down his walls? Oh, the judge'll love that.
- We gotta hit while the money's hot. - We don't know what we're up against.
Dan, listen. I wanna bring Superman in on this, officially.
You're kidding! Mannheim is mine, Maggie. My collar!
- Inspector, give it a rest. - All right.
You got your number-one man. Good luck.
Inspector Turpin, I believe.
Amazingly, you employed our weaponry quite well. My superior was pleased.
- Pleased enough to tell us who he is? - Pleased enough to give you this.
It emits a concentrated energy beam...
capable of destroying even the most invulnerable of targets.
Is that a fact?
Dan's a good soldier, Superman. Tough as a bulldog but not quite as patient.
- Think he'll come back? - If I had a dime for every time...
Dan Turpin threw in his badge, I'd make Lex Luthor look like a pauper.
Where the devil is he?
You don't think he'd try something foolish?
I'd count on it.
You know what having this gun means, Turpin?
- I can take it off your Christmas list? - I'm gonna own this town.
I'm gonna own the world.
With toys like these, who can stop me?
- Hey, this thing's going nuts. - It's an early-detection device.
- What's it detect? - Superman.
Well, here's our chance to give this little baby a workout.
Some grip, huh, Superman?
Guess I don't know my own strength.
Superman! You gotta get out! Mannheim's got some new weapon.
Strangest thing I've ever seen.
I think that hurt.
You know what's really amazing? I'm not even firing at full power.
Get ready to eat it, Superman.
Get off me!
Get off!
Kanto!
I'm just catching my breath. Go get him.
Wait. You've gotta help me. Give me something, some weapon.
You had your chance.
Not only is Mannheim out of business in Metropolis...
but we finally broke the back of Intergang once and for all.
We? Looks to me like Superman saved your skin again.
Other way around.
If it wasn't for Dan Turpin, I wouldn't be standing here tonight. Thanks.
Anytime, pal.
So tell us, where's Mannheim?
I think he's moved outside our jurisdiction.
- Where in God's name are we? - That depends.
Which god are you talking about?
Listen, I'm through with these games. I want some answers!
You gonna tell me who you work for?
- Welcome to Apokolips, Mr. Mannheim. - Who are you?
Your new lord and master. You may call me Darkseid.