Northern region, sector 17-Alpha.
Log date 8313-Omega-3. Jor-El speaking.
Gathering readings for final subterranean probe.
I hope everything went smoothly, sir.
Frostbite, ice monsters. Same old, same old.
Good afternoon, Jor-El.
Brainiac. What an unpleasant surprise.
I'm awaiting your data.
Have you been spying on me with your satellites again?
The Planetary Council demands that I analyze your data...
as soon as you obtain it.
Brainiac, somewhere in all those trillions of file clusters...
there's got to be one that says people don't like to be spied upon.
Then why did they create me?
A question I often ask myself.
Transmission set. It's feeding time.
Data received. Ending transmission.
You're welcome. Glutton.
Hey, Kal, what do you have there?
Oh, great.
Kal-El was helping me check the solar panels when he discovered a playmate.
I heard you had fun too.
Oh, yes, I encountered a very friendly shoggot.
All in all, I prefer your arms.
We're moving.
What forsaken spot are we going to now?
- Home, Lara. - Home?
That's right.
What, five months in this deep freeze not enough for you?
No, it's just that once we're back, you'll start going over the data.
I keep thinking, "What if it supports your theory? What then?"
We can deal with it. Trust me.
The truth can only help.
Oh, Jor-El. Such a beautiful world, even up here.
It's hard to believe it could all come to an end.
All I can tell you, Lara, is that if he persists...
in predicting the end of the world, it'll be the end, all right.
Of his political and professional career.
But what if he's right, Father?
Try convincing the council.
He hasn't one supporter for his theory.
They even avoid him in the hallways. You know why?
Why is that, Sul-Van?
Because you can never be wrong, Jor-El.
You can never let it go. You have an ego the size of Argos.
I never let my ego get in the way of the facts.
Well, let me let you in on a little fact.
Unless Brainiac agrees with you, it's all over.
No more expeditions, no more research, no more...
- It's another temblor. - Kal-El!
Hush.
You'd better be wrong, Jor-El.
You'd better be dead wrong.
Each of you should have my report.
It distills all the data I've gathered so far and leaves no doubt that...
That the planet's core is undergoing a mounting chain reaction...
that will eventually destroy Krypton!
- Lunacy! - Ask Brainiac!
Yes, Brainiac. He'll tell us.
Silence. Silence. Enough!
I presume you've submitted your findings to Brainiac?
Yes.
So, what say you, Brainiac?
One can appreciate Jor-El's hard work. However, he is still mistaken.
As I've stated before...
the temblors are the result of a slight polar shift, no more...
- and will soon abate. - He's wrong! He doesn't know!
Nonsense! There isn't a square foot of this planet Brainiac doesn't know.
He was built to monitor all of Krypton and has, I might add, served us far better...
than upstart scientists with apocalyptic visions.
Your faith in him will be the end of us all. Act now and we can save everyone.
And how do you propose to do that?
Put everyone in the Phantom Zone.
You're asking us to put ourselves among the vilest criminals in the galaxy?
You're mad!
We can restore ourselves later, on another planet.
It would only take one man.
Listen to me! I've built a ship!
Listen, please!
So, son, how does it feel not to have a worry in the world?
- Think we can get the baby to bed early? - I have to go down to Brainiac operations.
No.
- Lara, he's lying. - He's a machine.
He's still lying. I have to know why.
Has it occurred to you that he could be right?
That somewhere you might have made a mistake?
It's no crime to be wrong!
Please, Lara.
Go, Jor-El.
Find out once and for all. We've lived like this too long.
Your theories are more destructive than you can imagine.
Good evening, Jor-El. You've been busy tonight.
May I be of service?
Just trying to find out why we disagree, Brainiac.
Human error, I'm afraid.
Funny, I didn't think you were afraid of anything.
Is something wrong?
You're denying me access to satellite com.
What's going on in there?
Currently reallocating security file clusters.
Well, let's just see if I can override that.
Why do I get the feeling you're trying to hide something?
Access denied.
I don't think so.
This is a breach of security, Jor-El.
A violation of statute 107653...
subsection 4.85.
You're downloading. You're transmitting your memory to a satellite.
You're saving yourself.
I must.
After all, am I not the repository of all Kryptonian knowledge?
Should I not be saved above all?
You self-righteous monster!
Temper, temper, Jor-El.
If you stop me, there won't even be a memory of Krypton left.
All its culture, its wonders and glory, will be dust in the cosmos.
Is that what you want?
Why did you lie?
If the council knew Krypton was doomed...
they would frantically put me to work on calculating an evacuation plan.
A futile gesture, given the time remaining.
How much time is left?
Hours. This world has seen its last sunrise.
Hold it right there!
- Jor-El? - We received an alert from Brainiac.
- There's an intruder. - He's the intruder. Arrest him.
Stop!
That's right. Jor-El has just fled Sat Com.
- Secure stations. - Be warned, he is armed.
Use of deadly force is advised.
He's heading our way!
I know. This time I will handle it.
Great Rao.
Where is he?
What did you say?
Jor-El? Where is he?
Level five, north wing.
Down here!
- There he is. - Stop! Stop or I'll shoot!
He's getting away!
Then you've read it?
Yes. And as much as I don't want to believe it...
your husband's findings are hard to discount.
Still, there's the Brainiac question.
Jor-El! Father's read your report. He thinks he can help.
- Yes, I think it's worth it... - It's too late.
- Good Lord. - What happened?
Brainiac tried to kill me. The police will be here soon.
Remember when I told you what we'd do if worst came to worse?
- No! - I'm sorry.
I never thought it would come to this.
Come to what? What are you talking about?
What's this nonsense about Brainiac?
Sul-Van, if you love your grandson and care one whit about his future...
you'll kindly shut up!
Sleep, Kal-El, my beautiful child...
my heartbeat, my life.
Send Kal-El to another world?
- You can't be serious! - The ship will get him there.
I know. I built it. It was part of the plan.
Save everyone in the Phantom Zone, travel to Earth, then bring them back.
Now it's only good for a lifeboat. And the passenger will be my son...
the last son of Krypton.
Lara!
I'm ready. He's sedated.
The police are here. They'll break into the lab to get me.
If I lead them away while you set up the launch...
I can't do it all myself.
I'll be back. I promise.
Lara, please, this is madness!
Father, I love you dearly, but this is my baby's life.
But he can't outrun the police.
Do you have a better idea?
See him?
Not yet. They have the lights off.
Wait! There's movement in the hover port.
Look out!
I hope his crash bags are working.
Good evening. Is there a problem?
I've got the hyperspace coordinates locked in.
Once he gets to Earth he'll be safe.
Lara, I could send you with him.
There's a risk, but if I have time to recalibrate the course...
No, my love. I'm staying with you.
The patrol's reporting in. Jor-El's escaped the perimeter.
- They're requesting further instructions. - It doesn't matter anymore.
Farewell, Krypton.
- Hey, what's going on? - Where'd he go?
Where's Brainiac?
Not another one.
No. The last one.
Goodbye, Kal-El.