Holy Christmas! What was that?
Over here, Martha. Martha?
Martha? Martha?
You'll wake him.
Martha, what are you doing?
Put that thing back. We don't know where it came from.
He's not a thing, Jonathan. He's a baby. A little baby.
Who would put a baby in a spaceship?
That's just my point. Could be Russian.
- A sputnik baby. - Oh, really!
Maybe he's one of ours.
- You think NASA's missing a kid? - I don't care where he came from.
All I know is, he needs us, Jonathan. Look how he's reaching out to you.
Cute little fella.
Got a good grip too.
What do you think of the name Christopher?
Now, Martha, let's discuss this.
- Or Kevin? - Martha!
Or Kirk?
I know. We can use my maiden name. What do you think of...?
Clark!
Clark Kent!
Yes, Ms. Stevenson?
Looks like you daydreamed your way to another perfect score.
Once again the boy genius performs to his usual standards.
And so did you, Miss Lang.
For a guy who just aced his midterms, you don't look too happy. What's wrong?
Oh, I don't know. Lately I'm feeling kind of weird.
You've always been weird, if you ask me.
Hey, it's Lana. The girl who's had a crush on you since we were 3.
- You can tell me. - It's just...
in the last few months, I've been hearing things.
Things I couldn't before. Like over there.
Jenny's telling Pete Ross her folks are out tonight.
That little tart! You heard that?
And I can see things too, like in the gym.
Ms. Stevenson's putting up decorations for the dance.
Someone should hold that ladder.
You're saying you can see through walls?
So how many times have you peeked into the girls' locker room?
- Lana! - I'm just kidding. Jeez!
It's not a joke, Lana. I'm going through a bad time.
I thought if anybody'd understand, it'd be...
- Listen! - What is it?
Call an ambulance! There's gonna be an accident!
How do you know? Clark!
Hey, stop!
- Mommy! - Annie!
Help me! Mom and Daddy!
Oh, my God! Clark! Clark!
Mommy!
Annie!
You're not even burned. How...?
I don't know.
Getting stronger every day, Pa.
Hello?
And that's not the half of it. Look.
It's getting hot.
- All you did was look at it. - I know.
Yes, dear, I'll tell him.
That was Lana. Third time tonight, Clark.
Won't you talk to her?
What can I say, Ma? I don't even know how it happened.
Suddenly I was running faster than I've ever run in my life.
I ripped the camper apart like cardboard. The fire never touched me.
I always felt different, even before you told me I was adopted...
but how is it possible to do this?
I think it's time, Martha.
We never showed you this, son.
I guess we didn't know how to explain it.
Still don't.
You know how some babies are found in baskets?
Well, this is how we found you.
You're kidding, right?
You're not.
- So where did I come from? - We don't know.
There wasn't much inside, just some blankets and this.
Never could get the darn thing open. Maybe you've got the magic touch.
What's happening?
- Kal-El? - Who?
Hello, son. You've activated the message we placed in your escape rocket.
- I am Jor-El. - And I am Lara.
We are your parents.
By the time you see this, our world will have been gone for many years.
You are the sole survivor of Krypton...
a planet similar to Earth in many ways. This was our home.
No. No, it can't be true.
- It's hurting him. - Let him be, Martha.
You may have discovered that you are much stronger and faster...
than a normal human being.
I am a normal human being!
Your Kryptonian body draws its strength from Earth's yellow sun.
It will give you abilities that no other human has.
I don't believe any of this.
Some people will fear you, perhaps even try to destroy you.
Despite this, you must never use your powers in anger.
Be brave, my son.
Remember who you are and the legacy you carry inside you.
We love you, Kal-El. Always.
It's not true.
I'm not a freak. I'm not.
I'm not!
Clark!
Clark, come back!
Yes!
Oh, yeah!
Ma! Pa!
Oh, Clark!
It's okay.
Metropolis can boast of many amazing sights..
The country's biggest bridge. The world's tallest building.
But now it may have its most astonishing sight: a guardian angel.
Just ask little Danitra Evans. She saw him.
I was fooling around the window when I lost my balance and fell.
Suddenly this big blue angel with red wings came down and caught me.
He put me on the ground and flew away.
You should've heard my mommy scream.
This is where they found Danitra, and that's where she fell from.
Thirty floors up. If it wasn't an angel that saved her, what was it?
Friendly pigeons.
What's the matter? Don't believe in angels?
It's TV, boys, just a trumped-up story to boost ratings.
And maybe sell some papers?
Chief, I spent a week on the docks with rats and frizzed hair...
exposing the biggest gun-smuggling ring in 10 years...
and what makes the front page?
Some sprouty, New Age, granola-crunching fluff piece on angels.
- What's next? Interviews with Bigfoot? - Good timing, Lois.
I want you to be the first to know I'm hiring a new guy on the city desk.
Is he cute?
- You tell me. - Oh, hi.
- Hello. - This is the guy, Lois.
- Clark Kent from Smallville. - Smallville? Never heard of it.
- Have you ever been to Kansas? - God, no.
I've been reading his stuff. It's good.
I thought maybe he could tag along with you to get the lay of the land.
I'd love to play den mother, but I got that Lexcorp story in half an hour.
Oh, yeah. The great and benevolent Mr. Luthor...
is demonstrating a new weapons system today.
Lex is Lois' beat, but I'm sure she won't mind...
having another set of eyes with her. Right, Lois?
Smallville, nothing against you, but even as a kid I never liked babysitting.
You wanna keep up, be quick.
- I'm no tour guide and I don't hold hands. - You won't have to worry about that.
Jimmy. Jimmy Olsen, say hello to Clark Kent.
- The new guy? - Yeah.
Nice to meet you. I'm Jimmy.
I work as a copy boy, but I'm a photographer.
- Good for you. - I'd like to show you my pictures.
- Well, not right... - They're hot, Mr. Kent, really.
I'm fearless. You can ask Miss Lane. She uses me all the time.
Bye.
So I see.
You sure my nose isn't shiny?
Angela, don't tell me you're actually covering real news.
What happened? Run out of alien abductees?
At least my network doesn't have to send two reporters...
to cover the same story.
You'll have to introduce us sometime.
- Thanks for the quote. - How did you get here so fast?
Oh, I just flew.
- What'd you get? - A shared byline, if you use it.
I apologize. You're not the rube hayseed I took you for.
Thanks. I think.
Ladies and gentlemen of the press...
at this time we invite everyone into the main hall for our special presentation.
The long-awaited debut of the next word in military defense:
The Lexoskel 5000.
Constructed from a patented alloy, the Lexo suit is virtually indestructible.
As seen in this footage against these automated tanks...
the Lexo suit stands up to heavy punishment...
and returns it in kind.
Guiding this suit is a single soldier...
made more powerful than an entire battalion.
And now, here's to the future, and the man who's created it, Lex Luthor.
Bet you this beats the dog-and-pony shows back home.
Time to crash the party, gentlemen.
Excuse me.
I'd like to say that I view the Lexo suit...
not as an instrument of war, but as an instrument to end war.
No way.
- It's him! - The guy with the cape!
Gentlemen, believe it or not, we are being tailed at 6 o'clock.
I don't know who he is or what he is, but he's all yours.
I've got him.
He's dust.