Come on, answer.
I told you before, I'm not coming out.
What part of that didn't you understand?
Earl, you've got to listen to reason.
I have listened to reason. My own.
- What'd he say? - We're gonna have to do it your way.
All right. Okay, move in.
For the love of Mike.
- He's probably got the place reinforced. - Let's find out.
Right flank, advance.
Get him to the hospital, now.
It's just a little singe, Maggie.
Inspector Sawyer, Professor Hamilton.
Perfect timing. The man inside's Earl Garver.
Used to work at STAR Labs.
Until he stole a radioactive isotope from us.
He sent this to the mayor today.
He says he used the isotope to make a bomb.
And he'll detonate it if we don't pay by tonight.
It could take out a square mile of the city.
Let's see if I can change his mind.
Where's the bomb, Garver?
Wherever it is, it's already ticking and concealed in lead.
So the real question is, where's my money?
I don't play those games.
Did he say anything, doctor?
It's a concussion. He'll be unconscious for the next day or two.
The bomb goes off in four hours.
Even I couldn't search the city in that time.
If I might make a suggestion...
there's someone who might be able to tell us exactly where that bomb is.
I think I understand how you feel, Superman.
If it'd happened to me, I'd be leery too.
That's not it. What you want to do could be more dangerous than a dozen bombs.
We'll take every possible precaution.
But right now, he's our only hope.
Why should I help you? You're the one who put me here.
Rudy, the whole city's in trouble.
Tell somebody who cares.
The bomb could blow up a huge area of Metropolis.
- What if that includes Stryker's Island? - What if it does?
Think I'd miss this life of mine? These four stinking walls?
You want me to go into his mind and find out where the bomb is.
No skin off my nose.
- But I want something in return. - What's that?
Something to help the time go faster.
And not a bunch of boring books, either.
I want cable, and the premium channels.
- All set, Rudy? - You bet.
Get that big screen warmed up for me.
Something's wrong.
Rudy, can you hear me? Did you find out where the bomb is?
I know where it is, all right.
But you still have to pay.
- Sounds like Garver. - Rudy?
Sorry, Emil. I've put Rudy on the back burner.
- You're cooking with Earl now. - What's happening?
The Parasite has somehow taken Garver's consciousness, not just his memories.
- How? - Garver's intellect, his ego...
his force of personality. It all must have combined to...
- What's it going to be? - You're still stuck here, Garver.
You don't even know where you are.
If that bomb goes off, there's a good chance you'll go with it. Both of you.
Come on, what're you waiting for? They got you.
Cooperate and they'll treat you real good.
You'll never get away, Garver.
The best-laid plans...
He thought nobody would stumble across his bomb here.
There's the wreck.
Once you find the sucker, I can disarm it.
- See anything? - No, there's too much debris.
We'll have to go in.
Let's make this a short visit.
You're just wasting your time. I mean, our time.
Perhaps if we work together, Rudy.
You know, double the will, double the strength?
A partnership.
Wouldn't work. In a couple of hours...
you'll be gone. That's the way it is with the Parasite.
I can't keep what I take.
Don't be so short-sighted.
Suppose I could find a way for the Parasite to retain the power it takes, forever.
Yeah, what if pigs could fly?
I'm serious. I can help you.
But you have to help me too. Come on.
This could be your last chance for freedom and power.
But maybe you'd prefer your cable television?
That's it, Rudy.
Guard.
What's the matter?
I feel so weak.
That's better.
It's not here. He's playing games with us.
No, he's buying time. We'd better get back.
What was...?
They're gone.
Both of them.
- My leg. - How's that feel?
- It feels so strange. - Someone's got to help me.
I'm really hurting.
Twenty minutes left.
He'll call.
- Yes? - This isn't a game of chicken anymore.
I still want the money. Fifty million in unsigned bearer bonds.
- Understand? - So far.
There's just one modification.
I want Superman to bring it to me...
- and I want him to come alone. Agreed? - Agreed.
Very good, Superman. Go to the old subway extension.
Enter by way of the north-side station. I'll be waiting.
Welcome, Superman.
If you're trying to use your x-ray vision, you'll find the rock marbled with lead.
Now, go up the tracks and follow the Y to the right.
You'll find a pit. It's the reason they stopped construction.
It's so deep, I doubt whether even you could see the bottom.
Now, if you look to your left...
you'll see an exit sign.
Deposit the bonds there, and proceed to the center of the chamber...
where you'll find my little toy.
Hit the following keys:
Three, five, nine, one, then enter.
Did you really think I'd settle for money when I could have your power too?
You see, I've already gotten some of it.
Only a first course.
Time for the entrée.
The longer we do this, the weaker you'll get.
Then perhaps we should call an end to the stalemate?
What are you doing?
Two minutes. That's all you've got.
Now come over here and hold out your hand like a good boy.
Shut it off. You'll be killed too.
Will I? My real body is miles north of here...
resting peacefully in an ambulance.
Hear that, Rudy? He's willing to sacrifice you.
It'll never come to that.
He's already taken control of your body, Rudy.
What do you think he's going to do with your mind?
You gonna crowd me out? Is that where this is going?
Rudy, you're a loser without me.
- It's this or the cell. - Some choice.
What are you...?
Fight him, Rudy.
He's changed the code.
Rudy?
Cat's got his tongue.