Yeah, we lost them at Third and Shuster.
They were heading for the warehouse district.
- Yeah. - Put her there.
- All right. - Nice going.
We scored bigtime.
Hello, boys.
Who's that?
I'm ever so sorry to spoil your nice celebration...
but I have a very important message for your boss, Mr. Mannheim.
Please tell him the Toyman is calling time-out on his little games...
and don't be tardy.
Grab Pinocchio before he gets out.
Hey, come here. Come back here.
Johnny.
- Let's get out of here. - We can't, Spider, it's locked.
Get back in the car.
- When's it gonna stop? - Don't worry. These walls are solid steel.
We're gonna die.
- Somebody, help! - Help!
- Help! Get help. - We're gonna get greased.
Hey, it stopped.
We're safe.
- Hey, watch it. - What's going on?
It was... It was Toyman.
Calling time-out.
Tell Bruno, the Toyman.
What a smashup.
Odd thing. I heard it was parked at the time.
Where, at a monster truck rally?
Look on the bright side. At least you look good in silver.
Miss Lane, excuse me if I don't shake hands.
So, what's the lowdown on this Toyman character?
I hear he's got it in for your boss, Bruno Mannheim.
What boss? I happen to be a independent agent.
You're wasting your time, doll face. I'll see you in two to five.
Where to now, Miss Lane, the Planet?
Actually, I was thinking about a picnic in the park.
Testing, one, two, three. Testing, one, two, three.
Is this on? And it is my honor to dedicate Mannheim Park...
to the true heroes of Metropolis, our children.
Sounds good, Mr. Mannheim.
Enjoying a leisurely afternoon...
or have you been listening to the police band again?
Perry assigned me the park opening. Why, what's up?
- You haven't heard about the Toyman? - Who?
Nice try, Smallville, but this one's mine.
Mr. Mannheim, Lois Lane, Daily Planet.
Any comments on this morning's armored-car hijacking?
Why would I have a comment? I'm a legitimate businessman.
Of course. And you have no knowledge of someone calling himself the Toyman?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I'm a respected citizen, and I don't appreciate your little insinuations.
Look out!
I see a page-one photo.
Look out! They're coming back.
They're heading this way.
Wait.
You wanna get killed too?
What happened?
Looks like it just broke apart.
Get me out of here.
Read it and weep, Kent. It's all here.
The attacks on the armored car and Mannheim, and as a finishing touch...
a preliminary profile on the perp by a noted police psychiatrist.
- Based on what? - He uses toys as weapons.
We're talking about a guy with very serious issues.
Like the shrink says:
"An emotionally stunted amoral narcissist with paranoid delusions..."
"Desperately seeking external validation through antisocial behavior."
That creep made me into a laughingstock. How could you let him get so close?
You wouldn't let us in the park, boss, remember?
You was afraid we'd scare the kids.
He's out there somewhere, the slimy, little weasel.
Thinks he's gonna make me pay.
What?
What are you waiting for? Shoot it.
- It's a big ducky. - Shoot it!
Get out of here.
How does the saying go?
"Bubble, bubble, toil and trouble."
Yeah, it's you, Winslow. Same creepy voice.
I don't know how you came back from the dead, but it's gonna be a short visit.
Ashes, ashes, we all fall down.
Yeah. Mannheim's still missing, chief.
Dinner's here, bye.
Let it be flowers, please.
Hello, I'm Princess Nighty-Night.
Nighty-night.
Oh, Miss Lane?
Can you come out and play?
Still haven't heard from her?
- You think something's wrong? - I don't know.
First Mannheim's missing, now Lois.
If I only knew what the link was between Mannheim and Toyman.
You can cross-index with this system...
like "Mannheim" and "Toyman." Mind if I take a shot?
I'm so glad you decided to stay, Miss Lane. We're going to have a whole lot of fun.
Why me, Toyman?
Because of those lies you wrote about me in your little paper.
This time, I want you to get it right.
- Nothing yet. - Try "Mannheim" with just "toy."
Toymaker Sentenced to Ten Years.
Hey, look at this.
"Toymaker sentenced to 10 years."
It's a very sad story, one most people have forgotten.
Once upon a time...
there was a kindly man who loved nothing more than making toys.
He wanted to build the most wonderful toy factory in all the world.
Only he had no money to pay for it.
Then one day, a man came along.
A very bad man.
He offered to pay for the factory under one condition.
"The factory became a numbers racket front.
Bruno Mannheim was named as a suspect, but was never indicted.
Only the toymaker, Winslow Schott, was convicted."
Sounds like Bruno played him for a patsy.
The bad man watched and laughed...
while the police locked the kindly toymaker in the dungeon forever.
2-1, Schott's our Toyman.
I don't think so, Clark. Take a look.
- His obituary. - Poor guy. He died before making parole.
Yeah, but he had a survivor.
That's right, Miss Lane. The toymaker had a son.
But without his father...
the poor little boy was bounced from foster home to foster home...
like a little toy that nobody wanted.
A childhood is a terrible thing to lose, Miss Lane.
But I'm getting mine back.
With a vengeance.
Now the real fun begins.
You're going to play...
reporter.
This time, I want you to take good notes.
You just made the biggest mistake of your life, you miserable little freak.
I mean it, Schott. I got friends.
They'll find you.
On the other hand, maybe we can make a deal.
- No peeking now. - Please, don't.
- You can't be serious. - Deadly serious, Miss Lane.
Playtime is over. Ready.
Aim.
Hey.
You broke my toys.
You spoiled my fun.
Little boys shouldn't play with sharp objects.
Who invited you, Superman?
Superman? Superman, is that you?
Don't think I haven't prepared a surprise for you.
Here's something you can't break.
Very funny, Toyman.
Maybe you should read the warning.
Dopey Doh is a lethal biogenic organism.
Contact with the skin can prove fatal.
It won't stop growing until it asphyxiates its host.
- Not for children under 3. - Lois, no. Don't touch it.
- What can I do? - Get back.
Find something to hide behind. Hurry.
My playhouse!
Cheater.
You think you've got me, but I still get a free game.
- You sure you're okay? - Yeah.
He was a sicko, Kent, but I can't help feeling sorry for him.
He was a loser, a walking freak show, like his old man.
- This is one funeral I'll skip. - I'm not sure there's gonna be a funeral.
My people still haven't found the body. However, they did find this.