Feel anything?
Nothing. I feel fine.
Now, this metal's too hard to be lead.
Titanium-lead alloy?
Exactly. And the helmet is leaded polycarbonate.
Materials that will not only withstand Kryptonite...
but, well, I took into account the type of day you'll likely put the suit through.
You make it sound like I go looking for trouble.
Hey, Rudy, today or what?
You screw this up, you can forget about me paying that bookie of yours.
I know, Mr. Lebeau.
Jeez! I thought you knew how to work that thing.
- Sorry. - You there, hold it!
- Oh, it's you, Rudy. - Hey, what's up?
- You get cleared for machinery? - Yeah. I'm a forklift operator now.
And who's your friend, huh? Doing some early Christmas shopping?
- He... - That's all right, Rudy.
Maybe I can clear all this up.
No, don't.
You'll get us put away for good.
Speak for yourself. I'm not getting caught.
Emergency. Fire. Loading bay two.
Hold it.
Hey, stop!
- Help, help! - Somebody get help!
Over here!
Oh, please stop!
Messed me up for the last time, you stupid little parasite.
Hey, slow down!
Mr. Lebeau, stop the truck! Please, stop!
Please, Martin... help me.
Adios, freak.
I just can't believe it. Wimpy Rudy Jones?
And there's no telling what was in those drums.
He ain't kidding. Half the stuff the prof whips
up, folks would kill to get their hands on.
This is four-two heading north on Old Ocean Road.
- Hey, Gina, is that you? - Edna, you on the graveyard shift tonight?
I was just...
You trying to get killed?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
What's that in your hand? Drop it!
Four-two, please respond. Where'd you go? Gina, you okay?
All units, request assistance on Old Ocean Road.
This is four-two. Negative on the assistance. I'm fine, Edna.
10-4. You gave me a scare there. All units, disregard call for assistance.
Edna? Where the heck did I get Edna?
She must've been delirious when our boys found her.
Said something about being attacked by a purple monster.
Was its name Barney?
You here to make ha-ha, kid, or take pictures?
Guess that's a no.
Wouldn't touch that if I were you.
Right, thanks.
Did you ID Rudy Jones' partner from the security cameras?
Yeah. Name's Martin Lebeau. He's a known fence.
Last we knew, he was living down by the docks in Hob's Bay.
Don't you recognize me, Marty?
It's your old doormat, Rudy Jones.
Rudy, you ought to be in a hospital. You need help.
Help? I never felt better in my life.
Hey.
It's fantastic, Marty. I should be thanking you.
When I touch somebody, I get strong. I absorb their energy.
But more than that, I hear their thoughts.
I know what they know.
Really, words don't describe it.
Here, let me show you.
Rudy? Rudy Jones?
Put that man down.
Sure.
What's happened to you?
I don't know. It's as if I've turned into some kind of monster.
- Can you help me? - Let me take you back to STAR.
- Maybe Professor Hamilton can treat you. - Okay, Superman.
- Just don't hurt me. - I won't. Hang on.
Oh, you can count on it.
Man, what a rush.
So that's what real power feels like.
- Good heavens. - What is that?
What's he done to Superman?
Looks like you still got some juice left in you.
You all see that?
That's the new me.
That's what Rudy Jones can do.
Now tell your friends...
there's a new Superman in town.
Since this morning the thing that was once Rudy Jones has been sighted...
throughout the city, taking what he pleases
and driving citizens into their homes in fear.
I spoke personally with Professor Emil Hamilton of STAR Labs...
to find out how a simple janitor could clean out Metropolis.
The chemical Mr. Jones stole was developed
to catalyze energy absorption in human cells.
But clearly, he was exposed to far greater quantities...
than we'd ever tested on living subjects.
And now that this Parasite has sucked up all of Superman's powers...
how much longer until he sucks our city dry?
Wow. That sounds pretty bad.
Just fighting a bit of a cold.
No. I mean this Parasite thing.
I wonder where Superman is.
I'm sure he'd be here if he could.
Clark Kent.
That's right.
Thanks, we'll be right over. Let's take a ride. There may be some good news.
Like candy from a baby.
Huh? What gives?
Then about an hour ago, I just started feeling better.
My doctor says I can go home tomorrow.
Then the Parasite's drain is temporary.
Hey, you figure Superman's out there feeling better too?
I wouldn't be surprised.
Given the officer's recovery, Perry...
I bet we'll be seeing Superman anytime now.
Me? Yeah, my cold's doing better.
In fact, I thought I'd change and go out tonight.
Right. So long.
Good to see you again, Superman.
Or should I say "Clark"?
That's right, Kent. I got your powers, I got your thoughts...
and I got your secret.
- Comfy? - Where are we?
Why don't you use your x-ray vision?
I can't.
Ah, shucks.
Well, all you need to know is it ain't your apartment.
It's mine now.
Fits my new ritzy lifestyle.
When I don't go to work, people will come looking for me.
"Hi, Perry? That cold of mine is acting up again.
I think I'm going to be out sick for a while."
You see, Supes, you're my new meal plan.
Figure I'll keep you here, pop back every 12 hours or so for a recharge.
In fact, it's feeding time right about now.
It's been a week, people. This is a newspaper, we need facts.
Where does Parasite disappear to? Is Superman alive or dead?
And where the heck is Kent? Is he still out sick?
I was just noticing...
Parasite always flies south, along the coast.
That's toward S.T.A.R, where he used to work.
The police thought of that the first day.
Besides, it's not like the guy's going back to work.
But maybe the cops haven't checked out STAR lately.
Somebody should go down there.
And somebody should get his photos to
layout before he misses the evening edition.
- But, chief... - Okay, where were we?
Troupe, what's your excuse? Weaver, justify your existence. Lois...
So much is written on what Parasite does, I
thought if I looked around his workspace...
maybe I could learn about Rudy Jones, the man.
It's just that you seem kind of young for a reporter...
Mr. White.
Yeah, I know my age surprises people.
Did start out pretty young.
- Paper route at 7... - Jimmy.
Well, I guess you can't do any harm in here.
I'll be right outside if you need me.
All right.
I mean, great, thanks.
Oh, yeah, great.
Stop the presses. Olsen gets exclusive on empty broom closet.
S-O-S.
No way.
Superman.
Jimmy, quick. Where are we?
You don't know? You're in STAR Labs.
The cellar, or something.
Go up and get help. You can't stay here.
He'll be back any minute.
I can get you out of here.
He's back. Quick, hide.
Good evening, dinner.
Enjoy your night out?
You better believe it.
My whole life, everybody's been stepping on me.
Now I'm the one with all the power.
And what have you done with all this power, Rudy?
Gave the world the raw deal they gave you? Feel like you've gotten even yet?
What's with the chatter all of a sudden? You're up to something.
Somebody's here.
Cute, kid.
Hey, Rudy.
Clear out of here now.
Playing hide-and-seek now? Come on, Kent, this is beneath you.
You're wasting your time.
I'm still stronger.
Maybe, but for how long?
You've got a point. Guess I ought to end this quick.
Time to say good night.
We'll keep him here until a special cell is completed at Stryker's.
He's been like this ever since his fight with Superman.
I doubt he knows his own name, let alone any of what's transpired.
We're disturbing him. We should go.
Yeah. Doesn't look like he'll be giving interviews anytime soon.