Look at that. The only thing holding...
- that dress up is faith. - Hey, come on.
- Someone's coming! - It's Lex! She's with him!
Great!
Lex, over here.
It's the paparazzi wolves trying to get a scent of Lex's latest lady friend.
Not that I read the gossip columns or anything...
but I hear they're quite an item. Maybe I should warn her about him.
- No. - Who is she?
The trendy fashion designer, L.L.
L.L.? Lana Lang?
- Lana! - L.L., over here!
Give us a smile.
- What a couple. - Lana, are the jewels real?
Everything is real, boys.
Lana.
Sorry, no more questions. I am here to work.
- What's Lana doing with Luthor? - You know her?
- We used to date. - Get out.
- In high school. - She's certainly come up in the world.
From Smallville, I mean.
- Lana! - Marco, darling. Save me some dessert.
Mr. Luthor.
Mr. Eelan. Make me happy.
The buyers are definitely interested, but they insist on a demonstration.
Fine. Arrange it.
Finished. You look fabulous. Now go out there and wow the crowd.
We like your dress.
Thank you.
And we'd like it now!
Hey! What do you think you're doing? Put me down!
Lana?
Let me go, you fashion-disabled Amazon!
Keep your mouth shut, missy.
We got a room where you're gonna slip into something less expensive.
Look out!
Maybe you ladies haven't heard about me.
Yeah, we heard.
You like to save people.
I imagine you hear this a lot, but, thanks.
Hold on.
Red, blue, yellow. Primary, but it works in a superhero-ish kind of way.
- Let me guess, Martha sewed it for you. - What?
- By the way, Clark, how are the folks? - Lana!
Over here, men.
Lana, are you all right?
I'm fine, Lex, thanks to Superman.
You know, this is the first time I've been happy that alien showed up.
Me too.
- I still don't see how you knew. - Oh, come on, Clark.
Just because I'm gorgeous doesn't mean I'm stupid.
I saw you do the amazing things in high school...
then Superman shows up in Metropolis the same time as you do.
How do you know when I showed up in Metropolis?
I've been keeping track. Root beer float?
- See? I didn't forget. - Lana, I've come to warn you.
About Lex. I know. Everyone has.
Powerful men get those kinds of reputations.
And I like powerful men.
Lana, this is no joke. That man Luthor was speaking with tonight...
he's a known arms dealer, responsible for the deaths of thousands of people.
And you think Lex is buying weapons through him?
No. Selling.
I think Luthor's got a stockpile he's trying to unload.
Well, you're wrong. Besides, I know how to handle Lex.
I know how to handle most men, in fact.
It's only Clark Kent I've ever had any trouble pinning down.
- For me, Lana, just be careful. - For you, Clark, anything.
I just want to know what Superman was doing in your apartment last night.
And I want to know what business you have spying on me.
Are you jealous?
- Let's just say I'm curious. - He wanted to be sure I was all right.
And to warn me about you. He said you were a bad boy.
And what did you say?
I said I liked bad boys.
- Your 11:30's here, Mr. Luthor. - Show him in. Business.
- Well? - The merchandise is ready to ship.
When the client agrees to the terms, the deal will go through.
I've arranged for a demonstration. I think they'll be impressed.
- Where? - Down by the old Carter Mill, 1:00.
I'm telling you, she heard everything. I should take her for a nice little ride.
- No! - But she was listening.
Of course she was listening.
A woman like that is going to be curious about things, especially me.
Anyway, what does it matter? She couldn't possibly have understood what it meant.
- Hello. - Clark, it's Lana. You were right.
And the deal's going down today.
The rifle shoots a microwave beam, exciting electrons to their highest state.
- Nothing's happening. - Wait.
I'm gonna like this gun.
I think it's deer season.
Sorry. It's only open season on terrorists.
I should warn you, it's been done.
The terrorists are keeping their mouths shut.
But those weapons had Luthor written all over them.
I wish I knew where he was keeping them stockpiled.
Don't forget, you still have me.
Oh, no, I don't. It's too dangerous.
- But we make such a perfect team. - No.
I could be your trusty sidekick, your Dr. Watson, your Batgirl.
- Definitely no. - I still have feelings for you, Clark.
I knew it the minute I saw you. Don't pretend you didn't feel something.
Let me prove to you how good we could be together.
Lana, I don't...
I've seen enough.
I'm glad you could finally make time for me, Lana.
I was beginning to think you were trying to avoid me.
You're not getting rid of me, Lex. I'm sticking to you like glue.
Then I'll see you tonight for dinner. Mercy will pick you up at 7.
It's Eelan.
- Yes? - There's a problem.
I don't care. I want you in Central City waiting.
The client expects the shipment to be ready tonight. There'd better not be...
any surprise visitors this time.
Hello?
Clark, I've been trying to reach you all day.
The reason you haven't been able to find the merchandise in Metropolis is...
it isn't in Metropolis. It's in Central City.
- Our friend has a factory there. - How do you know this?
I overheard him. Oh, Clark, this is how it could be forever.
Me ferreting out crooks, you catching them.
Lana, I told you I didn't want you spying on Lex anymore.
I wasn't. I was sitting right next to him.
- Lana. - That must be the limo. Gotta run.
Remember, Central City is 500 miles away. I suggest you schedule a flight.
Lana, wait!
Sorry I'm late.
- Where's Mercy? - Sorry, no mercy tonight.
Just heard from Eelan. Should I cancel your dinner reservations?
Get out.
Get out!
Let me go, you maniac! Help! Help!
That won't do you any good, Ms. Lang. Nobody's here.
The factory is automated because of the lead fumes.
There's so much lead residue on the walls, Superman couldn't see through them.
Even if he weren't in Central City.
You're right, Eelan. I couldn't see you, but my hearing's pretty good.
What are you doing here? I thought you'd be in Central City.
You overheard too much. It was too easy.
I knew Central City had to be a setup, so I followed you.
Hurry. You'll be safe in here.
He calls this safe?
Yes!
Help! Help!
Clark! Clark!
You're a mess.
Lana! Going somewhere?
To Paris for the unveiling of the spring line. I think my strengths...
- are in fashion, not crime-fighting. - Lana, you know I really care about you.
- You're like... - Clark Kent, if you say I'm like...
a sister to you, I'm going back to Lex.
Sorry. But I know you'll find that special person someday.
So will you. You deserve it.
- Someone quiet, understanding, patient. - Hey, Smallville.
Get your tail in here. Perry's got an assignment for us.
Remember, if you ever change your mind about me, feel free to fly on up any time.
Kent!
Coming.