- Well, any ideas, guys? - Let's start with this.
Clang crash.
Kind of slow, aren't they?
They're still learning.
Let's go.
Still faster than Hawkman.
Hey!
I'll bet this was our ride in.
Now, it's our ride out.
Ugh! Oww!
That felt... different.
Thud.
We're out of here.
Boom.
You know how to fly this?
Wayne Tech has five of these from the invasion
the spoils of war.
Whoa!
Company's coming.
Vroom
clank.
We need a place to regroup where they can't find us.
Can't they trace this vehicle?
I've shut off all tracking devices.
But my android can still find us by reading our minds.
Not if we don't know where we're going.
Everyone, shut your eyes.
- No peeking. - What about you?
My cowl's lined with electronics.
The only thing he'll read is static.
You can look now, I've activated an electronic grid
to jam their mind-reading.
Zap.
- They're already here! - Batgirl, hold your fire.
You knew she was here?
I asked her to be on standby, just in case.
Okay, so, I guess this is where I ask
have I missed anything?
Whoa. Lots.
Even without their powers
the Justice League proved problematic.
Especially the one called Batman.
I told you he was the biggest threat.
We have to deal with them quickly.
You have to. I did my part, helping you steal their powers.
Now, do yours by giving me the knowledge of the Universe.
So be it.
Huh.
Thud
beep.
Magnificent.
Scour the city. Find the League.
'We cannot let them disrupt our mission.'
'As long as they remain alive, they are a danger.'
zap.
A kryptonite ray.
Boom.
This one fires yellow powder.
Well, what gives, partner?
You've prepared weapons to use against us.
Only as a precautionary measure.
Blame it on me, guys.
I went temporarily renegade
the last time we worked together.
This might have saved a lot of time and trouble.
- I can't even feel it. - Your android will.
I figure since they have your powers
they should have your weaknesses, too.
You better be ready to use those
'cause I don't think there's going to be any time
for target practice.
'And no one knows why the Justice League'
'is attacking Gotham.'
swoosh.
They've already covered half the city looking for us.
These comlinks will allow us to communicate anywhere in Gotham.
And these tracking devices can pick up
each of your powers' energy signatures.
Ready to jet!
Alright. Here's where we split up.
If we're gonna get back your powers
we have to capture each android intact.
We'll distract them while you attack.
You'll only get one shot, so make it count.
Vroom Can't this buggy go any faster?
I think they'll find us before we find them.
Screech
beep beep beep Looking for someone?
Click
pew Whoa!
Whoa-a-a-a!
Unh.
They're improving.
This will change the complexion.
Crash.
Okay. So, now how do we get our powers back?
You have no idea, do you?
I'm working on it.
Boom boom.
You're not gonna let me get away with that, are you?
Whoosh.
Droids. Not the sharpest tools in the shed.
Superman? We found someone we'd like you to meet.
As in, now!
Beep beep beep.
I got sunshine wrapped up. What about you?
- This one's gonna be tricky. - I'll calm him down.
If that yellow washes off, he's back in business.
- I got him covered. - How's yours, Hawkman?
A little on the crispy side, but still in one piece.
Huh?
They're stronger than we think.
Where did he go?
He's got my invisible power.
You got so many, it's hard to keep track.
- Ugh! - Arrow!
Thud.
Sorry I have to use this.
Ahh!
Ah-h-h-h!
Clang.
Hu-ahh!
What?
Batman! I think the chest is a weak spot.
It breaks through to the energy source.
Bats! Give me a hand.
Crash.
And I'm back, Jack.
Everyone! The chest is their Achilles heel.
'Sorry, pal.'
boom.
Your secret's out.
You read my mind.
Thud.
Happy landings.
'Hey, robo-ripoff.'
Time to return what you borrowed.
Huh!
Now, we finish this.
Crash.
Looks like Hugo got his wish.
Absorbing all that knowledge has overloaded
his cerebral cortex.
If that's the shortcut to total knowledge
I'll stick with middle school.
We took care of The Joining and Strange took care of himself.
Game over.
Not... over.
The superdroids were just the advance force.
The real invasion is about to begin.
The Joining invasion ship is on its way to Earth.
Looks like we're the greeting committee.
I'm patching into the League's satellite to monitor the fight.
- So, what do we do? - Make popcorn?
Think they've spotted us yet?
I'd say yes.
Kryptonite and yellow energy!
They came prepared.
Boom boom boom boom boom boom boom.
There's too many. They're getting past.
Hey, where did Hawkman go?
It's gonna be a street fight.
- My turf. - What are you gonna do?
Just watch me, kid.
Come on!
Swoosh.
Fire when ready.
Boom.
That mothership is endless. The attack-bots never stop!
- I should get out there. - 'Wait.'
Strange was communicating with the Joining
through this system. It has to connect with the mothership.
If we had the right code we could shut down
the invasion from here.
Yeah, but who knows what the code could be?
He does.
You're right, if Strange has all the knowledge of the Universe
he knows how to defeat the Joining.
Thud
boom.
Batgirl.
I need you to set up the signal, now.
Me? But I'm still trying to figure out the remote on my TV.
Boom
crash.
Not so big and bad now.
Whirr
zap.
Uh-oh. Extreme makeover!
Hey. How come I know how to do this?
I'm in your mind, relaying instructions from Strange.
Whoa. We need to talk personal boundaries after this.
Boom.
Ahh!
Snap.
I'm sending you the last of the code.
My typing teacher should see me now.
Upload, now!
Thud
zap
boom boom boom.
'Clean-up on aisle one.'
- So much for the Joining. - Now, the melting.
No sign of any other ships in our star system.
Earth is safe again.
While Hugo Strange becomes Arkham's most peaceful patient.
Even with our powers
'we couldn't have done this without you.'
Well, some of us need powers and some of us don't.
Man, we've got the coolest clubhouse.
We?
Yeah. Junior Justice League, teen division.
Nice try.