Don't let all this kiddie stuff fool you.
Toyman's not playing around. I learned that the hard way.
A psychiatrist could make a whole career out of this guy.
Just be careful.
Whirr
swish swish clang clang
whack crash
whack
zap boom
beep beep beep boom.
Superman, I've been expecting you and your masked friend, too.
Wanna play?
You're right about the psychiatrist.
Are you making fun of me?
That's not very nice.
Bark zap.
Hey! Who's been playing with my toys?
Huh?
Superman?
Superman.
'So, Central City fairground, huh?'
You sure you want in?
I mean, even I haven't been able to stop this guy.
Then maybe it's gonna take a little more than just speed.
Oh. You think you can do better, huh?
Fine, but don't get in my way.
Slowpoke.
How much trouble could some mirror guy be anyway?
What?
I just hate it when they bunch up in the back like this
don't you?
Hello, Flash. You found me. Congratulations.
You're Mirror Master, and this is a hall of mirrors.
Anyone with the IQ of a housefly could have found you.
That's what I was counting on.
Zap.
He's goin' from mirror to mirror.
He gets in through his reflection somehow.
There's no way to stop him.
Wanna bet?
Whoosh.
Take away his reflection, he's got no place to go.
Whoosh Do you hear somethin'?
What, you mean like a "thank you" maybe?
No. I mean..
This.
I don't know what kind of gas it is, but..
Flash..
And then he was gone.
I woke up about an hour later and..
You know, you don't seem surprised.
Almost the identical thing happened to Superman and me.
They got Superman, too? What's goin' on?
That's something I'd like to know as well.
Two of the Justice League's most powerful members
gone without a trace. How could that happen?
Wait a minute. You're not blaming us for this, are you?
'It's nobody's fault.'
Hawkman's missing, too, almost a week now.
So one by one, they're taking us.
Whoever they are.
But they didn't take Green Arrow or me.
And they sure had the opportunity.
We were both out cold.
- Yes, but... - But what?
Superman, Flash and Hawkman all have superpowers.
But you and Batman, well..
We're chopped liver.
- That's what you're saying, - No, but...
'Cause if you don't think we can hold our own with any of you...
We need to get back to Central City.
What for?
To see if we can dig up any other clues.
Yeah. We should. That's a great idea.
- I'll get my jet. - No need.
Zap.
Feel like a kid in the back seat of his parents' SUV.
Just don't ask me if we're there yet.
I don't sense anyone down there
but I'll scout it out just in case.
And we'll head over to the hall of mirrors.
Clatter.
It's a common sleeping gas
but the valves were activated by a radio signal.
Very sophisticated.
What are those things?
Don't know, but they're definitely gonna be a problem.
Aah! Aah!
Thud.
Arrow!
Crash
hiss.
Where are they?
Gone, both of 'em.
Too far.
Click click click
beep beep beep.
- 'Batman.' - Huh! Yeah.
- 'Got anything yet?' - 'No.'
It feels like I've been going over this remote relay for days.
'You have.'
There must be something wrong with me.
I-I can barely keep my eyes open.
This thing's not like anything I've ever seen before.
- 'How are you doin'?' - 'Goin' around in circles.'
You know, Superman and Flash might not have been our fault
but Lantern and the Martian, we should've seen that comin'.
Stop beating yourself up, Oliver. Mmm.
'They never had a problem with us being in the league.'
I was the one with the problem, always afraid
I wouldn't be able to keep up with 'em. Ever feel that way?
Bruce?
I know. I can be a real bore sometimes.
'Over and out.'
- It's going to be okay! I... - Hugo Strange. Hugo Strange.
Strange? What does he have to do with this?
- Hugo Strange. - What about him?
Bruce, are you okay?
What are you doing here? You're not in this.
Bruce.
- No, you're not.. - 'Bruce.'
- Huh! - Sorry. You were makin' noise.
I-I must've drifted off for a second. Whew.
What are you doin' up so late?
I couldn't sleep. I had a nightmare, too, sorta.
Kept hearin' the Martian's voice.
What?
He was trying to contact us. I'm sure of it.
Why didn't I hear him?
Because the mind is more receptive during sleep.
There are fewer distractions.
It's never bothered the Martian before.
Unless he's getting weaker.
But what does Hugo Strange have to do with this?
H-he's been locked up tight for months, hasn't he?
At this place, you never know.
Hello, Hugo.
Aren't you wondering why I'm here?
- Awful quiet, isn't he? - Usually you can't shut him up.
It's not him.
You're a lot heavier than Hugo, aren't you?
Crash
boom
crash
clang
pew boom.
I got ya.
Zap.
Better stay back, I don't wanna take
any chances with this thing.
Don't. I need to see something.
Radio controlled like the gas canister
back at the hall of mirrors, except this one's
still receiving a signal we can trace.
What is it? I've never seen anything like this before.
Because it's alien.
The Joining's back.
You'd think after that last time.
The Joining would steer clear, eh, of earth.
Maybe they were just testing us before.
The Batmobile is triangulating the robot's signal.
'It should automatically pinpoint the exact location.'
- Got it. - Great.
Now if you could just figure out how to get
some legroom back here.
Vroom.
Air raid shelter?
It goes back a long time, to a war.
People were worried about air attacks.
Like they don't worry now?
No. Wait.
You may wanna save that for later.
- What is that? - Force field.
You never disappoint me, Batman.
I built this trap mostly for you.
That's how sure I was you'd find me.
- Great. - What was it, Batman?
My robot duplicate?
Of course. I should have built an auto destruct switch.
But there's never enough time in the day, is there?
I told The Joining you were the cleverest of them all
but all they care about are the superpowered ones.
What made you go over to their side?
They have so much to offer someone like me.
Remember the first time The Joining came?
Oh, it was bedlam..
Destruction everywhere.
I could hear it all from my room.
Arkham's brave attendants left me and my fellow inmates
to our own devices.
I was one of the lucky ones.
All I wanted to do was get away.
But then, fate intervened.
Pew pew pew.
I knew the alien vehicle would have
all sorts of fascinating technology.
I took as much of The Joining's equipment as I could.
Including their vehicle's central communicator.
Then I came to this place.
I combined their equipment to make a radio transmitter
that could contact them
and then I made them my offer.
If they supplied me with their technology
I would neutralize The Justice League.
In return, The Joining would give me something
more valuable than even money or power..
The vast knowledge of the universe.
- Where are they? - Your friends? Voila.
Whirr.
My dream.
- What are you doing to them? - You'll see soon enough.
My, my, look what my associate found in your belt, Batman.
A mini explosive set to go off in 3 minutes.
I knew you were up to something.
You made it just a little too easy for me to catch you.
There had to be some sort of high tech surprise.
Actually, it's rather low tech.
Pfft
beep hiss.
Stop him!
Whack clang clang clang
whoosh
rizz rizz.
What do you think those tubes are for?
Don't know.
Then how 'bout we cut 'em loose?
Whoosh.
You okay?
Something doesn't feel right.
Well, you better get over it..
"Cause I have a feeling'
we're gonna be needing you.
Aah!
My powers, they're gone.
Uhh!
Zap.
The androids have taken our powers.
What do we do now?