I had no idea this could be so stimulating.
Yeah, you never forget your first crime.
Radioactive phosphorus
just what the doctor ordered.
Sorry, bug boy. You're gonna need a lawyer.
The name is Firefly.
And I'd be very careful.
I fumble this ball, we're all toast.
Boom
Blaise, let's go.
Whoosh.
Beauty, brains, and cool under fire.
- What did I do to deserve you? - Simple.
You were very, very bad.
But honestly, all I did
was design a few simple upgrades to your equipment.
It isn't rocket science.
No, wait, it is.
And nuclear Firefly 2.0
is gonna be in and out of the treasury
before the Bat even pulls on his tights.
'Once we have the gold, we'll steam away from Gotham'
'and never look back.'
'It'll be the sweet life for us.'
Look. We're famous.
Commissioner Gordon assures us they're doing everything
in their power to recover the isotopes
'stolen by Garfield Lynns'
'also known as Bee Man.'
I am so ready to blow this town.
Oh, crud!
Boom.
Garfield!
Beep
whoosh
boom
vroom
clink.
Her name's Blaise? Figures.
I've checked with Firefly's old associates.
Apparently, he and the girl are working on their own.
I wonder what he plans to do with that isotope.
A bigger mystery is, how come you always get the front seat?
Beep beep.
Explosion on the south side.
It's Firefly, alright.
This explosion could have been caused by the isotope.
You better check.
He gave you a radiation detector?
Why don't I get a radiation detector?
Anyone using the Batcomputer for something other than
downloading video game cheat codes?
Hmm?
Hey. Look what I found.
Yep, Blaise and Firefly.
Her real name is Dr. Jane Blaise Dale
nuclear physicist.
Quit her job at Gotham U when her project
for boosting nuclear energy output
was shut down over safety concerns.
Bruce Wayne's on the university's board.
So why's Brainy Jane hanging out with a creep like Firefly?
Chemistry.
Like Harley and Joker.
It's a bad boy thing.
I was talking about this kind of chemistry.
And I'll take weirder Science for 1000.
If the isotope blew up
the radiation should be off the scale
but it's barely above normal.
Where'd all that radiation go?
You're going to the emergency room
don't argue with me.
Do you want to go to jail? Pull over.
You took a lot of radiation.
You need to see a doctor, a real doctor.
I'm controlling it.
I'm fine.
Maybe I should be worried about you.
Middle of summer, you crank up the heat.
It's on cold. You're the one who's burning up.
I need air.
Hey, I'm walking here!
Help! It's bumblebee!
Don't move. Hands in the air.
Now, which is it?
Don't move..
Or hands in the air?
Ah!
Smokin'.
No point in having special powers
if you don't cash in.
Oh. Temperature control needs some work.
We have to get out of here.
Screech.
That's new.
Get the car.
Gah!
Dr. Blaise Dale, I presume?
Looking for these?
Whoa.
It's gonna take more than that to douse me, kid.
Ahh!
What is your crazy guess about
where the missing radiation went?
Go help Batgirl. I'll wrap up Firefly.
Boom.
Thanks for getting the name right, Batman.
'And I'm not Firefly anymore.'
With your last breath call me..
Phosphorus.
Please, we have to go.
Ohh!
Out.
Eh, I'll get used to it.
Too hot. In the back.
Whatever.
Batman!
Unh!
'Stand back!'
I liked it better when he was a bug.
At least it got us this far. Come on.
What are we gonna do, Garfield?
You can't be in a car without setting it on fire.
This power's gonna take some practice, that's all.
Just give me a chance.
I'm unstoppable, Blaise.
The Bat can't touch me.
But neither can I.
I know. But we'll figure it out.
Come on, babe. The sweet life, we're this close.
I need to know you're with me.
Creak
fizz fizz fizz.
- Freeze! - Freeze!
Burn.
This way.
Grab the door, babe.
Now, a moment to cool down and..
Okay, so I'm still working out the temperature thing.
You know, I'm a partner not a Hench girl.
What do you want from me?
For one thing, the secret to maintaining that healthy glow.
Boom.
Unh!
Aah!
Whoa. I could get used to this.
Lynns.
Ahh. Huh?
Aah!
Heat reactive carbon alloy nano fibers.
Durable to 4000 degrees kelvin.
Tell me, is Garfield..
Coming to your rescue?
I'm going with no.
He's been losing it since the accident.
He couldn't control the powers.
And of course you were secretly on our side the whole time.
I think she's really worried.
Throw all your ice pellets.
Aah!
Unh!
You took your best shot, Bats.
Care to see mine?
Ah.
Move.
Argh!
Whoa.
You don't carry any sunblock in that belt, do you?
No sign of him on the police scanners.
How much lead lining?
A centimeter all around should be
an effective radiation shield.
Very good, sir.
And as long as I've got it open
perhaps I could let out the shoulders.
Just the lining, Alfred.
So far, Phosphorus isn't leaking radiation only heat.
But as his powers outstrip his ability to control them
we may be staring at an uncontained reaction.
As in a nuclear bomb?
If he absorbed enough radiation, yes.
- But I don't think he did. - Whoo!
He's much more likely to melt down.
'Melt down? That doesn't sound good.'
'It's not, it means he'll get hot enough'
to melt into the ground.
But not before destroying most of Gotham.
- Where are you going? - I'm gonna scout around.
I'll call if I see him.
A guy who glows in the dark can't be too hard to find.
Vroom vroom.
What are you doing?
What does it look like I'm doing?
I'm hungry.
- It's raw. - Not when I'm done chewing it.
Garfield, your feet.
You can't eat, you can't drive.
You-you can't even stand anywhere.
This is insane!
I did this for you.
You wanted it.
I didn't want this.
Aah!
Blaise?
Blaise!
Slow down, doc.
Where's the fire?
I didn't just say that.
Whoosh boom.
Working with my enemies, is that it?
I'm done with your powers, Garfield.
Look at you. Think you're such hot stuff? Think again.
You okay?
He's crazy.
You used to think I was hot, Blaise.
Oh, I'm hot, alright.
But I could get hotter.
Where's he going?
'Nuclear power plant.'
vroom.
Ha!
Zap zap zap.
Huh?
Get out of here!
Huh! What the..
Vroom vroom.
Huh? Uh! Whoa!
Whoa!
Aah!
Crash.
Give it up, Lynns.
Give up?
I'm just getting warmed up.
Huh!
Clink clink clink.
Like ducks in a shooting gallery.
Uhh!
Uhh! Uhh!
I'm not one of your pathetic Arkham whack jobs, Bats.
I have real power.
I'll break through that suit
then I'm gonna soak up every bit of radiation
in the reactor and pop my top.
Gotham will be a memory
but long will live the name of Phosphorus.
Aah!
Garfield, don't do this. Please.
All I wanted was a big hit so I could blow this town.
Seems I can't have the hit but I can still blow this town.
You'll destroy us.
I guess some relationships are just too hot to handle, babe.
At least this time they'll get my name right.
'Lynns!'
You got to be kidding me.
Figured you'd think so.
Beep beep beep Huh? Uh! Gah!
Hyah!
Aah!
Huh?
'Liquid nitrogen.'
'Something had to cool him down.'
If Mr. Lynns had gotten help earlier
maybe something could have been done.
Right now, only a special gas mixture
'is able to keep him under control.'
Garfield.
Blaise, you got my message.
I came in person to say..
Whatever spark existed between us..
It's gone.
Blaise, wait. I..
Wait!
It's late, Garfield, lights out.