It's far too quiet.
Superman's not exactly Mr. Yappy.
Maybe he's already tossed Luthor in jail and left for Metropolis.
We would have heard over the police band.
Something's not right. We need a closer look.
Click click.
Lukewarm. Luthor hasn't been gone long.
Everything's so neat and clean.
You'd think Alfred lived here.
You still at it?
You really are a creature of the night.
I found some residue in Luthor's test tube.
Porphyrin rings with a magnesium center.
Uh, middle school?
- Chlorophyll. - Chlorophyll?
You mean plants?
Yes. Maybe poison plants.
If Ivy's involved, we might have to take precautions.
- Suit up. - Where are we going?
Luthor's weapons lab here in town.
Lucius tells me they've been working overtime
away from prying eyes.
And X-ray eyes, too.
You with me, Robin?
Got your back.
Whirr.
'And you, keep the north entrance covered.'
No one gets in.
Whirr
click.
How are we doing, Mercy?
All systems are go, Lex.
We even have perfect weather.
Then let's get them activated.
Beep beep.
Let me out. Let me out!
Thud thud
crash
bang.
I injected a flash dehydrate made especially
for you, Clayface.
Crumble crumble crumble.
You'll be okay. Just add water.
Looking for someone?
Snap.
Ivy's mind control spores laced with Kryptonite.
So you are as clever as they say.
He was a little resistant last night
so I thought I'd give him an extended dose.
- What are you up to, Luthor? - Saving the world, Batman.
You saw how helpless it was during the alien invasion.
We have no central control, no plan of attack.
Instead we put our faith in aliens.
Well, no more.
Only humans should be in charge of Earth's destiny.
Humans with robots.
Oh, they're more than just robots, Batman.
'They're powerful, aerial, wireless transmitters.'
Once aloft, they'll target the most strategic
military installations in the world
at which point, they'll interface
with the defense systems on the ground..
Giving me complete control.
Whirr.
I don't expect everyone to understand
what I'm doing at first but in the end
we'll have a single worldwide army.
One that will ensure protection against aliens.
No one will dominate the Earth again.
Except for you.
Well, someone has to be in charge
and who could stop me except for Superman?
And he may turn out to be the most valuable robot of all.
Destroy him.
Clang clang crackle
boom.
Find him!
Break him!
Whack
creak.
Robin, can you hear me? We have a problem.
Crash.
You're not kiddin'.
Click
pow Aah!
Oh, no.
Swoosh.
Gotcha!
See? Nothing to it.
Look, up in the sky!
Crash.
- Awesome! - Awesome!
Hey, superdude, you okay?
Whoa. Check out the blingbling.
Hello? That's Kryptonite.
Oh, ho, what do we do, man?
Uh, kick it in the water.
Splash.
Alright, superdude!
Give me five! Yeah!
- Ooh, hoo! Cool! - Yeah!
- Rock it, man! - Oh, that was gnarly, dude.
Whoosh What are we here for?
Insurance.
Beep beep beep
fiss.
So that's where you got the Kryptonite from.
I thought you gave it to Superman.
It was a fake, I decided to hang on
to the real thing in case..
Clang ...that.
Clang
clang clang crash.
Argh!
He's gonna blow!
Clang.
Uh! Ugh!
I got it!
Whoa!
Crash
creak
whirr.
When he gets out, he's not gonna be happy.
Whack I have an idea how to stop him
but I've got to get him out of here.
What do I do?
Maybe you can slow him down.
Swoosh.
Got him, Batman!
Ah!
'No one knows why they're fighting, folks'
'but it looks like a clash of titans from up here.'
Should we delay the countdown?
Not on your life.
No man in a tin can
is going to beat the Man Of Steel.
And if their battle distracts the city
so much the better.
We proceed as scheduled.
Clang
swoosh
boom
thud thud thud crash
clang
crackle crackle.
'Hey, blue boy.'
thud thud Cool.
You get a raise.
I get paid?
Come on.
Ew. Is this where you were leading him?
What are you going to do, stink him into submission?
Something like that.
Here we are.
Crash.
Put on your mask.
Creak fiss.
Uh! Ah!
Aa-argh!
Creak creak creak.
- Wha-what's going on? - That cured him?
Luthor had you under the spell of Poison Ivy's
mind-controlling plant spores.
But I just doused you with atrazine
a basic component of plant killers.
It wiped out the spores.
I owe you one.
It wasn't just me.
I guess teamwork does have its advantages.
Thirty seconds to launch, Lex.
You should pay attention, Ms. Ivy.
History is being made
and you provided the seeds of change.
Opening silo. Ten seconds to liftoff.
Whirr
whoosh.
I'll handle those. See if you can stop them from the inside.
Zap zap zap Aah!
Zap zap zap
buzz buzz buzz clang.
No! They have to take him out!
Zap zap zap whack zap zap zap
I'll put them all on him.
Clang clang clang.
Might want to cover your ears.
Boom
bang bang.
Keep on them.
Zap zap zap
swoosh swoosh swoosh
boom boom boom
whack
crash
boom boom
thunk
boom
zap zap zap
bang
whirr.
Lex, what about me? Uh! Uh!
That must be the daddy.
Whoosh.
Move!
'Two seconds to hyperdrive.'
'Program failure. Command terminated.'
What?
'Warning. Warning.'
'Virus detected.'
'Warning.'
Uh!
Clang
smash
boom.
You can't leave without saying goodbye.
Fiss.
- 'Morning.' - 'Is that when it is?'
Who can tell up here?
Have you seen today's headlines?
Been a little busy, Dick.
The Lex has been tossed in jail with Ivy and the others.
'Who says there's no good news?'
Hey, if you need some help up there, I could..
No, thanks. I've got a visitor. Out.
So, this is what all the excitement is about.
Still a work in progress, but it'll do for now.
I asked you here because I wanted to give you this
the real Kryptonite.
I dug it up from my lab.
Found the piece in the river, too.
You keep it.
At least then I'll know it's with someone who's on my side.
Now, tell me about this justice team of yours.
League. Justice league.
Told the Martian it sounded like a ball club.
Anyway, this is our command center.
Someone's always stationed here.
It's time-consuming, but the view's great.