Pliers.
Grunt.
Struggling only makes it worse.
Ball-peen.
We waste more time trying to get that thing off his head.
Don't tell me you're not curious to see
the face behind Black Mask.
'Sorry to disappoint you'
but I won't be here for my unveiling.
Another breakout attempt?
- We've seen them all. - This one you won't see.
Aah!
Always hire the best, I say.
You ain't seen nothing yet.
And they call you a creature of the shadows.
A talent like that can be used for more than just a breakout.
Word from the prison grapevine
is that Black Mask is planning something big.
Black Mask always thinks big.
Where do you think he'll strike?
With this guy? Almost anywhere he wants.
And this rare meteorite is the only known object
ever to impact the Earth from the Thanagar Star System.
This now concludes our tour.
'Please exit through this door.'
- I see the guy's shadow. - But where's the guy?
Drop the rock.
You told me you could do this without setting off alarms.
An unexpected glitch.
The unexpected I always expect.
You two, get the rock.
Three-minute police response time, Number One.
Our response time is better.
Something from the gift shop?
Now this, I expected.
Doesn't even tickle.
- I got him. - Robin, wait.
Okay, bad idea.
No more dark nights for you, Dark Knight.
Hawkman, what are you doing here?
I'm here to take you in, Shadow Thief.
- Get rid of him. - With pleasure.
Ah!
You got lucky.
Crash.
Step on it.
Don't suppose he'll just pull over and give up?
I'll fire a grappling hook and reel him in.
Huh?
- Ejection seats? - Bad option.
Brace for impact.
- That wasn't so bad. - We never hit.
Huh?
Nice catch.
Couldn't let a fine vehicle
like this get scratched.
I'm impressed.
Your setup here is not that much different
from police headquarters back on Thanagar.
More Earthbound, of course.
That's him. That's Shadow Thief.
His real name is Carl Sands.
You mean he's human?
Except for a missing conscience.
He thinks nothing of putting others in danger.
Of all the criminals I've fought on two planets
he's the most reckless and elusive.
It's this wrist device that gives him
his two dimensional abilities.
He can make his body solid at any time
'and that's the time he can be caught.'
It's done.
I hope you're not gonna say dinner is served.
It's a piece from the meteor they stole.
The radian analyzer shows one element unknown to Earth
with antigravity properties I've never seen before.
I have. It's called the Nth element.
It's part of my suit.
It's what gives me my strength and flying powers.
It's incredibly potent and unstable.
If this is what they're after, all of Gotham is in jeopardy.
If this stuff works like you say
then the gem depository is ours for the taking.
But it's practically a fort. Nobody's ever broken in.
You sound worried, Number One.
Let me demonstrate how I'll do it.
You see this sample of antigravity powder?
It's been chemically treated.
Once it makes contact with the air..
It activates.
Aah!
I'm taking the gem depository building, alright.
Right out of the ground.
Are you worried anymore, Number One?
No. No, Black Mask.
No, I'm not.
You should be.
Aah!
You.
You're my new Number One.
I think that honor is due me.
Hiring you put another costumed cop on my tail.
This caper was difficult enough without your fly boy around.
Don't worry, I have a little diversion in mind
that'll keep him and the bat quite busy.
'An anonymous tip on Shadow Thief.'
Tell me this isn't a trap.
Maybe not.
'Got anything?'
I see him.
The train.
That's right, Hawkman.
Next stop, the moon.
He used the Nth element.
How far up will it go?
It'll never stop.
Thwip.
The element's in place.
Get ready.
We're losing it.
Hold on.
Can someone tell me what Shadow Thief thought he was doing?
Keeping us away from the real crime.
Huh?
Anyone need a lift?
Batman, thank heavens.
Black Mask and his gang are emptying the vault.
You better get them out of here. We'll take care of Black Mask.
I hope you guys haven't just eaten.
It's payday, boys.
You still owe the state ten years, Mask.
Huh? Mm.
Time to fly, bird boy.
Uh.. Aah!
Don't wanna leave you out, Batman.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Where's a blimp when you need one?
You wouldn't like the ozone, son.
Trust me.
Aah!
Thanks. Gotta get back to Batman.
Going somewhere?
I thought bats liked to fly.
Nothing will save you now, Batman.
Aah! No!
Huh?
Nice job.
Back on top.
It's gonna drop.
Whoa!
You get the feeling this is gonna make the local news?
'This was the scene today'
'as Hawkman took custody of the Shadow Thief'
for a flight back to Midway City.
In a related story, scuba divers have finally recovered
the last of the jewels from the gem depository
after Black Mask's daring robbery.
And though the city has lost a building
'it seems to have gained a new water attraction.'
Where are you going?
To get my bathing suit.