'Ladies and gentlemen, as your new mayor'
'it's a great honor to come before you today'
in this celebration of courage and survival.
'One year ago, we faced an alien invasion'
'that almost spelled the end of the human race.'
'Of all the cities that were attacked'
'our fair Gotham was the first on the battle lines'
and the most severely damaged.
Since then, we have restored many of our buildings
though there is still hard work to be done.
To that end, the good people of Metropolis
our sister city, have raised funds to help us.
'And at any moment, a check for those funds will be flown here'
'by the man of steel himself, Superman.'
Wait till they see him, Ms. Lane.
The roof's going to come off the building!
Fanboy.
What're you, un-American? He's Superman.
Yeah? Well, we have our own hero.
The bat? He's okay, if you like the circus.
Superman's the real deal.
Yeah? If he's so super, why's he so late?
Clark? Where are you?
Uh, well, Lois, I... I got a little problem, I..
I left my press pass in my other pants
and they won't let me in.
Maybe if you came down to vouch for me..
I swear, Clark, it's a wonder you remember
to wear pants at all.
'Show's already started. Sorry.'
The moment you've been waiting for has finally arrived.
Here he is, straight from Metropolis..
Superman!
- Whoa. - Told ya.
Mayor Hill, it is my great privilege to present this check
to the good people of Gotham City.
The check's been canceled, Superman.
And so have you!
This isn't in the program.
Rip Metallo!
In the flesh.
That's right, Perry. Metallo's back.
Stay on the line.
Crash.
Come on!
You don't know how long I've waited!
Crash
screech.
What's say we take this somewhere more private?
Thud
crash thud
clang clang thud.
Lookin' a little green, Supes.
Me? I love kryptonite. Can't get enough.
But I guess one man's power source is another man's poison.
Swoosh.
Haa-a-ah!
Thud
screech Looking a little rusty, tin man.
Rumble rumble rumble Ah! Uh!
Thud
clang.
There's nothing you can do, Batman.
As long as I'm near Supes..
'...he's finished.'
And I'm not moving another inch.
Suit yourself.
Beep beep
screech clang
boom boom boom
beep
screech.
Do you see what I see?
Let's do it.
Clang clang.
Huh?
Boom.
Get that as far away from here as you can.
- Huh? - Hasta la vista, baby.
Vroom screech
thud.
'Let him go.'
clang
pow
crash.
Uh.. No!
Whirr.
He isn't even scratched, just powered down.
An internal battery will keep him alive.
- Where's the kryptonite? - Don't worry. We got it.
I want it.
You're not very trusting.
Not when it comes to that... Mr. Wayne.
Hey, you two.
How about a handshake?
It'd make a great page one.
Click I'll get it to you within 24 hours.
- Where? - I'll find you.
Screech.
Whoa! Nice ride.
'What?'
clack.
After all that work to get Metallo powered up
he's stopped by a clown in a bat suit!
What happened to my kryptonite?
It's probably with Superman by now.
But we still have a few small pieces left
and some dust.
Barely enough to give him a headache.
There's no one left to challenge the Kryptonian anymore.
No allies have any strength or cunning.
Not here, not in Metropolis.
I'm on my own.
Unless..
Mercy, get my jet ready.
We're going to be spending some time
with our Gotham division.
That's where we'll find the answer to our problem.
Screech
I can't believe he peeked under your mask.
That is so not cool.
It's Superman's way of saying he knows
how to find me if he wants to.
I'd like to even that playing field.
Screech
whirr.
This is the new tech lab?
Kickin'.
Having fun?
A blast.
You've been busy, Lucius.
You said you wanted to be prepared
if there's another alien invasion.
These are just prototypes
but I'd say we're making headway.
Whoa. This has got to be for me.
It's a jetpack, right? Please tell me it's a jetpack!
- A jetpack and rocket launcher. - Yes!
I know you didn't come here for a tour.
- What's up? - I need this gift-wrapped.
- In lead. - Fascinating.
- What you lookin' at? - Metropolis.
- What're those? - Supersonic disturbances.
This particular satellite picks up objects
moving faster than sound.
'Usually, they indicate jet craft'
but in Metropolis, almost all of them come from Superman.
Here's his pattern for the last 48 hours.
He gets around.
'What's that place?'
- "The Daily Planet." - That's where Lois Lane works.
I heard he likes her, but not that much.
That's not the only place he frequents.
Ding.
- You sure you're okay? - I got it.
Uh, by the way, Lois, there's a cable special tonight
on the plight of the long-eared jerboa.
- I was wondering if... - Gee, Clark, I'd love to.
But, um I have to... uh-um, wash my hair.
Whoa!
Heh. And they call me a split personality.
Mr. Wayne.
You really are the world's greatest detective.
Here it is, like you asked. It's sealed in lead.
You can take a peek, if you want but.
I wouldn't advise opening it.
I'll take your word.
I didn't think you were the trusting kind.
By the way, the Justice League's about to have
its first official meeting.
I heard the Martian invited you, but you declined.
I prefer to work alone.
So did I, once.
But I found out you never know when you might need a friend.
Clack clack clack.
What're you doing here so late?
I could ask you the same thing.
Pretty young lady alone in the building.
I'm emailing Luthor.
We were supposed to have an interview tomorrow
but he left for Gotham a few days ago
so I wanted to see if he could reschedule.
That's funny. I heard you were going to Gotham, too.
Not me. I just got back last week.
No, I'm sure of it.
Thud.
Uh! Uh-uh!
Bang bang bang
whirr.
Greetings from Gotham, Ms. Lane.
You can call me Black Mask.
Whoo-hoo!
Swoosh.
Just call me Rocket robin.
Alright, rocket. Time to come down to Earth.
We've got a city to patrol.
But there's nothing happening down there.
Even you said it's been quieter than the batcave.
Hey, why don't I patrol from up here?
Got the whole sky to myself.
Swoosh.
Whoa!
I got an idea for the next prototype..
Barf bags.
Crash.
Ninety seconds. Not bad.
I don't think that's going to do you much good.
Oh, but this was made to order.
Zap.
Feeling strange, Superman?
That energy blast mimics radiation from a red sun.
Your powers have been temporarily cut.
Creak
roar
crash
swoosh whack Huh?
Oof!
Crash
whack Huh?
Whack.
Now, freeze, before he fully recovers.
He's too weak to melt his way out.
He'll suffocate for sure.
Oh!
Crack crack crack No!
- Uh! - Oh!
Alright. Round two.
No wonder it's been so quiet lately.
Here's where the party is.
Thud
splat
whoosh.
Hyah!
Whack thud thud Huh?
Pow crash.
Not so fast!
Huh?
Eww.
Sizzle.
You okay?
Nothing a hot shower won't fix.
And you?
Feeling no pain.
So, why the sudden interest in Superman, Black Mask?
Getting tired of me?
- He's working with Luthor. - Luthor?
They were talking on the phone.
Luthor has been here in Gotham since last week.
That would explain where he got this.
I think I should pay Luthor a visit.
Maybe we both... should.
He's not much for conversation, is he?
Like you should talk.
Crash
thud
I take it Ms. Lane is alive and well once again.
You've gone too far this time, Lex.
But I'm on your side, Superman.
In fact, I've been doing some criminal capturing myself.
Click.
Ms. Poison Ivy, a fiery little flower.
She had the silly notion she could defeat you with this.
Plant spores, the mind-controlling variety.
Of course, they would never work on you.
You're invulnerable to spores and germs and bacteria..
Unless they were laced with kryptonite dust.
That's right, Superman.
That was my contribution.
At first, I wanted you destroyed.
But then, when Ms. Ivy came to me
at the 11th hour with this..
I saw new possibilities.
Of course, I couldn't let her have all the fun.
I wanted to control you myself.
Look at me when I talk to you.
Bow to me.
I said bow, you alien swine!