Uhh! I knew I should have splurged for the turbo.
Aah!
Whoa!
I take it those weren't pigeons.
Look.
' "S. W."'
pew pew pew.
Uh-oh.
They're gone.
Great, now the guys in hero suits are shooting at us.
You got them on video?
'A city traffic camera'
'recorded their getaway.'
Whoa. Look at the wheels his sidekick gets.
And last week, when killer Croc managed to escape us.
He must have had their help, too.
That time they didn't show themselves.
They're getting bolder.
So what do you think, alternate versions of us
from a parallel universe?
Or maybe our matter-antimatter twins.
You've been reading too many comic books.
You left out video games.
I thought you might need a reminder.
Bruce and Dick have an appointment
with their friends the Mallorys.
Andy Mallory?
Alright, I'll go.
But I'm not gonna have any fun.
Whoo-hoo!
And where, exactly, did you leave my brother?
Too slow.
'Maybe!'
But I got style.
Yee-haw!
Yeah, you fall way cooler than I do.
Yet you keep trying to impress me.
Come on, you two.
Andy and I both appreciate you guys lending us this gear
for our climb next week.
No problem, Wayne tech developed it for the military.
But I'd always rather it get used for fun.
Here, let me show you how the zip line works.
Whoosh.
The cable's threaded with Titanium.
It's thin but it can hold a ton.
Hook your harness to the line, and..
Okay, Dick, show Andy how to hook himself in.
Like I'm gonna learn from a loser.
Hey, I was first.
- Out of my way! - Look out!
Brilliant.
Your fault.
So, how to retrieve a stuck teammate.
I guess I'll see you at fencing next week.
Dick?
Yeah. See ya.
Guess they'll be having a talk.
So will we.
Aw, let it go, big bro.
Look at all the swag you scored
from your chump friend.
Every little bit helps when you got a bat to squash.
Good evening and welcome to the first broadcast
of the city's newest lottery sensation..
The Gotham Millionaire Fun Ball.
I can see why you think
this might attract someone's attention.
Let's get right to it and find out our first number.
'Wait!'
Wait for me!
Oh, this is awful.
I can't find my ticket.
Ah! There's the ticket.
Ha!
Now, that's what I call a winning smile.
What a million-dollar surprise.
Now I can win the lottery and scratch off Batman at the..
Huh?
Hey, you stepped on my line?
Take your money, Joker. We'll handle the Batman.
Who asked you?
Yaah!
Crash.
Whoa! Uh! Ah!
'W and S.'
"Wipeout" and "Sudden Stop."
That's "Wrath" and "Scorn."
Who are you? Why are you doing this?
Someone has to stand up to your kind.
Joker's just trying to make a living like anyone else.
Criminals are simple, Batman, direct.
Joker doesn't wear a mask.
He shows his face for the world to see.
Then you won't mind doing the same?
You first.
Beep beep.
Hey, Will, sorry about missing fencing class.
Suddenly my schedule got jammed.
That's okay, Bruce.
I've got some extra business
to take care of, too.
We'll hook up later.
Ciao.
What's wrong?
Sometimes our schedules are too similar.
Extra business, if it were a business.
Joker would cut us in on his take.
'All the criminals would.'
We're not doing it for money.
We're doing it for them.
Why bother? I don't even remember them.
They'd be proud of you.
They'd be proud of us both for taking on the Batman.
He's everything they hated.
That, mom, and dad, and I have in common.
It's funny. Last night I felt like we knew each other.
We were so... in sync.
Uh, don't tell me you're starting to respect him.
Little brother, you've got nothing to worry about there.
'In fact, now that we know we can take him.'
'It's time to move on to the next stage.'
- What's with the club meeting? - Yeah, I ain't no joiner.
Uh, that's true, Mr. Scarface tells me all the time
he works alone.
This better not be one of your teamwork schemes, Pengy.
I assure you I had nothing to do with this.
Joker?
Please.
I had no time to clean up
put out trail mix, grease the trapdoor.
'I invited you here.'
Oh, it's this one.
You know, I could have handled Batman myself.
But no, you had to take all the fun out of it.
Ah, now, just a second.
I was thrilled to have this good fellow's assistance
and I vote we hear the man out.
So, who are you and what's your racket?
No racket. I'm just a friend.
One who believes criminals have it tough enough
without having to deal with that rabid bat.
Scorn and I are just here to even the field.
What if we don't want your help?
That's up to you but there's a job tonight
'that can make you all infinitely rich.'
It's too ambitious for any one criminal.
But with my backup, you might be able to pull it off.
Engraving plates?
- For printing money? - Right.
They're being unloaded at the docks tonight.
It's too big a prize not to attract Wrath.
You know, it's kind of creepy
how you're getting into this guy's head.
It's like you and he are the same.
Not in a way that counts.
Thud.
Who's there?
What?
Nice shot, Mr. Scarface.
Shocking.
So what's left for me to do?
Hey. Help me unload this loot.
Oh, good times.
Harbor patrol.
Uhh!
Crash.
Get out of here.
Titanium cable.
Bruce?
It is you.
We are too much alike.
What's the problem, bird boy
too scared to take me head-on?
What's your problem, Scorn dog?
Too slow to catch me?
Bang.
Not too bright, either.
Sort of like fencing class, isn't it, old pal?
You know who I am, don't you?
I wish I didn't.
Then you know why I'm going to win.
I'm willing to destroy my enemies.
You just send yours to jail.
Jail will do.
Grrr.
- Where's Wrath? - Move it, dummy!
I'm outta here.
Splash
bang.
Where is he?
He's on speakerphone.
You failed us, friend.
We barely got out of there with our feathers intact.
I'll make it up to you and then some
'because I now know who Batman is.'
'And I'm going to rid the city of him once and for all.'
Did you hear that, dummy?
That'll be my gift to you.
Let's go.
'Next stop... Wayne Mansion.'
Where's your smile, Joker?
It's the end of the Batman.
Hmmh.
I can't believe it.
Will and Andy's parents
were notorious jewel thieves.
Explains the Mallory money.
Eventually they got caught and were sent to prison
around the same time my parents died.
So what's our next move?
We pay the Mallory brothers a visit.
'Unless we get to you first.'
Unh!
Whoosh.
I'm sorry, sir, he came up behind me as I opened the clock.
It's alright. Just stay hidden somewhere safe.
Come on out, Dickie bird.
We got a score to settle.
'Right behind you, Andrew.'
Yaah!
'I should have known you were Batman, Bruce.'
You were always so civic-minded.
It ends here and now.
'I destroy this place.'
'I destroy everything you are.'
'And then I'll destroy you.'
Somewhere safe, he says.
'Gotcha, Dickie.'
'It's over, Bruce.'
You've forgotten home court advantage.
'You have no court left.'
You'd be surprised.
Unh! Ah!
Huh? Aah!
You come to our house?
'Ah-ahem.'
Is it over?
If I go to jail, I'll tell everyone who you are.
You'll be a target the rest of your life.
But I swear, I'll never tell a soul
if you just let us go.
But that really would destroy everything I am.
You think I'm kidding, Batman?
You're finished! Through!
Hear me? It's over!
Get ready to be famous, Dickie.
So that's it? He tells and there's no more Batman?
I'm afraid so.
It was great while it lasted.
Bad night, boys?
Joker, hurry, uncuff us.
Oh, I'll do better than that.
'I'll completely unhinge you.'
What? You can't! We know who he is. We'll tell you!
Batman is..
'Destroying you is my game.'
And I won't have anyone stealing my fun.
'So does this mean we're back in business?'
'I don't think anyone's telling secrets'
'anytime soon.'