Wow. Today was so busy.
It wasn't even funny.
Miss Potter.
Ha ha ha!
Sorry. I.. Excuse me.
Miss Potter?
Ha ha ha!
Whoa!
Miss Potter!
Ha ha ha!
Huh!
What's so funny?
Ha ha ha!
- Going somewhere? - I don't think so.
Whoosh.
Tortured smile, uncontrollable laughing fits..
Joker.
Hardly seems like a simple
bank scheme is worth his time.
Ha ha ha!
Who said it was simple?
Vroom
screech boom
vroom.
'We did what we could'
'but the outbreak was too scattered.'
Too random to contain.
Tell me about it.
I had my people all over Gotham
trying to chase down these giggle bandits.
Fortunately, the change was only temporary.
The victims have no idea what came over them or why.
Clearly, Joker infected these people to do
his criminal bidding. But how?
That's the million dollar question.
None of his victims seem to have anything in common.
'What kind of person lets himself'
'go all giggly for that goon?'
Hey, it wasn't their fault.
Joker obviously got to them.
Maybe he used a gas or a powder or..
Ha ha. Something, I don't know.
You saw the tox screens, there was no trace
of anything in the victims.
- Ha ha ha! - Hey, I'm getting serious here.
So.. So am I.
Oh, boy.
'The Jewelry store. But who are they chasing?'
Batman, we've got a situ..
- Ha ha! - Uh!
Oh, no, you don't!
Hey! Uh! Whoa!
Ha ha ha!
Come on, Batgirl, snap out of it.
Ha ha ha! Uh!
Ah!
Ha ha ha!
Okay. This time I'm not fooling around.
- Batgirl. - Huh?
Ha ha ha!
Clank Ha ha ha!
Is it safe?
A brief time-out should reset her personality.
- Batman? - How do you feel?
Confused. What's going on?
Someone got a case of the giggles.
Who?
No!
I must have been really out of it. I hate pearls.
Do you know where you were taking the stolen jewels?
'No, but I've got an idea.'
Looks like the fish are biting tonight.
Ahoy, land lovers! Stopped by to see me off?
How thoughtful!
Punch. Get it!
Vroom.
Bon voyage, Bats!
Great. Now what?
We figure out how he got to you.
Slurp slurp Cute jacket.
This tanks.
Got a better idea?
No, but that doesn't make following
the shopping queen tank any less.
Joker did something to Barbara at some point during her day.
Yeah, and by retracing her steps
we're hoping to figure out when and where.
But, Bruce, we just spent the last two hours
watching her shop for handbags!
Well, you're in luck. I think she moved on to the main event.
Comic books?
Shoes.
Argh!
Ooh!
'After her morning shopping trip'
Barbara took the train to school.
Let's just hope they don't have a shoe store on campus.
Argh.
We can use some help here.
We got our own problems.
'And this was the scene last evening.'
'If this particular giggle bandit'
'looks familiar, he should.'
'It's none other than billionaire Bruce Wayne'
'proving even Gotham's elite can fall prey'
'to Joker's schemes.'
Annoying, isn't it? Welcome to my world.
Of course, all charges have been dropped
against Mr. Wayne and his companions
despite a scuffle with the police.
The authorities are lucky to have sustained
as few injuries as they did.
'This time Joker's victims threw'
'their stolen property'
'off the East Canal Bridge.'
Wait a minute.
That woman looks familiar.
She was on the train.
Yeah. Who could forget that hat?
The boy with the piercing, the old man.
They were there, too. They all were.
- The commuter train. - Joker's using the train.
How does he brainwash people with the train?
The lights.
Vroom.
'Life getting you down, bubby?'
'Feel like you're just along for the ride?'
Then relax, clear your minds
and look into the lights.
'The peaceful lights.'
'The soothing lights.'
beep beep.
Make sure everyone stays out of the first car.
Whoa. Whoa. Blast public transportation.
What's the matter with the lights?
Your scheme has just been derailed.
Excuse me. I'm the conductor here.
And all passengers must get their tickets punched.
Boys.
Thud thud swoosh.
Well, isn't that hospitable?
Judy wants you to have his seat.
- Whoa! - Whoa!
Hee-yah!
Whoa! Uh!
Thud.
If you'll excuse me, I've got business to conduct.
Boom.
Runaway train anyone?
Ha ha ha!
We're heading for a dead-end.
Well, we've got all those passengers back there.
And no air bags.
Grab my arm.
Boom boom.
- Whoa! - Whoa!
Screech - Whoa! - Whoa!
Crash.
Come on. We make the rest of this trip on foot.
It's all caves and tunnels down here.
Like a giant hunk of Swiss cheese.
In the late 1800s Gotham was a thriving coal mining town.
Who knows how many tunnels riddle this city's foundation.
'Ooh! Crime fighter and his truth confessor, all in one!'
'I'm so glad you decided to drop in!'
Ah!
'Must have been exciting in those days.'
chink chink.
'Such dangerous work down in the mines.'
'What, with all the accidents, cave-ins'
'and poison gas.'
hiss
screech thud.
Aww! Mmm, mmm, mmm. End of the line.
Rise and shine, Bat gang!
Look! You have your very own cage!
Just like Ralph here. Hee! Ha ha ha!
It's a pretty good haul, don't you think?
Just imagine what I'll get for these on the internet!
Let me guess. You're going to run us over with your train.
Real original.
I assure you, that joke is too obvious
even for me.
No, I've cooked up a far more crushing defeat
for my little cave bats. Heh heh heh!
You see, you're right about all the tunnels under Gotham.
The place is lousy with them.
So I thought I'd spruce them up a bit.
Dynamite.
Miles of it. Just imagine.
All these tunnels blowing at once.
The entire city swallowed into a great big sinkhole.
Ahh. Ashes to ashes, and all that rot.
Ooh! Love to chat! But I've got a schedule to keep.
Ta-ta!
'This is the cuckoo-choo-choo! Now leaving on track nine.'
Next stop, city limits and the end of Gotham as we know it.
Mwah! All aboard!
Honk
click click click
beep beep beep.
- GPS? - It can tell us where we are.
I can tell you where we are.
Stuck in a cave miles below the surface.
I hate to say it, Batman. But he's right.
There's no way we can catch Joker now.
- We've got nothing. - Not so.
'We've got explosives.'
boom.
- Good heavens. - Sorry about the mess, Alfred.
The front door too conventional for you, sir?
Vroom.
Well, hear that?
Screech
beep Get in.
Beep.
You gotta be kidding.
Beep beep beep.
'Train approaching.'
honk honk honk
vroom
vroom vroom.
That's it. We're moving.
Only three more miles to the city limits.
I'll miss you, Gotham and the swell times we had together.
But most of all, I'll miss the good old batty man.
I will.. Huh?
Beep beep beep.
Oh, I was so close.
Boom boom.
It seems like we're always saying goodbye.
Clang clang Huh?
Cover me.
Whoo hoo hoo! Circus time!
Ha ha ha!
Ooh!
Clang.
Ugh.
Ha ha ha!
Say goodbye, Gotham!
Click
click click click Huh?
- Argh. - Sorry, Joker.
You can't send a signal without a battery.
Ahh-h-h-h-h!
I've been railroaded?
Aa-a-a-h!
Screech.
- Oh. - Last stop, Joker.
You know, it's a really shame to seal it up.
Maybe you should expand. Add a Batgirl cave.
Batgirl cave?
I'm old enough to have my own cave.
I can park my cycle there, bring in some exercise equipment
a couple of beanbags.
How come she gets her own cave?
I want my own cave!
Nobody's getting their own cave.
Well, gotta go.
And where are you off to in such a hurry?
Late for a train?
Midnight madness sale at Gotham Shoes.
- You coming with me? - She's a regular Joker.