Beep beep
boom.
Really, it looks fine.
Fine's not good enough, Bruce.
It has to be perfect.
What are you doing? We'll be late for the party!
Oh, come on. It will be fun.
And this will give you more time to work on your makeup.
Not-not that you need it.
Aah!
Boom.
'Where'd he go?'
You're making kids sick, Wayne.
Next time, I won't let you off so easily.
Sick? What are you talking about?
Rip Are we having fun yet?
'It started about three weeks ago'
and it's been hitting kids especially hard.
First dizziness, then nausea.
Bet it's the flu. I had it one time.
You wouldn't believe what came out of me.
But there's no fever, and it stops just like that.
One other thing, it comes on mostly at night.
Do the cases cluster around any particular neighborhood?
Here's the map we made.
Hey, isn't that Wayne Labs?
It's right in the middle of it all.
Uh, not that that means anything.
My people at Wayne labs are so careful.
I don't understand how something like this could happen.
Probably just a virus or something. No biggie.
Tell me that after you've gone to med school.
How's he doing?
The dizziness is gone but they're telling me now
he broke his arm in two places when he fell off his bike.
Don't you worry. The doctors here are the best.
Need any more help with the bills?
Oh, no.
You've already done so much for us.
'Glad to help.'
Who's that guy?
His name's Oliver Queen.
Runs a big company in Star City.
- You know him? - In a way.
- 'How you doing?' - Almost done with the samples.
Don't think it's coming from Wayne Labs, huh?
I've had everything else checked. I..
What?
Arrow! It's me, Batman.
- Thought you were someone else. - I kind of figured that.
Robin. This is Green Arrow.
Yeah. The arrows and the greenness kind of give it away.
You're pretty far from Star City.
I thought you could use some help.
Gotham's favorite millionaire
has fallen in with the wrong crowd.
What do you mean?
People are getting sick around here
and it's because of that dirt bag Bruce Wayne.
Dirt bag?
If some kind of illness
is being caused by Wayne Labs
I guarantee you, Bruce Wayne doesn't know about it.
Bet he does. And I know who he's working with, too.
Whoa! Oh! Unh!
- 'Are we having an earthquake?' - An earthquake?
Ah!
- Ah! - You alright?
I think I'm gonna, gonna..
I'm starting to feel it now.
- He must be close. - Who?
We've got company.
Those headpieces they're wearing
must make them immune to the dizziness.
Let's see if they're immune to this!
Hmm?
Count Vertigo!
Too many. Can't focus.
Ah! Aa-aa-aa!
'Help!'
Help!
Ah!
'Hold on, kid!'
whoosh.
'There they are!'
- You okay? - Yeah, but he's not.
How are you doing?
Remember that time I had the flu?
That would be an improvement right now.
Sir?
I brought the medicine you requested.
Oh. Excuse me.
You didn't say you had company.
It's alright, Alfred.
Haven't I seen you before?
Perhaps the renaissance fair?
You were driving that limo.
The limo that belongs to..
'...Bruce Wayne.'
Now do you see why I'm so sure of him... Ollie?
Hey! How did you know?
He is The Batman, after all.
Now, let's hear about that man with the metal eye.
You know him, don't you?
A long time ago..
I was a spoiled rich kid..
Couldn't have cared less about running my company.
Just wanted to have fun.
Life was good..
Until I ran into some fog.
I started feeling dizzy.
And it only got worse.
Then I saw another ship.
The man with the metal eye was on board.
His name's Count Vertigo.
He was a scientist who used to work for me.
I fired him for stealing technology
and now, I was seeing firsthand how he used that technology.
I got dizzier and dizzier.
I tried to save myself
but Vertigo was merciless.
Sometime the next morning, I washed up onshore.
I figured the search parties would find
a rich, important guy like me
in a day or two.
All I had to do was find some shade and wait.
I never felt so helpless before.
Only one thing kept me going.
I knew that someday, I'd get another shot at Vertigo
and I wanted to be ready.
Those first couple of days were hard.
Then I got an idea.
From that day on, my life was transformed.
It seemed like nothing was impossible.
Every day, I built up my strength
tested my limits.
And kept on going.
I became strong, fearless.
All thanks to one thing.
After a few years on the island
I finally got some company.
When I came back, Count Vertigo had disappeared.
Then I heard about people getting sick near Wayne Labs
and I figured Vertigo had teamed up with Bruce Wayne.
He's stealing from me. That's what he's doing.
And he sent his men out tonight to make sure
you wouldn't get anywhere near him again.
Well, I'm going back anyway.
Not without me.
These footprints
they go right into a blank wall.
This wall doesn't belong here.
Allow me.
Concentrated acid.
Phosphorus would have been faster.
Whoa.
'Looks like a gyroscope.'
He built it right under my nose.
And at night, when he tested it
people got sick around here.
- What's it for? - Power.
'Imagine, a half million people'
unable to walk, unable to see straight.
That's how I was
before I created my eye.
Dizzy, helpless.
But just as the eye cured my affliction.
'I found it could inflict it on others.'
But with this, my powers
become almost limitless.
I'm going to cripple your city, Batman
and plunder it without a shot being fired.
And that's just the beginning.
Eventually, the whole world will stagger
and fall to the feet of Count Vertigo.
You miserable..
Your aim is a little off.
Make sure I don't see them again.
Beep.
- Put these in your ears. - What are they?
They'll seal off your inner ear so..
Just put them in!
- 'Still dizzy?' - They'll do.
Over here, guys.
- Ah! - Come on.
What makes you so sure he's hitting the mint?
Once a month, they send out new $100 bills..
And that's tonight.
- We're getting closer. - Got your plugs?
Got an improvement.
Crash
boom boom boom
beep.
- Arrow, come on! - But Vertigo.
Come on!
Arrow.
Clank.
Three times he's gotten away from me.
There won't be a fourth.
Thud.
Let's see how good an archer
you'll be without those fingers.
Huh?
Smack.
Argh!
Getting dizzy?
- 'No!' - Arrow!
What did you think I was gonna do?
You know, I like the set-up you have here.
Gives me some ideas for my place in Star City.
Which you're heading back to now, right?
'I guess I was a little..'
'You know.'
I know.
At least your partner's happy.
This is cool! Gives you distance.
Oh!
Then again, maybe I'll stick to our stuff.