Ohh! Unh!
'Working late?'
We're gonna need to see your employee ID.
Either Halloween came early
or someone likes playing dress-up.
Whoa! Unh!
Uh, okay. Which one do I clobber?
Batman?
Unh!
He's gotta be in here somewhere.
'There's no other doors, no windows, no air vents.'
Your imposter must have found some other way out.
You sure you don't have a twin brother?
Let's go.
Play that back again.
I've heard of copycat crooks, but this guy has you down cold.
There's one important difference.
The other Batman is left-handed.
Another break-in, this time at the Gotham
lens-grinding plant.
Let's go do some grinding of our own.
He's out cold just like the other one.
I'm ready to knock Batman on his butt!
Uh, you know what I mean.
Stay sharp. He's good.
Come here. I've got something for you.
Flash?
Too slow.
Hyah!
Uh!
Err!
Whoo.
Not again.
Let's look at what we have.
Both thieves stole precision optics, a prism and a lens.
They both dressed as heroes
and had all their skills and powers.
Definitely a pattern.
Hmm.
Something's not right.
Do you hear that?
Finally. I searched the whole city.
It took me over an hour to find this place.
Easy, kid. I'm on your side.
Huh?
I came as soon as I heard about the flash robbery.
How'd you get in here?
The entrance is eight feet of solid rock!
Easy!
When I vibrate my molecules, I create an energy field
that allows me to pass through solid objects.
But how do we know you're not the guy we're looking for.
Look at the screen.
- The lightning bolt. - It's backwards.
- He's a mirror image. - Mirrors?
Just like the left-handed Batman.
Did you say mirrors? I know exactly who's doing this.
This is bad. This is really bad.
Whoa, whoa! Slow down.
Sorry. I get excited.
I know who's doing this. Dr. Samuel Scudder.
A brilliant optical physicist from my hometown Central City.
Calls himself Mirror Master.
Master Bruce, you really must tell me
when you have guests down here.
Food!
Do you mind? I'm starving.
By all means.
And you thought I ate fast.
Sorry. My metabolism.
I'll come back with seconds.
Flash, what do you know about this Mirror Master?
He's the most powerful villain I've ever faced.
He's gone way beyond the looking glass.
There's nothing he can't do with mirrors.
It looks like he's discovered a way to capture
someone's reflection and turn it into
a three-dimensional henchman one that can escape
through mirrors, too.
What's he doing in Gotham?
And why's he stealing stuff like lenses?
So smooth and cool like glass.
It's only an energized reflection, Smoke.
But so beautiful.
Like a statue.
Beauty is in the eye of the beholder, my dear
and I have my eye on bigger things.
Well done.
Only one more component and my specular trap
will be complete.
Then the entire city of Gotham and every beautiful
and rich person in it will be at my mercy.
- What is it? - Intruder.
At the Gotham city observatory
and science museum.
Hate to eat and run.
So, Bats, where is the observatory?
Gotham hill. About two miles from here.
We should go in... together.
- Does he ever slow down? - No.
It's about time. What kept you?
There's nothing to worry about, guys.
False alarm. Sorry.
I did a quick run-through of the place, everything looks..
What did you do that for?
The guard's hair is parted on the other side.
- Huh. - Who did this to you?
Y-you did.
Where's Mirror Master?
We better check the place again.
Ah. The final piece.
We have company.
We're not alone.
Hey. A mirror me!
You're about to get seven years of bad luck.
Not bad. Do you practice in the mirror, too?
Hyah!
- Stop copying me! - Stop copying me!
- Oh. So you can talk. - Oh. So you can talk.
- Cut it out! - Cut it out!
- Quit it! - Quit it!
I like to smell my feet.
You like to smell your feet?
How'd I fall for that?
Ohh!
Hmm!
See ya.
Ready for the portal ray.
That's far enough, Mirror Master.
Batman and Robin I expected, but, Flash
you're a long way from Central City.
I took the fast lane.
Well, let me leave you with some shattering news.
Soon, all of Gotham will be in reflection.
Hold on.
Whoa!
- Tingly. - Whew.
What is Mirror Master trying to build, some kind of laser
a mass hypnotizer, a hologram projector?
We're missing his motive.
If we knew what he wanted, we could figure out
how he intends to get it.
Maybe he's building the world's ugliest chandelier.
What're you doing?
Pacing. Helps me think.
Smoke, my dear, it's time.
And now, Gotham, you're mine.
Did someone forget to pay the electric bill?
"All of Gotham will be in reflection."
Aah!
Ohh!
Get down now!
They're trapped.
There was a massive drain on Gotham's power grid
right before it happened.
'It was centered around this point.'
Come, my dear. Our prize awaits.
The only thing that awaits you is a prison cell.
Batman and Flash.
It's a wonder you escaped the effects of my device
but then again, you hero boys
seem to have that kind of luck.
What're you planning, to rob the city blind?
In a way.
I plan to collect the richest
100 people in the city..
All trapped in glass and ransom them.
We're talking billions, and if they don't pay up
I break them into a billion pieces.
Tell me how to reverse what you've done.
Gentlemen, this device cannot only trap you
inside your reflection.
It can exile you to the mirror dimension permanently.
Time to go through the looking glass.
Unh!
We're inside his mirror.
I can't vibrate out of here. We're trapped.
What're you doing?
Making sure they never get out.
Uh, Bats, I think we're in trouble.
Where's your portal ray?
'He took it!'
Unh!
Thanks for the help, Bats.
Now for Gotham.
This should change things back.
Where'd Bruce go? He was just here.
And why am I suddenly standing on my serving tray?
Good. Just checking.
- Everything's back to normal. - Thanks.
I should be thanking you.
If you hadn't grabbed that portal ray..
It was an impulsive move
something I learned from you.
I'll have them behind bars in no time.
Not fast enough for me.