Meow.
Uhh!
Ka-ching.
♪ The Batman ♪
'Our top story'
one of Gotham's wealthiest recent transplants
businessman Hideo Katsu
received a rude welcome last night.
Robinson Sprang has details.
The same Hideo Katsu
the Batman has been observing of late?
The same one I've been investigating without success..
So far.
Katsu's extensive collection of antiques remained intact
but, curiously, security cameras captured an image
of what appeared to be a costumed Catwoman.
What?
Joining me now is Gotham P.D.'s Ellen Yin.
Uh, detective, could there be some connection
between this Catwoman and the Batman?
While there seem to be similarities
in appearance and methodology
they have entirely different motives.
However, it's too early to rule out any possible links
between the Cat and the Bat.
This'll improve my relations with the police.
'I am most displeased.'
ching The sanctuary of my Murakami line
has been compromised.
Find this Catwoman.
Ka-ching I want her head.
- Hello, Fred. - Good afternoon, Miss Kyle.
Beep beep beep ding.
I missed you, too, sweeties.
Mama had to go shopping so she could feel better
after last night's disappointment.
You should've seen the prey
a big, shiny pussycat.
Missed it by a whisker.
Mmm. At least my adrenaline rushed.
' "Batman & Catwoman connected?"'
Hmm.
He looks tall, dark and handsome.
Mmm. Consider Selina Kyle... curious.
'All units, disturbance at 121 Simonsen.'
click
zing
screech.
Well, this is it. So where..
Hello, good-lookin'.
Nice cowl.
Really sets off your chin.
I take it you tripped the silent alarm.
Only way I knew to get you to come out and play.
Well, are you coming down, or do I have to come up?
Mm. Purr!
Catch me if you can.
Zing.
Unh!
You can stop playing hard-to-get.
And give up the thrill of the chase?
Snaps
clang.
Hate to cut our first date short, cutie
but I like to leave a man wanting more.
Zing.
'Hmm..'
Cute toy, Bat-bo.
Hyaah!
But corner a cat, get scratched!
Hmph!
Another cat fact
we always land on our feet.
Hmm... I think I'll take something
to remember you by.
'No way.'
My utility belt.
I know, Delilah
but I didn't take it for its looks.
I took it for the tools.
Hmm. Let's see.
Ka-ching.
Hmm.
This'll come in handy when I'm on the prowl.
Tap tap tap.
Got a little security feature, do you?
'You have found nothing on this Catwoman?'
'We must increase security'
'in the event she is foolish enough to return.'
Call for the Dragon's Fangs.
She wasn't supposed to be able to do that.
The belt's lock mechanism
must've been damaged in the fall.
This feline fatale is certainly proving
to be a sly one.
'I need to track that cat before she puts my utility belt'
'to no good use.'
Hmm..
Thud.
Goody.
Crash
Alfred, shut down the auxiliary bat-wave transmitter!
I believe this was the auxiliary transmitter, sir.
Come on.
'Start up.'
crash.
Okay, so what does this do?
Bang bang
beep.
Abracadabra.
Quick, disconnect the bat-wave receivers
from all the gear before she..
I don't believe this.
What good is this thing, anyway?
Crash
honk honk screech
crash
screech crash crash crash.
Uhh!
Uhh! Uhh!
Beep beep.
Whew.
Oh-oh-ho, scaredy-cats.
Hmm..
Can't wait to beta test.
And I know just the place.
Enjoy your drive, sir?
It had its twists and turns.
Are these all the bat-wave receivers?
Quite.
Thanks, Alfred.
If Catwoman were somehow, some way able
to trace the signals back here..
We would have to rename it, the Catcave.
An active bat-wave?
I was certain I'd disconnected all the receivers.
She took my remote control Batarang.
Maybe there's a way to trace the signal back to it
and Catwoman.
Click
ching.
The cat returns to Katsu.
How poetic. Ha ha ha.
Almost a Haiku.
I'll be sure to jot it down as soon as I get home.
I must insist you stay.
Then I must insist you eat steel!
Rizz rizz.
Ah. A dragon has many fangs.
If you inform me which family sent you
to steal my lion
I promise to make your comeuppance less..
Excruciating.
Family?
As in organized crime?
Yakuza.
Heh heh heh. Keep it.
'It is said cats have nine lives.'
Destroy her 10 times over!
Hyah!
Cling cling cling.
Better be some truth to that nine lives thing.
Yow!
'I should warn you fellas.'
Corner a cat, get scratched.
Mmm. Good-looking and good timing.
Yes.
You have something of mine.
Ah, she pilfered from you as well?
Take it.
It clashed with my boots anyway.
Click Now stand aside
so we may complete our business with her.
The lady leaves with me.
Then neither of you leaves.
Attack!
Boom boom.
Shall we, handsome?
There is no "we."
Clang That's not what they think.
Zing
zing zing zing.
Uhh!
Hyah!
Ugh! Uhh! Ugh!
Heh.
'Ahh.'
Heh heh heh.
Creak Unh!
Hyah!
Huh!
Alley-oop.
- Thanks. - Thanks.
Ugh! Uhh!
Oh! I think I broke it.
What?
A minidisc?
Pretty important, I bet.
Uhh! Aah!
Catwoman, that's our cue to..
'Too bad about the statue.'
Hmm. Win some, lose some.
Just glad you and I got to dance.
We have so much in common.
Less than you think.
That's not what they think.
Ahem.
What? You got your belt.
Most of it.
Uhh. You sure know how to spoil a girl.
'A minidisc found at the scene'
'revealed a chart of Japanese organized crime'
naming names
with Katsu at the top of a Yakuza family
intent on expanding into Gotham.
Detective, do you have a statement?
Rest assured.
Gotham P.D. is arresting the other Yakuza members
as we speak.
So, would you say the idea
of a Batman/Catwoman link wasn't so farfetched after all?
Yes, it's clear now that they work together
to take down Katsu as a vigilante team.
Ohh.
Not quite what I had in mind when I encouraged you
to meet women who share your interests, Master Bruce.
But it's a start.
♪ The Batman ♪