Mummy's just come from the most awful party, princess.
The catering was a disaster. The guests were strictly "B" list.
And Carrie would not shut up about her trip to New Zealand!
Mummy needs a long, hot bath.
'Hush, Princess! Mummy has a headache!'
Princess! What is going..
Aah!
♪ The Batman ♪
'Third high-rise this week, all with the same MO.'
No prints, no forced entry
no physical evidence of any kind.
I'd say it sounds like our Batman
if he were a burglar.
I thought I set it on the..
The Batman. Freeze!
Hey, you! Stop!
Go, Bats.
Hey, Alfred, check this out.
Strix nebulosa laponica.
'A rare species of owl native to China.'
'According to the Batwave search function'
'these scratches from the victim's dressing table'
'match the owl's talon span.'
Someone has trained a bird to perform burglaries.
Ahem.
Without suggesting that I'm not sufficiently impressed
with your deductive powers, Master Bruce
I must remind you that you have a gala fund-raiser to host.
Right, Alfred. Tomorrow night.
Sir, it is "tomorrow night."
We wouldn't want any guests growing suspicious
of how billionaire bachelor Bruce Wayne
really spends his time after dark, now, would we?
Hello, ladies.
'Beautiful. Beautiful.'
'Michael! Michael!'
'Over here! Over here! You're great!'
Make way! Make way!
The Oz-Meister is in the house.
Bruce Wayne, king of the castle, ruler of the roost.
- Have we met? - Cobblepot.
Oswald Cobblepot, of the new Casual Cobblepots.
But call me Ozzie.
We have a lot in common, you and I.
We're young, rich, and handsome.
I don't think I've heard of...
I've been abroad.
Just got back from a tour of the orient.
Uh-huh... I see.
Mm, and speaking of abroad..
Well, I, for one, have certainly heard of the Cobblepots.
My grandfather used to butler for them back in England
and they were an obnoxious lot then as well.
Grandpa Pennyworth worked himself to the bone
for those wretched snobs
and they treated him like a stray dog
then had the nerve to fire him!
'Get lost, creep!'
Ow.
Ooh... spunky.
Hey, miss, wait up.
How about some vittles there, Jeeves?
Crunch crunch crunch.
Hey... sorry about the weird guy.
Sure you don't want to stick around for the band?
Oh, Bruce! Amanda Raymont.
We met last year at the Earth Day thing?
'You know, uh, maybe I will stick around.'
Uh... pardon me.
Hmm.
You know, trespassing's against the law.
Oops. Busted.
Ethan. I see you brought a guest.
- My partner. - Hi. I'm Bruce.
Detective Yin.
Freeze!
You want to come in and join the party?
Not tonight. We're on the clock.
Chief's orders.
Keeping an eye on high-profile events
with that string of robberies and all.
Caw.
- Are you ok? - A bird attacked me.
Whoo! Freaky.
When I was a kid, a sea gull snagged my sandwich.
I'm sure it just thought your rubies were berries.
Hmm.
More shrimp, pops, and be quick about it.
And no skimping on the mayo this time.
I will have you know...
Everything okay here, Alfred?
I was about to inform Mr. Cobblepot
that his name does not appear
on the guest list.
Let me see that!
Hah. An oversight.
No doubt. But this is a charity event.
So if you wish to continue
devouring the hors d'oeuvres
'you must make the required donation.'
Is that so?
Here's my contribution, Jeeves.
'Oh, dear.'
Best teach the help some manners, Brucie.
That's what separates the Waynes
from the Cobblepots.
Ones?
The odd thing is, I was certain
I'd heard the Cobblepot fortune
had long since been squandered.
They had to leave England to avoid the shame.
I'd be a shame if you didn't get some sleep, Alfred.
And try not to dream of these Cobblepots.
And you, sir?
The Batman has some bird-watching to do.
I don't believe it.
My serving tray's gone missing.
That homunculus pilfered it just to spite me!
Well, Grandpa Pennyworth would have wanted to know
what became of the Cobblepots.
Vroom.
One of Cobblepot's girls.
Where's Kabuki twin number two?
Whoa.
Great. Double trouble.
Cobblepot Manor?
Well, you came this far, Pennyworth.
Hello?
So this is what became of the Cobblepot fortune.
Eew! Revolting.
- Aha! - Tweet, tweet!
I'm home, my pretties!
"High-rise jewel thefts baffle police.
"Dozens of similar crimes across Asia
"which suddenly stopped last week
and started up again in Gotham."
So Cobblepot is behind it.
Just got back from a tour of the orient.
Let me see that!
And he used my guest list
as a checklist for tonight's crime spree.
Alfred.
Alfred?
Huh. Maybe he's out running errands.
Mmm! Anchovies.
Ahh!
Huh? Who's there?
'Who trespasses in Cobblepot Manor?'
Hide-and-seek, then.
Huh?
Caw caw.
Oh.
Well, well, well.
Come to help with the dusting, Jeevsie?
Actually, I just popped in
to reclaim some missing property.
Fine, you can use it to serve me
more of those shrimp puffs.
The days of Pennyworths serving Cobblepots
are long since over.
Huh?
You're a Pennyworth?
And the only thing keeping me from walloping you soundly
is the shame that the news of the incident
would bring upon my Master Bruce.
Wayne, Shmayne.
The good old days when Cobblepots were king
are coming back, 'cause I am gonna restore the Cobblepot name
to its former wealth and glory.
Hmph, if you intend to do so by pilfering
it may take a while.
Not as long as you think, old man.
You? Birds? Oh, dear.
Uh... allow me to fetch those shrimp puffs right away.
Unhand me, you harridans!
My pets haven't been fed this evening
and they are famished.
But why feed them seed..
When they can feast on a treat of meat?
Ha ha!
Caw.
Ohh..
Huh?
Who's that?
What are you doing here?
Long story.
Oh, no, no!
Come back, my pretties!
Jolly good.
So, it seems the tales of the Batman are true.
But, really, who names himself
after a mangy flying rodent?
'Just one question, Batman.'
'How'd you find me?'
You left a trail of bread crumbs, Cobblepot.
Please!
Now that all pretenses are off
call me Penguin.
A flightless bird, but one with style!
Uhh!
My word!
A few tricks I picked up in the orient.
Huh?
I have a few tricks of my own.
Bring it on, rodent boy!
Huh? Watch where you're stepping.
Ahh!
Uhh!
Ha ha!
Ohh.
'Stay down, Penguin.'
Hah! And have you miss what's coming next?
Let me guess. A little something you picked up in the orient.
This penguin has claws!
Right, then.
Bird meets bat.
Huh?
Aah!
Boom.
Uhh!
There's a nice cage waiting for you, Penguin
in the Gotham State Pen.
As thrilling as it was watching you work, sir
from here on out, I shall leave the sleuthing to you.
'Cause I am gonna restore the Cobblepot name
to its former wealth and glory!
Waah!
Behind you!
Argh!
Uhh!
Aah!
Hmph. That is for Grandpa Pennyworth.
We'll leave this bird for the police.
Oh, dear.
And what of those birds?
'They flew the coop.'
Ohh!
Oh, my goodness!
That's game!
Dogs are on you, dawg!
Hey, congrats on the Cobblepot bust, Ethan.
You know, it's hard to believe
that such a big-time crook was at my party.
I can't take the credit for this one, Bruce.
Big secret, but Gotham's favorite vigilante
collared him for us.
Now, in some ways, man
I'm glad freaks like this Penguin
bring out the Batman.
Hopefully it's not the Batman who brings out the freaks.
Caw.
♪ The Batman ♪