'And now for the weather. Hot, hot, hot.'
'Gotham City is sizzling in a heat wave'
'and there's no end in sight.'
Sweltering weather we're having tonight.
Uh, Skipper, what's our procedure in case of an iceberg?
An iceberg in Gotham Bay in this heat?
Little buddy, I guarantee you, we don't have a procedure for..
Mayday! Mayday!
Weather's a bit... muggy.
You are not welcome here, mister..
Uh, mister..
Freeze will do.
Mr. Freeze, you do not have permission...
Aah! What do you want?
Ice.
I-I don't understand.
Think about it.
Think fast.
Have an ice evening.
♪ The Batman ♪
'All crime-fighting and no play'
make Master Bruce an extremely dull boy.
Even the Batman deserves to go on a holiday once in a while
'wouldn't you say?'
Alfred, you know how stir-crazy I'd be lying on some beach?
Which is why I've arranged for an athletic retreat
a way to hone the Batman's body and reflexes.
Not to mention escape this heat wave.
You've booked reservations, haven't you?
If I go, it's only to make you happy.
'The Batwave.'
The mind-boggling jewelry
theft here at Gotham Harbor
has left one man frozen solid
not to mention an actual iceberg floating in Gotham Bay.
'Little is known about the bizarre perpetrator'
'calling himself Mr. Freeze.'
There, you see? It's a sign.
A winter retreat is in your future.
What is that?
Will my husband be alright?
He's hypothermic, ma'am, but he'll pull through.
No thanks to that m-maniac.
So how'd he do it?
Not sure, but the victim seems to have been..
Flash-frozen.
He walked on water?
Froze it first.
Made a path of solid ice straight to the shore.
Well, no sign of that now.
Trail went cold.
Uh, so to speak.
'Trail wasn't quite cold enough..'
'Not in this weather.'
Not cold enough to the naked eye
but in infrared..
'Freeze's trail is a clear as crystal.'
'And his trail leads clear across Gotham.'
'Mind if I help myself?'
I didn't think so.
The choice cuts..
Must be in the icebox.
Ah.
Lovely little glaciers.
The Batman.
I thought you would never arrive.
I have been looking forward to our reunion.
Reunion?
Exercise will keep you warm for only so long.
Slowing, aren't we?
That would be the hypothermia setting in.
We both recognize the symptoms.
Reaction time slows, reflexes grow sluggish.
'Next come the hallucinations'
lack of consciousness, and finally..
The big chill.
Uhh!
You keep talking as if we've met, mister.
Victor Freeze?
But you're..
Uhh!
If I'm no longer living, Batman
you are the one who iced me.
Allow me to return the favor.
You, you..
I've had a makeover
'since our paths last crossed.'
I was just Victor Freeze then, common bank robber.
But I'd hit the big time. Diamonds!
The biggest score of my, uh, former life.
No way I'm letting some bat creep throw me in the cooler.
Wha..
Ahh-uhh!
The icy hand of fate led me to that cryonics lab.
Uhh!
Huh? Uhh!
- My diamonds! - Freeze, no!
No!
I was electrocuted.
At the same instant the blood froze in my veins.
Was I still among the living?
Presumably, the experts will determine that
but I made their job easy for them.
My body had mutated.
Neither living nor dead.
I was a walking cryonic miracle.
Though some might consider me a monstrosity.
It didn't take much for me to motivate an expert in the field
to produce a suit to contain my frosty disposition..
Until I so choose to disperse it.
Thank you for creating me, Batman.
Now..
Good-bye.
Police! Freeze!
As you wish.
- Uhh! - Uhh!
Another time, then, Batman..
Unless you catch your death of cold.
- Huh! He's gone. - But he left us a present.
Bennett here. Need paramedics... fast.
Hey, while we're waiting, we can take a peek.
Whoa. Hold up.
Can't say I'm not curious, Yin
but somehow, it doesn't seem right.
Hey, bats got into this pickle
'cause he was trying to stop Freeze.
I'm sure that Batman means well
but he's still a vigilante
and according to the law, Batman
that makes you a criminal.
'Just like the rest.'
Yin, hold up. What's that?
Something cold to drink, Master Bruce?
Master Bruce!
One hundred four point eight.
It's official, Master Bruce.
You are running a fever.
Freeze..
This earl grey will warm you.
No.
Freeze.
It's my fault he's what he is.
Master Bruce?
Yin was right.
I'm not helping the law. I'm just breaking it.
Master Bruce, you really must rest.
Right, Alfred.
Maybe it is time for the Batman to take a vacation.
A permanent one.
Baby, it's cold outside.
You there! Freeze!
Wha..
Uhh!
'I'm a criminal..'
like the rest.
I should give it up.
Sir, I would be more than delighted
to encourage you to hang up the cape and cowl
out of concern for your general health and welfare
but you would only hold it against me once your fever broke
and you came to your senses.
'Master Bruce?'
Alfred?
Alfred.
Ah. Regained some of our fire, have we?
The Batman's needed.
I thought as much.
That's why I've taken the liberty
of weatherproofing your suit.
The crime spree of Mr. Freeze continues.
He was last scene entering Gotham Municipal Park
but the police, who entered in pursuit
have yet to emerge.
Let it snow.
Now don't forget your cough syrup.
We're gonna need arctic survival gear
if we want to get our men any closer to that dome.
Getting warm.
Vroom.
'It was all too easy.'
The diamonds. The police.
Challenges for an ordinary criminal.
It's clear now that I'm destined for more than this.
After all, you've made me more than human.
Sorry, Vic, but I'm done taking credit for your handiwork.
We both know you put yourself on ice.
I'm here to bring on the thaw.
Go on, then.
Bring it.
Ugh!
Wha.. Slick as ice, Batman
but I won't need to see you
when you're buried!
You're finished, Batman.
I'm king of the mountain.
The new emperor of Gotham.
So get used to the weather.
No, Freeze, this is my mountain.
Cold always triumphs over heat.
Two words, Batman, snow tires.
Aah!
Ugh!
Let's go.
Bats may be a criminal
but he's my kind of criminal.
Hot tea and a lozenge, sir?
Cold drink on a warm beach?
'The Batwave.'
Another time, then.
Tahiti will have to wait.
♪ The Batman ♪