'It's time, dummy.'
bang Oh, careful.
You'll damage the parts.
Ah! Parts for what?
You gonna fill us in on the big secret, Wesker?
'What're you asking him for?'
'You got questions about my plan'
'you don't ask the toady.'
You ask me!
Now, put your back into it, punk.
Can you believe this nut?
Relax. There's gonna be one sweet payday.
Scarface is alright.
Alright? He's a dummy.
Excuse me?
Who are you calling dummy?
Do I look stupid to you?
Am I a moron?
Whoa!
Crunch Please, sir, don't. We need him.
Am I a dummy now?
No, Scarface. You're the boss! The boss!
Aah! Aah!
Don't ever forget it.
Now load the van. Crime's a wasting.
The problem with these knuckleheads?
They got no class.
♪ The Batman ♪
'Welding tools, motion-controlled gyroscopes'
and now, construction equipment?
They hardly seem valuable or related.
Unless someone's using them to build something, Alfred.
Let's see if the Batwave can't draw a connection.
Whoa! "Meet someone in your area."
Online dating?
Well, who'd have thought?
Alfred Pennyworth, ladies' man.
Actually, I was examining the website for you, Master Bruce.
Between Wayne Industries and your after-hours hobby
how else are you to meet women without criminal records?
I meet lots, Alfred.
I had three, maybe four dates just last weekend.
Indeed. All part of your swinging bachelor act.
But perhaps, it's time to stop acting
and let someone special get to know the real Bruce Wayne.
- I don't know. - Oh, very good, then.
Let's start with your interests.
Dispensing justice to the evildoers of Gotham.
How about driving fast cars, enjoys athletic pursuits
and being a night owl?
What? Do you have to look over my shoulder every waking moment?
Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. Scarface, sir.
He's not right.
Wesker's a little eccentric. So what?
That's how geniuses are.
Uh, s-sir, have you decided about the, uh, ranch?
Huh? What're you jabbering about now?
You remember, we talked about retiring after the big heist
to work the land under clear skies.
What do you think, Texas or Montana?
Tell you what. You go to Texas, I'll go to Montana.
Always with the jokes, sir.
He'd never leave me.
Her name is Becky. She's a psychologist.
"I'm usually social, but sometimes I retreat to my cave."
Fancy that. Someone even you can relate to.
Oh, she's a doll.
Just don't fill out annual income, Alfred
or post my photo.
It's probably not a good idea to advertise I'm a billionaire.
'Gotham Air And Space Museum.'
Sorry, Alfred.
Looks like I already have a date.
Boom.
Hmm.
I still wanna know how this junk is supposed to make us rich.
Funny you should ask.
Been wondering myself.
- Who's that? - Beats me.
What kind of a nut dresses like a bat?
Your aim stinks.
Aah!
Crash.
Gonna stand there, dummy?
Oh, Rhino, looks like he has things under control, sir.
Argh! Out of my way.
- Yo, pointy ears. - Huh?
Say hello to my little friend.
Ugh!
Bang.
Ooh! He's heading for more than just a pretty scar.
Let's go. Don't wanna splatter the suit.
Clang clang clang.
Ah! Nasty little puppet.
More potential dolls, I see.
I figure there are fewer dummies in Gotham than thieves.
So I'm trying to ID our perp through publicity head shots.
Oh, yes. He's clearly a smuggler.
And that chap screams embezzler if ever there was one.
There. Scarface.
'"The puppet belongs to a small time performer'
'"named Arnold Wesker.'
"One night, after an audience booed him off the stage.
Wesker and the doll robbed them."
Let's see if a search turns up anything
explaining Wesker's bizarre act.
"Care to chat?"
Bravo! Becky responded to your chat request.
And by your, I-I mean my.
'You have nothing better to do'
'while the Batwave completes its search on Wesker.'
Watch this.
So, uh, how things coming, Mr. Scarface?
Just need one more part, and that we swipe tonight.
Then we'll have everything we need to pull off
the biggest heist in Gotham history.
Aah!
Oh, he's good.
You bet it's a good plan.
'Signing off.'
- Well? - What?
I'm meeting Becky at a cafe tomorrow.
- But it's not a date. - Of course it isn't.
Merely the first step toward letting someone
get to know the real you.
You gave her the private number already?
Break-in at the Fewkes Computer Factory.
'What happened to us, Rhino?'
'We're taking orders from a block of wood.'
It'll be worth it, Mugsy.
Just keep an eye out for anything suspicious.
Like what? The bat got chopped into chip dip.
There.
Ah, the motherboard.
Here, dummy, keep this safe.
Only one heist away from retirement
and the clean, honest work of a cowboy.
'You know..'
Gotham Penitentiary has a thriving retirement community.
Where do you think you're going?
Texas, maybe Montana.
Take this punk out, or I get another partner.
Aah!
Buzz rizz rizz rizz.
Get up already. Get back in there.
Come on.
Enough with the act. Lose the dummy.
I would, but he keeps following me around!
This isn't an act, is it?
Aah!
Consider this therapy.
Dummy, he got me. I can't feel my legs.
Ooh! Ooh! Coming, sir!
Mr. Scarface!
No!
- The Batman's alive? - Get him.
Sir, say something.
Hang on, sir. Please hang on.
Don't leave me.
Quit bawling, dummy. I ain't gone yet.
Got the circuit board?
Good boy. Now take me back.
It's time for the phoenix to rise.
Start talking. What's this big heist Wesker's planning?
The gold at the Gotham Federal Reserve.
Scarface, uh, I-I mean, Wesker.
H-he was building something that was gonna help us
'bust in and carry it out.'
He-he, he never told us what. Honest.
I think I know what.
Aah! Amazing how good a new suit will make you feel.
Go ahead.
For your non-date with Becky
were you thinking semi-formal or semi-casual?
Not a good time, Alfred, Scarface is headed
for the Gotham Reserve.
Scarface? Don't you mean Arnold Wesker?
You'd be right either way. It's no act.
Wesker's a genuine case of split personality
and Scarface is his dominant side.
Alfred, I'm not sure if I can go through with this date.
'Sir?'
If The Batman is my dominant side
how can I let someone know the real Bruce Wayne?
Vroom
crash Large and in charge!
At least it has a weak spot, Wesker.
Well, look who don't know when to quit.
Bang
crash.
I'm not through with you, punk.
That's right, squeak toy.
I'm unstoppable
and I'm gonna hit every bank in Gotham.
But, sir, the ranch.
You said we'd retire!
Yeah? Change of plans.
Maybe Wesker's not the only weak spot.
That's it! I'm retiring alone!
Be my guest, tough guy. You're nothing without me!
'Hey, Scarface.'
Ah! My eyes! My eyes!
'I can't see!'
Look out, sir. Sir, look out!
Crash Do something.
Dummy!
We were gonna go to Texas or Montana.
We all have places we'd rather be.
- Becky? - Bruce?
You don't look like..
That is, you seem different online.
The young man you were expecting apologizes.
He won't be able to attend, I'm afraid.
Let me guess. He's married.
To his work.
♪ The Batman ♪