Screech
clank clank.
Hold up, the Batman nails thugs for us again
and this is the thanks he gets?
I just wanna tell him how grateful I am
up close and personal.
Screech.
Imagine that. Lost him.
Hmm.
Coincidence?
If you were the Batman
what kind of pets would you have?
'Let's see where these bats lead us.'
screech.
Wayne Industries.
Looks like your buddy Wayne has some explaining to do.
♪ The Batman ♪
ding Morning, Marlene.
Any messages for Gotham's most eligible?
Bruce, we need to talk.
Ethan. Uh, I hope this is a social visit.
Drop the act, buddy. We know you're the Batman.
Psych! Ha-ha-ha!
You the Batman! Ha-ha-ha!
We are, however
investigating a lead on the Batman.
We'd like to have a look in this building, Mr. Wayne.
Buzz buzz buzz 'Trust me, Detective Yin.'
If anyone here had anything to do with the Batman..
I'd be the first to know.
But if it's bats you want..
Dr. Langstrom is an audiometrist
an expert in the science of hearing.
Uh, bats are part of his research on..
Whoosh.
Sonar, Mr. Wayne?
Dr. Langstrom, uh, these are Detectives Yin and Bennett.
- Detectives? - Dark in here.
You aren't trying to hide anything, are you, doctor?
Bats are nocturnal. They prefer the dark.
That's common knowledge.
Dr. Langstrom, where were you last night
between 4 and 5 a.m.
Uh-uh, right here waiting for my bats to return.
I-I suppose I don't have much of a social life.
What do you know about the Batman?
I never paid much attention.
But if he likes bats, he can't be all bad.
Hmm. Thanks for your time, doctor.
Mr. Wayne, we'll be in touch.
Later, Bruce.
Bats prefer being kept in the dark, Dr. Langstrom.
I don't. Why wasn't I updated on your research?
I-I-I'm afraid paperwork isn't one of my strong points.
And I'm afraid I'm gonna have to shut down your project.
No! You can't.
My niece Carly.
'She lost her hearing when she was three'
after a bout with measles.
She's the reason for my research, Mr. Wayne.
'You see, I'm on the verge of a breakthrough.'
'A cure for deafness.'
Are you quite certain allowing Dr. Langstrom to continue
his bat research was the wisest decision, Master Bruce?
Giving Detective Yin a reason
to sniff around Wayne Industries
could spell disaster.
Langstrom's on the verge of a breakthrough, Alfred.
In scientific terms, sir.
"On the verge," could mean years.
Then maybe Bruce Wayne can provide
some charity on a personal level.
Ding dong.
Hi. Carly?
I brought you this hearing aid
'until your uncle can... '
Mom! There's some total weirdo at the door!
You can hear?
Thud Langstrom.
'Langstrom.'
Dr. Langstrom.
No one here. Okay.
If you're not curing deafness, what are you up to?
"The Batman. Vigilante or hero?"
'Internet sites?'
'Police reports!'
Mr. Wayne?
Quite a scrapbook for someone
who's never paid much attention to the Batman.
Oh, don't trouble yourself, Mr. Wayne.
A pompous, pretty boy like you could never understand my work.
- Try me, doctor. - I want to be like the Batman.
You wanna be a crime fighter?
No, Mr. Wayne.
I want to be feared!
You forced me to accelerate my testing schedule.
A pity the Batman himself can't be here to witness..
The birth of Man-Bat!
Langstrom, take it easy.
Can you hear me?
Langstrom!
Crackle crackle
clank clank clank
thud thud thud.
Chill.
Thud
creak
beep beep beep
vroom.
- Whoa! - Check it out.
Even billionaires put in overtime.
Detectives.
Uh, excuse me.
- E-mail from a cutie? - Spam.
So, why the late visit?
We wanna talk to Dr. Bat again.
That dork act didn't sit right with me.
Langstrom? Uh, he's gone.
Flew right out of here just minutes ago.
- Now, if you'll excuse me. - Uh-huh.
Your social life will have to wait, Mr. Wayne.
Langstrom's hiding something.
We need another look in his lab, Bruce.
Ethan, it's late and so am I, so, unless you have a...
'Search warrant?'
Yin.
- Uh, we're on our way. - What is it?
Assailant with bat wings, downtown.
- The Batman? - Who else?
We might just get that chat with Langstrom after all.
Later, Bruce.
Screech.
Alfred, anything unusual on the batwave?
And I mean, freaky unusual.
Let's have a look.
Would the discovery of several mammals
found completely drained of blood qualify?
Langstrom couldn't have used fruit bats?
'Begging your pardon, Master Bruce?'
Let's just say I'm no longer the only bat in town.
Screech
thud
swish
thud.
I knew you'd come calling, Batman.
So, tell me who's the better bat?
This has to end now
before you start feeding on humans.
Oh, but I'm so close to my goal.
Two more doses of my formula
and The Man-Bat will rule the night forever.
Clang clank clank.
Argh!
Freeze! Give it up, Langstrom.
I don't have time for this.
Poof.
Flush him out the other end. I'll cover the back.
Ugh!
Okay, Batman, where'd you ditch the muscle suit?
You are making a big mistake, detective.
He's right.
He's more dangerous than he looks.
Okay, so you're not the Batman
and you're not Langstrom.
Freeze! You, you bat thing!
Ugh! What the!
Bennett!
Swish.
You're gonna need more firepower to bring that thing down.
Wasn't trying to.
Detective Yin. I need a copter ASAP to track Man-Bat.
No, no, not Batman.
Man-Bat!
Beep beep beep.
Alfred, pick up.
Need I remind you we are not all creatures of the night?
Alfred, I'm on my way. I need you to prepare a few things.
'Sir, something's wrong?'
A friend is in trouble.
Beep beep beep.
Bingo.
So, where's the big, bad bat?
Out of the daylight..
Beep beep beep
'...and in its cave.'
Hold on, Ethan.
Beep beep beep.
Look out!
Stay back.
Time to see who is the better bat.
Clang.
Appreciate the save.
Splash.
Let's see how your sonar likes the look of this.
I'm not sure what's creepier
a big rat with wings or a drowned rat without 'em.
Bennett, you alright?
Batting 500.
One bat nearly ate me..
One saved me.
'Let's turn Langstrom's lab inside out.'
I want everything tagged and bagged so forensics can..
What happened here?
Maybe Langstrom didn't want anyone analyzing his work.
And you don't know anything about this, Wayne?
Hey, I've known Bruce since high school.
He'd never interfere in an police investigation.
Right, Bruce?
I like to think I help
law enforcement whenever I can.
Personally, I'm just glad we're back down to one bat guy.
Well, if Langstrom isn't the Batman, who is?
Later, Bruce.
In time, in time..
The night will belong to Man-Bat!
♪ The Batman ♪