'Master Bruce, haven't we discussed'
'not staying out late on school nights?'
What is it, Alfred?
'I thought it fit to remind you' of your meeting
'with the mayor tomorrow morning.'
'Actually that would be this morning now.'
The glass has been seared.
'Just like at the research lab two nights ago.'
Off you go, then.
Beep
ching zing.
Working late?
Midnight shift.
Like you, Batman.
Zoop zoop zoop
ka-ching.
♪ The Batman ♪
ching.
You're full of surprises.
I'm Firefly. Get it?
Fire and fly. Ha ha ha!
Zing zoop zing zoop.
Mm-mm-mm. You're gonna pay for that.
Next time.
Zoop.
Alfred, I've met our arsonist.
He targets computers. I'm not sure why.
But he has a jetpack and laser technology
like nothing I've ever..
Alfred.
Firefly, huh?
Ha-ha. Don't let that photograph fool you, Bruce.
I may be holding that fish, but your father caught it.
Dad always did subscribe to charity, Mayor Grange.
Bruce, it's been too long.
But unfortunately I didn't call you here for a social visit.
Wayne Foundation business?
Bruce, there's no easy way to say this.
As you may know, the city's about to award the contract
to rebuild and expand the children's hospital.
Right. To the Wayne Foundation.
The city council is leaning toward GothCorp.
- What? - Bruce...
Wayne Industries and the foundation have supported
the children's hospital from the beginning
since my father founded it.
GothCorp isn't known for its acts of public service.
They're known for allegations, investigations, resignations.
Too many "ations" for my taste.
Bruce, the council isn't concerned
with GothCorp's reputation.
They're leery of yours.
- Mine? - Your public image.
Well, let's just say it doesn't inspire much confidence.
Look, your father was one of my closest friends.
I see him in you.
But the council, they see you as, well..
A party boy.
Mayor Grange, let me make the case for the Wayne Foundation.
Give me the chance to convince them.
Please.
The council's voting on the contract tomorrow at 8 a.m.
Sharp!
And wear a tie.
I'll be here at the top of my game.
8 a.m. is bright and early for you, Master Bruce.
Perhaps you should think about getting some rest.
No, not until I've gathered enough ammo regarding.
GothCorp's questionable business practices.
The children's hospital was my father's personal cause, Alfred.
I need to be certain I can sway the council's vote.
The Batwave.
Police alert.
The security system of a law firm's
been tripped.
On the 64th floor?
Firefly.
Ah, I-I-I can't be in two places at once.
I'm quite the researcher, you know, sir.
Thank you, Alfred. I won't be long.
Crack
click zing
beep.
Firefly's work, alright.
But a law firm doesn't fit the profile.
Well, well, so the bat has wings.
Zoop.
You got some wings, let's play some chicken.
Oh, no.
Boom.
Tear gas? I'll give you something to cry about.
Zoop zoop zoop zoop boom
zoop
boom boom boom
zoop.
He's toying with me.
Zoop zoop zoop.
So long, Batman.
Crash.
'Master Bruce?'
'Master Bruce, are you there?'
'Please answer.'
Unh.
'Master Bruce, are you alright?'
Alfred..
'I've been trying to reach you for hours.'
- 'The communicator wasn't... ' - Hours?
Alfred, what time is it?
'Five minutes to 8:00.'
The council's voting on the contract 8 a.m.
Sharp!
- Do you have the research? - In the Batmobile.
With a fresh change of clothes and your electric razor.
Don't forget the tie.
Click.
Wait! Oh, wait, you blasted machine!
Great. No tie.
Screech.
Of course, I don't know how..
'Council members..'
ah, uh, ahem.
Um, forgive me for running late, gentlemen.
I, uh, I had a fender-bender on the way
but I'm here now, and I've prepared...
I'm sorry, Bruce.
The vote has been cast.
I... see.
Thank you, council members.
Well, he's no Thomas Wayne.
I failed twice today, Alfred.
As the Batman, and as Bruce Wayne.
I tried to do everything
and failed to accomplish anything.
You are, after all, only one man, Master Bruce.
Then maybe it's time to turn Wayne Industries over to someone
capable of running the business side of things.
Maybe it's time to be a full-time Batman.
Or a full-time Bruce Wayne.
Police are still investigating
this stream of arsons plaguing Gotham.
The latest victim is a law firm
which represents many of Gotham's industrial clients.
'The firm handled several major bankruptcy cases'
including those of Gotham Telecommunications..
Bankruptcy?
Those companies were arson victims, too.
"Gotham Telecom
declares bankruptcy after arson!"
Who'd profit from these companies being out of business?
GothCorp, that's who.
It was staring me in the face the whole time.
Firefly doesn't commit arson.
He commits corporate sabotage
and he's working for GothCorp.
It's no wonder that GothCorp is so interested
in funding the children's hospital.
Nothing like a little good PR
to distract the public from dirty business.
Perhaps the batman and Bruce Wayne can work together
to stop Firefly and GothCorp.
The Batman will fight fire with fire.
But first Bruce Wayne needs to lead
a certain moth to flame.
And in business, local billionaire Bruce Wayne
stepped into the spotlight again
this time with breaking news at Wayne Industries.
I can't reveal any details yet but, in the next few days
Wayne Industries will unveil a prototype
that will make us the premier technologies company in Gotham.
In fact, it'll set the tech world on fire.
Are you concerned about competition from GothCorp?
Let's just say I wouldn't want to be GothCorp right now.
Yeah, I'm watchin' it.
No problem.
My usual rate.
I understand, like the others.
Wayne Industries will go down in flames.
Zoop.
Firefly.
Batman. Ha-ha, I see you survived your crackup.
I know about GothCorp.
What? Is that a rock band or somethin'?
For someone who gets his kicks scorching tech companies
hard to believe you've never heard of them.
Zing Yaah!
You're done, firefly. Cooked.
Says who? Ha-ha-ha!
Boom No one touches me in the sky.
Click.
- What? - This time I brought the heat.
Whoosh
zoop zoop zoop.
Handles nice. But does it have horsepower?
Zoop
zoop zoop zoop.
Aaah!
I'm moving to Metropolis.
Cling zoop Huh? Aah!
Zoop zoop
honk
zoop zoop zoop
screech
crash.
Last chance, Firefly.
Huh?
You're empty.
Ka-ching.
Just you and me.
Aah!
- No one touches me. - In the sky?
Grraaah!
Unh!
Uhh!
Aah! Unh!
Face facts, Firefly.
You've been burned.
'"GothCorp employee of the month."'
Well, based on recent, uh, facts
that have come to light
I suggest that the council recast their vote
in the matter of the children's hospital
as well as all contracts currently held by GothCorp.
Yes, well..
Bruce, your father would be
proud of you if he were here today.
Thank you, Mayor Grange.
I like to think there's more to me than a good-looking tie.
♪ The Batman ♪