Previously on "The Batman.."
Ha ha ha ha! I call it Joker-putty.
And I can turn anything into it.
Don't let Yin scare you off.
She only has it out for The Batman.
One more blunder like tonight
and you can kiss your badge good-bye.
When Joker's through clowning with you..
You won't know where to find your mind!
Drop it!
You saved my partner's life.
This is the repayment of that debt.
The next time we meet, Batman, the mask comes off.
The Batman saved my butt tonight!
You're suspended.
♪ The Batman ♪
No!
Help me!
Thud.
Work! It's gotta work!
Can't.
No!
Help! Gotta find..
Help! Somebody!
Help me! Help me!
Please!
Help me!
No. Stay away.
Freeze!
Back away from the woman.
Sergeant!
What's he sayin'?
Who cares? Stay back!
Ooh!
- What is it? - I don't know.
But maybe we can stun it.
Aah!
Whoa! Unh.
Hey!
Ohh!
Officer down! Repeat, officer down!
It'll take time for Ethan to recover
from his trauma with Joker.
No doubt.
Now you really should think
about turning in, Master Bruce.
It's been a long night.
'The Batwave.'
'We're under attack from some kind of clay-faced creature.'
- 'We need backup!' - Clay-faced?
Could be the night's just getting started.
Get away from me!
Come on! Hurry!
Come on! Move!
No!
Get clear!
No! Stop!
Help!
Please!
Cut the water!
I think we did it.
'We beat the thing.'
Do we know what that Clayface was?
What about The Batman?
Settle down. I'll make a brief statement.
First of all, I'd like to once again congratulate.
Detective Ellen Yin
'for arresting Joker late last night.'
Next, credit is due to Sergeant Beechan here
for taking down this Clayface freak just an hour ago.
'Now, while it may seem that Gotham PD's'
'had a recent run of good fortune..'
our latest successes are no accident
but part of my new zero-tolerance policy
against all freaks.
Including the Dark Knight?
I mean, The Batman?
Especially The Batman.
I guarantee you, we will unmask him.
- Chief! - Where is Clayface?
Zero tolerance for freaks.
No, against freaks.
No, that's not it.
On freaks?
Ooh.
Huh?
Batman! Move!
Sorry, fella. Clay not spoken here.
Chief? What... Clayface... attacked me
a-and The Batman..
The Batman's working with Clayface?
No! Yes! I-I don't know!
Just take 'em down, both of 'em!
With zero tolerance!
Alright, freeze!
Yin, it's me! It's me!
I'm warning you, don't move.
No!
I want Rojas under 24-hour guard.
And what manner of mucky-muck would this be, Master Bruce?
'Organic matter.'
Mutated human DNA.
Which means Clayface may be more victim than criminal.
I'll need to run some tests.
Huh?
Yes!
My voi-voice.
'Bennett?'
Bennett!
Bennett, are you in there?
'Yeah. Just a minute.'
Why haven't you been answering your cell?
Open the door.
You okay? You sound horrible.
Throat's a little raw.
You know, from all the screaming last night.
What's up, Yin?
Just wanted to make sure you were alright.
You know, this Clayface thing
was first spotted in your neighborhood.
So, what do I care? Rojas suspended me.
His "Freaks" are his problem.
Take it easy, Bennett. We'll get you back in action.
- Whoa. - Um... I..
Just got out of the shower.
Look, Yin, I'm beat.
I need a break from everything.
Lab samples don't just get up and walk away.
You're quite sure?
Not without leaving a trail.
Alfred!
Are you alright?
Fit as a fiddle, sir.
Nasty puddle of putty, wouldn't you say?
- Putty. - Sir?
Joker's putty formula.
What if Ethan was infected?
Clayface was first seen in Ethan's neighborhood
and Ethan's been at odds with Chief Rojas.
Ethan..
Is Clayface.
Go right ahead, detective.
What is it, Yin?
Chief, I've just come from Detective Bennett's place
and, well, something's not right with him.
I knew it. I never trusted that guy.
Bennett never knew how to play ball.
No... I guess he didn't.
But he's learning.
'Sir, it seems you have a phone call from Detective Yin.'
'Rest assured the lady is phoning for Master Bruce.'
Patch her through.
'Hello. Mr. Wayne?'
'Please, detective. Bruce.'
'Look, uh, Wayne, um, you and Bennett..'
Ethan are best friends, right?
Well, since high school. Why?
Well, he's had a rough couple of days.
I was hoping you could talk to him.
We were supposed to shoot hoops today
at the old east Gotham gym
but I haven't been able to reach him.
Is something wrong?
'Ethan just... hasn't been himself.'
You don't know what this stuff does to humans.
Whoa.
Because Ethan's not himself.
- 'I'm sorry, detective?' - Uh-uh, nothing.
Look, I'm sorry I bothered you, Wayne. I have to go.
So do I, detective.
Detective, how'd you get back out?
Excuse me?
You... just went inside.
What?
Wait here.
Chief!
Hey, sarge, who's that?
Never seen him. You there, stop!
What in the...?
Ethan.
'Attention, all units.'
'Clayface has abducted'
'Police Chief Rojas.'
'Suspect should be considered dangerous.'
'Last seen heading towards East Gotham.'
East Gotham.
Let's shoot some hoops at the old gym.
Wayne said they were going to the East Gotham gym.
Come on in, Batman.
It's time to say our good-byes to Chief Rojas.
- Let him go. - What, you don't approve, Bats?
After all, to Rojas here, we're both
on the wrong side of the law.
It doesn't matter what he thinks.
It's the code you live by that matters.
'And you don't want to cross a line you can't uncross.'
Maybe you haven't noticed, Bats
but my line's been crossed for good.
Ethan, no!
It's not cool to reveal secret identities, Yin.
Not that it matters..
When I can be anyone I choose.
And when I'm no longer sure what I am..
Except a freak!
Do you know what separates the freaks from the normals?
'Just one rotten day.'
Ever had a really rotten day, Batman?
Thought so.
Joker's rotten to the core, by choice.
A choice that's still yours to make, detective.
Turn yourself in, Ethan. We can help you.
You don't get it, do you?
Joker didn't just melt my skin.
He melted my mind.
I'm a freak inside and out.
And Chief Rojas has zero tolerance
for the likes of me.
Ethan, no!
Nice try, Bats.
But the water pressure in this dump always did stink.
Ethan, stop!
Boys' locker room, Yin.
You could get expelled for this.
There's no blood on your hands yet.
Please, Ethan, don't cross the line.
You defending The Batman?
I never thought I'd see the day.
Yin..
What's become of us?
Ethan!
The next time we meet, Batman, the mask comes off.
I made you a promise last night, Batman
but I decided against it.
Didn't even peek.
No cuffs. No backup.
I'm not sure I understand.
All I've seen the last few months
the last 2 nights, has challenged
everything I ever believed in.
It all comes down to one thing..
Ethan. He was right.
'Gotham needs The Batman.'
You could lose your badge for thinking that way.
If you ever need me..
'When Ethan suggested we have coffee'
I never dreamed it would be without him.
- I miss him. - You'll find him.
And then?
We'll find a way to help him.
I suppose they'll try and saddle you with a new partner.
I hope not.
I think..
Maybe I already have one.
I'm sure whoever you have in mind, Ethan would approve.
He could be anywhere.
He could be anyone.
♪ The Batman ♪