♪
LANA [ON PA]: Whether you're riding the surf at Waikiki,
or dodging smaller deluges at poolside,
you'll be doing it in L.L.'s new swimwear this summer.
Boldly cut and physique-friendly,
L.L. lets you step out of your boring business clothes
and become the person that you really are.
Turning to the fall season,
L.L. offers a complete line of showstoppers.
I can't believe we're getting paid to do this.
Covering some fashion show?
That's why I became a reporter, Jimmy.
Come on, Clark.
You can't tell me you're not excited
about interviewing Darci Mason.
She's only a model.
Besides, what's there to talk about? Eyeliner?
And now, the face of the year,
the feature model of L.L.'s
summer swimwear campaign, Miss Darci Mason.
[CAMERAS CLICKING]
[MURMURING]
WOMAN: Here she is.
Watch out, Clark.
You're gonna burn a hole in those glasses.
What do you mean?
JIMMY: Well, the way you're staring at her.
Or is it just the suit?
[BOAT HORN HONKS]
Check out these guys.
Hey. You can't... [GRUNTING]
What? What? Hey.
[MUTTERING]
MAN: What is this all about?
WOMAN: Well... Now... [GRUNTS]
I've got a feeling this isn't part of the show.
Gotta get out of here.
This sure beats eyeliner, doesn't it, Clark?
Clark?
WOMAN 2: Somebody do something.
[WHIMPERS]
WOMAN 2: Frank, I wanna get out of here.
[SCREAMS]
[THUD]
[GASPS]
Robots?
[COCKS]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
I had a feeling you'd show up.
I was in the neighborhood.
DARCI: Help!
[WHIMPERING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
CLARK: This couldn't have been some random kidnapping.
And she knows more about it
than she told the police.
I'm sure of it.
That's Darci.
She takes reticence to a whole new plateau.
♪
Oh, Darci, Darci.
So beautiful.
Soon you'll be all mine.
Yippee, yee-haw!
[BARKS]
[TOY GUNSHOTS]
[BELL RINGS]
[GASPS]
Don't tell me, sheriff. I can guess.
Superman?
What's this?
[INHALES LOUDLY]
Oh, Darci.
The Ridgemont. Room 1002.
No photos, no letters.
Not a hint of her past.
What's your story, Darci?
I know these girls have to watch their figures,
but not even a diet soda?
DARCI: Hungry? Ahh.
Didn't I see you at the fashion show?
You some kind of stalker?
No. I'm a reporter.
Even worse.
At least stalkers are honest about what they do.
I'm also a friend of Lana's.
She and I want to help you.
I'm a big girl, and I can take care of myself.
Believe me.
After what happened yesterday,
I'm a little skeptical... [DISTANT BOOMING]
What's that?
[COGS RATTLING]
Get back.
[SCREAMS]
[MOANS]
[MOANING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
Hey, lady, you can't park there.
It's for emergencies only.
Your definition of emergency is way too limited.
[CRASHING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Him again.
It appears we have a rival.
Now, now, no need to curse, Teddy.
We'll take care of Superman in due time.
Nobody's going to come between my Darci and me.
[SIGHS]
You work too hard, girl.
♪
That's some makeover. [GASPS]
Who are you, Darci?
What are you?
Do you remember a doll they used to make?
The Darci doll?
I thought you would.
When you were a child,
it was every little girl's favorite.
I'll bet you had the entire collection.
You're right.
No wonder I chose you for my star model.
But where did you come from?
Winslow Schott's toy factory.
The Toyman?
He wanted a companion.
Someone with whom he could share his life.
Hasn't he ever heard of the personals?
You don't understand.
He kept me prisoner in that arcade,
like I was something you wind up or plug in.
There's so much to see in the world, so much to do,
and all Winslow wanted was to play with toys.
I have to stop him once and for all, Lana.
I wasn't supposed to feel this way.
I wasn't supposed to feel anything, but I do.
I guess he made me too perfect.
Darci... [GASPS]
[BEEPING]
Hello? Police?
[GASPS]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[EXPLOSION]
[COUGHING]
Cover your ears.
I was trying to find Darci.
Lucky for me.
She was here all right.
But now she's at the pier looking for Toyman.
Toyman? Did he do this?
No. This was Darci.
There's something about her
you should know.
[DOG BARKING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[CRUNCHING]
BOTH: Halt.
Friend or foe?
TOYMAN: Darci.
You couldn't leave me alone,
could you, Winslow?
You were made for me, Darci.
You know that.
You may have given me life, Winslow,
but I am not going to settle for this miserable existence.
[COCKS]
I... can't.
Of course you can't.
You could never hurt me.
I want to... so badly.
[GROANS]
It's not part of your program, my love.
You don't have the circuitry.
[SCREAMS]
This time things will be different.
Everything will be just perfect.
And I can make it that way
with a few small adjustments.
I'll never love you. Never.
I know there's a place
for me in your heart.
I just have to find it.
BOTH: Halt. Friend or foe?
Foe.
I know why you're here.
You want Darci for yourself.
That's not true, Schott.
Well, I built her, and she's mine.
But nothing's worth having
unless you're willing to fight for it.
So why don't we settle this the old-fashioned way.
With a duel.
[BUZZES]
I'm not playing your games, Winslow.
TOYMAN: I don't think you have a choice.
Allow me to introduce Death Fist Ninja,
my latest game.
You won't find this in the stores.
[SCREAMS]
[TOYS CHEERING]
[GRUNTING]
He-yah! [GRUNTING]
[CHUCKLES]
He-yah! He-yah!
He-yah!
[CACKLING]
Okay.
That's it.
Kick. Left jab.
Low kick. Left, right.
What's he doing?
He-yah! He-yah!
He's trying to work out the ninja's moves.
But the program's too complicated.
He'll never figure it out.
He-yah! He-yah!
[GASPS]
He-yah! He-yah! He-yah!
He-yah! He-yah!
[BEEPING]
He-yah!
[ROBOT SCREAMS]
My dear, it's time for us to go.
[GRUNTING]
Oh, this is just a small setback, Darci.
From now on, we'll always be together.
Always.
[GRUNTS]
What are you doing?
I can't hurt you,
but I can destroy your toys.
No!
REPORTER [ON TV]: After a search that took in the entire bay,
police have found no sign of supermodel Darci Mason,
or her captor, The Toyman.
The coast guard has expanded the search
to include the open sea.
But a spokesperson admits,
there is little hope of finding survivors.
I'll get this for you, ma'am.
[GRUNTING]
Well... guess I'll need a little help.
Uh, be right back.
♪