♪
JIMMY: "Wham!
"Pow!
Bam!"
Ha. How do you think this stuff up, Kyle?
It's awesome.
You're a one-man fan club, Jimmy.
Huh?
Read 'em and weep. I did.
"Dear, Mr. Rayner. Thank you for submitting your portfolio..."
Yada, yada, yada.
"Shows talent."
"Nothing at this time."
They all say pretty much the same thing:
"Don't quit your day job at the Planet, kid."
JIMMY: Hey, listen.
You know how many photos of mine Perry's rejected?
He's even threatened to take away my camera.
[GASPS]
Hey!
Ah!
[GROANS]
Quarterback at Metro High. You didn't stand a chance.
Hey!
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
Ah!
[GRUNTS]
[YELLS]
[GROANS]
Page one, for sure.
No page one, huh?
Not even the classifieds.
But you're still a hero in my book.
Meantime, I'm drawing soap.
Houston, we are coming home.
No matter how many times I see this,
I still get goosebumps.
Just a routine landing.
Yeah, right.
How many times have you flown around the moon, Smallville?
Reentry trajectory holding steady.
♪
PILOT: Jeez, Louise, what hit us?
[ALL GASPING]
Routine landing, huh?
PILOT: Trajectory is correcting. Any sign of that bogey?
HOUSTON CONTROL: Sorry, major.
[GROANING]
Must keep safe.
Go, find another.
Choose carefully.
Choose well.
♪
Here he comes!
[CHEERING]
All right, it's Superman!
All right! Way to go, Superman!
[BARKING]
Babbette.
Oh!
Huh?
Hey!
[YELPS]
Oh!
PERRY: Lois?
Have you seen Kyle Rayner?
Yeah, chief. He was heading to the one place in this world
even my credentials won't get me in.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Ow!
That's weird.
Someone's been eating Cracker Jacks.
♪
Ah!
PERRY: Rayner!
[GASPS]
There you are. I've been looking all over.
Are you okay?
Yeah, sure.
Well, you better be. I need drawings of the shuttle.
Front-page spread, cross sections,
burn areas, wing damage, the whole enchilada.
Rayner, are you with me?
Uh, sure, chief. Front-page, enchilada.
Then what are you still doing here?
Artists.
♪
[SIGHS]
You need help. I'll go...
No. Too late.
He needs your help now.
Who?
The Green Lantern.
Green Lantern?
Stand back.
I'm afraid your friend is...
Abin Sur was no friend of mine.
He hid the lantern,
but he couldn't have hidden the ring.
Where is it?
I don't know what... [YELLS]
The power ring. Give it to me.
[GROANING]
[YELLING]
[GRUNTING]
Ooh!
[YELLS]
You will give me the ring!
[GROANING]
I don't know what you're talking about.
No?
[GROANS]
[YELLING]
You really don't have it.
[GROANING]
But I will find that ring.
They won't stop me. They can't!
[GROANS]
How pathetic that Abin would entrust the ring
to brutes like these.
WOMAN: Abin?
Abin Sur?
No, it's the Kryptonian.
We are the Guardians of the Universe.
Welcome to Oa, Superman.
Unfortunately, your arrival
confirms our worst fears.
Abin Sur, Green Lantern of Sector 2814,
is dead.
What?
What was that? What was that?
What was that? I don't know.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Oh.
I must be losing it.
Get a grip, Kyle.
There's gotta be a reasonable explanation...
GIRL: My ball!
KIDS: Look out!
[YELLS]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[SCREAMS]
Cool. [LAUGHS]
[GASPS]
Help!
Do you see that?
Who is he?
Thank you very much.
And I thought I was going to have to come looking for you.
Do I know you?
The name's Sinestro.
You have something I want.
Are you nuts?
Give me the ring!
There's one little problem. We've sort of become attached.
[GRUNTS]
What?
Ever have gum in your hair?
It takes forever to get it out.
♪
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
Give me the ring.
I can't get it off.
I will. After your death.
Wait! Don't you want to talk first?
You know, banter back and forth
to show me your innate superiority?
No.
[GROANING]
Oh!
Whoa.
Awesome.
Uh-oh.
The Green Lantern Corps exists
to promote order and justice throughout the universe.
Recruits from all sentient interplanetary species
have answered our call.
GUARDIAN 2: We have entrusted each Green Lantern
with a great power.
A power which all have used wisely.
All but one.
Sinestro?
When we determined that he was unfit to wield the power,
we removed it.
But he found another source.
Abin Sur was not the first of his victims.
And with each ring he destroys, Sinestro gains power.
GUARDIAN 2: No Green Lantern can defeat him alone.
He needs you, Superman.
GUARDIAN: Help him.
Help the Green Lantern.
[GRUNTS]
[WOMAN YELLS, CROWD CLAMORING]
[GROANING]
You can't run from me, Green Lantern.
I never give up.
You never shut up, either.
Hey!
[GASPS]
As you can see, the ring's power has its limits.
GREEN LANTERN: You sure about this?
SUPERMAN: The Guardians called the lantern the battery.
It's the source of the ring's power.
How does it work?
You'd better figure it out.
♪
And fast.
[GRUNTING]
Do it, Kyle. Now.
GUARDIAN: In brightest day.
GUARDIANS: In blackest night.
No evil shall escape my sight.
Let those who worship evil's might.
Beware my power Green Lantern's light ♪
[GRUNTING]
Let's end this.
[SUPERMAN YELLS]
GREEN LANTERN: Yo, Sinestro!
[GROWLS]
Is that your best shot?
I could have been the greatest Green Lantern ever.
That's why the Guardians were afraid of me!
Why they took my ring away!
They never imagined I would return to destroy them all.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
Ugh!
All right. You win.
The ring.
Ha!
At last.
What?
[YELLS]
Fake out.
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
♪
[GROANING]
I think that took the fight out of him.
We are grateful for your help.
But there is much work for you on your home planet,
Green Lantern of Sector 2814.
No offense, but you guys can't be serious.
There must be someone better suited for the job.
Like him.
The ring has chosen you, Kyle Rayner.
But I'm just an artist.
I doodle in the margins of notepads.
I daydream about color and form and monster trucks.
I live half my life in a fantasy world.
You sound perfect.
♪