♪
[ROOSTER CALLING]
KARA: Yahoo!
Spring break at last.
[YELPS]
[DOOR SLAMS]
So long, Snoozeville. Hello, Metropolis.
Just a minute, little lady.
You still have your chores.
Done...
[CHICKENS CLUCKING]
And done.
Kara, you know how that upsets the chickens.
Good thing I didn't ask her to milk the cow.
[COW MOOS]
Oops.
I hope you'll try to act more normal
while you're staying with Clark.
You know how he likes to keep a low profile.
No offense, but what's so great about being normal?
Now see here.
If it's good enough for us humans,
it's good enough for you.
Mmm-mwah.
If you say so.
I can't wait.
The bus is just a mile away.
How do you kn...?
Oh, never mind.
Hey, Kara.
Hey, Owen.
Your folks said you were going to Metropolis,
so I brought you something to read on your trip.
Comic books?
[WHISPERS] Be nice.
Thanks.
No problem.
Uh, maybe you could drop me a post card
from the big city.
Gee, I'm gonna be pretty busy.
Sure.
Oh, darn, here's the bus.
See ya.
Have fun, sweetie.
♪
Oh, sorry.
Friendly guy.
Weird.
Heh.
Spider Powers.
Ew!
KARA: Dear Ma and Pa,
So far, I've been having a blast in Metropolis.
Clark's been showing me the sights
and introducing me to all the local celebrities.
Even better, Lois Lane's been taking me with her
to all the major press events.
The Metropolis Meteor has made me their honorary bat girl.
Won't Barbara be jealous.
Naturally, Supergirl's been seeing her share
of big-city action too.
You're out of your league, Super Snot.
If I was too hot for Superman,
I'll roast you like a marshmallow.
[GRUNTS]
You're all hot air, Volcana.
[GRUNTING]
Is it hot in here, or is it just me?
[GRUNTS]
Hot?
I think I'm getting frostbite.
It's your cremation, kiddo.
[VOLCANA SCREAMING]
KARA: Well, that's all for now.
See ya in a couple days.
Love, Kara.
Going back to Smallville is sad enough.
But do I have to take the bus again?
You know how important it is we keep a low profile.
Besides, it's only two days.
You get to see a lot of the country
and meet some interesting people.
CLARK: It'll be fun.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
[BABY CRYING]
"Fun," he said.
Look at that field, Eugene.
Would you say those are rutabagas or turnips?
I'd say turnips.
WOMAN: Really?
I'd swear they were rutabagas.
No, Vina, them's turnips.
Now, Eugene, I know rutabagas and I know turnips,
and those don't look like no turnips I've ever seen.
Brain imploding.
Shutting down.
Young lady, maybe you can settle this.
You see that field out there?
Would you say those are rutabagas or turnips?
I'm so out of here.
[DINGS]
My stop.
Out here?
This is the middle of nowhere.
I know. It's called Kansas.
EUGENE: What did she say, Vina?
I think she went out to check.
I'm home.
Ma?
Pa?
[MEOWS]
Hey, Streaky.
Miss me?
[MEOWS]
What's the matter?
No one feed you today?
JONATHAN: Kara?
Oh, hi, guys.
[GROWLING]
Streaky!
What's gotten into him?
You're early.
Well, I didn't want you
making a run to the bus station on my account.
But we were going to pick you up and take you some place special.
KARA: Let me guess.
It's all-you-can-eat night at the Pig Pit?
You'll see.
KARA: Wow.
The town is deader than usual.
Where is everybody?
Patience.
Here we are.
Don't tell me the circus is back so soon.
No, it's much better than that.
Hey, Owen. What's up?
Unity.
Unity? What's that?
New band?
[GASPS]
There you are, Jonathan and Martha.
We've been waiting for you.
Ah, and this must be Kara, about whom I've heard so much.
I know you.
The man from the bus station.
The Reverend Amos Howell at your service.
A humble traveler spreading the word of Unity.
Which is what, exactly?
The one true source of universal bliss.
Nations fall and demigods fade, but only Unity is absolute,
all-encompassing and eternal.
Ugh.
Does Pastor Ross know about this?
Oh, he was among the first converts.
Your stepparents, your neighbors,
indeed everyone in Smallville has embraced the call of Unity.
Now it is time for you to do the same.
PEOPLE [FLATLY]: Unity. Unity. Unity. Unity.
[GASPS]
Welcome, Kara.
Join us.
What have you done to them?
Made them one with a greater power.
We... are Unity.
[GASPS]
She won't get far.
Hey, preacher!
I'm shutting down your tent show.
[GRUNTS]
[ALL GROANING]
[GROANS]
No!
Wake up.
HOWELL: It's futile.
We are one,
like every other being who has joined Unity.
Planet after planet, age after age,
Unity grows stronger with each world we touch.
ALL: You cannot fight us.
Unity.
[BEEPING]
SUPERMAN: I got here as soon as I could.
What happened?
I told them I got a distress call from the Midwest.
I found her with that thing sticking out of her.
I've never seen anything like it.
The x-rays show some kind of parasite
wrapped around her brain stem.
We can't remove it without killing her.
Ohhh.
Mrs. Kent?
[WHISPERS] Ma?
Kara? Clark?
Help me.
[MOANING]
What's happening to her?
We have to run more tests.
Come on.
This is all my fault.
If I'd have stayed home,
none of this would have happened.
You couldn't have known about this.
But I did.
I saw that guy come into town.
He gave me the creeps.
I should've checked it out,
but I was in such a rush that I left anyway.
We've gotta get back there.
Everyone's in danger.
Pa, Owen, all my friends.
I need to know what we're fighting.
It's obviously an alien spore.
I wanna put it under a microscope.
Just hurry.
The EKG doesn't lie.
The parasite feeds off the electrical impulses
in her nervous system.
Is that possible?
It's not only possible, it's getting stronger.
HOWELL: Supergirl has compromised our cause...
but she cannot stop us. No one can.
For tonight, we shall go forth into this world
as we have done on countless others
and spread the power of Unity.
ALL: Unity. Unity. Unity. Unity.
Unity.
This tendril has an unbelievably dense cell structure.
It's hard to get a visual reading.
Let me take a look.
I see large mitochondria and...
Wait.
Something's happening.
[SIGHS]
Hey, guys, any word yet?
Mrs. Kent?
She's much better now.
No, she's not!
There's no greater healer than Unity.
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
[BOTH GROANING]
I'm sorry.
MARTHA: Give in, Kara. Don't resist.
MAN: Accept us.
ALL: Accept Unity.
SUPERMAN: Supergirl!
[ALL GROANING]
Thanks. But how did...?
Remember when Ma woke up?
It was the x-rays.
[GROANING]
Once they wake up, they should be fine.
Sleep well, Ma.
Let's go.
As shadows fall in twilight,
so shall we spread across the land.
Go now.
Go forth and spread Unity.
SUPERGIRL: Sorry.
Road's closed.
[GRUNTING]
Give up the fight, child.
Forces mightier than you couldn't stop us.
Let me try.
[ALL GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING]
You are nothing.
Behold the true power of Unity.
Superman!
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
Together, we will force your subjugation.
No, you don't!
[SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
Kara?
Shh.
Not so loud, Pa.
Let's go.
[MOOING]
[CLUCKING]
And we were actually part of some alien conspiracy?
Yeah, Pa.
And you were crankier than usual.
But I can't tell you how great it is
to have everything back to normal.
I thought you found normal boring.
Well, at this point, boring's not so bad.
I'm even meeting Owen down at the comic store.
Say, Martha, did you see what the Langs are growin'?
Looks like rutabaga.
MARTHA: I don't know, Jonathan.
Looks like turnips to me.
[SIGHS]
♪