♪
JIMMY: Cool, there goes another one!
[CLICKING]
I really appreciate you
taking us out on your boat, Bibbo.
Anything for you, Miss Lane.
Besides, she was just sitting idle.
All these stories about fish attacks
have got the fishermen spooked.
I can't find nobody to crew with me.
So you don't believe the stories.
Bunch of hooey.
You can quote me on that.
And while you're doing it,
I'll get us some cold cans of soda.
[CLICKING]
How did Clark manage to miss out on this?
LOIS: Smallville's got a problem with seasickness.
Says the only waves he can stand are "amber waves of grain."
Whoa, awesome!
♪
[CLICKING]
Ow!
[GROWLS]
Ah!
You got the camera?
I'm lucky I got my fingers.
Hey!
That was close.
[SCREAMS]
That was closer.
Whoa.
Forty years at sea,
I ain't never seen whales act like this before.
Bibbo, you have to radio for help.
No can do, Miss Lane.
If we don't do something, we're fish bait.
Maybe not.
[BEEPS]
[BEEPING]
♪
Ah!
Jimmy!
Jimmy.
[COUGHING]
Bunch of hooey, huh?
[SNIFFLES]
[GROWLS]
[CLICKS]
Whoa!
Animal behavior is very complex, Miss Lane.
During mating season, for example,
they exhibit all manner of bizarre behavior.
Since when is attacking ships a mating ritual?
The whales who attacked you
were probably protecting a calf
or an expectant mother.
But taken in context of the marine world,
there's really nothing unusual going on.
Yeah, right.
Are you really saying...?
[BEEPING]
I'm sorry, you'll have to excuse me.
No rest for the wicked.
Something stinks here, Jimmy, and it's not just the fish.
He did seem kind of nervous.
LOIS: And I think I know why.
These attacks are out of control, Cardy.
Even the men in my shipyards are expressing concern.
I know.
Two of my most experienced trainers have been injured.
Countless near misses.
I may have to shut down the whole park.
We both know what's causing this.
Yes, but what can I do?
Remove the problem.
Take it further inland, away from the water.
LEX: Use my security people if need be.
I leave it to you to make the arrangements.
Mercy, bring the car around.
♪
[INTERMITTENT BANGING]
[MUFFLED BANGING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[HONKING]
I'm moving, I'm moving!
JIMMY: Whoa!
[PHONE RINGING]
Lois? Yeah.
Where the heck are you?
I still can't find a parking space.
You may have to cruise a little longer.
But I've only got a learner's permit.
I'm not supposed to be driving alone.
Hang in there, kid.
I may have stumbled onto the story of the decade.
CARDY: Why so modest?
Why not the century?
[CLICKS]
Lois? Lois? Great.
Right foot, gas. Left foot, clutch.
Yeah, okay. I'm getting the hang of this.
Ah!
Big mistake!
Big mistake.
[GRUNTING]
Aquaman, huh?
Something wrong?
No, it's just that I always thought
you were an urban legend.
Nothing urban about me.
So you gonna tell me what's going on?
Some of your people... My people?
Surface dwellers.
They're about to cause the death of millions.
I have to stop them.
What else was I supposed to do? I had to take her.
LEX: Idiot! Having Lois Lane
is an open invitation for Superman
to stick his nose into your business.
Get rid of them both. Now.
But I was hoping to observe the creature in captivity.
LEX: You're the one who's going to be in captivity
unless you do what I say.
[CLICKS]
Change of plans.
Take the next cutoff.
LexCorp has been testing explosives
off the eastern seaboard.
The explosions have caused
extensive damage to my home, Atlantis.
Whoa. You mean Atlantis is real?
Very real. And very angry.
I was sent here to try to put a stop to the tests,
but my peaceful overtures
were met with violence and capture.
What happens if you don't make it back?
War.
What now?
End of the line.
Clark, has Lois called in?
Nope. Why don't you try her car phone?
Because it's in her car, and her car is, kind of...
in the shop.
What? It's not my fault.
I told her I wasn't supposed to be driving,
but I couldn't find a space,
and this guy kept honking and honking
and then the truck came out of nowhere...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Jimmy.
Slow down. What are you talking about?
I can't find Lois.
♪
I hate to lose such a fascinating specimen,
but better you than me.
Ow!
[YELLING]
[GUN CLICKS]
[SCREAMING]
Let's go!
Get me Luthor.
Neat trick back there. How did you...?
I communicate with the creatures of the sea telepathically.
There's not much time.
I need to get out to the blast site.
These guys have something else in mind.
♪
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
We're running out of road.
Keep going.
What? Trust me.
You can fly, right?
Fly? [GASPS]
[LOIS SCREAMING]
[GASPING AND CHOKING]
"Trust me," he says.
Can't get a bead on her.
Maybe we won't have to.
♪
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
♪
I thought I heard gunfire.
That's enough.
Hey!
[COUGHING]
Are you all right?
Are you nuts?
That was a great white.
Yes.
Lucky he was passing by.
I've got 10 more circling us right now.
Hope they're not hungry.
Want me to ask them?
How'd you find me?
Ran into a couple of Luthor's men.
I sort of squeezed it out of them.
SUPERMAN: Is that who I think it is?
Aquaman, in the flesh.
He isn't staying for introductions.
He doesn't have much time and neither do we.
They're setting the last of the charges now, Mr. Luthor.
Excellent.
You've gotta call off the test. Now.
It's Mr. Luthor that gives the orders here.
Mind your manners.
These are international waters,
and I'm perfectly within my legal rights.
The test will proceed,
and there is nothing you can do to stop it.
Yeah, I copy.
Mr. Luthor, one of our subs has spotted Aquaman.
Still think your test will proceed?
The man's nothing but an ecological terrorist.
Tell the divers they've got my authority to stop him
any way they can.
You can't... I'm just protecting my assets.
Tell the divers they better hurry.
♪
[GRUNTS]
You're dead meat, freak.
[MEN SCREAMING OVER RADIO]
Sounds like your assets are getting kicked.
Will you please get her out of here?
My pleasure.
Now, then, arm for detonation.
But our own men are still down there.
And their beneficiaries will be well-compensated.
Luthor said to get you out of there,
but he didn't say to where.
Oh, no, you don't, you...
Armed and ready, sir.
Very good.
[BEEPING]
It's over, Luthor.
Maybe... for now.
No. Forever.
[GASPS]
Warriors of Atlantis, prepare to fire!
Stop! I've disarmed the bombs.
My king, we await your command.
Did he say king?
Just when you think you know a guy.
You got what you wanted. Now, call off your troops.
How do I know
he or some other surface dweller won't try this again?
For too long, we've remained hidden and silent
and have suffered the consequences.
It's time to settle this once and for all
by blasting them back to the Stone Age.
I'll have to stop you.
You'd side with them?
They're polluting your sky
just as they're poisoning my ocean.
They're not all like Luthor.
Some are working to solve the problems.
Let's hope they succeed, for their sake.
Go on.
Run, you lousy, stinking fish!
[SCREAMS]
No!
Get me out of here, now!
ALL: Help!
MAN: Come back here!
Help us! Luthor!
Enough!
Tell the surface dwellers
to respect the sovereignty of my seas,
or we'll return and finish what we've started.
We'll be watching.
♪