♪
MAN: You can't do that!
You'll overload the accelerator and...
I didn't know what to do,
so I called the Legion of Super-Heroes.
Well, it's a little late.
What do you need heroes for if the villain's gone?
Well, he's not exactly gone. Look.
It's a temporal anomaly.
Brainiac made it by rewiring the circuits,
then overloading them.
Where does it lead?
It could be anywhere.
And any time.
That means Brainiac could be changing the past.
Or destroying the future.
Is there a way of pulling him back, professor?
This thing is too far beyond our own technology.
Let's go.
Didn't you hear me?
I have no way of bringing you back.
Let us worry about that.
This is crazy.
You asked for heroes.
You didn't say anything about sanity.
♪
[MOOS]
Well, we're here.
Wherever that is.
And whenever.
SATURN GIRL: Over here.
♪
I think I know what Brainiac's up to now.
And if I'm right, we don't have much time.
[GUN COCKS]
[BARKS]
Back, boy.
Ya thought I wouldn't catch ya, didn't ya?
He's had trouble with kids
coming onto his property at night, pulling pranks.
He means business.
You got that right, missy.
Now, if y'all just move toward the house.
Ah!
Huh?
[ROARS]
It's all right. You won't be harmed.
And you won't remember.
[FUN FUNK MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Feel that funky beat Uh-huh ♪
♪ Feel that funky beat Everybody now ♪
♪ Get up on your feet ♪
GIRL: Clark Kent.
You promised to get me some punch, remember?
Oh, sorry, Lana. I got... sidetracked.
What's this strange power you have?
What do you mean?
The ability to attract every airhead in Smallville.
BOY: Hey, Mr. Varsity.
[GRUNTS]
Airheads aren't the only ones.
You may have made All-State, Kent,
but I can burn your butt any day of the week.
Oh, yeah, Kenny?
How about any night?
You mean now?
Okay, let's do it.
[KIDS CHEERING]
Clark, this is a dance.
Kareem here says he can burn my butt.
I don't think he's even got a match.
BOY: Here we go, here we go!
BOY 2: You show him!
BOY 3: Come on!
[ALL CHEERING]
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
Heh. Showed that loudmouth.
Did more than that.
BOY: Is he moving?
[GROANS]
You just had to show him how tough you are.
Guess I don't know my own strength.
Maybe you should learn.
Hey, it's not like I meant to hurt him.
It's just that...
I've been going through some changes lately.
Me too!
[GRUNTS]
♪
[SIGHS]
[SCREAMS]
[MACHINE HUMMING]
Who are you?
[SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
Why are you doing this?
[SCREAMS]
[DOG BARKING]
Stop! There's no reason!
Ah, but there will be, Kal-El.
There will be.
Kal-El? I'm not... [SCREAMING]
[GROWLS]
Just in time.
Huh?
Chameleon Boy.
Cosmic Boy. Saturn Girl.
Where are the other Legionnaires?
Hey, it's only you.
Ah!
[PANTING]
You saw?
Yeah, he touched something on his belt, then poof.
He's built himself a spatial disrupter.
Uh... Excuse me.
It was something in the punch, right?
We should be safe here.
For the moment.
Wouldn't hurt to have a disguise.
Hold still.
Well?
Like a pair of glasses is going to fool anyone.
It better.
Brainiac's trying to alter our past.
And your future.
He wants to kill you before you ever become Superman.
Super who?
Superman.
You.
Red underpants?
Now I know you're crazy.
I realize all this is hard to take in,
and maybe we do seem a little...
Um, freaky?
But if you just open your mind.
The 30th century is an age
of unparalleled peace and prosperity.
But none of this would have been possible without you.
Me?
SATURN GIRL: Superman showed us that beings from different worlds
could work together for a greater good.
This is the principle on which
the Legion of Super-Heroes was founded.
But Brainiac would tear all this apart.
He's a living computer who destroys whole planets.
Superman stopped him, but after years of dormancy,
Brainiac managed to reassemble himself.
He's made his way back here to destroy you.
We've gotta stop him. Our past depends on it.
And your future.
How'd you do that?
CHAMELEON BOY: Shh!
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
Phew. That was close.
Hey.
He ran away.
He... He didn't believe us.
It wasn't like this in the history tapes.
[PEACEFUL POP PLAYING]
Ah, a lucky break, that's all it was.
You're lucky that's the only thing that broke.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
[BELL DINGS]
[GASPS]
Whoa. Check out Darth Vader.
Que pasa, man? Take a wrong turn at Tatooine?
[SCREAMS]
Where does Clark Kent live?
Clark? Wh-what is this?
Insufficient response.
[GROANING]
[WHIMPERS]
Ah!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
I repeat:
Where does...?
State Road 7. Where it dead ends.
Thank you.
[GRUNTS]
Well, no one said this was gonna be easy.
Pa!
Jeez!
You almost gave me a heart attack.
You have a visitor.
I just, uh... Hi, Clark.
Hi.
I needed to tell you that I'm sorry for walking away from you.
It's just that... Uh, Jonathan?
Aren't The Dukes of Hazzard on now?
It's just that you've become so darn arrogant lately.
It's time you learned a little humility.
Oh, I'm learning about that all right.
What was that?
He's here.
They're in the living room, checking the closet.
How do you know?
I can see them.
Who are they? What do they want?
They want me.
I'm gonna try to draw them away.
Whatever happens, stay down here.
Are you crazy? You can't go up there.
What was that?
I don't know, but I'm going to find out.
Don't be foolish.
You need something better than a shovel.
♪
[SCREAMS]
[GUNSHOT]
♪
Oh, no, you don't.
Pa!
[GRUNTS]
♪
You want me, Brainiac? Here I am!
[BLOWS THUDDING]
We'll take it from here.
This guy's mine.
Not tonight.
You two gonna be okay?
BRAINIAC: Kal-El.
Guess the history tapes weren't so far off after all.
[SCREAMS]
Clark, listen.
You must get to the control on Brainiac's belt.
It's the only way.
At last, the son of Jor-El kneels before me.
This time, history will show
that I am the superior survivor of Krypton.
SATURN GIRL: You know how to adjust it.
[BEEPING]
♪
You're lucky you're still in one piece, son.
That was the worst twister to hit town in 20 years.
Yeah, yeah. I don't care.
Ow!
Just get me down!
So they don't remember anything that happened last night?
Nothing. I blocked everyone's memories,
then made them think the damage was done by a storm.
It's just as well.
I don't know how I'd explain any of it.
What happens now?
We're gonna use the computer
in Brainiac's hover-chair to get us back to our own time.
Then I won't be seeing you again.
Don't look so sad. You'll hardly miss us.
What, are you kidding? After all you've shown me?
Mmm.
Aw, just when we were gettin' to be buds.
It's not right for a person to know his own future.
Yes. He needs to find his own way.
Up, up and away!
Heh. Always wanted to say that.
Hey, Clark.
Come on, we're gonna be late for class.
Where'd you get those?
Uh, I'm not sure.
Well, what do you think? Are they me?
You are so weird.
♪